{"Question": "DEEP + EDGE = ARMED", "Answer": "8662 + 6806 = 15468"}
{"Question": "DEEP + EDGE = ASIDE", "Answer": "8660 + 6826 = 15486"}
{"Question": "DEER + EDGE = START", "Answer": "8669 + 6826 = 15495"}
{"Question": "DEER + EDGE = BRING", "Answer": "5773 + 7507 = 13280"}
{"Question": "DEER + EDGE = GUARD", "Answer": "6779 + 7617 = 14396"}
{"Question": "SEEK + ELSE = KILL", "Answer": "8119 + 1081 = 9200"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = ASSET", "Answer": "7225 + 2872 = 10097"}
{"Question": "SEED + ELSE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8443 + 4684 = 13127"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = WHOLE", "Answer": "8442 + 4984 = 13426"}
{"Question": "SEEK + EASE = MAKER", "Answer": "9448 + 4394 = 13842"}
{"Question": "SEED + EASE = LOCAL", "Answer": "7556 + 5375 = 12931"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = GREEN", "Answer": "8552 + 5785 = 14337"}
{"Question": "SEED + ELSE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8554 + 5985 = 14539"}
{"Question": "SEEK + EASE = MEDIA", "Answer": "9552 + 5795 = 15347"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = CATCH", "Answer": "5663 + 6856 = 12519"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = LIMIT", "Answer": "7661 + 6276 = 13937"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = ENEMY", "Answer": "7662 + 6476 = 14138"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = SHEET", "Answer": "8662 + 6786 = 15448"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "8662 + 6986 = 15648"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = NIGHT", "Answer": "5778 + 7157 = 12935"}
{"Question": "SEED + EASE = BADLY", "Answer": "6772 + 7467 = 14239"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONTO = ALTER", "Answer": "8775 + 7087 = 15862"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ELSE = SMILE", "Answer": "1880 + 8918 = 10798"}
{"Question": "SEED + ELSE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9883 + 8198 = 18081"}
{"Question": "SOON + ONTO = TOSS", "Answer": "3449 + 4984 = 8433"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ELSE = SHOE", "Answer": "5440 + 4094 = 9534"}
{"Question": "FEED + EDGE = ONION", "Answer": "7448 + 4864 = 12312"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "8442 + 4274 = 12716"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONTO = TENT", "Answer": "3554 + 5495 = 9049"}
{"Question": "FEED + EDGE = STAFF", "Answer": "2775 + 7547 = 10322"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ELSE = BLOOD", "Answer": "4772 + 7237 = 12009"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONTO = START", "Answer": "4775 + 7527 = 12302"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONTO = STAFF", "Answer": "6775 + 7547 = 14322"}
{"Question": "FEED + EDGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9774 + 7427 = 17201"}
{"Question": "SEED + EDGE = SALES", "Answer": "1883 + 8398 = 10281"}
{"Question": "SOON + ONTO = SHORT", "Answer": "1889 + 8978 = 10867"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONTO = ENEMY", "Answer": "3882 + 8248 = 12130"}
{"Question": "BOOT + ONTO = SEVEN", "Answer": "9448 + 4284 = 13732"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ONTO = ENTRY", "Answer": "4667 + 6076 = 10743"}
{"Question": "EVER + MERE = LIMIT", "Answer": "6268 + 9686 = 15954"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ONTO = SERVE", "Answer": "4775 + 7657 = 12432"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ONTO = AWARD", "Answer": "6778 + 7387 = 14165"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ONTO = LEARN", "Answer": "6778 + 7587 = 14365"}
{"Question": "BOOT + ONTO = STAND", "Answer": "8776 + 7467 = 16243"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERE = DRAMA", "Answer": "7576 + 8767 = 16343"}
{"Question": "BOOT + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "4882 + 8328 = 13210"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ONTO = ACTOR", "Answer": "7889 + 8098 = 15987"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ELSE = ASSET", "Answer": "7225 + 2802 = 10027"}
{"Question": "COOL + ONTO = KNOCK", "Answer": "8229 + 2052 = 10281"}
{"Question": "EVEN + HERE = TENT", "Answer": "4942 + 1484 = 6426"}
{"Question": "AWAY + DATA = SWEET", "Answer": "4348 + 9424 = 13772"}
{"Question": "FEEL + EASE = HELLO", "Answer": "9442 + 4784 = 14226"}
{"Question": "POOL + ONTO = COLOR", "Answer": "9442 + 4804 = 14246"}
{"Question": "COOL + ONTO = ELECT", "Answer": "7664 + 6506 = 14170"}
{"Question": "TEEN + EASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "3776 + 7217 = 10993"}
{"Question": "MEET + ELSE = STEAL", "Answer": "6773 + 7017 = 13790"}
{"Question": "FEED + EASE = ASIDE", "Answer": "6770 + 7137 = 13907"}
{"Question": "DEEP + EASE = BASIS", "Answer": "6775 + 7427 = 14202"}
{"Question": "DEEP + EASE = SALAD", "Answer": "2884 + 8018 = 10902"}
{"Question": "FEEL + EASE = SALAD", "Answer": "2889 + 8018 = 10907"}
{"Question": "MEET + ELSE = STILL", "Answer": "4882 + 8018 = 12900"}
{"Question": "MEET + EASE = WASTE", "Answer": "4880 + 8328 = 13208"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "4886 + 8328 = 13214"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ONTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "9881 + 8208 = 18089"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = BELL", "Answer": "3438 + 4384 = 7822"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = PRIOR", "Answer": "3934 + 9349 = 13283"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = BEAN", "Answer": "4348 + 3483 = 7831"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = CHEST", "Answer": "4842 + 8428 = 13270"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "4843 + 8438 = 13281"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = FRESH", "Answer": "4943 + 9439 = 14382"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = CHEAP", "Answer": "5752 + 7527 = 13279"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = BEGIN", "Answer": "5753 + 7537 = 13290"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = FINAL", "Answer": "5852 + 8528 = 14380"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = STAR", "Answer": "6165 + 1651 = 7816"}
{"Question": "RARE + AREA = THEIR", "Answer": "7572 + 5725 = 13297"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "3835 + 8308 = 12143"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = STEAL", "Answer": "5752 + 7537 = 13289"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = START", "Answer": "5756 + 7537 = 13293"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = TREAT", "Answer": "5853 + 8518 = 14371"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = PRIOR", "Answer": "5856 + 8528 = 14384"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = GIVEN", "Answer": "6769 + 7627 = 14396"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = WHICH", "Answer": "6867 + 8628 = 15495"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = ARMED", "Answer": "6869 + 8628 = 15497"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = PILOT", "Answer": "7872 + 8708 = 16580"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONTO = BELOW", "Answer": "7876 + 8708 = 16584"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = DENY", "Answer": "1012 + 2113 = 3125"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = GENE", "Answer": "1013 + 3118 = 4131"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = ERROR", "Answer": "1918 + 8112 = 10030"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = APPLE", "Answer": "3938 + 8335 = 12273"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = BEAN", "Answer": "6961 + 1660 = 8621"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEED = DRESS", "Answer": "8985 + 5881 = 14866"}
{"Question": "BABY + ARAB = TREAT", "Answer": "9492 + 4349 = 13841"}
{"Question": "BABY + ARAB = TRUST", "Answer": "7574 + 5257 = 12831"}
{"Question": "BABY + ARAB = GUESS", "Answer": "8687 + 6268 = 14955"}
{"Question": "BABY + ARAB = CHEEK", "Answer": "6762 + 7576 = 14338"}
{"Question": "BABY + ARAB = CYCLE", "Answer": "5854 + 8285 = 14139"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TENT = ERROR", "Answer": "1912 + 8128 = 10040"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TENT = APPLE", "Answer": "7672 + 5725 = 13397"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BALL = REFER", "Answer": "7176 + 6755 = 13931"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BALL = CLASS", "Answer": "7978 + 8766 = 16744"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TENT = LEAVE", "Answer": "7678 + 9789 = 17467"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TENT = TITLE", "Answer": "8287 + 1871 = 10158"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TENT = THEME", "Answer": "8987 + 1871 = 10858"}
{"Question": "EVER + READ = DARE", "Answer": "1215 + 5136 = 6351"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BAKE = REFER", "Answer": "3139 + 9382 = 12521"}
{"Question": "NINE + ONTO = UPPER", "Answer": "4947 + 8428 = 13375"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEWS = SALAD", "Answer": "4249 + 9481 = 13730"}
{"Question": "EVER + READ = AWARE", "Answer": "5657 + 7518 = 13175"}
{"Question": "NEED + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "9556 + 5419 = 14975"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BAKE = MAKER", "Answer": "5759 + 9528 = 15287"}
{"Question": "EVER + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "5859 + 9531 = 15390"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEAR = RANGE", "Answer": "6965 + 5621 = 12586"}
{"Question": "ROOF + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "5667 + 6925 = 12592"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BAND = GREEN", "Answer": "6367 + 7625 = 13992"}
{"Question": "ROOT + OVER = THEME", "Answer": "8661 + 6298 = 14959"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEAR = GANG", "Answer": "7671 + 1748 = 9419"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEAD = GRADE", "Answer": "7072 + 5785 = 12857"}
{"Question": "ARAB + EASE = BUYER", "Answer": "7671 + 5785 = 13456"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEAR = BRAND", "Answer": "7378 + 8706 = 16084"}
{"Question": "HEEL + EACH = CABLE", "Answer": "8779 + 7618 = 16397"}
{"Question": "EVER + TENT = SENSE", "Answer": "7578 + 9739 = 17317"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEST = TASTE", "Answer": "8487 + 1831 = 10318"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEXT = STONE", "Answer": "8085 + 5873 = 13958"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NEAR = FRAME", "Answer": "8085 + 5893 = 13978"}
{"Question": "EVER + REST = TASTE", "Answer": "8487 + 7831 = 16318"}
{"Question": "AWAY + YARD = DRAMA", "Answer": "8987 + 7861 = 16848"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = PIANO", "Answer": "8223 + 2339 = 10562"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = AWFUL", "Answer": "8226 + 2667 = 10893"}
{"Question": "MOOD + ODDS = ADMIT", "Answer": "8553 + 5337 = 13890"}
{"Question": "GOOD + ODDS = EAGER", "Answer": "2774 + 7445 = 10219"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = ALSO", "Answer": "1775 + 7552 = 9327"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = VISIT", "Answer": "4775 + 7553 = 12328"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = CIVIL", "Answer": "5776 + 7662 = 13438"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = SENSE", "Answer": "5883 + 8331 = 14214"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = FALSE", "Answer": "1884 + 8442 = 10326"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = COAST", "Answer": "9884 + 8442 = 18326"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ODDS = BRIEF", "Answer": "7885 + 8552 = 16437"}
{"Question": "LOOK + OKAY = SHALL", "Answer": "6339 + 3927 = 10266"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DATA = TOSS", "Answer": "5443 + 4090 = 9533"}
{"Question": "NONE + INTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "4347 + 9483 = 13830"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FAIR = GREEN", "Answer": "7276 + 4732 = 12008"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DATA = TROOP", "Answer": "9778 + 7212 = 16990"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONCE = ENEMY", "Answer": "5773 + 7381 = 13154"}
{"Question": "NONE + INTO = BEGIN", "Answer": "7473 + 5784 = 13257"}
{"Question": "LOOK + OKAY = CIVIL", "Answer": "6884 + 8472 = 15356"}
{"Question": "NONE + INTO = ENTER", "Answer": "8481 + 9834 = 18315"}
{"Question": "LOOK + OKAY = LAYER", "Answer": "1887 + 8705 = 10592"}
{"Question": "MOON + ONLY = MAYOR", "Answer": "1887 + 8796 = 10683"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = LEGAL", "Answer": "3934 + 9347 = 13281"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = CYCLE", "Answer": "5653 + 6532 = 12185"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = IRAQI", "Answer": "5753 + 7538 = 13291"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = ABOUT", "Answer": "6762 + 7628 = 14390"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WALL = BROWN", "Answer": "6867 + 8622 = 15489"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WALL = BASIS", "Answer": "6963 + 9622 = 16585"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = ABUSE", "Answer": "7672 + 6725 = 14397"}
{"Question": "EVER + VERY = BASIS", "Answer": "7872 + 8723 = 16595"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = ACTOR", "Answer": "4845 + 8435 = 13280"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LADY = IDEAL", "Answer": "8447 + 4837 = 13284"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LADY = MEDIA", "Answer": "8449 + 4829 = 13278"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = ENTRY", "Answer": "5951 + 9531 = 15482"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = BREAD", "Answer": "5853 + 8523 = 14376"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = PRIOR", "Answer": "5857 + 8527 = 14384"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = EARLY", "Answer": "6861 + 8631 = 15492"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = AGAIN", "Answer": "6568 + 5608 = 12176"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = FAVOR", "Answer": "6769 + 7609 = 14378"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONCE = BELOW", "Answer": "7876 + 8706 = 16582"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RAIL = FIBER", "Answer": "4842 + 8436 = 13278"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "5754 + 7521 = 13275"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RACE = BUYER", "Answer": "5851 + 8527 = 14378"}
{"Question": "RARE + ARMY = EQUAL", "Answer": "5851 + 8529 = 14380"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WAIT = ELITE", "Answer": "5852 + 8539 = 14391"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONLY = CLEAN", "Answer": "5853 + 8542 = 14395"}
{"Question": "BABY + ABLE = LEGAL", "Answer": "5758 + 7513 = 13271"}
{"Question": "BABY + ABLE = IDEAL", "Answer": "5859 + 8523 = 14382"}
{"Question": "POOL + OPEN = ANGLE", "Answer": "8556 + 5804 = 14360"}
{"Question": "RARE + ARMY = LEGAL", "Answer": "5854 + 8527 = 14381"}
{"Question": "NINE + INTO = METAL", "Answer": "5854 + 8536 = 14390"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "5857 + 8534 = 14391"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8556 + 5839 = 14395"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DOWN = SNOW", "Answer": "3558 + 5379 = 8937"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RATE = VOTER", "Answer": "5759 + 7528 = 13287"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RATE = OTHER", "Answer": "5758 + 7539 = 13297"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LAST = TREAT", "Answer": "8660 + 6821 = 15481"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RACE = THERE", "Answer": "6860 + 8624 = 15484"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DOWN = UNION", "Answer": "8660 + 6825 = 15485"}
{"Question": "EVEN + VERY = NOISE", "Answer": "6761 + 7625 = 14386"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONLY = LEMON", "Answer": "6764 + 7612 = 14376"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WAIT = EXTRA", "Answer": "6862 + 8634 = 15496"}
{"Question": "BABY + ABLE = TREAT", "Answer": "6768 + 7603 = 14371"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WAGE = ORDER", "Answer": "6765 + 7629 = 14394"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WAIT = THEME", "Answer": "7874 + 8721 = 16595"}
{"Question": "NONE + ONLY = LEGAL", "Answer": "7573 + 5718 = 13291"}
{"Question": "BABY + ABLE = METAL", "Answer": "7874 + 8706 = 16580"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = ERROR", "Answer": "1910 + 8110 = 10020"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = EVERY", "Answer": "1012 + 9112 = 10124"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = ERROR", "Answer": "1915 + 8115 = 10030"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = OCCUR", "Answer": "3930 + 8330 = 12260"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = NERVE", "Answer": "4842 + 9442 = 14284"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = DEATH", "Answer": "4845 + 9445 = 14290"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEER = BREAD", "Answer": "5954 + 8554 = 14508"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = BEAN", "Answer": "6960 + 1660 = 8620"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = DRIVE", "Answer": "6263 + 7663 = 13926"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = BIRTH", "Answer": "8382 + 1882 = 10264"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = TROOP", "Answer": "8782 + 1882 = 10664"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEER = DRESS", "Answer": "8983 + 4883 = 13866"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = THEME", "Answer": "8984 + 1884 = 10868"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = FENCE", "Answer": "8584 + 9884 = 18468"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEEN = TREND", "Answer": "8987 + 1887 = 10874"}
{"Question": "EVER + TEEN = EVENT", "Answer": "1017 + 9112 = 10129"}
{"Question": "EVER + TEEN = FRONT", "Answer": "3732 + 8336 = 12068"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DEEP = APPLY", "Answer": "3935 + 8332 = 12267"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "4643 + 5441 = 10084"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEEP = PRIDE", "Answer": "4643 + 8441 = 13084"}
{"Question": "EVER + SEED = PRESS", "Answer": "4042 + 8446 = 12488"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEER = AWARE", "Answer": "4745 + 8449 = 13194"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEEP = PROOF", "Answer": "5452 + 6551 = 12003"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEEL = BELL", "Answer": "6960 + 1662 = 8622"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEED = DEAD", "Answer": "6960 + 1668 = 8628"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEEP = PRESS", "Answer": "7973 + 5771 = 13744"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEED = KNIFE", "Answer": "7872 + 4775 = 12647"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEEL = SOLVE", "Answer": "7475 + 8772 = 16247"}
{"Question": "EVER + SEED = DRESS", "Answer": "8985 + 6881 = 15866"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SEED = SCENE", "Answer": "8986 + 1882 = 10868"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DEEP = DANCE", "Answer": "8483 + 1885 = 10368"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FEEL = FULLY", "Answer": "8783 + 1886 = 10669"}
{"Question": "EVER + SEEM = TERMS", "Answer": "8483 + 9886 = 18369"}
{"Question": "NONE + KNEE = ODDS", "Answer": "2625 + 4255 = 6880"}
{"Question": "RARE + TREE = PARTY", "Answer": "3034 + 7344 = 10378"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = ANGRY", "Answer": "3139 + 7399 = 10538"}
{"Question": "NINE + KNEE = BEGIN", "Answer": "4642 + 7422 = 12064"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = AHEAD", "Answer": "4146 + 9466 = 13612"}
{"Question": "RARE + TREE = ACTOR", "Answer": "4147 + 6477 = 10624"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = LEAF", "Answer": "5651 + 2511 = 8162"}
{"Question": "NINE + KNEE = BLOOD", "Answer": "6364 + 5644 = 12008"}
{"Question": "RARE + TREE = METAL", "Answer": "6265 + 9655 = 15920"}
{"Question": "RARE + TREE = ELECT", "Answer": "7471 + 2711 = 10182"}
{"Question": "NONE + KNEE = SORRY", "Answer": "7273 + 4733 = 12006"}
{"Question": "NINE + KNEE = CHECK", "Answer": "8483 + 6833 = 15316"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = FLOOR", "Answer": "8384 + 1844 = 10228"}
{"Question": "RARE + TREE = THEIR", "Answer": "8584 + 1844 = 10428"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = FIELD", "Answer": "8786 + 1866 = 10652"}
{"Question": "RARE + FREE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8287 + 1877 = 10164"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEND = ERROR", "Answer": "1913 + 8137 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LOSS = LEAVE", "Answer": "9117 + 1833 = 10950"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TELL = EVENT", "Answer": "1015 + 9144 = 10159"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LESS = LEVEL", "Answer": "9113 + 1088 = 10201"}
{"Question": "COOL + ONLY = KNOCK", "Answer": "8225 + 2056 = 10281"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MALL = DRAMA", "Answer": "2027 + 8255 = 10282"}
{"Question": "AWAY + MASS = SWEEP", "Answer": "4249 + 8411 = 12660"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TALL = ELITE", "Answer": "4649 + 7422 = 12071"}
{"Question": "DEER + EARN = TREND", "Answer": "8442 + 4026 = 12468"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CALL = ELECT", "Answer": "4749 + 8433 = 13182"}
{"Question": "RARE + CREW = WEAR", "Answer": "4348 + 2486 = 6834"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERO = LOOSE", "Answer": "5753 + 6532 = 12285"}
{"Question": "RARE + CREW = SWEAR", "Answer": "5853 + 6532 = 12385"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERO = IRISH", "Answer": "5653 + 7534 = 13187"}
{"Question": "PEER + EARN = HAPPY", "Answer": "9553 + 5437 = 14990"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CALL = REFER", "Answer": "5153 + 9588 = 14741"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DESK = SHOOT", "Answer": "8661 + 6219 = 14880"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERO = ABOVE", "Answer": "6862 + 3624 = 10486"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERO = PROVE", "Answer": "6862 + 5624 = 12486"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DENY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6562 + 7624 = 14186"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "8664 + 6522 = 15186"}
{"Question": "EVER + BELL = NERVE", "Answer": "6864 + 9622 = 16486"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DESK = SMOKE", "Answer": "6771 + 7918 = 14689"}
{"Question": "EVEN + CELL = FENCE", "Answer": "7875 + 9722 = 17597"}
{"Question": "EVER + HERO = SHOE", "Answer": "7375 + 1752 = 9127"}
{"Question": "PIPE + OPEN = HELLO", "Answer": "7576 + 8762 = 16338"}
{"Question": "BEER + EARN = NERVE", "Answer": "9776 + 7861 = 17637"}
{"Question": "PIPE + OPEN = MINOR", "Answer": "7478 + 6782 = 14260"}
{"Question": "BEER + EARN = MAYBE", "Answer": "6778 + 7489 = 14267"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FALL = REFER", "Answer": "7173 + 9788 = 16961"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEND = TASTE", "Answer": "8783 + 1835 = 10618"}
{"Question": "BEER + EARN = TASTE", "Answer": "2883 + 8035 = 10918"}
{"Question": "EVER + CELL = CARRY", "Answer": "8382 + 1844 = 10226"}
{"Question": "EVEN + YELL = FUNNY", "Answer": "8382 + 6844 = 15226"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEND = BLADE", "Answer": "8785 + 1853 = 10638"}
{"Question": "EVER + TERM = THEME", "Answer": "8985 + 1853 = 10838"}
{"Question": "EVER + TERM = CRIME", "Answer": "8085 + 7853 = 15938"}
{"Question": "EVEN + MENU = MOUSE", "Answer": "8386 + 1862 = 10248"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DENY = DRIVE", "Answer": "8486 + 1862 = 10348"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DENY = DANCE", "Answer": "8786 + 1862 = 10648"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TEND = THEME", "Answer": "8986 + 1862 = 10848"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SEND = STUDY", "Answer": "8587 + 1876 = 10463"}
{"Question": "EVEN + CELL = KNOCK", "Answer": "8084 + 6877 = 14961"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BELL = NERVE", "Answer": "8581 + 9877 = 18458"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = CHEEK", "Answer": "7574 + 5654 = 13228"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = WHERE", "Answer": "7679 + 6169 = 13848"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = BIBLE", "Answer": "1812 + 8382 = 10194"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = SWEEP", "Answer": "7872 + 8682 = 16554"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = BUYER", "Answer": "1813 + 8583 = 10396"}
{"Question": "BABY + AWAY = BELOW", "Answer": "1813 + 8683 = 10496"}
{"Question": "RARE + AWAY = EAGER", "Answer": "9291 + 2728 = 12019"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DROP = TRUST", "Answer": "8554 + 5387 = 13941"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "7559 + 5278 = 12837"}
{"Question": "COOK + ONCE = VIDEO", "Answer": "8662 + 6384 = 15046"}
{"Question": "COOK + ONCE = NAKED", "Answer": "7668 + 6174 = 13842"}
{"Question": "COOL + ONCE = SALES", "Answer": "5778 + 7053 = 12831"}
{"Question": "RARE + AWAY = OWNER", "Answer": "8785 + 7673 = 16458"}
{"Question": "RARE + AWAY = WATER", "Answer": "9897 + 8182 = 18079"}
{"Question": "SEED + EASY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6883 + 8265 = 15148"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DROP = USUAL", "Answer": "7886 + 8273 = 16159"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEEP = POSE", "Answer": "5226 + 2337 = 7563"}
{"Question": "RARE + GRAB = LABEL", "Answer": "3236 + 9325 = 12561"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CARE = FEWER", "Answer": "4846 + 7482 = 12328"}
{"Question": "NINE + UNIT = LEGAL", "Answer": "4243 + 9428 = 13671"}
{"Question": "NONE + KNOW = BREAK", "Answer": "4347 + 6439 = 10786"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEER = CROSS", "Answer": "4553 + 5880 = 10433"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SPIN = ENTER", "Answer": "5651 + 7563 = 13214"}
{"Question": "POOR + ODDS = TRUST", "Answer": "7552 + 5339 = 12891"}
{"Question": "RARE + GRAB = BEGIN", "Answer": "6862 + 5681 = 12543"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEER = SHORT", "Answer": "8661 + 6229 = 14890"}
{"Question": "RARE + GRAY = BEGIN", "Answer": "6862 + 5687 = 12549"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ODDS = VISIT", "Answer": "7662 + 6885 = 14547"}
{"Question": "ARAB + PART = OTHER", "Answer": "6762 + 8675 = 15437"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CARD = UNDER", "Answer": "6264 + 7628 = 13892"}
{"Question": "ARAB + EARN = BUYER", "Answer": "7571 + 2754 = 10325"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CARE = BEGIN", "Answer": "7871 + 4782 = 12653"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CARE = BENCH", "Answer": "7871 + 5783 = 13654"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEEP = SPACE", "Answer": "6771 + 7554 = 14325"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEEP = SEIZE", "Answer": "8771 + 7665 = 16436"}
{"Question": "RARE + GRAY = LAYER", "Answer": "7673 + 8764 = 16437"}
{"Question": "RARE + DRAW = EAGER", "Answer": "8381 + 4837 = 13218"}
{"Question": "ARAB + WARN = SENSE", "Answer": "8384 + 7832 = 16216"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8582 + 7856 = 16438"}
{"Question": "TEEN + EARN = ERROR", "Answer": "8115 + 1905 = 10020"}
{"Question": "TEEN + EARN = ESSAY", "Answer": "8116 + 1976 = 10092"}
{"Question": "RARE + URGE = GEAR", "Answer": "2921 + 4271 = 7192"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = EAGER", "Answer": "2021 + 8291 = 10312"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "2521 + 8291 = 10812"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEAN = NERVE", "Answer": "2821 + 9261 = 12082"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "2126 + 4236 = 6362"}
{"Question": "RARE + URGE = ANGER", "Answer": "2126 + 8236 = 10362"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "2426 + 8276 = 10702"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "2526 + 8276 = 10802"}
{"Question": "NINE + ONCE = MINOR", "Answer": "2027 + 8257 = 10284"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = EARTH", "Answer": "3031 + 7341 = 10372"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEAR = GRADE", "Answer": "4942 + 7432 = 12374"}
{"Question": "DOOR + OVER = AWARE", "Answer": "8445 + 4705 = 13150"}
{"Question": "AWAY + EASY = WELL", "Answer": "4846 + 3476 = 8322"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "5752 + 4502 = 10254"}
{"Question": "AWAY + EASY = LAYER", "Answer": "5853 + 9543 = 15396"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "5358 + 7528 = 12886"}
{"Question": "EVER + YEAR = VERY", "Answer": "6961 + 2651 = 9612"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "6761 + 9631 = 16392"}
{"Question": "SOON + OPEN = PRESS", "Answer": "4662 + 6182 = 10844"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LEAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "6263 + 7613 = 13876"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LEAN = VALUE", "Answer": "6163 + 8643 = 14806"}
{"Question": "MOON + OPEN = ENEMY", "Answer": "7664 + 6514 = 14178"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "6468 + 3618 = 10086"}
{"Question": "EVER + NEAR = HONOR", "Answer": "7670 + 4750 = 12420"}
{"Question": "DOOR + OVER = GRADE", "Answer": "8775 + 7205 = 15980"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEAR = START", "Answer": "7076 + 5786 = 12862"}
{"Question": "MOON + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "6779 + 7419 = 14198"}
{"Question": "SOON + OPEN = SCENE", "Answer": "1882 + 8542 = 10424"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEAN = BLOOD", "Answer": "8682 + 1872 = 10554"}
{"Question": "SOON + OPEN = STONE", "Answer": "1882 + 8942 = 10824"}
{"Question": "MEET + EAST = MOTOR", "Answer": "1883 + 8423 = 10306"}
{"Question": "EVER + WEAR = WORRY", "Answer": "8483 + 1853 = 10336"}
{"Question": "AWAY + LADY = LIMIT", "Answer": "8583 + 1823 = 10406"}
{"Question": "NINE + ONCE = OFTEN", "Answer": "8384 + 1864 = 10248"}
{"Question": "EVER + FEAR = FORCE", "Answer": "8584 + 1894 = 10478"}
{"Question": "EVER + TEAR = THERE", "Answer": "8984 + 1864 = 10848"}
{"Question": "RARE + TRUE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8584 + 3874 = 12458"}
{"Question": "EVER + GEAR = ARGUE", "Answer": "8784 + 5814 = 14598"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BEAN = SENSE", "Answer": "8584 + 9834 = 18418"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEAR = NERVE", "Answer": "8584 + 9874 = 18458"}
{"Question": "SOON + OVEN = SERVE", "Answer": "1885 + 8905 = 10790"}
{"Question": "EVEN + MEAN = MONEY", "Answer": "8786 + 1896 = 10682"}
{"Question": "TEEN + EARN = TRIAL", "Answer": "1886 + 8906 = 10792"}
{"Question": "NINE + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8287 + 1807 = 10094"}
{"Question": "SOON + OPEN = SHAPE", "Answer": "1887 + 8347 = 10234"}
{"Question": "AWAY + VARY = VOTER", "Answer": "8687 + 1847 = 10534"}
{"Question": "NINE + ONCE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8087 + 2817 = 10904"}
{"Question": "EVER + DEAR = AVOID", "Answer": "8387 + 4817 = 13204"}
{"Question": "BEER + EACH = AGREE", "Answer": "7335 + 3198 = 10533"}
{"Question": "RARE + CROP = ORDER", "Answer": "3735 + 9318 = 13053"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "7441 + 4620 = 12061"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DARE = ERROR", "Answer": "5449 + 4601 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEAL = SCALE", "Answer": "6441 + 4382 = 10823"}
{"Question": "MOON + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "6441 + 4509 = 10950"}
{"Question": "BOOT + OVER = TRIBE", "Answer": "7441 + 4632 = 12073"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEBT = STONE", "Answer": "8441 + 4362 = 12803"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CAMP = UPPER", "Answer": "4846 + 7452 = 12298"}
{"Question": "ARAB + EACH = THERE", "Answer": "4346 + 8492 = 12838"}
{"Question": "COOK + OPEN = FENCE", "Answer": "5447 + 4903 = 10350"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DEAL = FALSE", "Answer": "7446 + 4923 = 12369"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "5854 + 6531 = 12385"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DIRT = STRIP", "Answer": "6551 + 5942 = 12493"}
{"Question": "PEER + EACH = HAPPY", "Answer": "8559 + 5321 = 13880"}
{"Question": "ARAB + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5657 + 8501 = 14158"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "5657 + 8541 = 14198"}
{"Question": "EVEN + YEAH = HEAVY", "Answer": "5758 + 9521 = 15279"}
{"Question": "NONE + UNIT = ENTER", "Answer": "5751 + 9563 = 15314"}
{"Question": "BOOT + OKAY = STAKE", "Answer": "6552 + 5837 = 12389"}
{"Question": "AWAY + LAST = STYLE", "Answer": "5358 + 7512 = 12870"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "7552 + 5613 = 13165"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DRAW = AWARE", "Answer": "8553 + 5614 = 14167"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TAKE = METER", "Answer": "5356 + 9584 = 14940"}
{"Question": "RARE + IRON = OWNER", "Answer": "5357 + 9518 = 14875"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ONCE = EVENT", "Answer": "3662 + 6481 = 10143"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DARE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7664 + 6821 = 14485"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MALE = LABEL", "Answer": "6763 + 9618 = 16381"}
{"Question": "ARAB + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "6368 + 7629 = 13997"}
{"Question": "AWAY + FAIR = REFER", "Answer": "7670 + 4751 = 12421"}
{"Question": "AWAY + PART = TROOP", "Answer": "7274 + 5731 = 13005"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DATE = STEAL", "Answer": "6771 + 7038 = 13809"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DECK = SCOPE", "Answer": "8771 + 7059 = 15830"}
{"Question": "ODDS + DENY = SENSE", "Answer": "8771 + 7645 = 16416"}
{"Question": "ARAB + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7678 + 9741 = 17419"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MALE = RELAX", "Answer": "7178 + 5792 = 12970"}
{"Question": "AWAY + HAIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7472 + 5713 = 13185"}
{"Question": "AWAY + RATE = METER", "Answer": "7872 + 5763 = 13635"}
{"Question": "ARAB + SAFE = FRESH", "Answer": "7672 + 8713 = 16385"}
{"Question": "RARE + GROW = ANGER", "Answer": "7175 + 9782 = 16957"}
{"Question": "EVER + BEND = NERVE", "Answer": "7875 + 9712 = 17587"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "8587 + 4831 = 13418"}
{"Question": "EVEN + PEAK = PLANE", "Answer": "8582 + 1846 = 10428"}
{"Question": "COOL + OKAY = BLACK", "Answer": "3882 + 8654 = 12536"}
{"Question": "DEEP + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "5886 + 8412 = 14298"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DEAL = PLANE", "Answer": "8582 + 7846 = 16428"}
{"Question": "FOOD + OPEN = FENCE", "Answer": "1887 + 8503 = 10390"}
{"Question": "SOON + OVER = SERVE", "Answer": "1883 + 8907 = 10790"}
{"Question": "ALLY + LOTS = USUAL", "Answer": "4885 + 8263 = 13148"}
{"Question": "COOL + OVEN = SOLVE", "Answer": "9884 + 8573 = 18457"}
{"Question": "EVEN + HEAD = HONEY", "Answer": "8685 + 1897 = 10582"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELL = EAGER", "Answer": "1291 + 9122 = 10413"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELL = CLOCK", "Answer": "3293 + 9322 = 12615"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELL = PAPER", "Answer": "4674 + 7466 = 12140"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELL = RIVER", "Answer": "5685 + 8566 = 14251"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELL = ORDER", "Answer": "6876 + 7688 = 14564"}
{"Question": "EASE + SEAT = ENTER", "Answer": "1291 + 9124 = 10415"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = OFTEN", "Answer": "1791 + 9176 = 10967"}
{"Question": "TEST + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "3493 + 9341 = 12834"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = ENTRY", "Answer": "5275 + 7521 = 12796"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = FRESH", "Answer": "5275 + 7523 = 12798"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = DRESS", "Answer": "5275 + 7524 = 12799"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = KNIFE", "Answer": "5375 + 7532 = 12907"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = SOLAR", "Answer": "5785 + 8572 = 14357"}
{"Question": "EASE + SEAT = METER", "Answer": "5695 + 9562 = 15257"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELF = FUEL", "Answer": "6416 + 1648 = 8064"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = DEAD", "Answer": "6516 + 1652 = 8168"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = NEXT", "Answer": "6816 + 1685 = 8501"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = NOISE", "Answer": "6276 + 7621 = 13897"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = IRISH", "Answer": "6476 + 7649 = 14125"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = ENJOY", "Answer": "7257 + 5721 = 12978"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = SHEET", "Answer": "7267 + 6729 = 13996"}
{"Question": "TEST + STEP = VISIT", "Answer": "7867 + 6780 = 14647"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = PROOF", "Answer": "7687 + 8762 = 16449"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = BEING", "Answer": "7097 + 9706 = 16803"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = TREAT", "Answer": "8518 + 1853 = 10371"}
{"Question": "EASE + SEAT = SKILL", "Answer": "8518 + 1859 = 10377"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = THEIR", "Answer": "8718 + 1875 = 10593"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SELF = OFFER", "Answer": "8438 + 3842 = 12280"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = ENEMY", "Answer": "8348 + 4831 = 13179"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = GUESS", "Answer": "8548 + 4852 = 13400"}
{"Question": "EASE + SEAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8358 + 5839 = 14197"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = FENCE", "Answer": "9429 + 2943 = 12372"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TONE = STAFF", "Answer": "9429 + 2948 = 12377"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = BENCH", "Answer": "9529 + 2954 = 12483"}
{"Question": "AREA + EARN = LEGAL", "Answer": "9539 + 3952 = 13491"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GENE = DOZEN", "Answer": "3173 + 7363 = 10536"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GENE = HELLO", "Answer": "4794 + 9434 = 14228"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GENE = NAKED", "Answer": "6246 + 4616 = 10862"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GENE = INNER", "Answer": "8548 + 4838 = 13386"}
{"Question": "EASE + AREA = SWEAR", "Answer": "4514 + 5945 = 10459"}
{"Question": "EASE + AREA = SPEAK", "Answer": "5715 + 7857 = 13572"}
{"Question": "EASE + AREA = EVERY", "Answer": "1821 + 8318 = 10139"}
{"Question": "EASE + AREA = RIVER", "Answer": "3893 + 8138 = 12031"}
{"Question": "EASE + AREA = SOLAR", "Answer": "6816 + 8468 = 15284"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = STOP", "Answer": "1351 + 5166 = 6517"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = BOOT", "Answer": "1961 + 6155 = 8116"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = OFTEN", "Answer": "1791 + 9166 = 10957"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = ASIAN", "Answer": "4784 + 8433 = 13217"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = SOFT", "Answer": "5015 + 1566 = 6581"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = WORRY", "Answer": "5695 + 9533 = 15228"}
{"Question": "EASE + SELL = ALTER", "Answer": "7157 + 5722 = 12879"}
{"Question": "EASE + SELL = VISIT", "Answer": "7087 + 8766 = 15853"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = TRAIN", "Answer": "8518 + 1877 = 10395"}
{"Question": "EASE + SELL = SHOOT", "Answer": "8918 + 1855 = 10773"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = UNION", "Answer": "8238 + 3844 = 12082"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOSS = LIMIT", "Answer": "8058 + 5877 = 13935"}
{"Question": "EASE + SELL = LATER", "Answer": "8678 + 7811 = 16489"}
{"Question": "DATA + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9121 + 1698 = 10819"}
{"Question": "TEST + STIR = TASTE", "Answer": "1791 + 9126 = 10917"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SEAT = TALL", "Answer": "2062 + 6238 = 8300"}
{"Question": "AREA + EASY = THERE", "Answer": "2582 + 8276 = 10858"}
{"Question": "TEST + STAR = AREA", "Answer": "4924 + 2473 = 7397"}
{"Question": "AREA + EACH = CRIME", "Answer": "4394 + 9415 = 13809"}
{"Question": "DATA + AIDS = BASIC", "Answer": "9484 + 4792 = 14276"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOUR = FORTH", "Answer": "4894 + 9402 = 14296"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GEAR = HEART", "Answer": "4894 + 9432 = 14326"}
{"Question": "TEST + STAR = LARGE", "Answer": "5965 + 6524 = 12489"}
{"Question": "AREA + EASY = YOURS", "Answer": "5375 + 7561 = 12936"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GEAR = APART", "Answer": "5675 + 7519 = 13194"}
{"Question": "AREA + EACH = THERE", "Answer": "5285 + 8543 = 13828"}
{"Question": "AREA + EAST = STORE", "Answer": "5095 + 9514 = 14609"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "6856 + 5612 = 12468"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GEAR = AWARD", "Answer": "6576 + 7619 = 14195"}
{"Question": "TEST + STIR = WRITE", "Answer": "6086 + 8674 = 14760"}
{"Question": "TEST + STOP = PIANO", "Answer": "6286 + 8671 = 14957"}
{"Question": "AREA + EAST = HAPPY", "Answer": "6796 + 9652 = 16448"}
{"Question": "AREA + EACH = LATER", "Answer": "6896 + 9602 = 16498"}
{"Question": "EASE + SELF = OFFER", "Answer": "7547 + 4732 = 12279"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SEAT = ALTER", "Answer": "7257 + 5719 = 12976"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOUR = APART", "Answer": "7457 + 5728 = 13185"}
{"Question": "AREA + EAST = THERE", "Answer": "7087 + 8721 = 15808"}
{"Question": "TEST + STAR = LEAVE", "Answer": "7687 + 8749 = 16436"}
{"Question": "DATA + AIDS = STAND", "Answer": "8767 + 7981 = 16748"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TOUR = THREE", "Answer": "8918 + 1837 = 10755"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SEAT = CLASS", "Answer": "8028 + 2894 = 10922"}
{"Question": "DATA + AIDE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5878 + 8053 = 13931"}
{"Question": "DATA + AIDS = USUAL", "Answer": "7808 + 8376 = 16184"}
{"Question": "AREA + EACH = CHECK", "Answer": "8098 + 9817 = 17915"}
{"Question": "AREA + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8398 + 9821 = 18219"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "1741 + 9177 = 10918"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BELL = CLIMB", "Answer": "5375 + 8533 = 13908"}
{"Question": "ELSE + HELL = LAUGH", "Answer": "6196 + 7611 = 13807"}
{"Question": "ELSE + HELL = SOUTH", "Answer": "7817 + 5788 = 13605"}
{"Question": "ELSE + WELL = WORKS", "Answer": "8758 + 1877 = 10635"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TELL = VISIT", "Answer": "8768 + 5877 = 14645"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9279 + 2742 = 12021"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = AIDS", "Answer": "5285 + 2872 = 8157"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = STUDY", "Answer": "8468 + 4614 = 13082"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = CATCH", "Answer": "8548 + 5465 = 14013"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = LABEL", "Answer": "3823 + 8258 = 12081"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASE = DOZEN", "Answer": "1861 + 8628 = 10489"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = ASIAN", "Answer": "1471 + 9147 = 10618"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = DRINK", "Answer": "1751 + 9175 = 10926"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = DRIVE", "Answer": "1761 + 9176 = 10937"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = LEVEL", "Answer": "2092 + 8209 = 10301"}
{"Question": "AREA + DARE = READ", "Answer": "3483 + 1348 = 4831"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = SOLAR", "Answer": "3853 + 6385 = 10238"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = DRESS", "Answer": "4384 + 9438 = 13822"}
{"Question": "AREA + DARE = OCCUR", "Answer": "4624 + 5462 = 10086"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = EASE", "Answer": "5725 + 1572 = 7297"}
{"Question": "AREA + DARE = FIELD", "Answer": "5735 + 8573 = 14308"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = RAISE", "Answer": "6826 + 5682 = 12508"}
{"Question": "AREA + DARE = BLOOD", "Answer": "7267 + 3726 = 10993"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = PROOF", "Answer": "7267 + 5726 = 12993"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = DEAD", "Answer": "7527 + 1752 = 9279"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = PRIOR", "Answer": "7537 + 2753 = 10290"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = ISSUE", "Answer": "8248 + 1824 = 10072"}
{"Question": "AREA + DARE = BROAD", "Answer": "8258 + 3825 = 12083"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8368 + 1836 = 10204"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = CHILD", "Answer": "8478 + 1847 = 10325"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = SENSE", "Answer": "8468 + 5846 = 14314"}
{"Question": "DEAD + IDEA = IRAQI", "Answer": "8538 + 1853 = 10391"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = CHEST", "Answer": "8658 + 1865 = 10523"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARE = OCCUR", "Answer": "9349 + 2934 = 12283"}
{"Question": "TENT + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "1741 + 9176 = 10917"}
{"Question": "EASE + YEAH = ESSAY", "Answer": "1901 + 8197 = 10098"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARD = RACE", "Answer": "2972 + 6295 = 9267"}
{"Question": "EASE + LEAD = USUAL", "Answer": "2902 + 7295 = 10197"}
{"Question": "TENT + ITEM = CRIME", "Answer": "4254 + 6428 = 10682"}
{"Question": "EASE + TEAM = WASTE", "Answer": "4264 + 8420 = 12684"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DATA = STEEL", "Answer": "4228 + 9434 = 13662"}
{"Question": "EASE + READ = AREA", "Answer": "4684 + 1462 = 6146"}
{"Question": "EASE + BEAT = METAL", "Answer": "4804 + 9482 = 14286"}
{"Question": "EASE + DEAL = BADLY", "Answer": "5265 + 7529 = 12794"}
{"Question": "EASE + HEAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "5385 + 7532 = 12917"}
{"Question": "EASE + LEAD = SALES", "Answer": "5315 + 8536 = 13851"}
{"Question": "EASE + BEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "5405 + 9546 = 14951"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BONE = LABEL", "Answer": "5875 + 4586 = 10461"}
{"Question": "AREA + HARD = COACH", "Answer": "5925 + 8593 = 14518"}
{"Question": "AREA + PART = METAL", "Answer": "6236 + 7628 = 13864"}
{"Question": "EASE + REAL = LATER", "Answer": "6426 + 7641 = 14067"}
{"Question": "AREA + FARM = DEAD", "Answer": "6516 + 2653 = 9169"}
{"Question": "EASE + YEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "6576 + 8652 = 15228"}
{"Question": "TENT + ITEM = SMILE", "Answer": "6896 + 5682 = 12578"}
{"Question": "AREA + YARD = DELAY", "Answer": "7257 + 8721 = 15978"}
{"Question": "TEST + ITEM = ONION", "Answer": "7467 + 2743 = 10210"}
{"Question": "EASE + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "7427 + 6749 = 14176"}
{"Question": "TENT + ITEM = SENSE", "Answer": "7647 + 8769 = 16416"}
{"Question": "EASE + NEAR = SEVEN", "Answer": "7617 + 9762 = 17379"}
{"Question": "TEST + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "7867 + 5789 = 13656"}
{"Question": "TEST + ITEM = ISSUE", "Answer": "8208 + 1824 = 10032"}
{"Question": "ELSE + RELY = RURAL", "Answer": "8328 + 1835 = 10163"}
{"Question": "KICK + SKIN = SENSE", "Answer": "8378 + 1832 = 10210"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOND = ADAPT", "Answer": "8328 + 5834 = 14162"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LONG = LEGAL", "Answer": "8478 + 1843 = 10321"}
{"Question": "AREA + CARD = DREAM", "Answer": "8538 + 6851 = 15389"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BELT = BASIS", "Answer": "8658 + 1867 = 10525"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LONG = LEVEL", "Answer": "8728 + 1873 = 10601"}
{"Question": "EASE + MEAT = MOTOR", "Answer": "8728 + 1876 = 10604"}
{"Question": "EASE + DEAL = ORDER", "Answer": "8708 + 5876 = 14584"}
{"Question": "EASE + BEAN = INNER", "Answer": "8708 + 6875 = 15583"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = RURAL", "Answer": "4734 + 7433 = 12167"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = COOL", "Answer": "4284 + 2488 = 6772"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = BALL", "Answer": "6156 + 1655 = 7811"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = METAL", "Answer": "7927 + 9722 = 17649"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = ADULT", "Answer": "8528 + 5822 = 14350"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = CARRY", "Answer": "8728 + 7822 = 16550"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LESS = BLOOD", "Answer": "9839 + 8933 = 18772"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = TOTAL", "Answer": "2912 + 9218 = 12130"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = HOTEL", "Answer": "3923 + 9324 = 13247"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = EVENT", "Answer": "3843 + 8341 = 12184"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = PILOT", "Answer": "5825 + 8527 = 14352"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = CLEAN", "Answer": "5745 + 7542 = 13287"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = EARN", "Answer": "5265 + 2567 = 7832"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = LABEL", "Answer": "6726 + 7625 = 14351"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6826 + 8625 = 15451"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = TIGHT", "Answer": "7817 + 8714 = 16531"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = SHEET", "Answer": "7827 + 8725 = 16552"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = ARMED", "Answer": "7547 + 5749 = 13296"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = TRAIN", "Answer": "8718 + 7819 = 16537"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = LATIN", "Answer": "8428 + 4826 = 13254"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = CHEEK", "Answer": "8728 + 7825 = 16553"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = AGENT", "Answer": "8738 + 7835 = 16573"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = BEING", "Answer": "8738 + 7836 = 16574"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = PAPER", "Answer": "8348 + 3849 = 12197"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = GIVEN", "Answer": "8748 + 7849 = 16597"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOTE = ENEMY", "Answer": "9239 + 2931 = 12170"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "2972 + 9207 = 12179"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = COURT", "Answer": "4864 + 8416 = 13280"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = SWEAR", "Answer": "5835 + 8523 = 14358"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = BUYER", "Answer": "6826 + 8602 = 15428"}
{"Question": "AREA + RATE = COLOR", "Answer": "6826 + 8632 = 15458"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = CHEST", "Answer": "7637 + 6713 = 14350"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = EAGER", "Answer": "8918 + 9801 = 18719"}
{"Question": "AREA + RATE = SHOOT", "Answer": "8528 + 5802 = 14330"}
{"Question": "AREA + RATE = COURT", "Answer": "8748 + 7824 = 16572"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8578 + 5807 = 14385"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = TREAT", "Answer": "9329 + 3962 = 13291"}
{"Question": "AREA + RACE = CREAM", "Answer": "9879 + 8917 = 18796"}
{"Question": "AREA + RANK = DANCE", "Answer": "4924 + 9438 = 14362"}
{"Question": "AREA + RAIN = ELITE", "Answer": "5715 + 7526 = 13241"}
{"Question": "AREA + RANK = KNIFE", "Answer": "5765 + 7531 = 13296"}
{"Question": "AREA + RAIN = NEAR", "Answer": "5285 + 2567 = 7852"}
{"Question": "AREA + RAIL = ENTER", "Answer": "6816 + 8602 = 15418"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DEAR = SALAD", "Answer": "6806 + 8652 = 15458"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LEAD = STUDY", "Answer": "6816 + 8623 = 15439"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LEAD = SKILL", "Answer": "6816 + 8672 = 15488"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DEBT = THING", "Answer": "6876 + 8621 = 15497"}
{"Question": "AREA + RAIL = EXIST", "Answer": "7517 + 5729 = 13246"}
{"Question": "AREA + RAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "7617 + 6734 = 14351"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LEAN = STAND", "Answer": "7617 + 6735 = 14352"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DENY = GIVEN", "Answer": "7617 + 6758 = 14375"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DEAL = NAKED", "Answer": "7627 + 6749 = 14376"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NOSE = LIMIT", "Answer": "8728 + 7834 = 16562"}
{"Question": "EASE + MESS = ELECT", "Answer": "1961 + 8166 = 10127"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = EARTH", "Answer": "1071 + 9177 = 10248"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = SLEEP", "Answer": "2012 + 8211 = 10223"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = SEVEN", "Answer": "2812 + 9211 = 12023"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = PANEL", "Answer": "2062 + 8266 = 10328"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = USUAL", "Answer": "4734 + 8433 = 13167"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = LIMIT", "Answer": "4154 + 6455 = 10609"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = ALBUM", "Answer": "4354 + 9455 = 13809"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = ALLY", "Answer": "4864 + 3466 = 8330"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = SALAD", "Answer": "5215 + 7511 = 12726"}
{"Question": "EASE + MESS = USUAL", "Answer": "5635 + 7533 = 13168"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = RURAL", "Answer": "5635 + 8533 = 14168"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = METAL", "Answer": "5845 + 9544 = 15389"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = BELL", "Answer": "6956 + 1655 = 8611"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = BALL", "Answer": "6156 + 3655 = 9811"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = COLOR", "Answer": "6276 + 9677 = 15953"}
{"Question": "EASE + LESS = LOCAL", "Answer": "8738 + 1833 = 10571"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = ASIAN", "Answer": "8058 + 7855 = 15913"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "8568 + 3866 = 12434"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MESS = LEARN", "Answer": "8168 + 9866 = 18034"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9289 + 2782 = 12071"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = SEVEN", "Answer": "9319 + 3713 = 13032"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = LOTS", "Answer": "4374 + 3873 = 8247"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = MUSIC", "Answer": "4534 + 5835 = 10369"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = UNTIL", "Answer": "4534 + 5935 = 10469"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = STAR", "Answer": "2582 + 5685 = 8267"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7587 + 5685 = 13272"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = STEP", "Answer": "1681 + 6486 = 8167"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = SALAD", "Answer": "5715 + 7317 = 13032"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = SHALL", "Answer": "6716 + 7317 = 14033"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8718 + 7317 = 16035"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = LABEL", "Answer": "4784 + 7287 = 12071"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = PAPER", "Answer": "5785 + 7387 = 13172"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = FAITH", "Answer": "7837 + 8638 = 16475"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "5845 + 8348 = 14193"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = ASIAN", "Answer": "6856 + 8158 = 15014"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1861 + 8268 = 10129"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = LEARN", "Answer": "9869 + 8168 = 18037"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = LOCAL", "Answer": "3873 + 8178 = 12051"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASE = ALBUM", "Answer": "4874 + 8178 = 13052"}
{"Question": "TEST + ELSE = STILL", "Answer": "4914 + 9319 = 14233"}
{"Question": "DATA + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8131 + 1932 = 10063"}
{"Question": "DATA + AUTO = AWARD", "Answer": "8161 + 1967 = 10128"}
{"Question": "DATA + AUTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "9171 + 1476 = 10647"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "1571 + 9174 = 10745"}
{"Question": "HERE + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "6212 + 2917 = 9129"}
{"Question": "ELSE + DESK = STEEL", "Answer": "3013 + 9317 = 12330"}
{"Question": "EASE + BEST = SALES", "Answer": "3213 + 9318 = 12531"}
{"Question": "HERE + EARN = REFER", "Answer": "9313 + 3718 = 13031"}
{"Question": "THAT + STAR = HEART", "Answer": "3153 + 9350 = 12503"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = SEVEN", "Answer": "3563 + 9362 = 12925"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = EVEN", "Answer": "3083 + 4387 = 7470"}
{"Question": "EASE + REST = AREA", "Answer": "4674 + 1472 = 6146"}
{"Question": "EASE + DESK = BASIS", "Answer": "5285 + 7583 = 12868"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = TENT", "Answer": "5895 + 3594 = 9489"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOTS = TITLE", "Answer": "6516 + 3618 = 10134"}
{"Question": "MERE + EARN = ARMED", "Answer": "7636 + 6132 = 13768"}
{"Question": "EASE + REST = INNER", "Answer": "6936 + 8632 = 15568"}
{"Question": "THAT + STAR = BASIS", "Answer": "6256 + 9653 = 15909"}
{"Question": "HERE + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "7686 + 6482 = 14168"}
{"Question": "THAT + STAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "6296 + 7693 = 13989"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEST = STILL", "Answer": "7317 + 8716 = 16033"}
{"Question": "THAT + STAR = WASTE", "Answer": "7837 + 5739 = 13576"}
{"Question": "HERE + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "8737 + 7936 = 16673"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = GIVEN", "Answer": "7067 + 8763 = 15830"}
{"Question": "MERE + EARN = MINOR", "Answer": "1828 + 8624 = 10452"}
{"Question": "ONTO + VOTE = NEVER", "Answer": "8138 + 9837 = 17975"}
{"Question": "EASE + REST = AGREE", "Answer": "8148 + 9840 = 17988"}
{"Question": "EASE + BEST = WASTE", "Answer": "8658 + 7850 = 16508"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEST = USUAL", "Answer": "8268 + 7864 = 16132"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOTH = BASIS", "Answer": "8378 + 1874 = 10252"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOTH = NERVE", "Answer": "8178 + 3874 = 12052"}
{"Question": "DATA + AUTO = UNION", "Answer": "4878 + 8175 = 13053"}
{"Question": "THAT + STAR = IRISH", "Answer": "8278 + 5874 = 14152"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEST = LEGAL", "Answer": "8178 + 9873 = 18051"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOTS = NOISE", "Answer": "8178 + 9875 = 18053"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = ROOT", "Answer": "2872 + 5242 = 8114"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = TOOTH", "Answer": "3903 + 8313 = 12216"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = EAGER", "Answer": "4814 + 9404 = 14218"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = TREND", "Answer": "4264 + 8414 = 12678"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = WHERE", "Answer": "4384 + 6454 = 10838"}
{"Question": "EASE + HERE = PAPER", "Answer": "6536 + 8626 = 15162"}
{"Question": "EASE + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "8108 + 9878 = 17986"}
{"Question": "EASE + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "8468 + 9828 = 18296"}
{"Question": "EASE + HERE = HONOR", "Answer": "8538 + 1868 = 10406"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATA = BREAD", "Answer": "8538 + 6848 = 15386"}
{"Question": "EASE + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "1781 + 9133 = 10914"}
{"Question": "AREA + FADE = READ", "Answer": "1351 + 2165 = 3516"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = ADAPT", "Answer": "1951 + 8175 = 10126"}
{"Question": "AREA + FADE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1351 + 9165 = 10516"}
{"Question": "AREA + FATE = ADAPT", "Answer": "1961 + 8176 = 10137"}
{"Question": "AREA + TAKE = ACTOR", "Answer": "1761 + 9186 = 10947"}
{"Question": "AREA + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "1871 + 9107 = 10978"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1681 + 9138 = 10819"}
{"Question": "AREA + NAME = MEAN", "Answer": "2142 + 6284 = 8426"}
{"Question": "AREA + HATE = OTHER", "Answer": "2642 + 8204 = 10846"}
{"Question": "AREA + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "2462 + 8206 = 10668"}
{"Question": "EASE + TELL = SPLIT", "Answer": "2412 + 8266 = 10678"}
{"Question": "AREA + BALL = REFER", "Answer": "2102 + 8299 = 10401"}
{"Question": "ONTO + PORT = FLOOR", "Answer": "3953 + 6385 = 10338"}
{"Question": "AREA + FADE = SALAD", "Answer": "3653 + 9385 = 13038"}
{"Question": "EASE + BELL = HELLO", "Answer": "4804 + 9422 = 14226"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = DEAD", "Answer": "4934 + 2413 = 7347"}
{"Question": "EASE + CELL = BASIS", "Answer": "4274 + 8433 = 12707"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "4054 + 6495 = 10549"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = SPEAK", "Answer": "4054 + 8495 = 12549"}
{"Question": "AREA + TALE = VITAL", "Answer": "4354 + 8495 = 12849"}
{"Question": "AREA + SAFE = FRESH", "Answer": "4264 + 8416 = 12680"}
{"Question": "EASE + WELL = AWAY", "Answer": "4674 + 1488 = 6162"}
{"Question": "ONTO + MOST = DRAMA", "Answer": "4784 + 5468 = 10252"}
{"Question": "EDGE + BELL = GLAD", "Answer": "5685 + 2511 = 8196"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOSS = ASIAN", "Answer": "5795 + 6522 = 12317"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = LATIN", "Answer": "5725 + 8542 = 14267"}
{"Question": "AREA + MALE = CLEAR", "Answer": "5835 + 6523 = 12358"}
{"Question": "AREA + NAME = MENU", "Answer": "5845 + 1574 = 7419"}
{"Question": "GENE + EARN = BASIS", "Answer": "8545 + 5364 = 13909"}
{"Question": "AREA + LAKE = ROLL", "Answer": "5765 + 1546 = 7311"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = LATER", "Answer": "6826 + 9602 = 16428"}
{"Question": "AREA + MALL = CREAM", "Answer": "6076 + 4688 = 10764"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = AGAIN", "Answer": "6486 + 5618 = 12104"}
{"Question": "AREA + HAVE = EVERY", "Answer": "7417 + 5731 = 13148"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = STAND", "Answer": "7027 + 5782 = 12809"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ROLL = MOTOR", "Answer": "7857 + 9722 = 17579"}
{"Question": "AREA + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "7457 + 2715 = 10172"}
{"Question": "EASE + NEWS = OWNER", "Answer": "7567 + 2706 = 10273"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = ENTER", "Answer": "7087 + 3728 = 10815"}
{"Question": "ONTO + PORT = TROOP", "Answer": "8018 + 9871 = 17889"}
{"Question": "EDGE + SELL = SALES", "Answer": "8548 + 1833 = 10381"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOST = LEVEL", "Answer": "8538 + 1863 = 10401"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = REFER", "Answer": "8138 + 4893 = 13031"}
{"Question": "AREA + HAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8038 + 5893 = 13931"}
{"Question": "AREA + CASE = CHECK", "Answer": "8548 + 1864 = 10412"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = CATCH", "Answer": "8548 + 7864 = 16412"}
{"Question": "AREA + FACE = FOCUS", "Answer": "8758 + 1865 = 10623"}
{"Question": "AREA + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "8758 + 3825 = 12583"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAKE = CLOCK", "Answer": "8368 + 1846 = 10214"}
{"Question": "ONTO + COAT = CABIN", "Answer": "8468 + 1806 = 10274"}
{"Question": "AREA + HATE = HUMOR", "Answer": "8468 + 1856 = 10324"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAKE = CHECK", "Answer": "8768 + 1846 = 10614"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAKE = CHEST", "Answer": "8768 + 1856 = 10624"}
{"Question": "ONTO + POET = PIECE", "Answer": "8678 + 1857 = 10535"}
{"Question": "AREA + BAKE = BLACK", "Answer": "8978 + 1857 = 10835"}
{"Question": "AREA + DATE = BROAD", "Answer": "8478 + 5807 = 14285"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ROLL = ENTER", "Answer": "8438 + 5877 = 14315"}
{"Question": "AREA + LAKE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8978 + 5807 = 14785"}
{"Question": "ONTO + POET = NERVE", "Answer": "8178 + 6857 = 15035"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BOAT = UNION", "Answer": "8578 + 6807 = 15385"}
{"Question": "AREA + LAKE = RELAX", "Answer": "8178 + 9807 = 17985"}
{"Question": "AREA + FADE = RAPID", "Answer": "8178 + 9857 = 18035"}
{"Question": "AREA + FALL = FEWER", "Answer": "8708 + 1899 = 10607"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ELSE = STAFF", "Answer": "8408 + 4614 = 13022"}
{"Question": "THAT + HIGH = AGAIN", "Answer": "8518 + 5645 = 14163"}
{"Question": "DATA + ACID = PITCH", "Answer": "8525 + 5748 = 14273"}
{"Question": "GANG + AREA = ENTRY", "Answer": "8658 + 6716 = 15374"}
{"Question": "GANG + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "5635 + 6926 = 12561"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ELSE = BASIS", "Answer": "8658 + 6746 = 15404"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ONTO = MIGHT", "Answer": "5715 + 7927 = 13642"}
{"Question": "DATA + ACID = TRIAL", "Answer": "6717 + 7856 = 14573"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "6786 + 7427 = 14213"}
{"Question": "GANG + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "3873 + 8208 = 12081"}
{"Question": "TENT + EASE = SALES", "Answer": "3863 + 8218 = 12081"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ELSE = ALTER", "Answer": "5815 + 8468 = 14283"}
{"Question": "GANG + AREA = REFER", "Answer": "3893 + 8128 = 12021"}
{"Question": "HERE + EACH = PAPER", "Answer": "4828 + 8354 = 13182"}
{"Question": "THAT + HIGH = EAGER", "Answer": "5845 + 8768 = 14613"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ONTO = NIGHT", "Answer": "6876 + 8148 = 15024"}
{"Question": "HERE + EACH = ACTOR", "Answer": "7858 + 8167 = 16025"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BORN = ENTER", "Answer": "3263 + 9352 = 12615"}
{"Question": "EDGE + HEAD = ADMIT", "Answer": "4294 + 8412 = 12706"}
{"Question": "AREA + FAIR = DRESS", "Answer": "4274 + 8492 = 12766"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MEAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "5295 + 7512 = 12807"}
{"Question": "AREA + FAIR = ONION", "Answer": "5865 + 7548 = 13413"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BORN = ACTOR", "Answer": "5285 + 9572 = 14857"}
{"Question": "EDGE + TEND = OFTEN", "Answer": "5375 + 9583 = 14958"}
{"Question": "ELSE + DEAL = STAND", "Answer": "6216 + 8692 = 14908"}
{"Question": "ELSE + REAL = LABOR", "Answer": "6196 + 7631 = 13827"}
{"Question": "AREA + FAIR = SEIZE", "Answer": "6846 + 7658 = 14504"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BORN = STAND", "Answer": "7247 + 6782 = 14029"}
{"Question": "AREA + FAIR = RIFLE", "Answer": "7187 + 9761 = 16948"}
{"Question": "AREA + HAIR = BENCH", "Answer": "8528 + 3875 = 12403"}
{"Question": "ONTO + DOWN = ENTER", "Answer": "8438 + 5874 = 14312"}
{"Question": "AREA + HAIR = HOUSE", "Answer": "8648 + 1876 = 10524"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOAN = LEAST", "Answer": "8758 + 1867 = 10625"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BORN = DRESS", "Answer": "8458 + 7864 = 16322"}
{"Question": "AREA + TANK = ENTER", "Answer": "2612 + 8204 = 10816"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAST = TRACE", "Answer": "2032 + 8251 = 10283"}
{"Question": "HIGH + THAN = GIANT", "Answer": "3213 + 9356 = 12569"}
{"Question": "THAT + STEP = PHASE", "Answer": "3253 + 9341 = 12594"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "3473 + 9385 = 12858"}
{"Question": "AREA + FACT = CATCH", "Answer": "4804 + 9412 = 14216"}
{"Question": "HIGH + THUS = GUEST", "Answer": "4614 + 7423 = 12037"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOSE = STEEL", "Answer": "4924 + 7413 = 12337"}
{"Question": "ONTO + COAL = PLANT", "Answer": "4964 + 7432 = 12396"}
{"Question": "AREA + CASH = THERE", "Answer": "4274 + 9453 = 13727"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SOIL = TITLE", "Answer": "5615 + 7534 = 13149"}
{"Question": "EASE + DEBT = BASIS", "Answer": "5395 + 8514 = 13909"}
{"Question": "EDGE + REAL = AWARE", "Answer": "5675 + 8510 = 14185"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEAN = TASTE", "Answer": "5395 + 7520 = 12915"}
{"Question": "ONTO + CORE = GREEN", "Answer": "5465 + 7529 = 12994"}
{"Question": "AREA + FAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "5625 + 8547 = 14172"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MENU = USUAL", "Answer": "5645 + 8531 = 14176"}
{"Question": "MERE + EAST = TERMS", "Answer": "9535 + 5861 = 15396"}
{"Question": "THAT + STEP = EASE", "Answer": "5845 + 1572 = 7417"}
{"Question": "AREA + CASH = TASTE", "Answer": "5875 + 9542 = 15417"}
{"Question": "HIGH + CHEF = PIECE", "Answer": "5295 + 7583 = 12878"}
{"Question": "TENT + STAR = GRASS", "Answer": "5385 + 7592 = 12977"}
{"Question": "AREA + BACK = EAGER", "Answer": "6816 + 9602 = 16418"}
{"Question": "AREA + PATH = THEME", "Answer": "6296 + 7613 = 13909"}
{"Question": "EDGE + TEAM = ADMIT", "Answer": "6596 + 8612 = 15208"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOVE = NEVER", "Answer": "6156 + 7683 = 13839"}
{"Question": "EDGE + REAL = PAPER", "Answer": "7467 + 2705 = 10172"}
{"Question": "AREA + MATH = THEIR", "Answer": "7307 + 8716 = 16023"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BODY = THEME", "Answer": "7517 + 4786 = 12303"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEAR = START", "Answer": "7617 + 4735 = 12352"}
{"Question": "HIGH + THAN = NIGHT", "Answer": "7637 + 8741 = 16378"}
{"Question": "AREA + SAND = DRESS", "Answer": "7637 + 8751 = 16388"}
{"Question": "AREA + CAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7587 + 9731 = 17318"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TERM = DRAMA", "Answer": "7287 + 6743 = 14030"}
{"Question": "EDGE + NEAR = NAKED", "Answer": "8478 + 1806 = 10284"}
{"Question": "THAT + STIR = IRISH", "Answer": "8348 + 6815 = 15163"}
{"Question": "ONTO + COME = CREAM", "Answer": "8728 + 1835 = 10563"}
{"Question": "ONTO + CORE = ENTER", "Answer": "8328 + 4891 = 13219"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOUD = ADULT", "Answer": "8438 + 6825 = 15263"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ROLE = ALTER", "Answer": "8428 + 7869 = 16297"}
{"Question": "THAT + ITEM = ISSUE", "Answer": "8238 + 1857 = 10095"}
{"Question": "ONTO + LOVE = EVENT", "Answer": "8298 + 4831 = 13129"}
{"Question": "AREA + GAIN = SENSE", "Answer": "8638 + 4875 = 13513"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BEND = BASIS", "Answer": "8548 + 1876 = 10424"}
{"Question": "ONTO + POEM = NERVE", "Answer": "8178 + 5846 = 14024"}
{"Question": "HIGH + THUS = TRUST", "Answer": "8678 + 1853 = 10531"}
{"Question": "ONTO + MOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8678 + 4853 = 13531"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = WALL", "Answer": "2655 + 5267 = 7922"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = AREA", "Answer": "5285 + 2853 = 8138"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = BLAME", "Answer": "8258 + 2587 = 10845"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = ODDS", "Answer": "3844 + 4380 = 8224"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = EASE", "Answer": "3483 + 4835 = 8318"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = FEWER", "Answer": "7457 + 4572 = 12029"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STOP = PIANO", "Answer": "4877 + 7481 = 12358"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8438 + 4381 = 12819"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = METER", "Answer": "8438 + 4382 = 12820"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STOP = VISIT", "Answer": "4388 + 8436 = 12824"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = LEVEL", "Answer": "9439 + 4392 = 13831"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = DEATH", "Answer": "7527 + 5271 = 12798"}
{"Question": "AREA + REAL = ELITE", "Answer": "8518 + 5183 = 13701"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = BLADE", "Answer": "5685 + 6853 = 12538"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = FLESH", "Answer": "7627 + 6279 = 13906"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = TOTAL", "Answer": "6477 + 7649 = 14126"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = SHARE", "Answer": "2752 + 7523 = 10275"}
{"Question": "AREA + REAL = BLADE", "Answer": "4764 + 7642 = 12406"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = WORLD", "Answer": "7255 + 5721 = 12976"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = COULD", "Answer": "7255 + 5723 = 12978"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = SENSE", "Answer": "6746 + 7468 = 14214"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = WORRY", "Answer": "7688 + 8761 = 16449"}
{"Question": "AREA + REAL = APPLY", "Answer": "1821 + 8213 = 10034"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLOW = APPLE", "Answer": "8433 + 3847 = 12280"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = GUIDE", "Answer": "5875 + 8752 = 14627"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = EAGER", "Answer": "6856 + 8561 = 15417"}
{"Question": "THAT + HATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "6876 + 8761 = 15637"}
{"Question": "AREA + READ = BASIS", "Answer": "2962 + 9623 = 12585"}
{"Question": "NONE + OPEN = PEAK", "Answer": "5158 + 1685 = 6843"}
{"Question": "NONE + OPEN = SPEND", "Answer": "8589 + 5398 = 13987"}
{"Question": "NONE + OPEN = PIANO", "Answer": "7679 + 6197 = 13876"}
{"Question": "NONE + OPEN = APART", "Answer": "7675 + 6457 = 14132"}
{"Question": "NONE + OPEN = BENCH", "Answer": "8785 + 7058 = 15843"}
{"Question": "NONE + OVEN = HEAVY", "Answer": "8786 + 7568 = 16354"}
{"Question": "LESS + SLOW = BIBLE", "Answer": "3788 + 8349 = 12137"}
{"Question": "EVER + VOTE = TRUST", "Answer": "8483 + 4718 = 13201"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROAD = HEART", "Answer": "4504 + 5948 = 10452"}
{"Question": "PASS + SPIN = INNER", "Answer": "5877 + 7513 = 13390"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SLIP = PIANO", "Answer": "5877 + 7531 = 13408"}
{"Question": "NINE + IRON = LEVEL", "Answer": "8583 + 5048 = 13631"}
{"Question": "NINE + IRON = REFER", "Answer": "8583 + 5148 = 13731"}
{"Question": "EVER + VOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "8583 + 5218 = 13801"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DIET = FIELD", "Answer": "8508 + 5387 = 13895"}
{"Question": "PASS + SPOT = WASTE", "Answer": "5388 + 8509 = 13897"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STAR = APART", "Answer": "6577 + 7619 = 14196"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STIR = FIRST", "Answer": "7822 + 2705 = 10527"}
{"Question": "LESS + SLIP = RIFLE", "Answer": "7344 + 4729 = 12073"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7944 + 4726 = 12670"}
{"Question": "LESS + SLIP = TASTE", "Answer": "7866 + 6752 = 14618"}
{"Question": "EVER + VOTE = GREAT", "Answer": "8785 + 7038 = 15823"}
{"Question": "LESS + SLOW = AWARE", "Answer": "7488 + 8706 = 16194"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROAD = AWARE", "Answer": "1871 + 8316 = 10187"}
{"Question": "LESS + SLOW = HELLO", "Answer": "8022 + 2864 = 10886"}
{"Question": "EVEN + VOTE = COUNT", "Answer": "5852 + 8475 = 14327"}
{"Question": "TOSS + STAR = CRACK", "Answer": "8755 + 5864 = 14619"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DIET = TIRED", "Answer": "7807 + 8671 = 16478"}
{"Question": "NINE + IRON = ORDER", "Answer": "7879 + 8617 = 16496"}
{"Question": "NINE + IRON = KNOCK", "Answer": "5956 + 9325 = 15281"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BALL = AHEAD", "Answer": "1558 + 9155 = 10713"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BALL = AGREE", "Answer": "1667 + 9166 = 10833"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MALL = ADMIT", "Answer": "1776 + 9177 = 10953"}
{"Question": "ALLY + HALL = THAT", "Answer": "2114 + 3211 = 5325"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BALL = FLOOR", "Answer": "3228 + 9322 = 12550"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MALL = LIMIT", "Answer": "6119 + 7611 = 13730"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TALL = FLOAT", "Answer": "6334 + 7633 = 13967"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TALL = ELITE", "Answer": "6338 + 7633 = 13971"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CALL = BLOCK", "Answer": "7228 + 5722 = 12950"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TALL = EXTRA", "Answer": "7225 + 9722 = 16947"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TALL = ELECT", "Answer": "7442 + 6744 = 14186"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BALL = REFER", "Answer": "8229 + 6822 = 15051"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FALL = FEWER", "Answer": "8552 + 1855 = 10407"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CALL = CHECK", "Answer": "8557 + 1855 = 10412"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CALL = CROSS", "Answer": "8667 + 1866 = 10533"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BALL = BUYER", "Answer": "8776 + 1877 = 10653"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FALL = REFER", "Answer": "8774 + 6877 = 15651"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = LATIN", "Answer": "9133 + 1395 = 10528"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = RIVER", "Answer": "9344 + 3497 = 12841"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = VOTER", "Answer": "9522 + 5298 = 14820"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "3655 + 6531 = 10186"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1833 + 8314 = 10147"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = APPLY", "Answer": "3844 + 8436 = 12280"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = RIFLE", "Answer": "3855 + 8530 = 12385"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEFT = FINAL", "Answer": "1866 + 8612 = 10478"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAF = BALL", "Answer": "7144 + 1467 = 8611"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NECK = EVEN", "Answer": "5166 + 1695 = 6861"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAF = TRAIL", "Answer": "8466 + 4608 = 13074"}
{"Question": "TREE + REST = OCCUR", "Answer": "7588 + 5807 = 13395"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAF = SKILL", "Answer": "7588 + 5867 = 13455"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAF = PANEL", "Answer": "4622 + 6204 = 10826"}
{"Question": "TREE + REST = FEWER", "Answer": "5722 + 7205 = 12927"}
{"Question": "TREE + REST = AFTER", "Answer": "3855 + 8503 = 12358"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NECK = LEVEL", "Answer": "6855 + 8596 = 15451"}
{"Question": "TREE + REST = THIRD", "Answer": "1866 + 8621 = 10487"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LESS = PRIOR", "Answer": "6544 + 5488 = 12032"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LESS = BASIC", "Answer": "2788 + 7866 = 10654"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LESS = BEACH", "Answer": "6855 + 8577 = 15432"}
{"Question": "HERE + THEM = HUMOR", "Answer": "1252 + 9123 = 10375"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FAIL = ASIAN", "Answer": "1448 + 9164 = 10612"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FAIL = AGREE", "Answer": "1448 + 9174 = 10622"}
{"Question": "BEER + ABLE = BOARD", "Answer": "1776 + 9187 = 10963"}
{"Question": "BALL + ALSO = SHOOT", "Answer": "8277 + 2719 = 10996"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "9322 + 3286 = 12608"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAD = SHALL", "Answer": "7344 + 3489 = 10833"}
{"Question": "BEER + ABLE = RELAX", "Answer": "4221 + 8462 = 12683"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NEAR = BRAIN", "Answer": "8522 + 5273 = 13795"}
{"Question": "BALL + ALSO = CLOCK", "Answer": "8533 + 5379 = 13912"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "8533 + 5392 = 13925"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROAD = SERVE", "Answer": "5331 + 9573 = 14904"}
{"Question": "CALL + ALSO = SHOCK", "Answer": "8577 + 5712 = 14289"}
{"Question": "FREE + READ = DRAFT", "Answer": "9577 + 5721 = 15298"}
{"Question": "TREE + READ = EXTRA", "Answer": "7611 + 6154 = 13765"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOND = SENSE", "Answer": "6221 + 7692 = 13913"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TAIL = VITAL", "Answer": "6220 + 8642 = 14862"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "9622 + 6258 = 15880"}
{"Question": "HERE + THEM = REACH", "Answer": "6414 + 7642 = 14056"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAN = NEWLY", "Answer": "7644 + 6421 = 14065"}
{"Question": "FREE + READ = AWARE", "Answer": "7655 + 6510 = 14165"}
{"Question": "TREE + READ = APART", "Answer": "7655 + 6512 = 14167"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RAIL = FLOOR", "Answer": "6553 + 8675 = 15228"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOND = ASIAN", "Answer": "6884 + 7628 = 14512"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LEAD = PANEL", "Answer": "3722 + 7205 = 10927"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "7225 + 3712 = 10937"}
{"Question": "FREE + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "2744 + 7403 = 10147"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "7443 + 6724 = 14167"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NEAR = BRAND", "Answer": "6755 + 7524 = 14279"}
{"Question": "BEER + ABLE = IRAQI", "Answer": "7883 + 5708 = 13591"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ALSO = STAFF", "Answer": "7882 + 6718 = 14600"}
{"Question": "BEER + ABLE = CLASS", "Answer": "7885 + 6748 = 14633"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "8229 + 3802 = 12031"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "8339 + 1803 = 10142"}
{"Question": "TREE + RELY = TOTAL", "Answer": "1833 + 8329 = 10162"}
{"Question": "TALL + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "1833 + 8350 = 10183"}
{"Question": "BEER + ABLE = APART", "Answer": "8339 + 1853 = 10192"}
{"Question": "TREE + REAL = LEAST", "Answer": "5844 + 8421 = 14265"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROAD = START", "Answer": "8441 + 6824 = 15265"}
{"Question": "NEED + ONCE = INDEX", "Answer": "8442 + 9804 = 18246"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOAD = LEAST", "Answer": "8559 + 1835 = 10394"}
{"Question": "HERE + CHEF = CATCH", "Answer": "8565 + 1853 = 10418"}
{"Question": "FREE + REST = METER", "Answer": "6855 + 8503 = 15358"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOAD = TASTE", "Answer": "8554 + 7865 = 16419"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROAD = RAISE", "Answer": "8667 + 1806 = 10473"}
{"Question": "MALL + ALSO = MORAL", "Answer": "1866 + 8620 = 10486"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SHOE = SALES", "Answer": "8665 + 1896 = 10561"}
{"Question": "FREE + READ = INNER", "Answer": "5866 + 8602 = 14468"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SHOE = APPLY", "Answer": "8667 + 5806 = 14473"}
{"Question": "NEED + ONCE = SEVEN", "Answer": "8662 + 7806 = 16468"}
{"Question": "FREE + REAL = ORDER", "Answer": "9866 + 8602 = 18468"}
{"Question": "WALL + ALSO = WHOLE", "Answer": "1877 + 8796 = 10673"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = CLUB", "Answer": "4166 + 1468 = 5634"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8177 + 1875 = 10052"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = PAPER", "Answer": "9233 + 2937 = 12170"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = EXTRA", "Answer": "7544 + 5741 = 13285"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = FLOAT", "Answer": "5844 + 8542 = 14386"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = CLEAN", "Answer": "5844 + 8543 = 14387"}
{"Question": "BALL + ABLE = DOUBT", "Answer": "7833 + 8739 = 16572"}
{"Question": "IRON + RING = EVER", "Answer": "2175 + 1256 = 3431"}
{"Question": "POLE + OPEN = ENJOY", "Answer": "5761 + 7513 = 13274"}
{"Question": "CALL + ACID = DREAM", "Answer": "5866 + 8521 = 14387"}
{"Question": "TIRE + ITEM = FRUIT", "Answer": "7642 + 6725 = 14367"}
{"Question": "PULL + UPON = FOCUS", "Answer": "6722 + 7648 = 14370"}
{"Question": "TIRE + ITEM = REACT", "Answer": "6714 + 7642 = 14356"}
{"Question": "TIRE + ITEM = MEDIA", "Answer": "7624 + 6741 = 14365"}
{"Question": "IRON + RING = ANGRY", "Answer": "6835 + 8654 = 15489"}
{"Question": "SURE + USED = TERMS", "Answer": "8645 + 6853 = 15498"}
{"Question": "CALL + ACID = PIECE", "Answer": "8722 + 7863 = 16585"}
{"Question": "PULL + UPON = SWEEP", "Answer": "7833 + 8724 = 16557"}
{"Question": "IRON + RING = FEWER", "Answer": "8724 + 7843 = 16567"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = LABOR", "Answer": "9139 + 1733 = 10872"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = BELL", "Answer": "6156 + 1455 = 7611"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = FEEL", "Answer": "2312 + 3911 = 6223"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = WHICH", "Answer": "8348 + 3744 = 12092"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = WHEEL", "Answer": "9349 + 3644 = 12993"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = SELF", "Answer": "1681 + 6488 = 8169"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = SHEET", "Answer": "2712 + 7511 = 10223"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = SORRY", "Answer": "5815 + 8411 = 14226"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = RURAL", "Answer": "6826 + 8322 = 15148"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = EARLY", "Answer": "1841 + 8944 = 10785"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = COULD", "Answer": "3843 + 8244 = 12087"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "3853 + 8255 = 12108"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = LEAVE", "Answer": "1822 + 9128 = 10950"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = LEGAL", "Answer": "1744 + 9147 = 10891"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = LIMIT", "Answer": "1255 + 9152 = 10407"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = SCALE", "Answer": "2611 + 8216 = 10827"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = TRAIL", "Answer": "3588 + 9385 = 12973"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = PHOTO", "Answer": "4255 + 9452 = 13707"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = EACH", "Answer": "4677 + 1476 = 6153"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = START", "Answer": "5911 + 4519 = 10430"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = LEARN", "Answer": "5311 + 8513 = 13824"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = CIVIL", "Answer": "5322 + 9523 = 14845"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "5288 + 7582 = 12870"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = HELLO", "Answer": "5399 + 8593 = 13992"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = CLOCK", "Answer": "6755 + 8657 = 15412"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = DATA", "Answer": "6477 + 1674 = 8151"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "7611 + 2716 = 10327"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = CLUB", "Answer": "7522 + 1725 = 9247"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "7433 + 6734 = 14167"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = COACH", "Answer": "7855 + 6758 = 14613"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = APPLE", "Answer": "8244 + 1842 = 10086"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = ADULT", "Answer": "8544 + 1845 = 10389"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ALSO = AHEAD", "Answer": "8755 + 1857 = 10612"}
{"Question": "BELL + ABLE = ONION", "Answer": "8755 + 3857 = 12612"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8122 + 1924 = 10046"}
{"Question": "TALL + ABLE = AGENT", "Answer": "9122 + 1627 = 10749"}
{"Question": "PASS + ALSO = ADOPT", "Answer": "9144 + 1748 = 10892"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = SALE", "Answer": "1255 + 4157 = 5412"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = EAGER", "Answer": "9155 + 1058 = 10213"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9155 + 1658 = 10813"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = THEIR", "Answer": "1466 + 9168 = 10634"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8177 + 1976 = 10153"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = EARTH", "Answer": "9188 + 1087 = 10275"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = SCALE", "Answer": "2611 + 8215 = 10826"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = OFFER", "Answer": "2844 + 7241 = 10085"}
{"Question": "TALL + ABLE = METAL", "Answer": "8266 + 2560 = 10826"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = PEER", "Answer": "2699 + 5297 = 7996"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = VITAL", "Answer": "9355 + 3054 = 12409"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = AGREE", "Answer": "9366 + 3167 = 12533"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = CABLE", "Answer": "7388 + 3085 = 10473"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = CROSS", "Answer": "3088 + 7389 = 10477"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = GUESS", "Answer": "3488 + 7389 = 10877"}
{"Question": "LESS + EASY = TASTE", "Answer": "6455 + 4059 = 10514"}
{"Question": "WALL + ABLE = BELOW", "Answer": "9466 + 4163 = 13629"}
{"Question": "TREE + ITEM = ADMIT", "Answer": "5822 + 4523 = 10345"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = HOTEL", "Answer": "5422 + 8523 = 13945"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = USUAL", "Answer": "7533 + 5634 = 13167"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = VALUE", "Answer": "9533 + 5432 = 14965"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = PEACE", "Answer": "5244 + 7548 = 12792"}
{"Question": "POLL + ONLY = UNION", "Answer": "8577 + 5376 = 13953"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = DRESS", "Answer": "5288 + 7589 = 12877"}
{"Question": "HALL + ABLE = COACH", "Answer": "3655 + 6958 = 10613"}
{"Question": "TREE + ITEM = DRESS", "Answer": "6077 + 4678 = 10755"}
{"Question": "FULL + UGLY = REFER", "Answer": "9677 + 6274 = 15951"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = SMILE", "Answer": "2711 + 7816 = 10527"}
{"Question": "LESS + EASY = STYLE", "Answer": "2711 + 7916 = 10627"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = METAL", "Answer": "9744 + 7845 = 17589"}
{"Question": "TALL + ABLE = EXTRA", "Answer": "8766 + 7061 = 15827"}
{"Question": "MASS + ALSO = LOCAL", "Answer": "6788 + 7183 = 13971"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "9788 + 7086 = 16874"}
{"Question": "TREE + STEP = SWEAR", "Answer": "8533 + 1832 = 10365"}
{"Question": "POLL + ONLY = PIANO", "Answer": "1833 + 8635 = 10468"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = ANGLE", "Answer": "6833 + 8135 = 14968"}
{"Question": "MESS + EAST = MOTOR", "Answer": "1855 + 8352 = 10207"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = COACH", "Answer": "1855 + 8957 = 10812"}
{"Question": "TALL + ABLE = ELECT", "Answer": "6855 + 8251 = 15106"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = COACH", "Answer": "8055 + 9857 = 17912"}
{"Question": "BILL + ABLE = AGAIN", "Answer": "8266 + 1863 = 10129"}
{"Question": "LESS + ALSO = AGREE", "Answer": "8366 + 1867 = 10233"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = CROSS", "Answer": "1866 + 8567 = 10433"}
{"Question": "FULL + UGLY = GUESS", "Answer": "9866 + 8167 = 18033"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = CHEEK", "Answer": "1877 + 8675 = 10552"}
{"Question": "CALL + ABLE = CHAIN", "Answer": "1877 + 8976 = 10853"}
{"Question": "BILL + ABLE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8177 + 4870 = 13047"}
{"Question": "LESS + EAST = TABLE", "Answer": "4877 + 8371 = 13248"}
{"Question": "MASS + ALSO = LABOR", "Answer": "9877 + 8175 = 18052"}
{"Question": "FALL + ABLE = BASIC", "Answer": "9877 + 8176 = 18053"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ONLY = ERROR", "Answer": "2944 + 9348 = 12292"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = BEAT", "Answer": "8144 + 1284 = 9428"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = LIGHT", "Answer": "9144 + 1094 = 10238"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = BELL", "Answer": "5266 + 2356 = 7622"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = SELF", "Answer": "2311 + 3821 = 6132"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = OCCUR", "Answer": "5422 + 4652 = 10074"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = SHELL", "Answer": "6477 + 4267 = 10744"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = ANGER", "Answer": "9477 + 4197 = 13674"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = STEEL", "Answer": "9477 + 4297 = 13774"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = LAYER", "Answer": "9477 + 4397 = 13874"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = IDEAL", "Answer": "4688 + 6148 = 10836"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = VOTER", "Answer": "9688 + 6298 = 15986"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = ELECT", "Answer": "2711 + 7421 = 10132"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = CARRY", "Answer": "3744 + 7034 = 10778"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = METER", "Answer": "9766 + 7096 = 16862"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1822 + 8312 = 10134"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = FUNNY", "Answer": "1822 + 8512 = 10334"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = FRUIT", "Answer": "1833 + 8413 = 10246"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFE = FRESH", "Answer": "1833 + 8513 = 10346"}
{"Question": "TREE + RATE = THEIR", "Answer": "1844 + 8614 = 10458"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFT = LATIN", "Answer": "9133 + 1294 = 10427"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = ADOPT", "Answer": "9133 + 1496 = 10629"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = ACTOR", "Answer": "9133 + 1792 = 10925"}
{"Question": "SELL + EAST = EARTH", "Answer": "9144 + 1093 = 10237"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "9144 + 1395 = 10539"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WELL = WHITE", "Answer": "9192 + 1644 = 10836"}
{"Question": "NINE + IDEA = BEAN", "Answer": "7175 + 1352 = 8527"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROLL = ROUGH", "Answer": "9193 + 1055 = 10248"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = LOAD", "Answer": "5166 + 1052 = 6218"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WELL = LAWN", "Answer": "5152 + 1366 = 6518"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = ADAPT", "Answer": "8166 + 1982 = 10148"}
{"Question": "SELL + EAST = METER", "Answer": "9344 + 3892 = 13236"}
{"Question": "NINE + ITEM = TELL", "Answer": "1318 + 3482 = 4800"}
{"Question": "MASS + ARMY = STAR", "Answer": "4388 + 3749 = 8137"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = ERROR", "Answer": "5422 + 4658 = 10080"}
{"Question": "THEN + HATE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7513 + 5671 = 13184"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WELL = LEAVE", "Answer": "8582 + 5311 = 13893"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = COACH", "Answer": "8533 + 5984 = 14517"}
{"Question": "THEM + HATE = AGENT", "Answer": "9572 + 5197 = 14769"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROLL = SOLAR", "Answer": "8586 + 5399 = 13985"}
{"Question": "EVER + VARY = ARGUE", "Answer": "7673 + 6134 = 13807"}
{"Question": "NONE + OVER = SERVE", "Answer": "8685 + 6350 = 15035"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "5677 + 6852 = 12529"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LIFT = BIBLE", "Answer": "7699 + 6470 = 14169"}
{"Question": "EVER + VARY = DRESS", "Answer": "8785 + 7059 = 15844"}
{"Question": "NONE + OVER = TREAT", "Answer": "6768 + 7083 = 13851"}
{"Question": "NONE + OVER = EVERY", "Answer": "4841 + 8315 = 13156"}
{"Question": "CELL + EACH = LABEL", "Answer": "7811 + 8670 = 16481"}
{"Question": "CELL + EACH = SALES", "Answer": "5822 + 8459 = 14281"}
{"Question": "MALL + ARMY = CLEAR", "Answer": "4833 + 8249 = 13082"}
{"Question": "PIPE + IDEA = RAPID", "Answer": "5853 + 8734 = 14587"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WELL = BLADE", "Answer": "5853 + 8744 = 14597"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ONLY = LEMON", "Answer": "1866 + 8519 = 10385"}
{"Question": "TALL + AUTO = TOTAL", "Answer": "1877 + 8310 = 10187"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TOSS = OFTEN", "Answer": "1776 + 9166 = 10942"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = SALE", "Answer": "2774 + 1244 = 4018"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = WHEEL", "Answer": "3664 + 8344 = 12008"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = SLOW", "Answer": "3775 + 1355 = 5130"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TOSS = SHOT", "Answer": "3557 + 4377 = 7934"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = ASSET", "Answer": "5772 + 6522 = 12294"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TOSS = CATCH", "Answer": "5883 + 4533 = 10416"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = FULLY", "Answer": "6225 + 8655 = 14880"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = STEAL", "Answer": "7881 + 2711 = 10592"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = ALLOW", "Answer": "7334 + 2744 = 10078"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TOSS = PILOT", "Answer": "7334 + 8744 = 16078"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "7338 + 2788 = 10126"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = IDEAL", "Answer": "7448 + 6788 = 14236"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = SOLID", "Answer": "8221 + 9811 = 18032"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8332 + 1822 = 10154"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = ERROR", "Answer": "8662 + 5822 = 14484"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = BLOCK", "Answer": "8993 + 1833 = 10826"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSS = LEAVE", "Answer": "8775 + 1855 = 10630"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOSS = BASIC", "Answer": "8776 + 1866 = 10642"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TOSS = THEME", "Answer": "8557 + 1877 = 10434"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TREE = RATIO", "Answer": "1779 + 9188 = 10967"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TREE = FORTH", "Answer": "2008 + 8277 = 10285"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = ALONE", "Answer": "8416 + 4168 = 12584"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = LARGE", "Answer": "8426 + 4268 = 12694"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = ELITE", "Answer": "8548 + 5433 = 13981"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = DREAM", "Answer": "8516 + 5168 = 13684"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = TASTE", "Answer": "8537 + 5378 = 13915"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = SALAD", "Answer": "8538 + 5399 = 13937"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = ALTER", "Answer": "7617 + 6133 = 13750"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = BREAD", "Answer": "3685 + 6853 = 10538"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = CARRY", "Answer": "7637 + 6355 = 13992"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = FUNNY", "Answer": "8625 + 6258 = 14883"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = PHOTO", "Answer": "9759 + 7533 = 17292"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = TREAT", "Answer": "5786 + 7865 = 13651"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FREE = HAPPY", "Answer": "7228 + 8766 = 15994"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FREE = COLOR", "Answer": "7668 + 8799 = 16467"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TREE = ENTRY", "Answer": "8775 + 5811 = 14586"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = AWARD", "Answer": "1832 + 8321 = 10153"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FREE = FIELD", "Answer": "8441 + 1822 = 10263"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TREE = THIRD", "Answer": "8661 + 1822 = 10483"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = ASIAN", "Answer": "1892 + 8921 = 10813"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = LEVEL", "Answer": "9852 + 8529 = 18381"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = CLOCK", "Answer": "5875 + 8744 = 14619"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = AGAIN", "Answer": "1835 + 8351 = 10186"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "1865 + 8651 = 10516"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALL = TRUTH", "Answer": "1841 + 8477 = 10318"}
{"Question": "NEAR + EARN = KNOCK", "Answer": "7934 + 9347 = 17281"}
{"Question": "ODDS + NOSE = OFTEN", "Answer": "1552 + 9127 = 10679"}
{"Question": "RIDE + IDEA = DEAR", "Answer": "2134 + 1348 = 3482"}
{"Question": "TEAR + EARN = ENTER", "Answer": "9174 + 1740 = 10914"}
{"Question": "TELL + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "1744 + 9173 = 10917"}
{"Question": "TALL + STAR = THERE", "Answer": "1255 + 9128 = 10383"}
{"Question": "SELL + USER = SALAD", "Answer": "1466 + 9142 = 10608"}
{"Question": "TELL + ITEM = TASTE", "Answer": "1377 + 9136 = 10513"}
{"Question": "SELL + USED = SOLVE", "Answer": "1577 + 9158 = 10735"}
{"Question": "ODDS + NOSE = OWNER", "Answer": "1778 + 9186 = 10964"}
{"Question": "SELL + USER = PURE", "Answer": "2855 + 1283 = 4138"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ARMY = START", "Answer": "2556 + 8264 = 10820"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = AIDE", "Answer": "6238 + 2385 = 8623"}
{"Question": "BEAR + EARN = ARAB", "Answer": "4269 + 2695 = 6964"}
{"Question": "HELL + CHEF = FLEE", "Answer": "2699 + 5267 = 7966"}
{"Question": "HELL + THEN = PLANT", "Answer": "3522 + 9357 = 12879"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROPE = HELLO", "Answer": "8364 + 3642 = 12006"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROPE = GREEN", "Answer": "9384 + 3842 = 13226"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROPE = SUPER", "Answer": "7325 + 3258 = 10583"}
{"Question": "TELL + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "3588 + 7351 = 10939"}
{"Question": "CITE + ITEM = ELECT", "Answer": "8471 + 4716 = 13187"}
{"Question": "TELL + STEP = ELITE", "Answer": "4122 + 8419 = 12541"}
{"Question": "SELL + USER = ARGUE", "Answer": "4533 + 8452 = 12985"}
{"Question": "SELL + USER = ARISE", "Answer": "4866 + 7482 = 12348"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ARMY = WOMAN", "Answer": "4226 + 8463 = 12689"}
{"Question": "TELL + ITEM = SPLIT", "Answer": "4266 + 9428 = 13694"}
{"Question": "ROPE + OPEN = HONOR", "Answer": "9486 + 4863 = 14349"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAR = START", "Answer": "6438 + 4382 = 10820"}
{"Question": "ODDS + COST = STAND", "Answer": "5331 + 7512 = 12843"}
{"Question": "LOSS + PLOT = STYLE", "Answer": "5411 + 7542 = 12953"}
{"Question": "MOVE + OVEN = ENEMY", "Answer": "7561 + 5613 = 13174"}
{"Question": "TELL + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "5322 + 7531 = 12853"}
{"Question": "POLL + UPON = COUNT", "Answer": "5422 + 9546 = 14968"}
{"Question": "TELL + ITEM = SEIZE", "Answer": "5233 + 7529 = 12762"}
{"Question": "SPIN + PINE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7563 + 5631 = 13194"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = BLAME", "Answer": "8573 + 5734 = 14307"}
{"Question": "SHOP + HOPE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9583 + 5834 = 15417"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSE = FULLY", "Answer": "5886 + 4563 = 10449"}
{"Question": "FARM + ARMY = PROOF", "Answer": "8546 + 5462 = 14008"}
{"Question": "HILL + THIS = VISIT", "Answer": "5299 + 7528 = 12827"}
{"Question": "ROLL + DROP = COLOR", "Answer": "5399 + 8536 = 13935"}
{"Question": "ODDS + POLL = SENSE", "Answer": "6881 + 7633 = 14514"}
{"Question": "DEAR + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "8624 + 6240 = 14864"}
{"Question": "HIDE + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "1685 + 6853 = 8538"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOSE = USED", "Answer": "6885 + 2653 = 9538"}
{"Question": "HIDE + IDEA = BREAD", "Answer": "7685 + 6853 = 14538"}
{"Question": "HELL + THEM = BLAME", "Answer": "6755 + 8672 = 15427"}
{"Question": "RIDE + IDEA = CARRY", "Answer": "5687 + 6872 = 12559"}
{"Question": "ODDS + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "6228 + 7689 = 13917"}
{"Question": "HELL + THEN = ENTER", "Answer": "6199 + 8614 = 14813"}
{"Question": "SITE + ITEM = TERMS", "Answer": "5712 + 7123 = 12835"}
{"Question": "HILL + THIS = ASSET", "Answer": "7622 + 5763 = 13385"}
{"Question": "HILL + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "7422 + 6745 = 14167"}
{"Question": "GEAR + EARN = ANGLE", "Answer": "8712 + 7125 = 15837"}
{"Question": "WIDE + IDEA = ALLOW", "Answer": "4753 + 7531 = 12284"}
{"Question": "SPIN + PINE = ENTER", "Answer": "5783 + 7831 = 13614"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROSE = FEWER", "Answer": "7223 + 8735 = 15958"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROSE = INNER", "Answer": "7334 + 2748 = 10082"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LATE = SHELF", "Answer": "3724 + 7249 = 10973"}
{"Question": "TALL + STAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7244 + 5729 = 12973"}
{"Question": "HILL + THIN = NIGHT", "Answer": "7344 + 5731 = 13075"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ARMY = SMALL", "Answer": "7884 + 6749 = 14633"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROSE = TIRED", "Answer": "7885 + 6753 = 14638"}
{"Question": "GEAR + EARN = ARGUE", "Answer": "8715 + 7152 = 15867"}
{"Question": "TELL + ITEM = ELITE", "Answer": "7155 + 8716 = 15871"}
{"Question": "SITE + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "9725 + 7254 = 16979"}
{"Question": "LOVE + OVEN = SHELL", "Answer": "5786 + 7869 = 13655"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = ASIDE", "Answer": "5871 + 8716 = 14587"}
{"Question": "HALL + THAN = TIGHT", "Answer": "8522 + 1859 = 10381"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "3842 + 8426 = 12268"}
{"Question": "ROLL + IRON = BLIND", "Answer": "8522 + 3857 = 12379"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ARMY = INNER", "Answer": "8552 + 4826 = 13378"}
{"Question": "RIDE + IDEA = AWARD", "Answer": "5832 + 8321 = 14153"}
{"Question": "TALL + STAR = IRISH", "Answer": "8322 + 5834 = 14156"}
{"Question": "LOOK + FLEE = APPLE", "Answer": "8660 + 5822 = 14482"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = CLAIM", "Answer": "6842 + 8425 = 15267"}
{"Question": "ODDS + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "8332 + 7825 = 16157"}
{"Question": "BEAR + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "7862 + 8620 = 16482"}
{"Question": "BITE + ITEM = LIMIT", "Answer": "9862 + 8624 = 18486"}
{"Question": "TELL + ITEM = ISSUE", "Answer": "8233 + 1829 = 10062"}
{"Question": "ODDS + POSE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8443 + 1837 = 10280"}
{"Question": "BITE + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "1843 + 8439 = 10282"}
{"Question": "CITE + ITEM = TEACH", "Answer": "5813 + 8137 = 13950"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROPE = FEWER", "Answer": "6823 + 8235 = 15058"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "6853 + 8531 = 15384"}
{"Question": "OVER + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "6853 + 8532 = 15385"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = READY", "Answer": "6853 + 8534 = 15387"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "8556 + 9833 = 18389"}
{"Question": "HELL + CHEF = COLOR", "Answer": "8544 + 1859 = 10403"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MASS = USUAL", "Answer": "8339 + 5844 = 14183"}
{"Question": "THAN + HAND = ENTER", "Answer": "5864 + 8649 = 14513"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = TASTE", "Answer": "5874 + 8743 = 14617"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DEAL = ELITE", "Answer": "9814 + 8147 = 17961"}
{"Question": "SIDE + IDEA = SHELL", "Answer": "1865 + 8657 = 10522"}
{"Question": "ODDS + NOSE = NAKED", "Answer": "8775 + 1852 = 10627"}
{"Question": "HIDE + IDEA = SALAD", "Answer": "3875 + 8752 = 12627"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "7865 + 8653 = 16518"}
{"Question": "HELL + CHEF = CATCH", "Answer": "8566 + 1852 = 10418"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TREE = THEIR", "Answer": "8772 + 1866 = 10638"}
{"Question": "ODDS + POLL = SALAD", "Answer": "8771 + 4866 = 13637"}
{"Question": "HELL + CHEF = FALSE", "Answer": "8766 + 5871 = 14637"}
{"Question": "ODDS + POLL = SOLID", "Answer": "8771 + 9866 = 18637"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOST = LEAVE", "Answer": "8667 + 1873 = 10540"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LATE = REFER", "Answer": "5867 + 8674 = 14541"}
{"Question": "OVER + VERY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6827 + 8275 = 15102"}
{"Question": "SKIN + KING = TIGHT", "Answer": "6857 + 8574 = 15431"}
{"Question": "ROPE + OPEN = ERROR", "Answer": "7981 + 9816 = 17797"}
{"Question": "STIR + TIRE = ASSET", "Answer": "4952 + 9527 = 14479"}
{"Question": "FREE + RULE = RURAL", "Answer": "9122 + 1042 = 10164"}
{"Question": "PASS + AIDS = ADMIT", "Answer": "9166 + 1706 = 10872"}
{"Question": "MASS + AIDS = AWARD", "Answer": "8177 + 1947 = 10124"}
{"Question": "MASS + AIDS = ADMIT", "Answer": "9177 + 1807 = 10984"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NOTE = EVENT", "Answer": "6311 + 3821 = 10132"}
{"Question": "MASS + AIDS = SALAD", "Answer": "9311 + 3721 = 13032"}
{"Question": "FREE + RACE = CARRY", "Answer": "7322 + 3012 = 10334"}
{"Question": "FREE + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "5422 + 4602 = 10024"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "5422 + 4802 = 10224"}
{"Question": "FREE + ROLE = ELECT", "Answer": "7511 + 5631 = 13142"}
{"Question": "LOSS + PLUS = ERROR", "Answer": "5922 + 8572 = 14494"}
{"Question": "LESS + PLUS = REPLY", "Answer": "5433 + 9523 = 14956"}
{"Question": "TREE + RISE = VISIT", "Answer": "8544 + 5394 = 13938"}
{"Question": "FREE + RIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "3622 + 6542 = 10164"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "7633 + 6293 = 13926"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NAME = SMELL", "Answer": "7655 + 6845 = 14500"}
{"Question": "TREE + RIDE = DIRTY", "Answer": "3722 + 7012 = 10734"}
{"Question": "LESS + PLUS = NURSE", "Answer": "7844 + 2704 = 10548"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NOSE = SOUND", "Answer": "8755 + 7615 = 16370"}
{"Question": "TREE + ROPE = APART", "Answer": "2766 + 7406 = 10172"}
{"Question": "TREE + RACE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1833 + 8293 = 10126"}
{"Question": "MASS + AIDS = MUSIC", "Answer": "1833 + 8523 = 10356"}
{"Question": "TREE + RICE = THEIR", "Answer": "1844 + 8624 = 10468"}
{"Question": "FREE + RACE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1844 + 8934 = 10778"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "3844 + 8624 = 12468"}
{"Question": "TREE + RACE = METER", "Answer": "5844 + 8704 = 14548"}
{"Question": "KNEE + NOSE = ONION", "Answer": "9844 + 8174 = 18018"}
{"Question": "FREE + RACE = CREAM", "Answer": "9855 + 8715 = 18570"}
{"Question": "FREE + RULE = FLOAT", "Answer": "1866 + 8506 = 10372"}
{"Question": "LESS + PLUS = PHASE", "Answer": "8477 + 1897 = 10374"}
{"Question": "FREE + RATE = FIRST", "Answer": "1877 + 8947 = 10824"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = ERROR", "Answer": "8128 + 1902 = 10030"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOTS = LIMIT", "Answer": "9159 + 1645 = 10804"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = ESSAY", "Answer": "8168 + 1926 = 10094"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = AWARD", "Answer": "8178 + 1957 = 10135"}
{"Question": "MINE + ITEM = TELL", "Answer": "5148 + 1685 = 6833"}
{"Question": "SNOW + NEWS = DOZEN", "Answer": "8204 + 2548 = 10752"}
{"Question": "AREA + RISE = USUAL", "Answer": "7267 + 2906 = 10173"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = PAPER", "Answer": "7207 + 2988 = 10195"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRUG = GRASS", "Answer": "9319 + 3281 = 12600"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROPE = MORAL", "Answer": "7327 + 3052 = 10379"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "8328 + 3902 = 12230"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROSE = STAIR", "Answer": "7367 + 3416 = 10783"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = IDEA", "Answer": "3413 + 4821 = 8234"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = STUFF", "Answer": "9419 + 4281 = 13700"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAG = GRASS", "Answer": "9419 + 4381 = 13800"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = LATER", "Answer": "9439 + 4511 = 13950"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = REFER", "Answer": "9429 + 4612 = 14041"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = ALTER", "Answer": "9419 + 4533 = 13952"}
{"Question": "AREA + RIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8458 + 4125 = 12583"}
{"Question": "NOSE + OPEN = SPEND", "Answer": "9417 + 4379 = 13796"}
{"Question": "AREA + RULE = SOLAR", "Answer": "6486 + 4278 = 10764"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = ELECT", "Answer": "7517 + 5631 = 13148"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = METER", "Answer": "9509 + 5433 = 14942"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = BOARD", "Answer": "8548 + 5304 = 13852"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = USUAL", "Answer": "8548 + 5604 = 14152"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "9569 + 5816 = 15385"}
{"Question": "NOSE + OPEN = PIANO", "Answer": "8507 + 5178 = 13685"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "7587 + 5218 = 12805"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "7537 + 5288 = 12825"}
{"Question": "NOSE + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "8671 + 6518 = 15189"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = PLATE", "Answer": "5635 + 6722 = 12357"}
{"Question": "AREA + RULE = MORAL", "Answer": "3653 + 6985 = 10638"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = SENSE", "Answer": "8638 + 6577 = 15215"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = AGREE", "Answer": "9679 + 6187 = 15866"}
{"Question": "MISS + ITEM = TASTE", "Answer": "4688 + 6124 = 10812"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRUG = GUARD", "Answer": "6716 + 7541 = 14257"}
{"Question": "THIS + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "5732 + 7425 = 13157"}
{"Question": "AREA + RICE = CLEAR", "Answer": "4734 + 7613 = 12347"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "2752 + 7305 = 10057"}
{"Question": "ROLL + OVER = HELLO", "Answer": "2755 + 7802 = 10557"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAG = PRIOR", "Answer": "4784 + 7268 = 12052"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAG = GUARD", "Answer": "7817 + 8091 = 15908"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAG = GRAND", "Answer": "7817 + 8641 = 16458"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOTS = STEEL", "Answer": "7817 + 8961 = 16778"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "4824 + 8362 = 13186"}
{"Question": "NOTE + OPEN = SPEND", "Answer": "5832 + 8425 = 14257"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAG = AWARD", "Answer": "6826 + 8312 = 15138"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = COLOR", "Answer": "6826 + 8532 = 15358"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = SOLAR", "Answer": "5835 + 8423 = 14258"}
{"Question": "NOTE + OPEN = ADAPT", "Answer": "6893 + 8236 = 15129"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = VISIT", "Answer": "6836 + 8523 = 15359"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDS = EXACT", "Answer": "1851 + 8975 = 10826"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = IDEAL", "Answer": "4854 + 8695 = 13549"}
{"Question": "AREA + RICE = APART", "Answer": "1861 + 8326 = 10187"}
{"Question": "TENT + EARN = THEIR", "Answer": "1861 + 8976 = 10837"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROLE = LEARN", "Answer": "7867 + 8916 = 16783"}
{"Question": "THUS + HOST = TRUTH", "Answer": "1847 + 8571 = 10418"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NEXT = OFTEN", "Answer": "1871 + 8927 = 10798"}
{"Question": "RULE + USER = CLASS", "Answer": "6857 + 8376 = 15233"}
{"Question": "ROLL + OVER = TREAT", "Answer": "6955 + 9326 = 16281"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELL = STATE", "Answer": "8928 + 9355 = 18283"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = LIMIT", "Answer": "9134 + 1473 = 10607"}
{"Question": "LESS + BLUE = LABEL", "Answer": "1833 + 9148 = 10981"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = LEGAL", "Answer": "9156 + 1635 = 10791"}
{"Question": "KNEE + SKIN = DESK", "Answer": "1566 + 7105 = 8671"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = HONEY", "Answer": "1766 + 9107 = 10873"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = THIRD", "Answer": "1677 + 9186 = 10863"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HERO = IRISH", "Answer": "6358 + 3805 = 10163"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAR = CRACK", "Answer": "3255 + 9362 = 12617"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = AIDS", "Answer": "3478 + 4867 = 8345"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DATE = STILL", "Answer": "8473 + 4327 = 12800"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = START", "Answer": "4519 + 5901 = 10420"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = LOVER", "Answer": "5311 + 7523 = 12834"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = EIGHT", "Answer": "5411 + 7524 = 12935"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = VISIT", "Answer": "4526 + 5682 = 10208"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = SALAD", "Answer": "7532 + 5293 = 12825"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = GUESS", "Answer": "8537 + 5763 = 14300"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAR = VISIT", "Answer": "5877 + 4528 = 10405"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = SKILL", "Answer": "9573 + 5327 = 14900"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = ONION", "Answer": "9632 + 6283 = 15915"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HERO = FORTH", "Answer": "8642 + 6294 = 14936"}
{"Question": "KNEE + SKIN = DRESS", "Answer": "6855 + 3678 = 10533"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = STEEL", "Answer": "4716 + 7621 = 12337"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = USUAL", "Answer": "5734 + 7423 = 13157"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = RAPID", "Answer": "5743 + 7314 = 13057"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7455 + 6714 = 14169"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = BASIS", "Answer": "4782 + 7258 = 12040"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = VISIT", "Answer": "7899 + 6748 = 14647"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAR = SMART", "Answer": "8622 + 1846 = 10468"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAR = HEART", "Answer": "8622 + 3846 = 12468"}
{"Question": "YELL + TYPE = NEWLY", "Answer": "8622 + 7806 = 16428"}
{"Question": "LESS + CLUE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8533 + 1875 = 10408"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = GREAT", "Answer": "8533 + 6845 = 15378"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = SALAD", "Answer": "8544 + 1865 = 10409"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = ADULT", "Answer": "1849 + 8934 = 10783"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOTS = APPLE", "Answer": "1852 + 8235 = 10087"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAR = SHOOT", "Answer": "8355 + 1873 = 10228"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HERO = SUPER", "Answer": "1854 + 8495 = 10349"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8755 + 1807 = 10562"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HERO = COVER", "Answer": "6854 + 8495 = 15349"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DARE = ADOPT", "Answer": "9851 + 8175 = 18026"}
{"Question": "LESS + BLUE = BUYER", "Answer": "8766 + 1807 = 10573"}
{"Question": "KNEE + SKIN = SHEET", "Answer": "8766 + 1897 = 10663"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = SORRY", "Answer": "8966 + 1809 = 10775"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DATE = ADOPT", "Answer": "9861 + 8176 = 18037"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHOE = CROSS", "Answer": "8677 + 3856 = 12533"}
{"Question": "TREE + STIR = IRAQI", "Answer": "8477 + 5814 = 14291"}
{"Question": "STEP + TAPE = TREAT", "Answer": "9147 + 1274 = 10421"}
{"Question": "STEP + TAPE = PEAK", "Answer": "6157 + 1375 = 7532"}
{"Question": "FREE + ROLL = PILOT", "Answer": "8266 + 2477 = 10743"}
{"Question": "PURE + USER = VIRUS", "Answer": "6485 + 4358 = 10843"}
{"Question": "CORE + OVER = ARAB", "Answer": "2487 + 4378 = 6865"}
{"Question": "OPEN + PINE = INTO", "Answer": "1583 + 5738 = 7321"}
{"Question": "FREE + ROLL = LEAF", "Answer": "1544 + 5877 = 7421"}
{"Question": "STEP + TYPE = REPLY", "Answer": "9548 + 5284 = 14832"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LOSS = YIELD", "Answer": "7566 + 5088 = 12654"}
{"Question": "CORE + OVER = DRAMA", "Answer": "7648 + 6584 = 14232"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LOSS = OCEAN", "Answer": "9688 + 6144 = 15832"}
{"Question": "CORE + OVER = IRISH", "Answer": "8657 + 6475 = 15132"}
{"Question": "USED + SIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "9685 + 6158 = 15843"}
{"Question": "PURE + USER = SLEEP", "Answer": "7698 + 6189 = 13887"}
{"Question": "TREE + ROLL = AGENT", "Answer": "2744 + 7688 = 10432"}
{"Question": "OPEN + PINE = MINOR", "Answer": "3748 + 7084 = 10832"}
{"Question": "STEP + TAPE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6748 + 7284 = 14032"}
{"Question": "PURE + USER = IRISH", "Answer": "6748 + 7384 = 14132"}
{"Question": "BONE + OPEN = BUNCH", "Answer": "1857 + 8675 = 10532"}
{"Question": "BALL + AIDE = ASSET", "Answer": "8122 + 1935 = 10057"}
{"Question": "BALL + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8122 + 1953 = 10075"}
{"Question": "FULL + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8122 + 1957 = 10079"}
{"Question": "OPEN + PANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "9152 + 1827 = 10979"}
{"Question": "HALL + CHIP = HAPPY", "Answer": "1044 + 9182 = 10226"}
{"Question": "CALL + AUTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "9144 + 1728 = 10872"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8155 + 1907 = 10062"}
{"Question": "TELL + STAY = THREE", "Answer": "1255 + 9167 = 10422"}
{"Question": "PART + AUTO = ACTOR", "Answer": "9175 + 1352 = 10527"}
{"Question": "LESS + CLUB = LABEL", "Answer": "1455 + 9186 = 10641"}
{"Question": "PULL + SPOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1655 + 9183 = 10838"}
{"Question": "MALL + AIDE = ARMED", "Answer": "9155 + 1783 = 10938"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ABLE = BLACK", "Answer": "1855 + 9107 = 10962"}
{"Question": "SALT + AUTO = ALLOW", "Answer": "8106 + 1967 = 10073"}
{"Question": "HELL + EAST = EARTH", "Answer": "9166 + 1073 = 10239"}
{"Question": "STEP + TIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9162 + 1486 = 10648"}
{"Question": "PASS + UPON = POUND", "Answer": "1866 + 9107 = 10973"}
{"Question": "BALL + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9177 + 1436 = 10613"}
{"Question": "SIDE + ITEM = TERMS", "Answer": "9352 + 3127 = 12479"}
{"Question": "FUEL + UGLY = GLASS", "Answer": "9372 + 3128 = 12500"}
{"Question": "LESS + BLOW = WHOLE", "Answer": "3544 + 7391 = 10935"}
{"Question": "PLUS + LIST = UNTIL", "Answer": "7314 + 3649 = 10963"}
{"Question": "TIME + IDEA = DREAM", "Answer": "7395 + 3154 = 10549"}
{"Question": "HALL + AUTO = OUGHT", "Answer": "7388 + 3091 = 10479"}
{"Question": "BELL + EASY = MAYBE", "Answer": "9388 + 3205 = 12593"}
{"Question": "FREE + RUSH = SHELL", "Answer": "9388 + 3412 = 12800"}
{"Question": "HILL + THEM = LIMIT", "Answer": "4011 + 6495 = 10506"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ABLE = SOLAR", "Answer": "4211 + 8469 = 12680"}
{"Question": "TREE + RING = EIGHT", "Answer": "8411 + 4297 = 12708"}
{"Question": "HIDE + ITEM = DEATH", "Answer": "8412 + 4326 = 12738"}
{"Question": "HELL + WHAT = ALTER", "Answer": "4322 + 8417 = 12739"}
{"Question": "HELL + CHIP = PLACE", "Answer": "4322 + 8461 = 12783"}
{"Question": "HELL + THIS = SLICE", "Answer": "4322 + 8471 = 12793"}
{"Question": "SHOP + HERO = POWER", "Answer": "8421 + 4532 = 12953"}
{"Question": "MALL + ACID = CLIMB", "Answer": "9433 + 4157 = 13590"}
{"Question": "CELL + ACID = ELITE", "Answer": "4133 + 9468 = 13601"}
{"Question": "HIRE + IDEA = DEATH", "Answer": "9473 + 4136 = 13609"}
{"Question": "HELL + THAN = ALTER", "Answer": "4533 + 9417 = 13950"}
{"Question": "BURN + USER = SENSE", "Answer": "9476 + 4137 = 13613"}
{"Question": "CHEF + HUGE = GUESS", "Answer": "9482 + 4318 = 13800"}
{"Question": "RISE + IDEA = ESSAY", "Answer": "6521 + 5713 = 12234"}
{"Question": "INTO + NEXT = THREE", "Answer": "7519 + 5081 = 12600"}
{"Question": "WRAP + ROPE = POWER", "Answer": "7531 + 5214 = 12745"}
{"Question": "TELL + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "7511 + 5243 = 12754"}
{"Question": "WRAP + ROPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7531 + 5614 = 13145"}
{"Question": "SALT + AUTO = TOTAL", "Answer": "7541 + 5613 = 13154"}
{"Question": "THEN + HANG = NIGHT", "Answer": "8541 + 5217 = 13758"}
{"Question": "SEND + EARN = NURSE", "Answer": "8514 + 5271 = 13785"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ONCE = CLEAR", "Answer": "6522 + 5914 = 12436"}
{"Question": "TREE + ROAD = DEATH", "Answer": "6522 + 5941 = 12463"}
{"Question": "HELL + SHIT = ELITE", "Answer": "5122 + 7569 = 12691"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LAND = SENSE", "Answer": "7522 + 5390 = 12912"}
{"Question": "AUTO + UNIT = ONION", "Answer": "8521 + 5392 = 13913"}
{"Question": "LESS + PLAY = CYCLE", "Answer": "5622 + 8534 = 14156"}
{"Question": "UPON + PANT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8542 + 5621 = 14163"}
{"Question": "TALL + ITEM = ELECT", "Answer": "5633 + 7512 = 13145"}
{"Question": "BURN + USER = DRESS", "Answer": "8537 + 5063 = 13600"}
{"Question": "BELL + EARN = ALONE", "Answer": "8533 + 5192 = 13725"}
{"Question": "WHOM + HERO = FEWER", "Answer": "9537 + 5403 = 14940"}
{"Question": "POLL + ONCE = COLOR", "Answer": "9533 + 5817 = 15350"}
{"Question": "TREE + RICH = CHART", "Answer": "6544 + 5812 = 12356"}
{"Question": "HALL + CHIP = PITCH", "Answer": "5844 + 6521 = 12365"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ITEM = ONION", "Answer": "5144 + 7568 = 12712"}
{"Question": "ROLL + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "5644 + 7513 = 13157"}
{"Question": "BEND + EARN = LABEL", "Answer": "8547 + 5304 = 13851"}
{"Question": "HALL + THEM = MATCH", "Answer": "5344 + 8521 = 13865"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TAPE = PAINT", "Answer": "7569 + 5216 = 12785"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LADY = IDEAL", "Answer": "8566 + 5039 = 13605"}
{"Question": "LESS + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "5166 + 9547 = 14713"}
{"Question": "BALL + AIDE = FIBER", "Answer": "9566 + 5407 = 14973"}
{"Question": "BILL + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "6577 + 5841 = 12418"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TONE = ONION", "Answer": "7584 + 5128 = 12712"}
{"Question": "BELL + EACH = SALES", "Answer": "7588 + 5263 = 12851"}
{"Question": "ROLL + TRIP = PILOT", "Answer": "5288 + 9541 = 14829"}
{"Question": "ROLL + OKAY = AGREE", "Answer": "9588 + 5312 = 14900"}
{"Question": "PASS + UPON = SOUND", "Answer": "6911 + 5623 = 12534"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ITEM = SMILE", "Answer": "6911 + 5632 = 12543"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "5629 + 6412 = 12041"}
{"Question": "STAR + TIRE = LEAST", "Answer": "7652 + 6924 = 14576"}
{"Question": "TREE + RAIL = FLOAT", "Answer": "7644 + 6283 = 13927"}
{"Question": "PLUS + LAST = USUAL", "Answer": "7614 + 6542 = 14156"}
{"Question": "FUEL + URGE = REFER", "Answer": "8647 + 6194 = 14841"}
{"Question": "THEM + HOLE = METAL", "Answer": "8641 + 6254 = 14895"}
{"Question": "SONG + OPEN = PRESS", "Answer": "4659 + 6185 = 10844"}
{"Question": "USER + SAFE = TREAT", "Answer": "8674 + 6027 = 14701"}
{"Question": "CORE + OPEN = PRESS", "Answer": "7638 + 6184 = 13822"}
{"Question": "BOSS + OVER = SERVE", "Answer": "3711 + 7209 = 10920"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ABLE = STAFF", "Answer": "7611 + 4789 = 12400"}
{"Question": "PLOT + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "5731 + 7416 = 13147"}
{"Question": "TREE + RAIN = ENTRY", "Answer": "5711 + 7863 = 13574"}
{"Question": "BOSS + OKAY = SKILL", "Answer": "6711 + 7489 = 14200"}
{"Question": "BONE + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "4712 + 7320 = 12032"}
{"Question": "STAR + TURN = GRANT", "Answer": "4732 + 7625 = 12357"}
{"Question": "TREE + RAIL = ALTER", "Answer": "8722 + 7105 = 15827"}
{"Question": "USED + SHOE = HOUSE", "Answer": "8720 + 7152 = 15872"}
{"Question": "HALL + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "7422 + 8765 = 16187"}
{"Question": "YARD + AIDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "8752 + 7926 = 16678"}
{"Question": "NEWS + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "8713 + 7634 = 16347"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAY = GRASS", "Answer": "7044 + 3789 = 10833"}
{"Question": "NEWS + EAST = ASIAN", "Answer": "8765 + 7153 = 15918"}
{"Question": "MASS + ABLE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8755 + 7316 = 16071"}
{"Question": "USER + SITE = TRUST", "Answer": "9756 + 7215 = 16971"}
{"Question": "TREE + RING = NIGHT", "Answer": "5766 + 7219 = 12985"}
{"Question": "CELL + ACID = SLIDE", "Answer": "7566 + 8729 = 16295"}
{"Question": "TREE + STAY = DRESS", "Answer": "7088 + 3745 = 10833"}
{"Question": "HELL + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "7688 + 4729 = 12417"}
{"Question": "DIRT + INTO = NORTH", "Answer": "5798 + 7182 = 12980"}
{"Question": "LOSS + FLAT = TASTE", "Answer": "7088 + 6731 = 13819"}
{"Question": "HELL + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "7188 + 9726 = 16914"}
{"Question": "ROLL + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "8922 + 7846 = 16768"}
{"Question": "EAST + AIDS = ERROR", "Answer": "1837 + 8253 = 10090"}
{"Question": "HALL + SHUT = SOUTH", "Answer": "8433 + 1825 = 10258"}
{"Question": "POLL + OVEN = PIECE", "Answer": "1833 + 8429 = 10262"}
{"Question": "STAR + TIRE = SHEET", "Answer": "1823 + 8735 = 10558"}
{"Question": "SITE + IDEA = START", "Answer": "1803 + 8937 = 10740"}
{"Question": "FILL + IRON = FENCE", "Answer": "1833 + 8927 = 10760"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LOTS = USUAL", "Answer": "6833 + 8275 = 15108"}
{"Question": "BELL + EARN = RELAX", "Answer": "9833 + 8517 = 18350"}
{"Question": "AIDE + ITEM = ADAPT", "Answer": "1804 + 8349 = 10153"}
{"Question": "STAR + TERM = SALES", "Answer": "1804 + 8547 = 10351"}
{"Question": "FLEE + LADY = FIELD", "Answer": "1844 + 8639 = 10483"}
{"Question": "LONG + OPEN = LEGAL", "Answer": "1847 + 8904 = 10751"}
{"Question": "TALL + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "1844 + 8937 = 10781"}
{"Question": "PILE + IDEA = ADAPT", "Answer": "3894 + 8241 = 12135"}
{"Question": "BILL + ITEM = ELECT", "Answer": "5844 + 8319 = 14163"}
{"Question": "FULL + URGE = REFER", "Answer": "9844 + 8127 = 17971"}
{"Question": "INTO + NEXT = ISSUE", "Answer": "1857 + 8235 = 10092"}
{"Question": "ACID + CODE = ASSET", "Answer": "1835 + 8259 = 10094"}
{"Question": "PULL + UNIT = PIECE", "Answer": "1855 + 8407 = 10262"}
{"Question": "CALL + AIDE = CROSS", "Answer": "1855 + 8467 = 10322"}
{"Question": "BELL + EARN = BROAD", "Answer": "1855 + 8607 = 10462"}
{"Question": "FALL + ACID = FULLY", "Answer": "1855 + 8697 = 10552"}
{"Question": "TIRE + IDEA = TREAT", "Answer": "1805 + 8756 = 10561"}
{"Question": "TREE + RING = THEIR", "Answer": "1855 + 8723 = 10578"}
{"Question": "LIFT + INTO = LATIN", "Answer": "1835 + 8752 = 10587"}
{"Question": "HALL + THUS = TRUTH", "Answer": "8755 + 1863 = 10618"}
{"Question": "BILL + IDEA = BEACH", "Answer": "1855 + 8907 = 10762"}
{"Question": "POLL + OVEN = PHONE", "Answer": "1855 + 8972 = 10827"}
{"Question": "LAST + AUTO = RURAL", "Answer": "4825 + 8359 = 13184"}
{"Question": "MASS + ABLE = USUAL", "Answer": "6855 + 8327 = 15182"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DRAG = RAPID", "Answer": "7825 + 8153 = 15978"}
{"Question": "LAND + AIDS = IDEAL", "Answer": "7835 + 8152 = 15987"}
{"Question": "CAST + AUTO = LOCAL", "Answer": "7825 + 8956 = 16781"}
{"Question": "CODE + OPEN = POUND", "Answer": "9875 + 8152 = 18027"}
{"Question": "PASS + AUTO = PRIOR", "Answer": "1866 + 8374 = 10240"}
{"Question": "BELL + EARN = BRING", "Answer": "1866 + 8407 = 10273"}
{"Question": "CREW + RULE = COLOR", "Answer": "1862 + 8546 = 10408"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ONCE = TREAT", "Answer": "1866 + 8725 = 10591"}
{"Question": "PART + AUTO = PROOF", "Answer": "1806 + 8967 = 10773"}
{"Question": "CELL + ACID = AGREE", "Answer": "8377 + 1856 = 10233"}
{"Question": "HALL + THIN = TIGHT", "Answer": "8577 + 1804 = 10381"}
{"Question": "THIN + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1807 + 8674 = 10481"}
{"Question": "FIRE + ITEM = FRUIT", "Answer": "1807 + 8679 = 10486"}
{"Question": "CALL + AUTO = CROSS", "Answer": "1877 + 8645 = 10522"}
{"Question": "FULL + URGE = FIELD", "Answer": "1877 + 8695 = 10572"}
{"Question": "RISE + IDEA = BASIS", "Answer": "4807 + 8273 = 13080"}
{"Question": "BELL + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "4877 + 8503 = 13380"}
{"Question": "THEN + HOME = MOUNT", "Answer": "6879 + 8517 = 15396"}
{"Question": "BELL + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "6877 + 8541 = 15418"}
{"Question": "LESS + FLAT = ELITE", "Answer": "8177 + 9864 = 18041"}
{"Question": "HILL + ITEM = EIGHT", "Answer": "9877 + 8215 = 18092"}
{"Question": "STOP + TYPE = ASSET", "Answer": "3952 + 9427 = 13379"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = STATE", "Answer": "8215 + 2589 = 10804"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAN = SENSE", "Answer": "9314 + 3498 = 12812"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEAR = EARN", "Answer": "2497 + 4721 = 7218"}
{"Question": "LUNG + UGLY = SENSE", "Answer": "8427 + 4786 = 13213"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEAR = HEART", "Answer": "8503 + 5389 = 13892"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = SORRY", "Answer": "8514 + 5489 = 14003"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEAN = SENSE", "Answer": "8534 + 5480 = 14014"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = ODDS", "Answer": "1628 + 6814 = 8442"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = USUAL", "Answer": "2704 + 7423 = 10127"}
{"Question": "CORN + ONCE = HELLO", "Answer": "4795 + 7542 = 12337"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = SHALL", "Answer": "5718 + 7859 = 13577"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "1834 + 8412 = 10246"}
{"Question": "CORN + ONCE = CHECK", "Answer": "1897 + 8716 = 10613"}
{"Question": "CORN + ONCE = CREAM", "Answer": "1809 + 8917 = 10726"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAN = INNER", "Answer": "5836 + 8654 = 14490"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOAD = MORAL", "Answer": "7806 + 8672 = 16478"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "2958 + 9827 = 12785"}
{"Question": "ARAB + REAL = BLADE", "Answer": "8481 + 4382 = 12863"}
{"Question": "EVER + VIEW = IRAQI", "Answer": "8482 + 4189 = 12671"}
{"Question": "ARAB + READ = BIBLE", "Answer": "5651 + 6453 = 12104"}
{"Question": "EVEN + VIEW = AWARE", "Answer": "5653 + 6452 = 12105"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WRAP = UPPER", "Answer": "4743 + 7542 = 12285"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WHAT = TRUTH", "Answer": "5759 + 7051 = 12810"}
{"Question": "ARAB + REAL = LEVEL", "Answer": "8780 + 7681 = 16461"}
{"Question": "ARAB + REAL = APPLE", "Answer": "1819 + 8213 = 10032"}
{"Question": "AWAY + WEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "5859 + 8654 = 14513"}
{"Question": "EVEN + VIEW = FENCE", "Answer": "3935 + 9638 = 13573"}
{"Question": "EVER + VIEW = NERVE", "Answer": "4946 + 9748 = 14694"}
{"Question": "BABY + ALLY = AGREE", "Answer": "9192 + 1552 = 10744"}
{"Question": "BABY + ALLY = AHEAD", "Answer": "9193 + 1223 = 10416"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = ENTER", "Answer": "9124 + 1294 = 10418"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POST = PIECE", "Answer": "9164 + 1694 = 10858"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = TITLE", "Answer": "7281 + 2871 = 10152"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = THEME", "Answer": "7291 + 2971 = 10262"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = TRUTH", "Answer": "8231 + 2381 = 10612"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "8241 + 2481 = 10722"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = TRIBE", "Answer": "8261 + 2681 = 10942"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = ODDS", "Answer": "2356 + 3526 = 5882"}
{"Question": "BABY + ALLY = CLASS", "Answer": "7379 + 3009 = 10388"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = ONION", "Answer": "9316 + 3196 = 12512"}
{"Question": "BABY + ALLY = RURAL", "Answer": "7478 + 4668 = 12146"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = MOTOR", "Answer": "9438 + 4398 = 13836"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = THREE", "Answer": "9631 + 6391 = 16022"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = TERMS", "Answer": "2761 + 7621 = 10382"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "5718 + 7158 = 12876"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = VISIT", "Answer": "6780 + 7860 = 14640"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = SCENE", "Answer": "1862 + 8612 = 10474"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = SEIZE", "Answer": "1845 + 8415 = 10260"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = SOUTH", "Answer": "1857 + 8517 = 10374"}
{"Question": "SEAT + EAST = INNER", "Answer": "3845 + 8435 = 12280"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "4831 + 8341 = 13172"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOST = TASTE", "Answer": "5861 + 8651 = 14512"}
{"Question": "SALT + ALSO = ACTOR", "Answer": "9135 + 1392 = 10527"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROOF = RIFLE", "Answer": "9192 + 1446 = 10638"}
{"Question": "NONE + ODDS = OWNER", "Answer": "9196 + 1772 = 10968"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = AHEAD", "Answer": "9194 + 1223 = 10417"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = LEAD", "Answer": "4342 + 3889 = 8231"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOST = TRUTH", "Answer": "7342 + 3471 = 10813"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROOT = EXTRA", "Answer": "7378 + 3559 = 10937"}
{"Question": "SALE + ALSO = HOTEL", "Answer": "8364 + 3682 = 12046"}
{"Question": "NONE + ODDS = LEMON", "Answer": "9392 + 3447 = 12839"}
{"Question": "UPON + POUR = ROUGH", "Answer": "7523 + 5271 = 12794"}
{"Question": "REAL + EARN = LARGE", "Answer": "7521 + 5274 = 12795"}
{"Question": "READ + EARN = UNDER", "Answer": "7584 + 5873 = 13457"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = INNER", "Answer": "3638 + 6445 = 10083"}
{"Question": "SALE + ALSO = OCEAN", "Answer": "4628 + 6241 = 10869"}
{"Question": "THAN + HATE = AFTER", "Answer": "7615 + 6179 = 13794"}
{"Question": "SALE + ALSO = ORDER", "Answer": "2769 + 7621 = 10390"}
{"Question": "THAN + HATE = AGENT", "Answer": "3715 + 7138 = 10853"}
{"Question": "NONE + ODDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "4741 + 7552 = 12293"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROCK = APPLE", "Answer": "4752 + 7546 = 12298"}
{"Question": "REAL + EARN = LABEL", "Answer": "5721 + 7250 = 12971"}
{"Question": "CLUB + LUCK = BUILD", "Answer": "5721 + 7253 = 12974"}
{"Question": "REAL + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "5721 + 7254 = 12975"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROOT = STATE", "Answer": "6765 + 7884 = 14649"}
{"Question": "SHOW + HOST = WORRY", "Answer": "8761 + 7682 = 16443"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = SLEEP", "Answer": "8784 + 7665 = 16449"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = EAGER", "Answer": "9791 + 7228 = 17019"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROOT = AFTER", "Answer": "1816 + 8442 = 10258"}
{"Question": "SALE + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "1875 + 8712 = 10587"}
{"Question": "SLOW + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "1873 + 8715 = 10588"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROOT = START", "Answer": "3830 + 8552 = 12382"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROCK = UPPER", "Answer": "3842 + 8436 = 12278"}
{"Question": "NONE + ODDS = ASSET", "Answer": "3837 + 8442 = 12279"}
{"Question": "SLIP + LIST = TITLE", "Answer": "4839 + 8341 = 13180"}
{"Question": "SHOP + HOST = DEPTH", "Answer": "5876 + 8752 = 14628"}
{"Question": "READ + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "7812 + 8175 = 15987"}
{"Question": "REAL + EARN = UNCLE", "Answer": "7852 + 8576 = 16428"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = ERROR", "Answer": "3931 + 9442 = 13373"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALLY = TREAT", "Answer": "3934 + 9557 = 13491"}
{"Question": "SHIT + HOST = HELLO", "Answer": "9172 + 1492 = 10664"}
{"Question": "DATE + AIDE = AGENT", "Answer": "9184 + 1294 = 10478"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8231 + 2581 = 10812"}
{"Question": "LATE + ABLE = STEEL", "Answer": "8209 + 2789 = 10998"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PAST = TOSS", "Answer": "4397 + 3547 = 7944"}
{"Question": "RARE + AIDE = DEAD", "Answer": "5354 + 3084 = 8438"}
{"Question": "CODE + ONCE = SPEND", "Answer": "7368 + 3478 = 10846"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "7378 + 3508 = 10886"}
{"Question": "DARE + AIDE = IDEA", "Answer": "3492 + 4832 = 8324"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RATE = UPPER", "Answer": "5417 + 4657 = 10074"}
{"Question": "CORE + ONCE = ENTER", "Answer": "9421 + 4391 = 13812"}
{"Question": "IRON + RAIN = HONOR", "Answer": "9437 + 4297 = 13734"}
{"Question": "LATE + ABLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "4512 + 5642 = 10154"}
{"Question": "DARE + AIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "7508 + 5278 = 12786"}
{"Question": "LAKE + ABLE = BREAD", "Answer": "8567 + 5187 = 13754"}
{"Question": "IRON + RAIN = ANGRY", "Answer": "9564 + 5194 = 14758"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = BELOW", "Answer": "9594 + 5174 = 14768"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LIFT = TAIL", "Answer": "2678 + 6028 = 8706"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LIFT = TITLE", "Answer": "7691 + 6471 = 14162"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HOST = MOUTH", "Answer": "7608 + 6478 = 14086"}
{"Question": "SHIT + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "8653 + 6483 = 15136"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = STAFF", "Answer": "4702 + 7342 = 12044"}
{"Question": "LATE + ABLE = METAL", "Answer": "4732 + 7642 = 12374"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = APPLE", "Answer": "5718 + 7658 = 13376"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = APPLY", "Answer": "5719 + 7659 = 13378"}
{"Question": "CODE + ONCE = EVENT", "Answer": "8751 + 7381 = 16132"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = HELLO", "Answer": "9796 + 7086 = 16882"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LIFT = FRAME", "Answer": "1852 + 8712 = 10564"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = FIBER", "Answer": "1862 + 8712 = 10574"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = FRAME", "Answer": "1843 + 8613 = 10456"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RATE = THEIR", "Answer": "1824 + 8614 = 10438"}
{"Question": "CODE + ONCE = CHECK", "Answer": "1896 + 8716 = 10612"}
{"Question": "CODE + ONCE = CABIN", "Answer": "1837 + 8417 = 10254"}
{"Question": "CORE + ONCE = CRAFT", "Answer": "1807 + 8517 = 10324"}
{"Question": "CORE + ONCE = CREAM", "Answer": "1807 + 8917 = 10724"}
{"Question": "DATE + AIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "1827 + 8917 = 10744"}
{"Question": "CODE + ONCE = CHEAP", "Answer": "1837 + 8917 = 10754"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = HELLO", "Answer": "2857 + 8027 = 10884"}
{"Question": "DARE + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "3826 + 8536 = 12362"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = INNER", "Answer": "4847 + 8527 = 13374"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = CLEAR", "Answer": "4847 + 8937 = 13784"}
{"Question": "RARE + ABLE = ESSAY", "Answer": "5851 + 8631 = 14482"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RATE = METER", "Answer": "5894 + 8654 = 14548"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = PAPER", "Answer": "6857 + 8267 = 15124"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEFT = ANGLE", "Answer": "6817 + 8467 = 15284"}
{"Question": "COME + ONCE = LEMON", "Answer": "7806 + 8276 = 16082"}
{"Question": "LAWN + ABLE = AGENT", "Answer": "9132 + 1496 = 10628"}
{"Question": "BABY + AIDE = AGENT", "Answer": "9193 + 1264 = 10457"}
{"Question": "STIR + TASK = THERE", "Answer": "9143 + 1695 = 10838"}
{"Question": "LAST + ABLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "7251 + 2876 = 10127"}
{"Question": "USED + SOUL = LESS", "Answer": "7243 + 2179 = 9422"}
{"Question": "USER + SHUT = TRUST", "Answer": "8240 + 2581 = 10821"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALSO = CLEAR", "Answer": "8283 + 2045 = 10328"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TAIL = ADMIT", "Answer": "7395 + 3178 = 10573"}
{"Question": "DARE + AIDS = IDEA", "Answer": "2491 + 4723 = 7214"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALSO = LEVEL", "Answer": "8482 + 4139 = 12621"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LEAN = SENSE", "Answer": "9415 + 4398 = 13813"}
{"Question": "USER + SOUL = ROUTE", "Answer": "7501 + 5279 = 12780"}
{"Question": "COAL + ONCE = ELECT", "Answer": "7503 + 5671 = 13174"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TRIP = PRIME", "Answer": "8509 + 5381 = 13890"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LEFT = AGREE", "Answer": "8513 + 5087 = 13600"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALSO = MORAL", "Answer": "8589 + 5263 = 13852"}
{"Question": "SELF + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "8506 + 5389 = 13895"}
{"Question": "CROP + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "7681 + 6475 = 14156"}
{"Question": "DRAG + RIDE = EAGER", "Answer": "7645 + 6871 = 14516"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LIFE = REFER", "Answer": "7658 + 6073 = 13731"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALSO = SLEEP", "Answer": "7679 + 6315 = 13994"}
{"Question": "DATE + AIDS = TIRED", "Answer": "7619 + 6478 = 14097"}
{"Question": "CREW + RICH = WHERE", "Answer": "4731 + 7642 = 12373"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TRIP = APART", "Answer": "4795 + 7342 = 12137"}
{"Question": "RARE + AIDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "5751 + 7623 = 13374"}
{"Question": "STIR + TASK = ARISE", "Answer": "5792 + 7158 = 12950"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RICH = CHART", "Answer": "5759 + 7813 = 13572"}
{"Question": "MALE + ARMY = LEGAL", "Answer": "5713 + 7958 = 13671"}
{"Question": "RARE + ALSO = FLOOR", "Answer": "5756 + 7239 = 12995"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "5758 + 7639 = 13397"}
{"Question": "ARAB + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "6768 + 7149 = 13917"}
{"Question": "DRAG + RIDE = ANGER", "Answer": "6719 + 7268 = 13987"}
{"Question": "THIN + HATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8735 + 7081 = 15816"}
{"Question": "SLIP + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "1876 + 8412 = 10288"}
{"Question": "SLIP + LOSE = STEEL", "Answer": "1843 + 8715 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ARAB + RICE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1817 + 8695 = 10512"}
{"Question": "BABY + AUTO = LOOSE", "Answer": "3835 + 8462 = 12297"}
{"Question": "DARE + AIDS = MEDIA", "Answer": "4823 + 8645 = 13468"}
{"Question": "BABY + ALSO = ERROR", "Answer": "4846 + 8527 = 13373"}
{"Question": "CROP + RACE = EAGER", "Answer": "5867 + 8451 = 14318"}
{"Question": "CREW + RICH = AWARE", "Answer": "7806 + 8374 = 16180"}
{"Question": "RARE + AUTO = TREAT", "Answer": "7973 + 9418 = 17391"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = RADIO", "Answer": "1669 + 9167 = 10836"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = THEME", "Answer": "2338 + 8237 = 10575"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = INNER", "Answer": "7332 + 2735 = 10067"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = SMALL", "Answer": "7334 + 4732 = 12066"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = BOARD", "Answer": "7335 + 5739 = 13074"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = FIFTH", "Answer": "8331 + 1834 = 10165"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = FEWER", "Answer": "8551 + 1857 = 10408"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FROM = FIBER", "Answer": "8661 + 1867 = 10528"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = HERE", "Answer": "1449 + 7167 = 8616"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = FEAR", "Answer": "2117 + 5235 = 7352"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = THERE", "Answer": "2449 + 8278 = 10727"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ELSE = STEEL", "Answer": "2664 + 8218 = 10882"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THAT = ELITE", "Answer": "3112 + 9379 = 12491"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EARN = THREE", "Answer": "7347 + 3486 = 10833"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EAST = SALES", "Answer": "8428 + 4213 = 12641"}
{"Question": "THAT + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "8428 + 4256 = 12684"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THAT = PLATE", "Answer": "4223 + 9469 = 13692"}
{"Question": "AIDS + IDEA = STATE", "Answer": "8431 + 4398 = 12829"}
{"Question": "THAT + HARD = RADIO", "Answer": "9439 + 4317 = 13756"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = DEAD", "Answer": "4885 + 1431 = 6316"}
{"Question": "ROOT + AREA = MOTOR", "Answer": "5228 + 7597 = 12825"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YARD = DREAM", "Answer": "5228 + 8531 = 13759"}
{"Question": "ROOT + AREA = THEIR", "Answer": "5771 + 4524 = 10295"}
{"Question": "AIDS + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "2586 + 5842 = 8428"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALF = ALTER", "Answer": "7617 + 6132 = 13749"}
{"Question": "RUSH + USER = SHRUG", "Answer": "7613 + 6147 = 13760"}
{"Question": "THEN + HEAT = ENTER", "Answer": "8614 + 6198 = 14812"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YARD = TRIAL", "Answer": "6227 + 7635 = 13862"}
{"Question": "AREA + REST = STATE", "Answer": "8628 + 6214 = 14842"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "7637 + 6319 = 13956"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YARD = RURAL", "Answer": "6553 + 3612 = 10165"}
{"Question": "DROP + ROAD = AWARD", "Answer": "7650 + 6517 = 14167"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "8658 + 6502 = 15160"}
{"Question": "ROOT + AREA = TOTAL", "Answer": "6551 + 8638 = 15189"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASE = WHEEL", "Answer": "6883 + 5675 = 12558"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SORT = ENTER", "Answer": "6887 + 7625 = 14512"}
{"Question": "THAT + HAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "7687 + 6854 = 14541"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SORT = DOOR", "Answer": "6992 + 2675 = 9667"}
{"Question": "AREA + RELY = ELITE", "Answer": "5715 + 7126 = 12841"}
{"Question": "YEAR + EASY = THREE", "Answer": "8729 + 7248 = 15977"}
{"Question": "THAT + HAIR = BIRTH", "Answer": "8728 + 7259 = 15987"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EACH = CABLE", "Answer": "5735 + 7312 = 13047"}
{"Question": "AREA + RELY = LEGAL", "Answer": "5735 + 7316 = 13051"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ELSE = WORKS", "Answer": "7443 + 6796 = 14239"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SOUP = APPLE", "Answer": "7554 + 4732 = 12286"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRIP = ELITE", "Answer": "7558 + 8723 = 16281"}
{"Question": "ROOM + AREA = BLAME", "Answer": "7665 + 4794 = 12459"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EASY = TASTE", "Answer": "8768 + 7649 = 16417"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRUE = OWNER", "Answer": "8112 + 2856 = 10968"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THAT = EARLY", "Answer": "8113 + 4824 = 12937"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "8112 + 9869 = 17981"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRUE = UNDER", "Answer": "8225 + 5813 = 14038"}
{"Question": "DOOR + EDGE = EVERY", "Answer": "8335 + 1821 = 10156"}
{"Question": "AREA + RELY = AWARE", "Answer": "1831 + 8352 = 10183"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = AWARE", "Answer": "8334 + 1851 = 10185"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = APART", "Answer": "8336 + 1851 = 10187"}
{"Question": "AIDS + IDEA = AWARE", "Answer": "1835 + 8361 = 10196"}
{"Question": "AIDS + IDEA = USUAL", "Answer": "5834 + 8325 = 14159"}
{"Question": "THAT + HALF = FIFTH", "Answer": "7837 + 8341 = 16178"}
{"Question": "DROP + ROAD = PAPER", "Answer": "7831 + 8367 = 16198"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THAT = TRACE", "Answer": "8443 + 1821 = 10264"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRIP = THIRD", "Answer": "8551 + 1836 = 10387"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THAT = TRUTH", "Answer": "8557 + 1861 = 10418"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = HEART", "Answer": "8557 + 3823 = 12380"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "3853 + 8529 = 12382"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRUE = COURT", "Answer": "8556 + 6830 = 15386"}
{"Question": "RUSH + USER = THEME", "Answer": "7856 + 8537 = 16393"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "8559 + 9823 = 18382"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "8552 + 9839 = 18391"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRIP = THERE", "Answer": "8661 + 1823 = 10484"}
{"Question": "HEAT + EACH = HOTEL", "Answer": "1864 + 8621 = 10485"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASE = EQUAL", "Answer": "8665 + 1821 = 10486"}
{"Question": "SLOW + LOTS = SHALL", "Answer": "1867 + 8621 = 10488"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YARD = ESSAY", "Answer": "8665 + 5820 = 14485"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SOIL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8665 + 5824 = 14489"}
{"Question": "ROOM + AREA = MOTOR", "Answer": "8661 + 7807 = 16468"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TRIP = COURT", "Answer": "8667 + 7820 = 16487"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7867 + 8651 = 16518"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SOIL = SHIFT", "Answer": "8771 + 1864 = 10635"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AREA = START", "Answer": "8779 + 5805 = 14584"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASE = STEAL", "Answer": "8772 + 5815 = 14587"}
{"Question": "DEAD + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "6876 + 8704 = 15580"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = EAGER", "Answer": "9159 + 1059 = 10218"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = ENTER", "Answer": "9159 + 1759 = 10918"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = DATE", "Answer": "2162 + 1462 = 3624"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = ENTRY", "Answer": "9169 + 1769 = 10938"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = ENEMY", "Answer": "8178 + 1978 = 10156"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = EACH", "Answer": "6216 + 2916 = 9132"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = BELL", "Answer": "1261 + 2861 = 4122"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = EASE", "Answer": "4314 + 3814 = 8128"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "9319 + 3019 = 12338"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = SHELF", "Answer": "9319 + 3619 = 12938"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = SEVEN", "Answer": "9319 + 3719 = 13038"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = ONTO", "Answer": "4354 + 3854 = 8208"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = AREA", "Answer": "4384 + 3684 = 8068"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = PLATE", "Answer": "7387 + 3487 = 10874"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = FEEL", "Answer": "2412 + 4812 = 7224"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = CABLE", "Answer": "8438 + 4638 = 13076"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = PAPER", "Answer": "8438 + 4738 = 13176"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = AWARE", "Answer": "8518 + 5618 = 14136"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = CARRY", "Answer": "8538 + 5238 = 13776"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "9619 + 6319 = 15938"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = EXTRA", "Answer": "7647 + 6147 = 13794"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = ASIDE", "Answer": "8648 + 6148 = 14796"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = SEED", "Answer": "1681 + 6981 = 8662"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = CLASS", "Answer": "4694 + 6294 = 10988"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = CAUSE", "Answer": "8698 + 6598 = 15296"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = SHEET", "Answer": "2712 + 7512 = 10224"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "4724 + 7824 = 12548"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "8738 + 7138 = 15876"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = LATER", "Answer": "6746 + 7946 = 14692"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = ABUSE", "Answer": "4804 + 8104 = 12908"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = LOOSE", "Answer": "4804 + 8504 = 13308"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = SORRY", "Answer": "6816 + 8516 = 15332"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "4824 + 8124 = 12948"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = TRACK", "Answer": "1831 + 8531 = 10362"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = MORAL", "Answer": "4854 + 8354 = 13208"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = TITLE", "Answer": "1871 + 8271 = 10142"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = TROOP", "Answer": "1871 + 8571 = 10442"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = THEIR", "Answer": "1871 + 8971 = 10842"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOSE = HOTEL", "Answer": "4874 + 8374 = 13248"}
{"Question": "TEST + EAST = AGREE", "Answer": "4894 + 8194 = 13088"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = STAGE", "Answer": "2932 + 9432 = 12364"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAT = STATE", "Answer": "7937 + 9437 = 17374"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = ERROR", "Answer": "8138 + 1932 = 10070"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = THERE", "Answer": "9163 + 1069 = 10232"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LIST = LATIN", "Answer": "9169 + 1365 = 10534"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = EXTRA", "Answer": "9169 + 1768 = 10937"}
{"Question": "DRAW + READ = AWARD", "Answer": "7210 + 2917 = 10127"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = DATE", "Answer": "2312 + 3816 = 6128"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = APART", "Answer": "6319 + 3816 = 10135"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "9319 + 3617 = 12936"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = TALL", "Answer": "5368 + 3265 = 8633"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "9389 + 3482 = 12871"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = ISSUE", "Answer": "8438 + 4936 = 13374"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "9479 + 4378 = 13857"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = ANGER", "Answer": "7518 + 5317 = 12835"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LEAF = AGREE", "Answer": "9514 + 5319 = 14833"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = PLATE", "Answer": "4524 + 5723 = 10247"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LEAF = CABLE", "Answer": "7526 + 5327 = 12853"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = TRAIL", "Answer": "4531 + 5834 = 10365"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = APART", "Answer": "8537 + 5638 = 14175"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = MEDIA", "Answer": "8546 + 5348 = 13894"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "9549 + 5146 = 14695"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = ROUTE", "Answer": "6586 + 5781 = 12367"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = METAL", "Answer": "7598 + 5297 = 12895"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = SAUCE", "Answer": "7617 + 6419 = 14036"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = AWARE", "Answer": "7617 + 6518 = 14135"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = SHELL", "Answer": "9619 + 6314 = 15933"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "7627 + 6125 = 13752"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LIST = FIFTH", "Answer": "8648 + 6549 = 15197"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = TASTE", "Answer": "9651 + 6059 = 15710"}
{"Question": "DRAG + ROAD = EAGER", "Answer": "9657 + 6059 = 15716"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LEAF = EAGER", "Answer": "9658 + 6159 = 15817"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = STEEL", "Answer": "2712 + 7513 = 10225"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = SALES", "Answer": "3713 + 7018 = 10731"}
{"Question": "DRAG + ROAD = ANGER", "Answer": "8719 + 7218 = 15937"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = FIRST", "Answer": "4723 + 7624 = 12347"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = USUAL", "Answer": "5735 + 7439 = 13174"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "8738 + 7436 = 16174"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = VITAL", "Answer": "2742 + 7845 = 10587"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "8759 + 7158 = 15917"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = DANCE", "Answer": "9769 + 7061 = 16830"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = CRASH", "Answer": "5785 + 7082 = 12867"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = ARISE", "Answer": "6783 + 7086 = 13869"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = DEPTH", "Answer": "6786 + 7481 = 14267"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = TOTAL", "Answer": "7801 + 8307 = 16108"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = TITLE", "Answer": "1821 + 8327 = 10148"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = SORRY", "Answer": "1824 + 8621 = 10445"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = ENTRY", "Answer": "1821 + 8725 = 10546"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = TRIBE", "Answer": "1821 + 8726 = 10547"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = HOTEL", "Answer": "4824 + 8723 = 13547"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = SHADE", "Answer": "9829 + 8425 = 18254"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = ERROR", "Answer": "1831 + 8239 = 10070"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = TRACE", "Answer": "1831 + 8534 = 10365"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "1831 + 8634 = 10465"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = EQUAL", "Answer": "1831 + 8637 = 10468"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "6836 + 8539 = 15375"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = CHASE", "Answer": "9839 + 8536 = 18375"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = ERROR", "Answer": "1841 + 8249 = 10090"}
{"Question": "EASE + ALSO = EQUAL", "Answer": "1841 + 8746 = 10587"}
{"Question": "STIR + THIS = FIFTY", "Answer": "5842 + 8345 = 14187"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = TRADE", "Answer": "9847 + 8649 = 18496"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = WASTE", "Answer": "7857 + 8650 = 16507"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = REACH", "Answer": "7857 + 8651 = 16508"}
{"Question": "TEST + EASY = THEME", "Answer": "1861 + 8967 = 10828"}
{"Question": "DRAG + READ = LARGE", "Answer": "7862 + 8967 = 16829"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOST = ENJOY", "Answer": "1871 + 8475 = 10346"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = WATER", "Answer": "4874 + 8372 = 13246"}
{"Question": "DRAW + READ = FEWER", "Answer": "5873 + 8475 = 14348"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LIST = SALES", "Answer": "3913 + 9018 = 12931"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAF = AFTER", "Answer": "8912 + 9318 = 18230"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAD = STATE", "Answer": "5925 + 9328 = 15253"}
{"Question": "THAT + HEAR = STARE", "Answer": "8928 + 9325 = 18253"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAST = METER", "Answer": "7937 + 9635 = 17572"}
{"Question": "EASE + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8108 + 1978 = 10086"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9129 + 1789 = 10918"}
{"Question": "THAT + HURT = AREA", "Answer": "3263 + 2913 = 6176"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDE = USUAL", "Answer": "8438 + 4708 = 13146"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DARE = GREAT", "Answer": "9419 + 4539 = 13958"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LIFE = SELF", "Answer": "3593 + 5763 = 9356"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "3643 + 6513 = 10156"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAKE = STEEL", "Answer": "3613 + 6723 = 10336"}
{"Question": "EASE + AIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "7627 + 6137 = 13764"}
{"Question": "TENT + EAST = DANCE", "Answer": "8628 + 6578 = 15206"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "8638 + 6148 = 14786"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DATE = STEEL", "Answer": "7807 + 8967 = 16774"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DARE = RAPID", "Answer": "4894 + 8314 = 13208"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "4814 + 8634 = 13448"}
{"Question": "THAT + HOST = COACH", "Answer": "4824 + 8394 = 13218"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DARE = BREAD", "Answer": "9829 + 8079 = 17908"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LAKE = USUAL", "Answer": "4834 + 8294 = 13128"}
{"Question": "THAT + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "9879 + 8039 = 17918"}
{"Question": "THAT + HURT = STAIR", "Answer": "6946 + 9526 = 16472"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DATA = TEND", "Answer": "6106 + 1575 = 7681"}
{"Question": "TURN + UNIT = IRISH", "Answer": "6308 + 3816 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TRUE + REST = YOURS", "Answer": "7406 + 4637 = 12043"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = EAGER", "Answer": "8428 + 4191 = 12619"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = METER", "Answer": "9509 + 5434 = 14943"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = INNER", "Answer": "7627 + 6858 = 14485"}
{"Question": "TRUE + REST = BASIS", "Answer": "7652 + 6297 = 13949"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = PAPER", "Answer": "6746 + 7393 = 14139"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = LATER", "Answer": "5845 + 8727 = 14572"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERE = STAIR", "Answer": "8938 + 9424 = 18362"}
{"Question": "STAY + THUS = TRUST", "Answer": "9132 + 1459 = 10591"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DISH = SIGHT", "Answer": "9359 + 3217 = 12576"}
{"Question": "STOP + THUS = COUCH", "Answer": "9325 + 3489 = 12814"}
{"Question": "SALE + AIDS = LEGAL", "Answer": "8413 + 4628 = 13041"}
{"Question": "SNAP + NEWS = AWARE", "Answer": "8419 + 4738 = 13157"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ONCE = LEMON", "Answer": "9479 + 4263 = 13742"}
{"Question": "THAT + HERO = METER", "Answer": "8508 + 5324 = 13832"}
{"Question": "THAT + HIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7517 + 5630 = 13147"}
{"Question": "ELSE + LOAD = TASTE", "Answer": "7597 + 5320 = 12917"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELP = SALES", "Answer": "8548 + 5723 = 14271"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NEWS = ASSET", "Answer": "8528 + 5964 = 14492"}
{"Question": "STOP + THIS = PHOTO", "Answer": "8591 + 5368 = 13959"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELP = LEAVE", "Answer": "5705 + 7318 = 13023"}
{"Question": "AREA + ROCK = LOCAL", "Answer": "5745 + 7306 = 13051"}
{"Question": "HIGH + IDEA = LEGAL", "Answer": "6706 + 7345 = 14051"}
{"Question": "BOMB + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "6726 + 7413 = 14139"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NAME = METER", "Answer": "6726 + 7514 = 14240"}
{"Question": "AREA + RICH = CHART", "Answer": "6756 + 7914 = 14670"}
{"Question": "DROP + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "6791 + 7346 = 14137"}
{"Question": "THAT + HELP = PATCH", "Answer": "6746 + 7891 = 14637"}
{"Question": "GANG + ARMY = HONOR", "Answer": "5805 + 8237 = 14042"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DOWN = WOUND", "Answer": "3843 + 8215 = 12058"}
{"Question": "NEWS + EARN = WATER", "Answer": "3814 + 8273 = 12087"}
{"Question": "SAME + AIDS = MEDIA", "Answer": "5813 + 8095 = 13908"}
{"Question": "THAT + HUGE = GUESS", "Answer": "5865 + 8412 = 14277"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DRAW = GUARD", "Answer": "6816 + 8092 = 14908"}
{"Question": "STIR + THUS = IRISH", "Answer": "7816 + 8357 = 16173"}
{"Question": "AREA + RICH = AWARE", "Answer": "1861 + 8325 = 10186"}
{"Question": "THUS + HEAT = TRUTH", "Answer": "1827 + 8391 = 10218"}
{"Question": "TEST + EARN = THREE", "Answer": "1861 + 8427 = 10288"}
{"Question": "SALE + AIDS = IDEAL", "Answer": "5849 + 8135 = 13984"}
{"Question": "TUBE + UNIT = ONION", "Answer": "5879 + 8435 = 14314"}
{"Question": "EDGE + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "7837 + 8641 = 16478"}
{"Question": "ONTO + NAME = LEMON", "Answer": "5865 + 8093 = 13958"}
{"Question": "SEED + USED = STUFF", "Answer": "1772 + 9172 = 10944"}
{"Question": "SEED + USED = STUDY", "Answer": "1774 + 9174 = 10948"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = MAKER", "Answer": "2331 + 8231 = 10562"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = MERE", "Answer": "3665 + 1365 = 5030"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = INNER", "Answer": "6448 + 3648 = 10096"}
{"Question": "SEED + USED = DRAMA", "Answer": "6551 + 7651 = 14202"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = COACH", "Answer": "6557 + 8657 = 15214"}
{"Question": "SEED + USED = CLASS", "Answer": "6883 + 7683 = 14566"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = FENCE", "Answer": "8445 + 1845 = 10290"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = CRAFT", "Answer": "8445 + 9845 = 18290"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = FLAME", "Answer": "8662 + 1862 = 10524"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FROM = FAITH", "Answer": "8667 + 1867 = 10534"}
{"Question": "POOR + SPOT = PARTY", "Answer": "1223 + 9124 = 10347"}
{"Question": "DEER + IDEA = RARE", "Answer": "1449 + 8145 = 9594"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MALE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1556 + 9157 = 10713"}
{"Question": "SEED + USER = START", "Answer": "1667 + 9163 = 10830"}
{"Question": "PEER + OPEN = PHONE", "Answer": "1773 + 9174 = 10947"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ITEM = EMPTY", "Answer": "3118 + 9312 = 12430"}
{"Question": "ROOT + CROP = ENTER", "Answer": "3559 + 7354 = 10913"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CODE = AHEAD", "Answer": "3556 + 7359 = 10915"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MALE = LEVEL", "Answer": "4118 + 9413 = 13531"}
{"Question": "POOR + UPON = ROUND", "Answer": "5331 + 8536 = 13867"}
{"Question": "POOL + UPON = COULD", "Answer": "5337 + 8539 = 13876"}
{"Question": "DEEP + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "5778 + 3579 = 9357"}
{"Question": "TOOL + STOP = PLATE", "Answer": "6334 + 8631 = 14965"}
{"Question": "DEER + IDEA = RAPID", "Answer": "6441 + 8645 = 15086"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THEM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6551 + 3652 = 10203"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ITEM = FENCE", "Answer": "6552 + 8653 = 15205"}
{"Question": "PEER + OPEN = ENTRY", "Answer": "7112 + 6713 = 13825"}
{"Question": "LOOK + SLOW = WORKS", "Answer": "7224 + 5721 = 12945"}
{"Question": "DEER + IDEA = BROAD", "Answer": "7223 + 6724 = 13947"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CODE = ERROR", "Answer": "7339 + 2731 = 10070"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "7445 + 6741 = 14186"}
{"Question": "PEER + OPEN = TROOP", "Answer": "7884 + 6783 = 14667"}
{"Question": "LOOK + PLOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8337 + 4831 = 13168"}
{"Question": "HEEL + CHEF = CYCLE", "Answer": "8337 + 1836 = 10173"}
{"Question": "DEEP + IDEA = ASIAN", "Answer": "8559 + 4851 = 13410"}
{"Question": "ROOT + CROP = CATCH", "Answer": "8554 + 1859 = 10413"}
{"Question": "DEER + IDEA = CRACK", "Answer": "8556 + 7854 = 16410"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CODE = CHEST", "Answer": "8662 + 1865 = 10527"}
{"Question": "PEER + OPEN = CROSS", "Answer": "8664 + 5869 = 14533"}
{"Question": "LOOK + FLOW = AWFUL", "Answer": "8773 + 6875 = 15648"}
{"Question": "POOR + SPOT = SERVE", "Answer": "8776 + 1874 = 10650"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PALE = PRESS", "Answer": "8779 + 1876 = 10655"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PALE = UPPER", "Answer": "9338 + 2937 = 12275"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = TRAIL", "Answer": "9143 + 1453 = 10596"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = TRACE", "Answer": "9163 + 1683 = 10846"}
{"Question": "USED + SEND = STUFF", "Answer": "9176 + 1746 = 10922"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "8231 + 2391 = 10622"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASY = SHOOT", "Answer": "2337 + 8217 = 10554"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EAST = TRIBE", "Answer": "8251 + 2531 = 10782"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = ENTER", "Answer": "8251 + 2561 = 10812"}
{"Question": "BONE + ONCE = CHEEK", "Answer": "8257 + 2517 = 10774"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = EAGER", "Answer": "8261 + 2651 = 10912"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = NURSE", "Answer": "8261 + 2691 = 10952"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASY = SHEET", "Answer": "2667 + 8217 = 10884"}
{"Question": "MEAT + EAST = THEME", "Answer": "7291 + 2981 = 10272"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BLUE = CLEAN", "Answer": "9325 + 3265 = 12590"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MANY = FINAL", "Answer": "3447 + 9387 = 12834"}
{"Question": "TONE + ONCE = METER", "Answer": "9352 + 3572 = 12924"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MANY = HUMAN", "Answer": "3554 + 9384 = 12938"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = FLOOR", "Answer": "9427 + 4237 = 13664"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LAST = STILL", "Answer": "8432 + 4312 = 12744"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = METER", "Answer": "8432 + 4392 = 12824"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "9437 + 4317 = 13754"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LAST = USUAL", "Answer": "5472 + 4702 = 10174"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "7512 + 5142 = 12654"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POET = HELLO", "Answer": "9526 + 5246 = 14772"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EAST = STILL", "Answer": "7532 + 5312 = 12844"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = VISIT", "Answer": "5339 + 7589 = 12928"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASY = CYCLE", "Answer": "5664 + 8504 = 14168"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = USUAL", "Answer": "5664 + 8534 = 14198"}
{"Question": "HEAT + EAST = FIFTH", "Answer": "8569 + 5629 = 14198"}
{"Question": "TONE + ONCE = ASSET", "Answer": "6578 + 5708 = 12286"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HURT = THREE", "Answer": "9581 + 5841 = 15422"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TERM = DRAMA", "Answer": "8672 + 6752 = 15424"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = ALTER", "Answer": "3678 + 6708 = 10386"}
{"Question": "PLAN + LAWN = SENSE", "Answer": "3685 + 6825 = 10510"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = SALAD", "Answer": "7221 + 9741 = 16962"}
{"Question": "PURE + URGE = ORDER", "Answer": "5726 + 7236 = 12962"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = NAKED", "Answer": "5731 + 7341 = 13072"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = EVENT", "Answer": "2741 + 7451 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BLUE = USUAL", "Answer": "5742 + 7412 = 13154"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EASY = USUAL", "Answer": "7442 + 5732 = 13174"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOPE = UPPER", "Answer": "4758 + 7528 = 12286"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EAST = INNER", "Answer": "5769 + 7609 = 13378"}
{"Question": "SURE + URGE = GRASS", "Answer": "8769 + 7619 = 16388"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = SHALL", "Answer": "7881 + 2741 = 10622"}
{"Question": "LEAN + EARN = NOVEL", "Answer": "2781 + 7891 = 10672"}
{"Question": "MEAT + EAST = STORM", "Answer": "4782 + 7812 = 12594"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = ISSUE", "Answer": "1826 + 8246 = 10072"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LAND = RANGE", "Answer": "3827 + 8207 = 12034"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1832 + 8342 = 10174"}
{"Question": "MEAT + EAST = MOTOR", "Answer": "1832 + 8372 = 10204"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TERM = IRISH", "Answer": "1836 + 8306 = 10142"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HURT = RURAL", "Answer": "4836 + 8316 = 13152"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POET = THESE", "Answer": "6841 + 8421 = 15262"}
{"Question": "VARY + ARMY = MAYOR", "Answer": "9842 + 8412 = 18254"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POET = SHELL", "Answer": "1843 + 8423 = 10266"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POET = SCENE", "Answer": "1846 + 8426 = 10272"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LAND = GUESS", "Answer": "1846 + 8476 = 10322"}
{"Question": "USED + SEND = UNCLE", "Answer": "1847 + 8407 = 10254"}
{"Question": "PLAY + LADY = BADLY", "Answer": "6850 + 8530 = 15380"}
{"Question": "PLAN + LAWN = NEWLY", "Answer": "7851 + 8531 = 16382"}
{"Question": "ALLY + VARY = VOTER", "Answer": "8552 + 1842 = 10394"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = DEATH", "Answer": "6852 + 8532 = 15384"}
{"Question": "USED + SEND = UNDER", "Answer": "1853 + 8503 = 10356"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = ESSAY", "Answer": "8553 + 4823 = 13376"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOLE = CHEST", "Answer": "9853 + 8543 = 18396"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = SENSE", "Answer": "9854 + 8564 = 18418"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = BRING", "Answer": "1856 + 8506 = 10362"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = BUYER", "Answer": "1856 + 8526 = 10382"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOLE = SALAD", "Answer": "1856 + 8546 = 10402"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "4856 + 8526 = 13382"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = BRICK", "Answer": "1857 + 8507 = 10364"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = LABOR", "Answer": "8557 + 1827 = 10384"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = FAITH", "Answer": "3857 + 8527 = 12384"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "6859 + 8539 = 15398"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MANY = ESSAY", "Answer": "8660 + 5820 = 14480"}
{"Question": "PLAY + LADY = EARLY", "Answer": "7860 + 8620 = 16480"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOTS = LIMIT", "Answer": "8662 + 1842 = 10504"}
{"Question": "PURE + URGE = POWER", "Answer": "1863 + 8673 = 10536"}
{"Question": "SPOT + POET = SEIZE", "Answer": "1865 + 8605 = 10470"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = TOWER", "Answer": "1869 + 8629 = 10498"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RULE = INNER", "Answer": "5869 + 8629 = 14498"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BLUE = AFTER", "Answer": "1872 + 8752 = 10624"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAM = SMART", "Answer": "5874 + 8764 = 14638"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "6875 + 8705 = 15580"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EARN = BRIEF", "Answer": "1876 + 8706 = 10582"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOPE = SMELL", "Answer": "1876 + 8746 = 10622"}
{"Question": "TONE + ONCE = TREND", "Answer": "1876 + 8796 = 10672"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HOLE = ESSAY", "Answer": "4951 + 9531 = 14482"}
{"Question": "CREW + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "7318 + 3195 = 10513"}
{"Question": "SLIP + LINE = PANEL", "Answer": "7341 + 3482 = 10823"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RATE = METER", "Answer": "3447 + 9382 = 12829"}
{"Question": "KING + INTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "8372 + 3765 = 12137"}
{"Question": "CHEF + HEAR = REACH", "Answer": "8423 + 4261 = 12684"}
{"Question": "DEAL + EAST = SALES", "Answer": "8426 + 4215 = 12641"}
{"Question": "HEEL + WHAT = DEATH", "Answer": "4225 + 8469 = 12694"}
{"Question": "PEER + SPOT = TERMS", "Answer": "4338 + 9471 = 13809"}
{"Question": "TRIP + RISE = SPORT", "Answer": "8432 + 4316 = 12748"}
{"Question": "THIN + HIRE = METER", "Answer": "8437 + 4392 = 12829"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOAT = STAGE", "Answer": "5221 + 8573 = 13794"}
{"Question": "CROP + ROAD = PEACE", "Answer": "9521 + 5273 = 14794"}
{"Question": "THEN + HERO = NORTH", "Answer": "9521 + 5274 = 14795"}
{"Question": "SHIT + HIRE = METER", "Answer": "8527 + 5203 = 13730"}
{"Question": "CARE + ARMY = METER", "Answer": "9524 + 5218 = 14742"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ARMY = METER", "Answer": "5227 + 9518 = 14745"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LAKE = EAGER", "Answer": "8539 + 5371 = 13910"}
{"Question": "DROP + ROLE = MODEL", "Answer": "8536 + 5304 = 13840"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THIS = SENSE", "Answer": "5443 + 8571 = 14014"}
{"Question": "FAIR + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "7542 + 5409 = 12951"}
{"Question": "ROOF + WRAP = PAPER", "Answer": "5664 + 7531 = 13195"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EAST = TITLE", "Answer": "5667 + 8501 = 14168"}
{"Question": "ITEM + TEAR = ADMIT", "Answer": "8572 + 5713 = 14285"}
{"Question": "TRIP + RIDE = DEPTH", "Answer": "8572 + 5714 = 14286"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LOVE = SEVEN", "Answer": "5881 + 6542 = 12423"}
{"Question": "RAIL + AIDE = CLEAR", "Answer": "6582 + 5874 = 12456"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "5883 + 9574 = 15457"}
{"Question": "TOOL + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "6223 + 7641 = 13864"}
{"Question": "WRAP + RACE = POWER", "Answer": "8621 + 6235 = 14856"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DATE = STEAL", "Answer": "6224 + 7638 = 13862"}
{"Question": "HEAD + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "7628 + 6235 = 13863"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TAKE = METAL", "Answer": "6338 + 9625 = 15963"}
{"Question": "TEEN + STOP = APART", "Answer": "6552 + 7634 = 14186"}
{"Question": "ROOT + URGE = VOTER", "Answer": "6552 + 8694 = 15246"}
{"Question": "ROOF + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "6553 + 7614 = 14167"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HOUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "8671 + 6745 = 15416"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "6778 + 9641 = 16419"}
{"Question": "THIS + HIRE = FRESH", "Answer": "8672 + 6754 = 15426"}
{"Question": "THIN + HIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "5682 + 6831 = 12513"}
{"Question": "ODDS + VOTE = SEVEN", "Answer": "6881 + 5642 = 12523"}
{"Question": "ODDS + HOUR = BRUSH", "Answer": "6883 + 7654 = 14537"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TAPE = PANEL", "Answer": "7338 + 9715 = 17053"}
{"Question": "ALLY + HAIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7442 + 8716 = 16158"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOAT = TASTE", "Answer": "7553 + 8761 = 16314"}
{"Question": "WAIT + AIDS = TASTE", "Answer": "9751 + 7563 = 17314"}
{"Question": "ODDS + COME = LEMON", "Answer": "7553 + 8726 = 16279"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RACE = INNER", "Answer": "7558 + 4706 = 12264"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BONE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7663 + 5721 = 13384"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOAT = STAFF", "Answer": "7881 + 5763 = 13644"}
{"Question": "BEAN + EAST = STONE", "Answer": "6823 + 8215 = 15038"}
{"Question": "GRAB + RAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "6831 + 8359 = 15190"}
{"Question": "ODDS + VOTE = VISIT", "Answer": "8332 + 1875 = 10207"}
{"Question": "LOOK + PLUS = USUAL", "Answer": "8332 + 7816 = 16148"}
{"Question": "LEAD + EASY = CYCLE", "Answer": "7832 + 8346 = 16178"}
{"Question": "HEEL + THIN = TITLE", "Answer": "8334 + 1809 = 10143"}
{"Question": "TOOL + STAR = LEAST", "Answer": "8441 + 6827 = 15268"}
{"Question": "TOOL + STAR = SALES", "Answer": "8442 + 1809 = 10251"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "8449 + 1832 = 10281"}
{"Question": "HEAD + EAST = CATCH", "Answer": "5842 + 8473 = 14315"}
{"Question": "RACE + ACID = RIVER", "Answer": "1845 + 8406 = 10251"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CORE = ERROR", "Answer": "8552 + 4831 = 13383"}
{"Question": "OVEN + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "6851 + 8534 = 15385"}
{"Question": "ROOT + CREW = THERE", "Answer": "8551 + 7832 = 16383"}
{"Question": "PEER + SPIN = SHARP", "Answer": "8552 + 1876 = 10428"}
{"Question": "UPON + PORT = ENTER", "Answer": "3852 + 8564 = 12416"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "8559 + 1823 = 10382"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BOWL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8559 + 4823 = 13382"}
{"Question": "BEAT + EARN = RATIO", "Answer": "6853 + 8519 = 15372"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DARE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8559 + 6823 = 15382"}
{"Question": "REAL + EACH = COLOR", "Answer": "7853 + 8514 = 16367"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RUSH = THERE", "Answer": "1864 + 8620 = 10484"}
{"Question": "ODDS + FOUR = ERROR", "Answer": "8660 + 5824 = 14484"}
{"Question": "DEAL + EACH = LABEL", "Answer": "7861 + 8620 = 16481"}
{"Question": "ACID + CITE = PIECE", "Answer": "7860 + 8624 = 16484"}
{"Question": "ODDS + NOTE = SPEND", "Answer": "8661 + 3875 = 12536"}
{"Question": "READ + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "4867 + 8621 = 13488"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BONE = ERROR", "Answer": "8663 + 5821 = 14484"}
{"Question": "NEED + INTO = LOOSE", "Answer": "8662 + 5834 = 14496"}
{"Question": "LEAF + EARN = REFER", "Answer": "9864 + 8617 = 18481"}
{"Question": "ALLY + WARN = WRONG", "Answer": "8665 + 1807 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ALLY + SAND = STYLE", "Answer": "8665 + 1897 = 10562"}
{"Question": "ODDS + PORT = STRIP", "Answer": "8771 + 5864 = 14635"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BASE = STEAL", "Answer": "8772 + 4815 = 13587"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SHUT = SOUTH", "Answer": "8775 + 1863 = 10638"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EAST = STEAL", "Answer": "8773 + 5814 = 14587"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CARE = CREAM", "Answer": "8779 + 1805 = 10584"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = BIRTH", "Answer": "9135 + 1537 = 10672"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NECK = NAKED", "Answer": "9137 + 1738 = 10875"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = LEAVE", "Answer": "9138 + 1832 = 10970"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = LEGAL", "Answer": "9146 + 1645 = 10791"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = TALL", "Answer": "6154 + 1457 = 7611"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = TASTE", "Answer": "9157 + 1756 = 10913"}
{"Question": "DIET + ITEM = MESS", "Answer": "8164 + 1469 = 9633"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = THERE", "Answer": "9174 + 1472 = 10646"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = THIRD", "Answer": "9175 + 1578 = 10753"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOTE = TEEN", "Answer": "1235 + 2537 = 3772"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = WHEEL", "Answer": "8235 + 2537 = 10772"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = SHELF", "Answer": "7316 + 3619 = 10935"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NECK = HELLO", "Answer": "9382 + 3287 = 12669"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = TOTAL", "Answer": "6387 + 3781 = 10168"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = PRINT", "Answer": "9483 + 4381 = 13864"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = ORDER", "Answer": "5487 + 4783 = 10270"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = METAL", "Answer": "8492 + 4297 = 12789"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = USUAL", "Answer": "7536 + 5639 = 13175"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = TEACH", "Answer": "7542 + 5241 = 12783"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOTE = LEVEL", "Answer": "7568 + 5863 = 13431"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "8571 + 5174 = 13745"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = SELL", "Answer": "1576 + 5679 = 7255"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = PRICE", "Answer": "7582 + 5281 = 12863"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOTE = TRAIN", "Answer": "3619 + 6917 = 10536"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "8645 + 6541 = 15186"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = LIMIT", "Answer": "3702 + 7205 = 10907"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "8712 + 7219 = 15931"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = STAFF", "Answer": "6719 + 7914 = 14633"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = ESSAY", "Answer": "4725 + 7521 = 12246"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = ENTER", "Answer": "6751 + 7159 = 13910"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "2754 + 7450 = 10204"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = FLESH", "Answer": "9804 + 8402 = 18206"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = FRUIT", "Answer": "7806 + 8602 = 16408"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BELT = LEGAL", "Answer": "3812 + 8219 = 12031"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "4823 + 8325 = 13148"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = SEIZE", "Answer": "1824 + 8426 = 10250"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOST = HOTEL", "Answer": "6825 + 8523 = 15348"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NECK = OFTEN", "Answer": "1836 + 8632 = 10468"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOSE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1857 + 8756 = 10613"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NECK = ORDER", "Answer": "1863 + 8367 = 10230"}
{"Question": "DIET + ITEM = DRIVE", "Answer": "1869 + 8967 = 10836"}
{"Question": "STIR + TRIP = PRESS", "Answer": "4873 + 8371 = 13244"}
{"Question": "DATA + IDEA = DRIVE", "Answer": "1787 + 9147 = 10934"}
{"Question": "DATA + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "2171 + 8241 = 10412"}
{"Question": "DATA + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "4878 + 3468 = 8346"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHOE = CROSS", "Answer": "5828 + 6538 = 12366"}
{"Question": "DATA + IDEA = HABIT", "Answer": "7626 + 8756 = 16382"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHOE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8626 + 1806 = 10432"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHOE = SOLID", "Answer": "8727 + 1807 = 10534"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHOE = STAIR", "Answer": "8363 + 1893 = 10256"}
{"Question": "CLUE + LEAD = LUNCH", "Answer": "9105 + 1587 = 10692"}
{"Question": "CLUE + LEAN = LUNCH", "Answer": "9106 + 1687 = 10793"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LEAD = LABEL", "Answer": "9178 + 1803 = 10981"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOCK = LUCKY", "Answer": "9165 + 1573 = 10738"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOVE = SHELL", "Answer": "6415 + 4529 = 10944"}
{"Question": "LOCK + OKAY = CYCLE", "Answer": "8417 + 4763 = 13180"}
{"Question": "STAR + TRIP = RAISE", "Answer": "8421 + 4159 = 12580"}
{"Question": "HERE + CHIP = PITCH", "Answer": "4363 + 8421 = 12784"}
{"Question": "TYPE + YEAR = HEART", "Answer": "8492 + 4276 = 12768"}
{"Question": "WORK + OKAY = CRACK", "Answer": "7523 + 5390 = 12913"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHOW = WORKS", "Answer": "5727 + 8541 = 14268"}
{"Question": "HERE + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "5131 + 7582 = 12713"}
{"Question": "TRUE + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "8563 + 5391 = 13954"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEND = DELAY", "Answer": "7582 + 5291 = 12873"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HEAR = CRASH", "Answer": "7583 + 5392 = 12975"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOVE = SEVEN", "Answer": "8617 + 6735 = 15352"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHIT = BIRTH", "Answer": "6737 + 8659 = 15396"}
{"Question": "TYPE + YEAR = HAPPY", "Answer": "3792 + 7205 = 10997"}
{"Question": "TRUE + READ = HEART", "Answer": "8746 + 7632 = 16378"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LOUD = ASIDE", "Answer": "1805 + 8567 = 10372"}
{"Question": "HERE + THUS = TRUST", "Answer": "8606 + 1845 = 10451"}
{"Question": "GENE + UGLY = UNTIL", "Answer": "8707 + 1836 = 10543"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HEAR = SORRY", "Answer": "1807 + 8745 = 10552"}
{"Question": "BIRD + IDEA = BREAK", "Answer": "1807 + 8756 = 10563"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BEST = ALTER", "Answer": "1807 + 8765 = 10572"}
{"Question": "STAR + TRUE = GUESS", "Answer": "6809 + 8957 = 15766"}
{"Question": "STAR + TRIP = APART", "Answer": "6813 + 8325 = 15138"}
{"Question": "HERE + SHIP = IRISH", "Answer": "8363 + 7815 = 16178"}
{"Question": "TYPE + YEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "7815 + 8563 = 16378"}
{"Question": "FAIL + ALSO = ONION", "Answer": "5823 + 8391 = 14214"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HEAR = START", "Answer": "1834 + 8426 = 10260"}
{"Question": "HERE + CHIP = COLOR", "Answer": "8575 + 1832 = 10407"}
{"Question": "TRUE + REAL = LATER", "Answer": "5837 + 8741 = 14578"}
{"Question": "HERE + WHAT = DEATH", "Answer": "8595 + 6843 = 15438"}
{"Question": "INTO + NOSE = VISIT", "Answer": "6924 + 9438 = 16362"}
{"Question": "TYPE + YEAR = START", "Answer": "4926 + 9658 = 14584"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DIET = FIFTH", "Answer": "2938 + 9237 = 12175"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DIET = TITLE", "Answer": "2943 + 9241 = 12184"}
{"Question": "LAST + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "3841 + 8342 = 12183"}
{"Question": "DIET + IDEA = BLADE", "Answer": "5829 + 8523 = 14352"}
{"Question": "LAST + ALSO = HOTEL", "Answer": "5742 + 7543 = 13285"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DIET = AVOID", "Answer": "6831 + 8637 = 15468"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DIET = STAIR", "Answer": "6834 + 8635 = 15469"}
{"Question": "OPEN + POET = MONTH", "Answer": "6935 + 9637 = 16572"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LAST = UNTIL", "Answer": "7823 + 8725 = 16548"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DIET = SALAD", "Answer": "7836 + 8732 = 16568"}
{"Question": "LAST + ALSO = METAL", "Answer": "7845 + 8742 = 16587"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BAKE = DEAL", "Answer": "1426 + 4186 = 5612"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BASE = USUAL", "Answer": "3805 + 8325 = 12130"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BASE = STEAL", "Answer": "5742 + 7512 = 13254"}
{"Question": "BAKE + ABLE = IDEAL", "Answer": "5823 + 8563 = 14386"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NOSE = FOCUS", "Answer": "5946 + 9526 = 15472"}
{"Question": "CARD + ACID = DREAM", "Answer": "6851 + 8631 = 15482"}
{"Question": "BAKE + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "6835 + 8645 = 15480"}
{"Question": "CARD + ACID = WHICH", "Answer": "7823 + 8753 = 16576"}
{"Question": "DISH + IDEA = HEAD", "Answer": "1657 + 6184 = 7841"}
{"Question": "LATE + ALSO = ELECT", "Answer": "2951 + 9234 = 12185"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "4732 + 7415 = 12147"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LAKE = SHELL", "Answer": "4816 + 8472 = 13288"}
{"Question": "RATE + ARMY = TREAT", "Answer": "4913 + 9478 = 14391"}
{"Question": "USED + SUCH = DRESS", "Answer": "4821 + 8467 = 13288"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DISH = SHADE", "Answer": "5873 + 8514 = 14387"}
{"Question": "BACK + ABLE = LEGAL", "Answer": "5867 + 8514 = 14381"}
{"Question": "NICE + INTO = TOPIC", "Answer": "6872 + 8615 = 15487"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "6823 + 8645 = 15468"}
{"Question": "SUIT + USER = ARISE", "Answer": "6738 + 7624 = 14362"}
{"Question": "SUIT + USER = VIRUS", "Answer": "6852 + 8634 = 15486"}
{"Question": "ACID + CAMP = PIECE", "Answer": "7864 + 8721 = 16585"}
{"Question": "SUCH + USER = TERMS", "Answer": "7832 + 8765 = 16597"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = BEAT", "Answer": "6108 + 1708 = 7816"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8124 + 1924 = 10048"}
{"Question": "BEST + EAST = ERROR", "Answer": "8135 + 1935 = 10070"}
{"Question": "FADE + AIDE = ASSET", "Answer": "8137 + 1937 = 10074"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = STAR", "Answer": "4152 + 1052 = 5204"}
{"Question": "MALE + ABLE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9156 + 1456 = 10612"}
{"Question": "FADE + AIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "8163 + 1963 = 10126"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8164 + 1964 = 10128"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAT = HELLO", "Answer": "9164 + 1064 = 10228"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = MESS", "Answer": "4172 + 1072 = 5244"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = LOSS", "Answer": "4172 + 1572 = 5744"}
{"Question": "BEST + EAST = EXTRA", "Answer": "9178 + 1678 = 10856"}
{"Question": "SPIN + PAIN = PANEL", "Answer": "9182 + 1082 = 10264"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = MISS", "Answer": "2183 + 1083 = 3266"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = TOOL", "Answer": "1204 + 2804 = 4008"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "7214 + 2814 = 10028"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NICE = MINOR", "Answer": "8243 + 2043 = 10286"}
{"Question": "BEST + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "8261 + 2461 = 10722"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "8261 + 2561 = 10822"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "8264 + 2164 = 10428"}
{"Question": "PLAN + LOAN = NOVEL", "Answer": "8271 + 2071 = 10342"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = EXTRA", "Answer": "8271 + 2571 = 10842"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = BASE", "Answer": "6280 + 2980 = 9260"}
{"Question": "BEST + EAST = THEME", "Answer": "7281 + 2981 = 10262"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = CROSS", "Answer": "8294 + 2694 = 10988"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = LOTS", "Answer": "4312 + 3812 = 8124"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = RATE", "Answer": "5319 + 3819 = 9138"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = EAST", "Answer": "1407 + 4607 = 6014"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "9437 + 4137 = 13574"}
{"Question": "FADE + AIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8452 + 4052 = 12504"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = AREA", "Answer": "2468 + 4368 = 6836"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = AGREE", "Answer": "6472 + 4172 = 10644"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = AREA", "Answer": "1473 + 4673 = 6146"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NICE = LEMON", "Answer": "8492 + 4092 = 12584"}
{"Question": "SPIN + PAIN = BASIS", "Answer": "8504 + 5304 = 13808"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAT = FEWER", "Answer": "9523 + 5423 = 14946"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = SHINE", "Answer": "8547 + 5347 = 13894"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = FLESH", "Answer": "9548 + 5348 = 14896"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = PARTY", "Answer": "7549 + 5249 = 12798"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = SHELL", "Answer": "7583 + 5283 = 12866"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = FREE", "Answer": "1594 + 5894 = 7488"}
{"Question": "PLAN + LEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "9612 + 6412 = 16024"}
{"Question": "PLAN + LEAN = HAPPY", "Answer": "5627 + 6927 = 12554"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = MEDIA", "Answer": "8641 + 6341 = 14982"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = ORDER", "Answer": "3645 + 6945 = 10590"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = RARE", "Answer": "2649 + 6849 = 9498"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAT = STATE", "Answer": "9675 + 6075 = 15750"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "8706 + 7306 = 16012"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = ARGUE", "Answer": "5714 + 7814 = 13528"}
{"Question": "HUGE + URGE = GREAT", "Answer": "5719 + 7219 = 12938"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "6731 + 7231 = 13962"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = WASTE", "Answer": "5739 + 7839 = 13578"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAT = THREE", "Answer": "9761 + 7261 = 17022"}
{"Question": "REST + EAST = THEIR", "Answer": "2781 + 7981 = 10762"}
{"Question": "QUIT + UNIT = ONION", "Answer": "3806 + 8206 = 12012"}
{"Question": "BEST + EAST = STONE", "Answer": "5814 + 8914 = 14728"}
{"Question": "SUIT + UNIT = SHINE", "Answer": "1823 + 8423 = 10246"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = GRAVE", "Answer": "1827 + 8427 = 10254"}
{"Question": "SUIT + UNIT = SCENE", "Answer": "1832 + 8632 = 10464"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NICE = OFFER", "Answer": "1837 + 8237 = 10074"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = DAILY", "Answer": "5841 + 8941 = 14782"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1842 + 8342 = 10184"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = METAL", "Answer": "3842 + 8542 = 12384"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LEAD = HELLO", "Answer": "2843 + 8043 = 10886"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = ISSUE", "Answer": "1847 + 8247 = 10094"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAR = SMART", "Answer": "1849 + 8649 = 10498"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "6851 + 8251 = 15102"}
{"Question": "HUGE + URGE = HONOR", "Answer": "1852 + 8452 = 10304"}
{"Question": "MALE + ABLE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1852 + 8752 = 10604"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NICE = OWNER", "Answer": "1862 + 8962 = 10824"}
{"Question": "ONCE + NICE = INDEX", "Answer": "9862 + 8162 = 18024"}
{"Question": "TALE + ABLE = TRAIL", "Answer": "1863 + 8963 = 10826"}
{"Question": "HOLY + ONLY = NOVEL", "Answer": "9863 + 8163 = 18026"}
{"Question": "WEST + EAST = WHERE", "Answer": "1864 + 8964 = 10828"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = START", "Answer": "1865 + 8965 = 10830"}
{"Question": "MALE + ABLE = BASIS", "Answer": "9865 + 8165 = 18030"}
{"Question": "PALE + ABLE = PRESS", "Answer": "1872 + 8372 = 10244"}
{"Question": "SPOT + PLOT = SHALL", "Answer": "1872 + 8472 = 10344"}
{"Question": "GLAD + LOAD = GUESS", "Answer": "1872 + 8672 = 10544"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = STAFF", "Answer": "1872 + 8972 = 10844"}
{"Question": "HOLY + ONLY = HUMAN", "Answer": "1873 + 8673 = 10546"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEM = IRISH", "Answer": "1876 + 8276 = 10152"}
{"Question": "SALE + ABLE = SHELF", "Answer": "1896 + 8796 = 10692"}
{"Question": "ROCK + ONCE = OFFER", "Answer": "8132 + 1936 = 10068"}
{"Question": "DATE + AUTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "9135 + 1738 = 10873"}
{"Question": "LADY + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9157 + 1658 = 10815"}
{"Question": "RATE + AUTO = AFTER", "Answer": "9162 + 1467 = 10629"}
{"Question": "STAR + TEAM = THREE", "Answer": "9165 + 1368 = 10533"}
{"Question": "WRAP + REAL = REPLY", "Answer": "9172 + 1074 = 10246"}
{"Question": "USER + STEP = STARE", "Answer": "9174 + 1073 = 10247"}
{"Question": "STAR + THAN = THREE", "Answer": "9182 + 1084 = 10266"}
{"Question": "EAST + ALSO = ALONE", "Answer": "9187 + 1082 = 10269"}
{"Question": "STAR + THAN = THERE", "Answer": "9187 + 1085 = 10272"}
{"Question": "HALF + ABLE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8319 + 3712 = 12031"}
{"Question": "FADE + AIDS = DELAY", "Answer": "9312 + 3418 = 12730"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LOAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "9318 + 3512 = 12830"}
{"Question": "DATE + AUTO = TODAY", "Answer": "9318 + 3612 = 12930"}
{"Question": "BASE + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "9318 + 3517 = 12835"}
{"Question": "CITE + INTO = KNOCK", "Answer": "9346 + 3245 = 12591"}
{"Question": "THIS + HAIR = ASIAN", "Answer": "9352 + 3158 = 12510"}
{"Question": "SNAP + NEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "8416 + 4317 = 12733"}
{"Question": "LADY + AIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8423 + 4125 = 12548"}
{"Question": "VIEW + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "8459 + 4051 = 12510"}
{"Question": "USER + STEP = TREAT", "Answer": "8462 + 4169 = 12631"}
{"Question": "BEST + EASY = WASTE", "Answer": "8475 + 4279 = 12754"}
{"Question": "MATH + AUTO = HUMAN", "Answer": "8521 + 5329 = 13850"}
{"Question": "HERO + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "7529 + 5823 = 13352"}
{"Question": "BEST + EASY = TABLE", "Answer": "7531 + 5234 = 12765"}
{"Question": "WRAP + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "7531 + 5634 = 13165"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAD = STAFF", "Answer": "6532 + 5834 = 12366"}
{"Question": "USER + STEP = TERMS", "Answer": "8536 + 5139 = 13675"}
{"Question": "ITEM + THEN = SHINE", "Answer": "9536 + 5437 = 14973"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LOUD = ERROR", "Answer": "7541 + 5842 = 13383"}
{"Question": "WRAP + READ = UPPER", "Answer": "7543 + 5842 = 13385"}
{"Question": "THUS + HOUR = BRUSH", "Answer": "8562 + 5063 = 13625"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HOUR = TOUCH", "Answer": "7581 + 5284 = 12865"}
{"Question": "TRIP + RAIN = PAINT", "Answer": "7581 + 5286 = 12867"}
{"Question": "GRAB + REAL = BLADE", "Answer": "7591 + 5392 = 12983"}
{"Question": "CAST + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "7631 + 6534 = 14165"}
{"Question": "FADE + AIDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "7631 + 6834 = 14465"}
{"Question": "HOLE + ONLY = ERROR", "Answer": "8631 + 6934 = 15565"}
{"Question": "THAN + HEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "7645 + 6149 = 13794"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "8649 + 6147 = 14796"}
{"Question": "UPON + PLOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8653 + 6451 = 15104"}
{"Question": "TALK + ABLE = ELECT", "Answer": "8657 + 6451 = 15108"}
{"Question": "CASH + ALSO = SHELL", "Answer": "6714 + 7319 = 14033"}
{"Question": "CAMP + ARMY = UPPER", "Answer": "8726 + 7923 = 16649"}
{"Question": "FUEL + USER = DRESS", "Answer": "8729 + 7526 = 16255"}
{"Question": "THAN + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "5729 + 7128 = 12857"}
{"Question": "LADY + AIDE = YIELD", "Answer": "8741 + 7643 = 16384"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "6742 + 7845 = 14587"}
{"Question": "SHIT + HAIR = FIFTH", "Answer": "8762 + 7365 = 16127"}
{"Question": "TRIP + RAIL = PAINT", "Answer": "3781 + 7082 = 10863"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAD = DEATH", "Answer": "3786 + 7081 = 10867"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HOUR = BRUSH", "Answer": "6784 + 7083 = 13867"}
{"Question": "RATE + AUTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "9783 + 7086 = 16869"}
{"Question": "PLAY + LEAD = CYCLE", "Answer": "6784 + 7389 = 14173"}
{"Question": "FUEL + USED = SLEEP", "Answer": "5792 + 7198 = 12990"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LOAD = TOTAL", "Answer": "4801 + 8307 = 13108"}
{"Question": "BEST + EASY = STYLE", "Answer": "4813 + 8715 = 13528"}
{"Question": "FUEL + USED = FALSE", "Answer": "1823 + 8529 = 10352"}
{"Question": "BASE + ALSO = LEVEL", "Answer": "7825 + 8126 = 15951"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAR = WORTH", "Answer": "1836 + 8432 = 10268"}
{"Question": "STAY + TEAR = SMART", "Answer": "1832 + 8536 = 10368"}
{"Question": "STEP + THEM = APPLE", "Answer": "5834 + 8639 = 14473"}
{"Question": "COAL + OKAY = BLACK", "Answer": "7836 + 8539 = 16375"}
{"Question": "WRAP + ROAD = PAPER", "Answer": "6851 + 8257 = 15108"}
{"Question": "BITE + INTO = ENTER", "Answer": "7851 + 8659 = 16510"}
{"Question": "CASE + ALSO = CHECK", "Answer": "1853 + 8459 = 10312"}
{"Question": "TAIL + ACID = ELITE", "Answer": "3862 + 8769 = 12631"}
{"Question": "PAST + ALSO = PRIOR", "Answer": "1867 + 8563 = 10430"}
{"Question": "DATE + AUTO = DRESS", "Answer": "1864 + 8569 = 10433"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HEAR = THREE", "Answer": "9871 + 8473 = 18344"}
{"Question": "SHUT + HOUR = IRISH", "Answer": "4875 + 8273 = 13148"}
{"Question": "GRAY + READ = CYCLE", "Answer": "4873 + 8279 = 13152"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LEAD = ELITE", "Answer": "9875 + 8176 = 18051"}
{"Question": "CASE + ALSO = CHEST", "Answer": "1895 + 8697 = 10592"}
{"Question": "EASY + ARMY = ASSET", "Answer": "8106 + 1976 = 10082"}
{"Question": "CLUE + LINE = LUNCH", "Answer": "9106 + 1786 = 10892"}
{"Question": "DRAG + RING = RADIO", "Answer": "9106 + 1876 = 10982"}
{"Question": "ACID + COLD = CLASS", "Answer": "9137 + 1807 = 10944"}
{"Question": "USER + STAR = STATE", "Answer": "9184 + 1024 = 10208"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BIKE = BREAK", "Answer": "9128 + 1768 = 10896"}
{"Question": "USER + STAR = SMART", "Answer": "9153 + 1683 = 10836"}
{"Question": "SHOT + HEAT = HELLO", "Answer": "9168 + 1058 = 10226"}
{"Question": "MODE + ONCE = ORDER", "Answer": "9165 + 1485 = 10650"}
{"Question": "URGE + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8251 + 2361 = 10612"}
{"Question": "STIR + TEAR = WASTE", "Answer": "9308 + 3628 = 12936"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HOST = ALLOW", "Answer": "6318 + 3758 = 10076"}
{"Question": "SHOE + HATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "5402 + 4612 = 10014"}
{"Question": "STIR + TEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "9461 + 4231 = 13692"}
{"Question": "USER + STAR = DRESS", "Answer": "8452 + 4092 = 12544"}
{"Question": "EASY + ARMY = CREAM", "Answer": "8507 + 5347 = 13854"}
{"Question": "LOSE + ONCE = CYCLE", "Answer": "8570 + 5610 = 14180"}
{"Question": "ROPE + ONCE = PAPER", "Answer": "8519 + 5679 = 14198"}
{"Question": "MYTH + YEAH = CATCH", "Answer": "7590 + 5320 = 12910"}
{"Question": "FUND + USED = SENSE", "Answer": "9572 + 5142 = 14714"}
{"Question": "DARE + ABLE = BREAD", "Answer": "4607 + 6157 = 10764"}
{"Question": "GRAY + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "4608 + 6218 = 10826"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LIST = STATE", "Answer": "8635 + 6715 = 15350"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LINE = UNTIL", "Answer": "5618 + 6428 = 12046"}
{"Question": "BELT + EAST = LATER", "Answer": "7619 + 6349 = 13968"}
{"Question": "GRAY + RELY = EAGER", "Answer": "8643 + 6173 = 14816"}
{"Question": "MYTH + YEAH = TASTE", "Answer": "2714 + 7804 = 10518"}
{"Question": "BURN + UPON = TROOP", "Answer": "2704 + 7854 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ROPE + ONCE = UPPER", "Answer": "2706 + 7356 = 10062"}
{"Question": "LOSE + ONCE = SCENE", "Answer": "4710 + 7320 = 12030"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LIST = STAFF", "Answer": "4732 + 7612 = 12344"}
{"Question": "URGE + RATE = GREAT", "Answer": "9712 + 7542 = 17254"}
{"Question": "EASY + ARMY = SWEAR", "Answer": "5714 + 7864 = 13578"}
{"Question": "STIR + TEAR = ARISE", "Answer": "6754 + 7814 = 14568"}
{"Question": "BORN + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "6735 + 7415 = 14150"}
{"Question": "USER + STIR = IRISH", "Answer": "8756 + 7416 = 16172"}
{"Question": "DENY + EASY = NAKED", "Answer": "8719 + 7659 = 16378"}
{"Question": "HOPE + ONCE = UPPER", "Answer": "4729 + 7569 = 12298"}
{"Question": "DRAG + RING = GUARD", "Answer": "2731 + 7641 = 10372"}
{"Question": "MORE + ONCE = GREEN", "Answer": "5732 + 7492 = 13224"}
{"Question": "NEXT + EAST = ASIAN", "Answer": "8764 + 7154 = 15918"}
{"Question": "SAME + ABLE = SMELL", "Answer": "1803 + 8563 = 10366"}
{"Question": "TURN + UPON = TROOP", "Answer": "1803 + 8643 = 10446"}
{"Question": "STEP + TRIP = SEIZE", "Answer": "1805 + 8425 = 10230"}
{"Question": "USER + STIR = ARISE", "Answer": "6805 + 8975 = 15780"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LINE = BUNCH", "Answer": "1806 + 8536 = 10342"}
{"Question": "FLAG + LONG = FAVOR", "Answer": "1806 + 8546 = 10352"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LAKE = BUILD", "Answer": "1806 + 8576 = 10382"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BITE = ALTER", "Answer": "1806 + 8756 = 10562"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BIKE = ALLOW", "Answer": "1807 + 8257 = 10064"}
{"Question": "TWIN + WHEN = TITLE", "Answer": "1807 + 8347 = 10154"}
{"Question": "SHOP + HELP = SOLVE", "Answer": "1807 + 8427 = 10234"}
{"Question": "BURY + UGLY = BRING", "Answer": "1807 + 8457 = 10264"}
{"Question": "GRAY + RELY = GLASS", "Answer": "1837 + 8507 = 10344"}
{"Question": "PRAY + RELY = PANEL", "Answer": "1807 + 8547 = 10354"}
{"Question": "BODY + OKAY = BASIS", "Answer": "1827 + 8607 = 10434"}
{"Question": "DARE + ABLE = DRESS", "Answer": "1807 + 8937 = 10744"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HURT = WATER", "Answer": "1807 + 8947 = 10754"}
{"Question": "SALE + AIDE = SLEEP", "Answer": "1807 + 8967 = 10774"}
{"Question": "PRAY + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "1809 + 8329 = 10138"}
{"Question": "RELY + EASY = LAYER", "Answer": "6813 + 8573 = 15386"}
{"Question": "GAME + AIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6814 + 8094 = 14908"}
{"Question": "TRUE + RIDE = UNDER", "Answer": "7814 + 8534 = 16348"}
{"Question": "MORE + ONCE = CREAM", "Answer": "4837 + 8917 = 13754"}
{"Question": "SPIN + PLAN = SHALL", "Answer": "1823 + 8643 = 10466"}
{"Question": "TALE + AIDE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1826 + 8356 = 10182"}
{"Question": "MALE + AIDE = MODEL", "Answer": "1826 + 8536 = 10362"}
{"Question": "POSE + ONCE = PRESS", "Answer": "1826 + 8796 = 10622"}
{"Question": "STEP + TRIP = PRESS", "Answer": "2891 + 8031 = 10922"}
{"Question": "SHOP + HELP = SCOPE", "Answer": "1832 + 8492 = 10324"}
{"Question": "VOTE + ONCE = ENTER", "Answer": "6841 + 8571 = 15412"}
{"Question": "BLUE + LAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "1892 + 8342 = 10234"}
{"Question": "UNIT + NEXT = FIFTH", "Answer": "5843 + 8293 = 14136"}
{"Question": "UNIT + NEXT = ONION", "Answer": "9864 + 8754 = 18618"}
{"Question": "GATE + ABLE = GUEST", "Answer": "1863 + 8493 = 10356"}
{"Question": "SIGN + IRON = SWING", "Answer": "1863 + 8973 = 10836"}
{"Question": "HOLE + ONCE = NOVEL", "Answer": "9863 + 8173 = 18036"}
{"Question": "STAR + TYPE = APART", "Answer": "8415 + 4739 = 13154"}
{"Question": "TAPE + ALSO = SLEEP", "Answer": "9457 + 4318 = 13775"}
{"Question": "HAVE + ALSO = LEVEL", "Answer": "8462 + 4159 = 12621"}
{"Question": "USER + SOFT = ROUTE", "Answer": "7501 + 5289 = 12790"}
{"Question": "AIDS + ITEM = STATE", "Answer": "8521 + 5309 = 13830"}
{"Question": "LIST + IDEA = STEAL", "Answer": "6512 + 5834 = 12346"}
{"Question": "STIR + THAN = IRISH", "Answer": "8514 + 5672 = 14186"}
{"Question": "MARK + AIDE = DREAM", "Answer": "8546 + 5712 = 14258"}
{"Question": "STIR + TEAM = ARISE", "Answer": "9574 + 5218 = 14792"}
{"Question": "GOAL + OVER = LARGE", "Answer": "6521 + 5843 = 12364"}
{"Question": "THUS + HERO = SOUTH", "Answer": "8521 + 5764 = 14285"}
{"Question": "TRIP + REAL = LATER", "Answer": "8594 + 5231 = 13825"}
{"Question": "THIN + HAVE = EVENT", "Answer": "8537 + 5641 = 14178"}
{"Question": "INTO + NAME = OFTEN", "Answer": "7561 + 5084 = 12645"}
{"Question": "FARM + ALSO = MORAL", "Answer": "7591 + 5362 = 12953"}
{"Question": "DISH + ITEM = THEME", "Answer": "9564 + 5173 = 14737"}
{"Question": "CROP + REAL = PLACE", "Answer": "7581 + 5392 = 12973"}
{"Question": "AUTO + USER = TREAT", "Answer": "5619 + 6732 = 12351"}
{"Question": "FLAT + LOSE = STEEL", "Answer": "5632 + 6814 = 12446"}
{"Question": "TRIP + READ = ADAPT", "Answer": "7623 + 6514 = 14137"}
{"Question": "LAST + ACID = STEEL", "Answer": "9615 + 6274 = 15889"}
{"Question": "RUSH + UGLY = SHRUG", "Answer": "9615 + 6348 = 15963"}
{"Question": "CLUB + LAWN = BUNCH", "Answer": "7631 + 6248 = 13879"}
{"Question": "COAL + OVEN = SLAVE", "Answer": "6704 + 7328 = 14032"}
{"Question": "LEFT + EASY = STYLE", "Answer": "4732 + 7815 = 12547"}
{"Question": "DRAW + RELY = AWARD", "Answer": "5713 + 7462 = 13175"}
{"Question": "GAME + ALSO = SMELL", "Answer": "6742 + 7513 = 14255"}
{"Question": "AIDE + IRON = ORDER", "Answer": "8734 + 7612 = 16346"}
{"Question": "AUTO + URGE = GREAT", "Answer": "5734 + 7219 = 12953"}
{"Question": "WIPE + IRON = POWER", "Answer": "9718 + 7264 = 16982"}
{"Question": "DRUG + REAL = GUARD", "Answer": "4721 + 7853 = 12574"}
{"Question": "DRAG + REST = TASTE", "Answer": "5729 + 7081 = 12810"}
{"Question": "THIN + HALF = FIFTH", "Answer": "5736 + 7421 = 13157"}
{"Question": "OPEN + PART = TROOP", "Answer": "5726 + 7831 = 13557"}
{"Question": "FARM + ABLE = METAL", "Answer": "6721 + 7354 = 14075"}
{"Question": "CREW + RUSH = WHERE", "Answer": "6751 + 7824 = 14575"}
{"Question": "HERO + EAST = OTHER", "Answer": "6751 + 7924 = 14675"}
{"Question": "IDEA + DUST = TASTE", "Answer": "5732 + 7081 = 12813"}
{"Question": "STAY + TOUR = YOURS", "Answer": "3741 + 7082 = 10823"}
{"Question": "WHAT + HERO = TOWER", "Answer": "8741 + 7065 = 15806"}
{"Question": "USER + SPIN = PRESS", "Answer": "6793 + 7184 = 13977"}
{"Question": "THIS + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1809 + 8472 = 10281"}
{"Question": "SOFT + OVER = SERVE", "Answer": "1847 + 8503 = 10350"}
{"Question": "THUS + HARD = TRUST", "Answer": "1834 + 8507 = 10341"}
{"Question": "SICK + IRON = SCENE", "Answer": "1805 + 8467 = 10272"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BOTH = ALTER", "Answer": "1805 + 8647 = 10452"}
{"Question": "MOST + OPEN = METER", "Answer": "1895 + 8607 = 10502"}
{"Question": "COAL + OVER = CARRY", "Answer": "1805 + 8967 = 10772"}
{"Question": "ALSO + LIFE = ASSET", "Answer": "1807 + 8256 = 10063"}
{"Question": "TRIP + REAL = TITLE", "Answer": "1807 + 8356 = 10163"}
{"Question": "ABLE + BIND = ALTER", "Answer": "1806 + 8457 = 10263"}
{"Question": "CAST + ABLE = STEAL", "Answer": "6815 + 8472 = 15287"}
{"Question": "MYTH + YOUR = TRULY", "Answer": "7812 + 8536 = 16348"}
{"Question": "DRAW + RELY = AWARE", "Answer": "5814 + 8369 = 14183"}
{"Question": "KNOW + NEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "5874 + 8319 = 14193"}
{"Question": "TOUR + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "4875 + 8319 = 13194"}
{"Question": "WRAP + RICE = PAPER", "Answer": "6851 + 8327 = 15178"}
{"Question": "SHOW + HURT = WORTH", "Answer": "6851 + 8427 = 15278"}
{"Question": "CLUB + LEAD = BADLY", "Answer": "7821 + 8563 = 16384"}
{"Question": "POSE + OKAY = PRESS", "Answer": "1825 + 8697 = 10522"}
{"Question": "FARM + AUTO = FLOOR", "Answer": "1825 + 8947 = 10772"}
{"Question": "WRAP + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "4831 + 8297 = 13128"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = BEAN", "Answer": "1513 + 1501 = 3014"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = BABY", "Answer": "2625 + 2632 = 5257"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = BELL", "Answer": "4348 + 4374 = 8722"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = FLOOR", "Answer": "5459 + 5425 = 10884"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = CLEAR", "Answer": "6468 + 6496 = 12964"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = THEIR", "Answer": "6569 + 6506 = 13075"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = CHECK", "Answer": "6762 + 6756 = 13518"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = BLADE", "Answer": "7371 + 7387 = 14758"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = BREAD", "Answer": "7571 + 7507 = 15078"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = ONION", "Answer": "8689 + 8628 = 17317"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = DRESS", "Answer": "8786 + 8758 = 17544"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = URBAN", "Answer": "8785 + 8798 = 17583"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = REFER", "Answer": "9192 + 9189 = 18381"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AREA = LEVEL", "Answer": "9392 + 9389 = 18781"}
{"Question": "BABY + BOMB = ONION", "Answer": "6867 + 6146 = 13013"}
{"Question": "AWAY + AREA = WHICH", "Answer": "6167 + 6856 = 13023"}
{"Question": "BABY + BOMB = ERROR", "Answer": "6467 + 6926 = 13393"}
{"Question": "EVER + EDGE = BREAD", "Answer": "6763 + 6926 = 13689"}
{"Question": "AWAY + AREA = FRAME", "Answer": "7278 + 7457 = 14735"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "7479 + 7657 = 15136"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ELSE = BIBLE", "Answer": "7470 + 7697 = 15167"}
{"Question": "EVER + EASE = RURAL", "Answer": "7471 + 7697 = 15168"}
{"Question": "BABY + BOMB = MAYOR", "Answer": "8687 + 8018 = 16705"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ELSE = SHELL", "Answer": "8782 + 8018 = 16800"}
{"Question": "AWAY + AREA = SWEAR", "Answer": "8684 + 8298 = 16982"}
{"Question": "BABY + BOMB = TOTAL", "Answer": "8382 + 8748 = 17130"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = SHARP", "Answer": "1668 + 8611 = 10279"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = LIMIT", "Answer": "2887 + 7822 = 10709"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = ASIAN", "Answer": "3779 + 9733 = 13512"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = TOOTH", "Answer": "4668 + 8644 = 13312"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = PHOTO", "Answer": "5668 + 8655 = 14323"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = THEME", "Answer": "5994 + 4955 = 10949"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = CLIMB", "Answer": "6773 + 3766 = 10539"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = BLOOD", "Answer": "7662 + 2677 = 10339"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = BEACH", "Answer": "7668 + 8677 = 16345"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = MAJOR", "Answer": "8661 + 1688 = 10349"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "8665 + 5688 = 14353"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MESS = MARRY", "Answer": "8771 + 1788 = 10559"}
{"Question": "SOON + BOSS = SCENE", "Answer": "1223 + 9211 = 10434"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = SCALE", "Answer": "1776 + 8711 = 10487"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = OWNER", "Answer": "2123 + 8112 = 10235"}
{"Question": "NONE + SOON = ODDS", "Answer": "2329 + 1332 = 3661"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = ONTO", "Answer": "2624 + 3662 = 6286"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = ISSUE", "Answer": "2664 + 9622 = 12286"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ROLL = BEER", "Answer": "3449 + 2433 = 5882"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = ENTER", "Answer": "3831 + 9883 = 13714"}
{"Question": "SOON + LOSS = ONLY", "Answer": "4887 + 3844 = 8731"}
{"Question": "SOON + TOSS = MONTH", "Answer": "5224 + 7255 = 12479"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = AIDE", "Answer": "5661 + 2655 = 8316"}
{"Question": "SOON + BOSS = ENTER", "Answer": "5664 + 8655 = 14319"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = ASIDE", "Answer": "5883 + 9855 = 15738"}
{"Question": "NONE + SOON = ENEMY", "Answer": "7571 + 9557 = 17128"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ROLL = START", "Answer": "7665 + 4677 = 12342"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = SORRY", "Answer": "7672 + 8667 = 16339"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = FENCE", "Answer": "7669 + 8677 = 16346"}
{"Question": "LOOK + POLL = SLEEP", "Answer": "7662 + 9677 = 17339"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = INNER", "Answer": "7876 + 9887 = 17763"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = FEWER", "Answer": "8382 + 4338 = 12720"}
{"Question": "SEED + MESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "8441 + 2488 = 10929"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = LEVEL", "Answer": "8483 + 5448 = 13931"}
{"Question": "SOON + BOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8559 + 1588 = 10147"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8557 + 4588 = 13145"}
{"Question": "LOOK + POLL = TOTAL", "Answer": "8550 + 6588 = 15138"}
{"Question": "NONE + SOON = SHALL", "Answer": "8687 + 1668 = 10355"}
{"Question": "LOOK + POLL = CIVIL", "Answer": "8660 + 5688 = 14348"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = TERMS", "Answer": "8684 + 5668 = 14352"}
{"Question": "SOON + LOSS = LABEL", "Answer": "8773 + 1788 = 10561"}
{"Question": "NONE + SOON = SHELF", "Answer": "8785 + 1778 = 10563"}
{"Question": "NONE + MOON = MAKER", "Answer": "8786 + 1778 = 10564"}
{"Question": "LOOK + POLL = PIANO", "Answer": "8779 + 1788 = 10567"}
{"Question": "SOON + TOSS = AGENT", "Answer": "8776 + 4788 = 13564"}
{"Question": "SEED + LESS = LABEL", "Answer": "9332 + 1399 = 10731"}
{"Question": "SEED + MESS = LEVEL", "Answer": "9332 + 4399 = 13731"}
{"Question": "LOOK + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "9446 + 5499 = 14945"}
{"Question": "LESS + SELF = STATE", "Answer": "9311 + 1392 = 10703"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = STORM", "Answer": "8611 + 1687 = 10298"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = TEAM", "Answer": "7811 + 1876 = 9687"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = PILOT", "Answer": "7622 + 2675 = 10297"}
{"Question": "KILL + LIKE = CLOCK", "Answer": "9622 + 2697 = 12319"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = FLEE", "Answer": "6133 + 3167 = 9300"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = ALTER", "Answer": "9833 + 3892 = 13725"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = TREAT", "Answer": "8344 + 4387 = 12731"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9644 + 4693 = 14337"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = ELSE", "Answer": "1744 + 4712 = 6456"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8744 + 4783 = 13527"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = SHAKE", "Answer": "8944 + 4982 = 13926"}
{"Question": "LESS + SELF = FUEL", "Answer": "4055 + 5049 = 9104"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = SALES", "Answer": "7255 + 5276 = 12531"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = HUMAN", "Answer": "7355 + 5379 = 12734"}
{"Question": "KILL + LIKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "8655 + 5683 = 14338"}
{"Question": "LESS + SELF = ISSUE", "Answer": "9755 + 5792 = 15547"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = EXTRA", "Answer": "4855 + 5843 = 10698"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = TREAT", "Answer": "7266 + 6275 = 13541"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = EVENT", "Answer": "7566 + 6571 = 14137"}
{"Question": "KILL + LIKE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8566 + 6583 = 15149"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = USUAL", "Answer": "9566 + 6592 = 16158"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = BLOOD", "Answer": "9766 + 6792 = 16558"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFT = BRIEF", "Answer": "8966 + 6982 = 15948"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = MESS", "Answer": "2177 + 7123 = 9300"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = AGENT", "Answer": "8177 + 7183 = 15360"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = IRAQI", "Answer": "8177 + 7184 = 15361"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = NEWLY", "Answer": "9277 + 7296 = 16573"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = DELAY", "Answer": "5377 + 7359 = 12736"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = SALES", "Answer": "6377 + 7364 = 13741"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = CREAM", "Answer": "6477 + 7469 = 13946"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = AGAIN", "Answer": "8577 + 7582 = 16159"}
{"Question": "WALL + LAWN = ENTER", "Answer": "4677 + 7642 = 12319"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = FLOAT", "Answer": "9677 + 7692 = 17369"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = INDEX", "Answer": "7188 + 8176 = 15364"}
{"Question": "LESS + SELF = EQUAL", "Answer": "7188 + 8179 = 15367"}
{"Question": "WALL + LAWN = ANGLE", "Answer": "9188 + 8197 = 17385"}
{"Question": "CALL + LACK = BASIC", "Answer": "4288 + 8246 = 12534"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = CHEEK", "Answer": "6288 + 8265 = 14553"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = LEGAL", "Answer": "5488 + 8453 = 13941"}
{"Question": "KILL + LIKE = BREAK", "Answer": "7488 + 8479 = 15967"}
{"Question": "TALL + LATE = ELECT", "Answer": "9588 + 8591 = 18179"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFT = TROOP", "Answer": "5688 + 8651 = 14339"}
{"Question": "FILL + LIFE = EIGHT", "Answer": "7688 + 8671 = 16359"}
{"Question": "LESS + SELF = REFER", "Answer": "7688 + 8673 = 16361"}
{"Question": "MASS + SAME = LEVEL", "Answer": "4788 + 8743 = 13531"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = ASSET", "Answer": "2502 + 7522 = 10024"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "2612 + 3622 = 6234"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = IDEAL", "Answer": "3673 + 8633 = 12306"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = ONION", "Answer": "6846 + 5866 = 12712"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7837 + 2877 = 10714"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = FINAL", "Answer": "8658 + 1688 = 10346"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLEE = FIBER", "Answer": "8798 + 1788 = 10586"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = LUCKY", "Answer": "8611 + 1678 = 10289"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = STAR", "Answer": "4711 + 1764 = 6475"}
{"Question": "KISS + SICK = SHEET", "Answer": "8711 + 1738 = 10449"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SORT = ENTER", "Answer": "7822 + 2897 = 10719"}
{"Question": "TELL + LEFT = QUITE", "Answer": "7922 + 2957 = 10879"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = ASIAN", "Answer": "9833 + 3879 = 13712"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = FIELD", "Answer": "8544 + 4538 = 13082"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = METER", "Answer": "5744 + 4765 = 10509"}
{"Question": "KISS + SICK = BASIC", "Answer": "8744 + 4728 = 13472"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = ISSUE", "Answer": "9744 + 4719 = 14463"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "9844 + 4819 = 14663"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOUL = FULLY", "Answer": "8944 + 4938 = 13882"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = ANGER", "Answer": "7855 + 5837 = 13692"}
{"Question": "KISS + SINK = UNTIL", "Answer": "7955 + 5937 = 13892"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SORT = ACTOR", "Answer": "8955 + 5938 = 14893"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SORT = ERROR", "Answer": "9266 + 6259 = 15525"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = AGAIN", "Answer": "3566 + 6593 = 10159"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOFT = FORTH", "Answer": "8566 + 6518 = 15084"}
{"Question": "KISS + SICK = OCCUR", "Answer": "8766 + 6758 = 15524"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = SOLAR", "Answer": "7866 + 6817 = 14683"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = SKIN", "Answer": "1577 + 7581 = 9158"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = ENEMY", "Answer": "6577 + 7546 = 14123"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = COULD", "Answer": "8677 + 7608 = 16285"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOUL = COUCH", "Answer": "8677 + 7638 = 16315"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = COLOR", "Answer": "2877 + 7832 = 10709"}
{"Question": "KISS + SICK = CYCLE", "Answer": "4588 + 8514 = 13102"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = TROOP", "Answer": "1688 + 8651 = 10339"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = TERMS", "Answer": "1688 + 8691 = 10379"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = COACH", "Answer": "7688 + 8627 = 16315"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOIL = WORRY", "Answer": "7688 + 8647 = 16335"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = GIVEN", "Answer": "7688 + 8657 = 16345"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAST = TRUTH", "Answer": "1788 + 8731 = 10519"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOUL = LAUGH", "Answer": "1788 + 8751 = 10539"}
{"Question": "TELL + LEFT = CATCH", "Answer": "5788 + 8725 = 14513"}
{"Question": "KILL + LINK = TOOTH", "Answer": "6788 + 8726 = 15514"}
{"Question": "TELL + LEFT = SALES", "Answer": "3988 + 8903 = 12891"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = OPEN", "Answer": "3622 + 2688 = 6310"}
{"Question": "YELL + LESS = ALLY", "Answer": "2133 + 3199 = 5332"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = SLOW", "Answer": "4133 + 3177 = 7310"}
{"Question": "HELL + LESS = SHOE", "Answer": "3144 + 4177 = 7321"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = SLIP", "Answer": "3255 + 5288 = 8543"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = DELAY", "Answer": "7255 + 5288 = 12543"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = HELLO", "Answer": "7255 + 5299 = 12554"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = SHOP", "Answer": "3455 + 5488 = 8943"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = REFER", "Answer": "7455 + 5466 = 12921"}
{"Question": "WELL + LESS = FEWER", "Answer": "9455 + 5488 = 14943"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = OCCUR", "Answer": "7166 + 6188 = 13354"}
{"Question": "MESS + SELL = ELITE", "Answer": "9166 + 6155 = 15321"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = SAFE", "Answer": "2466 + 6488 = 8954"}
{"Question": "TELL + LESS = ENTRY", "Answer": "3177 + 7188 = 10365"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "3277 + 7288 = 10565"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = ISSUE", "Answer": "8277 + 7255 = 15532"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = COLOR", "Answer": "6377 + 7355 = 13732"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = BELOW", "Answer": "9377 + 7355 = 16732"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = TASTE", "Answer": "4677 + 7633 = 12310"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOSS = OCCUR", "Answer": "5188 + 8177 = 13365"}
{"Question": "CELL + LESS = EXACT", "Answer": "6188 + 8177 = 14365"}
{"Question": "YELL + LESS = EARLY", "Answer": "7188 + 8199 = 15387"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = ASIDE", "Answer": "6288 + 8244 = 14532"}
{"Question": "MESS + SELL = COLOR", "Answer": "6288 + 8255 = 14543"}
{"Question": "YELL + LESS = APPLY", "Answer": "7288 + 8299 = 15587"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = PAPER", "Answer": "1588 + 8544 = 10132"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSS = PIECE", "Answer": "1688 + 8655 = 10343"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = BRIEF", "Answer": "1688 + 8677 = 10365"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = BADLY", "Answer": "1688 + 8699 = 10387"}
{"Question": "MESS + SELL = BLOOD", "Answer": "5688 + 8644 = 14332"}
{"Question": "YELL + LESS = NEWLY", "Answer": "7688 + 8699 = 16387"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOSS = RIVER", "Answer": "1788 + 8733 = 10521"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = BIRTH", "Answer": "1788 + 8744 = 10532"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = BASIC", "Answer": "1788 + 8755 = 10543"}
{"Question": "CELL + LESS = CABLE", "Answer": "1788 + 8799 = 10587"}
{"Question": "CELL + LESS = WHICH", "Answer": "3788 + 8744 = 12532"}
{"Question": "BELL + LESS = CABLE", "Answer": "5788 + 8799 = 14587"}
{"Question": "TELL + LESS = TREAT", "Answer": "1988 + 8933 = 10921"}
{"Question": "TELL + LESS = TRUST", "Answer": "1399 + 9322 = 10721"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOME = STEEL", "Answer": "9411 + 1478 = 10889"}
{"Question": "LESS + SEAT = SCALE", "Answer": "9411 + 1483 = 10894"}
{"Question": "EDGE + IDEA = ESSAY", "Answer": "1521 + 8513 = 10034"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAG = APPLE", "Answer": "1531 + 8512 = 10043"}
{"Question": "SELL + LEAD = LOOSE", "Answer": "8511 + 1574 = 10085"}
{"Question": "TALL + LACK = LIMIT", "Answer": "8611 + 1697 = 10308"}
{"Question": "HALL + LATE = THAT", "Answer": "4711 + 1765 = 6476"}
{"Question": "KISS + SITE = START", "Answer": "8711 + 1709 = 10420"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "9522 + 2513 = 12035"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SOIL = HELLO", "Answer": "7822 + 2846 = 10668"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAF = FLEE", "Answer": "5133 + 3178 = 8311"}
{"Question": "TALL + LADY = ADULT", "Answer": "7133 + 3104 = 10237"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOSE = SWEEP", "Answer": "7233 + 3214 = 10447"}
{"Question": "BILL + LIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "9233 + 3248 = 12481"}
{"Question": "KICK + LIKE = FIELD", "Answer": "3263 + 9234 = 12497"}
{"Question": "SELL + LEFT = TASTE", "Answer": "9433 + 3481 = 12914"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAW = SWEAR", "Answer": "3503 + 8532 = 12035"}
{"Question": "BALL + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "8533 + 3520 = 12053"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SORT = ERROR", "Answer": "8633 + 3629 = 12262"}
{"Question": "AREA + GRAB = BEACH", "Answer": "4234 + 9241 = 13475"}
{"Question": "RARE + PAIR = CHEAP", "Answer": "4245 + 9284 = 13529"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOME = MODEL", "Answer": "9344 + 4315 = 13659"}
{"Question": "HALL + LATE = CATCH", "Answer": "9344 + 4375 = 13719"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAF = REFER", "Answer": "9344 + 4387 = 13731"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = HELLO", "Answer": "4642 + 7694 = 12336"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAG = ONION", "Answer": "4764 + 8749 = 13513"}
{"Question": "KICK + LIKE = CELL", "Answer": "4864 + 1847 = 6711"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOUL = LIMIT", "Answer": "5844 + 4861 = 10705"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9844 + 4816 = 14660"}
{"Question": "BALL + LAWN = GANG", "Answer": "1944 + 4982 = 6926"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOVE = EVER", "Answer": "3155 + 5128 = 8283"}
{"Question": "LESS + SEAT = TAIL", "Answer": "4155 + 5129 = 9284"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOAN = INNER", "Answer": "9255 + 5234 = 14489"}
{"Question": "NONE + JOIN = VIDEO", "Answer": "5358 + 7325 = 12683"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "8355 + 5376 = 13731"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SONG = HONOR", "Answer": "8355 + 5379 = 13734"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = COVER", "Answer": "5354 + 8395 = 13749"}
{"Question": "KISS + SIGH = CHEEK", "Answer": "7455 + 5432 = 12887"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAG = EDGE", "Answer": "5695 + 3654 = 9349"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = AGENT", "Answer": "5652 + 4605 = 10257"}
{"Question": "BALL + LAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "4655 + 5683 = 10338"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LONG = ANGER", "Answer": "7655 + 5632 = 13287"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = UPPER", "Answer": "5654 + 7695 = 13349"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = FEWER", "Answer": "5654 + 8695 = 14349"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAF = FLAME", "Answer": "9655 + 5621 = 15276"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = ANGER", "Answer": "5652 + 9675 = 15327"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SOUP = APPLE", "Answer": "8755 + 5734 = 14489"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = INNER", "Answer": "5753 + 9785 = 15538"}
{"Question": "NONE + JOIN = PIANO", "Answer": "5853 + 4805 = 10658"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = ENTER", "Answer": "5851 + 9865 = 15716"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOAN = HELLO", "Answer": "5954 + 8935 = 14889"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOWN = ASSET", "Answer": "6263 + 9276 = 15539"}
{"Question": "RARE + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "6361 + 7326 = 13687"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = LEVEL", "Answer": "6365 + 9386 = 15751"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "8466 + 6421 = 14887"}
{"Question": "RARE + PAIR = HAPPY", "Answer": "6463 + 8426 = 14889"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAG = BREAD", "Answer": "6506 + 8562 = 15068"}
{"Question": "CELL + LEFT = FENCE", "Answer": "8566 + 6519 = 15085"}
{"Question": "BALL + LAWN = PANEL", "Answer": "8566 + 6530 = 15096"}
{"Question": "BALL + LATE = ELECT", "Answer": "9566 + 6571 = 16137"}
{"Question": "RARE + FAIR = LEGAL", "Answer": "6765 + 8706 = 15471"}
{"Question": "RARE + FAIR = BRIEF", "Answer": "6863 + 9876 = 16739"}
{"Question": "MALL + LADY = DRAMA", "Answer": "9077 + 7013 = 16090"}
{"Question": "TELL + LEAD = ENTER", "Answer": "3177 + 7142 = 10319"}
{"Question": "MALL + LAKE = ARMED", "Answer": "3177 + 7152 = 10329"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOSE = OFFER", "Answer": "5177 + 7108 = 12285"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOME = LIMIT", "Answer": "6277 + 7259 = 13536"}
{"Question": "HALL + LAST = TOOTH", "Answer": "8277 + 7241 = 15518"}
{"Question": "GANG + PAGE = EAGER", "Answer": "7347 + 6371 = 13718"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "7378 + 6357 = 13735"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOAD = COLOR", "Answer": "6377 + 7359 = 13736"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAD = SALES", "Answer": "8377 + 7354 = 15731"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRAG = GUIDE", "Answer": "7487 + 5471 = 12958"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOWN = METER", "Answer": "7476 + 9487 = 16963"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "9577 + 7508 = 17085"}
{"Question": "BALL + LATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "4677 + 7630 = 12307"}
{"Question": "RARE + FAIR = ONION", "Answer": "7675 + 4637 = 12312"}
{"Question": "YELL + LEAN = NEWLY", "Answer": "8677 + 7601 = 16278"}
{"Question": "CELL + LEAD = FENCE", "Answer": "8677 + 7609 = 16286"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOVE = NOVEL", "Answer": "8677 + 7630 = 16307"}
{"Question": "AREA + GRAB = BRING", "Answer": "7657 + 8671 = 16328"}
{"Question": "BILL + LIFE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8677 + 7690 = 16367"}
{"Question": "CALL + LADY = BLOOD", "Answer": "9677 + 7658 = 17335"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = PRIOR", "Answer": "7873 + 2807 = 10680"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAF = FALSE", "Answer": "5877 + 7831 = 13708"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEFT = TABLE", "Answer": "6877 + 7801 = 14678"}
{"Question": "EDGE + IDEA = GUIDE", "Answer": "7817 + 6870 = 14687"}
{"Question": "LESS + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "6877 + 7841 = 14718"}
{"Question": "MASS + SALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "6977 + 7914 = 14891"}
{"Question": "TELL + LEAF = AFTER", "Answer": "8977 + 7916 = 16893"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "4288 + 8235 = 12523"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOAD = HONOR", "Answer": "4288 + 8236 = 12524"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORN = PORCH", "Answer": "8289 + 4258 = 12547"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LONG = NEVER", "Answer": "2388 + 8314 = 10702"}
{"Question": "LESS + SEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "4388 + 8327 = 12715"}
{"Question": "HALL + LAST = CATCH", "Answer": "5388 + 8327 = 13715"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LOAN = HONOR", "Answer": "5388 + 8347 = 13735"}
{"Question": "CALL + LAND = DANCE", "Answer": "5388 + 8371 = 13759"}
{"Question": "MASS + SALT = LEVEL", "Answer": "2488 + 8413 = 10901"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOIL = PILOT", "Answer": "7488 + 8459 = 15947"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SOUL = BIBLE", "Answer": "1588 + 8576 = 10164"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAD = BIBLE", "Answer": "1588 + 8597 = 10185"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAD = ADAPT", "Answer": "7588 + 8516 = 16104"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = BRIEF", "Answer": "8689 + 1608 = 10297"}
{"Question": "AREA + PRAY = PIECE", "Answer": "8638 + 1685 = 10323"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOWN = TREAT", "Answer": "8683 + 1658 = 10341"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SUPER", "Answer": "8684 + 1658 = 10342"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOAD = PRIOR", "Answer": "1688 + 8672 = 10360"}
{"Question": "TALL + LAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "1688 + 8673 = 10361"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SOLID", "Answer": "8684 + 1678 = 10362"}
{"Question": "KICK + BIKE = BASIS", "Answer": "8678 + 1685 = 10363"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOWN = THROW", "Answer": "8689 + 1678 = 10367"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOIL = THESE", "Answer": "1688 + 8695 = 10383"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SOFT = ERROR", "Answer": "4688 + 8675 = 13363"}
{"Question": "POLL + LOTS = SLEEP", "Answer": "9688 + 8651 = 18339"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SNOW = START", "Answer": "8708 + 1782 = 10490"}
{"Question": "NONE + BORN = BREAD", "Answer": "8784 + 1708 = 10492"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORN = CHECK", "Answer": "8785 + 1728 = 10513"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SHALL", "Answer": "8784 + 1738 = 10522"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORN = CLEAR", "Answer": "8785 + 1738 = 10523"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SALES", "Answer": "8783 + 1748 = 10531"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SHELL", "Answer": "8785 + 1748 = 10533"}
{"Question": "FALL + LAND = FENCE", "Answer": "1788 + 8752 = 10540"}
{"Question": "KICK + LIKE = LOCAL", "Answer": "8758 + 1783 = 10541"}
{"Question": "BELL + LEAN = BRAND", "Answer": "1788 + 8754 = 10542"}
{"Question": "CELL + LEAD = CHASE", "Answer": "1788 + 8759 = 10547"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SHEET", "Answer": "8785 + 1768 = 10553"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOIL = TRUST", "Answer": "1788 + 8793 = 10581"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIGN = SPEND", "Answer": "8785 + 1798 = 10583"}
{"Question": "GANG + PAGE = ONION", "Answer": "8728 + 3784 = 12512"}
{"Question": "BALL + LAWN = SENSE", "Answer": "4788 + 8725 = 13513"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOAN = EAGER", "Answer": "8781 + 4738 = 13519"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SOIL = ELITE", "Answer": "4788 + 8753 = 13541"}
{"Question": "EDGE + IDEA = LABEL", "Answer": "8798 + 4783 = 13581"}
{"Question": "EDGE + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "8728 + 5786 = 14514"}
{"Question": "SELL + LEAD = SALES", "Answer": "1988 + 8903 = 10891"}
{"Question": "CALL + LAKE = CRACK", "Answer": "1988 + 8924 = 10912"}
{"Question": "BALL + LAST = STAFF", "Answer": "3988 + 8912 = 12900"}
{"Question": "GANG + PAGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8908 + 4983 = 13891"}
{"Question": "HALL + LATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6299 + 9217 = 15516"}
{"Question": "EVER + TREE = ENTRY", "Answer": "1712 + 9211 = 10923"}
{"Question": "EVER + TREE = ELECT", "Answer": "1417 + 8711 = 10128"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = TOOTH", "Answer": "5657 + 8755 = 14412"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "5658 + 4855 = 10513"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = ONCE", "Answer": "6960 + 1066 = 8026"}
{"Question": "EVER + TREE = VOTE", "Answer": "6860 + 2066 = 8926"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = NEWLY", "Answer": "6861 + 9166 = 16027"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = DRESS", "Answer": "6867 + 5766 = 12633"}
{"Question": "EVER + TREE = PHOTO", "Answer": "6568 + 3866 = 10434"}
{"Question": "EVER + FREE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8684 + 1488 = 10172"}
{"Question": "EVEN + KNEE = BREAK", "Answer": "8384 + 2488 = 10872"}
{"Question": "EVER + TREE = APART", "Answer": "8387 + 5788 = 14175"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TREE = APART", "Answer": "6769 + 5366 = 12135"}
{"Question": "EVER + FLEE = LEARN", "Answer": "7875 + 9177 = 17052"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FLEE = LEAST", "Answer": "7876 + 9177 = 17053"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = AWARD", "Answer": "6268 + 3886 = 10154"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = FIFTH", "Answer": "6268 + 5886 = 12154"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = UNIT", "Answer": "7274 + 1447 = 8721"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = CIVIL", "Answer": "7375 + 6557 = 13932"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEER = MEDIA", "Answer": "7275 + 8557 = 15832"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = METAL", "Answer": "7276 + 9667 = 16943"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = TREAT", "Answer": "8983 + 1338 = 10321"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DEEP = RAPID", "Answer": "8384 + 2448 = 10832"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEEN = HONOR", "Answer": "8384 + 5448 = 13832"}
{"Question": "THAT + DATA = PAPER", "Answer": "8648 + 5484 = 14132"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEEN = MONTH", "Answer": "8285 + 4558 = 12843"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = HONOR", "Answer": "8285 + 6558 = 14843"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = COLOR", "Answer": "8286 + 7668 = 15954"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEEN = FINAL", "Answer": "8087 + 2778 = 10865"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DEEP = TIRED", "Answer": "9294 + 3449 = 12743"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TENT = TITLE", "Answer": "8218 + 1921 = 10139"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "4514 + 1651 = 6165"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AREA = APART", "Answer": "8518 + 1651 = 10169"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = LARGE", "Answer": "1558 + 8711 = 10269"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = LATIN", "Answer": "1668 + 8711 = 10379"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = SPLIT", "Answer": "3556 + 6833 = 10389"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = WORKS", "Answer": "4338 + 8744 = 13082"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = DRAMA", "Answer": "4558 + 8644 = 13202"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MASS = LEGAL", "Answer": "5226 + 6855 = 12081"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MASS = USUAL", "Answer": "5779 + 9355 = 15134"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KISS = LEGAL", "Answer": "6225 + 5866 = 12091"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TENT = ACTOR", "Answer": "3763 + 6876 = 10639"}
{"Question": "FALL + LEAF = BASIS", "Answer": "6477 + 7846 = 14323"}
{"Question": "FALL + LEAF = PAPER", "Answer": "8677 + 7468 = 16145"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SPOT = PARTY", "Answer": "6877 + 7186 = 14063"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MISS = DRAMA", "Answer": "8554 + 4688 = 13242"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KILL = BASIS", "Answer": "8664 + 4588 = 13252"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MASS = MORAL", "Answer": "8771 + 1588 = 10359"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TENT = BELOW", "Answer": "6786 + 8578 = 15364"}
{"Question": "AREA + WEAR = ALLOW", "Answer": "1731 + 8317 = 10048"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAR = ADAPT", "Answer": "1741 + 8417 = 10158"}
{"Question": "AREA + GEAR = ANGRY", "Answer": "1541 + 9415 = 10956"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = EARN", "Answer": "1651 + 3516 = 5167"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = APART", "Answer": "1651 + 8516 = 10167"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = ROUND", "Answer": "1517 + 8751 = 10268"}
{"Question": "AREA + GEAR = ANGLE", "Answer": "1451 + 9514 = 10965"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = RACE", "Answer": "1561 + 3615 = 5176"}
{"Question": "AREA + DEAR = FADE", "Answer": "1561 + 7615 = 9176"}
{"Question": "AREA + YEAR = ANGRY", "Answer": "1761 + 8617 = 10378"}
{"Question": "RARE + GEAR = ROUGH", "Answer": "1715 + 8571 = 10286"}
{"Question": "AREA + DEAR = ASIDE", "Answer": "1671 + 8716 = 10387"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "4247 + 8724 = 12971"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = BLOOD", "Answer": "4643 + 7364 = 12007"}
{"Question": "RARE + NEAR = EVEN", "Answer": "5157 + 2715 = 7872"}
{"Question": "AREA + GEAR = RING", "Answer": "5815 + 3158 = 8973"}
{"Question": "RARE + WEAR = ALLOW", "Answer": "5159 + 4915 = 10074"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "5451 + 9145 = 14596"}
{"Question": "AREA + HEAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "5265 + 7652 = 12917"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FADE = AREA", "Answer": "5275 + 1752 = 7027"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = ROOF", "Answer": "6726 + 1267 = 7993"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAR = TERMS", "Answer": "6264 + 8426 = 14690"}
{"Question": "RARE + NEAR = FUNNY", "Answer": "6267 + 9726 = 15993"}
{"Question": "AREA + YEAR = REPLY", "Answer": "6136 + 7361 = 13497"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAR = DATA", "Answer": "6056 + 1560 = 7616"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAR = ASSET", "Answer": "7179 + 2917 = 10096"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = MEDIA", "Answer": "7275 + 8527 = 15802"}
{"Question": "RARE + GEAR = BEGIN", "Answer": "7276 + 9627 = 16903"}
{"Question": "AREA + HEAR = COACH", "Answer": "7247 + 9472 = 16719"}
{"Question": "RARE + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7571 + 8157 = 15728"}
{"Question": "RARE + NEAR = PANEL", "Answer": "7572 + 8257 = 15829"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "7187 + 9871 = 17058"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEAR = ADAPT", "Answer": "8189 + 7918 = 16107"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEAR = TOOTH", "Answer": "8287 + 1728 = 10015"}
{"Question": "AREA + FEAR = STAFF", "Answer": "8438 + 2384 = 10822"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "8438 + 6384 = 14822"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = BIBLE", "Answer": "8648 + 1486 = 10134"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAR = BLIND", "Answer": "8487 + 1748 = 10235"}
{"Question": "AREA + GEAR = GLOVE", "Answer": "8758 + 1587 = 10345"}
{"Question": "AREA + FEAR = CRAFT", "Answer": "8258 + 4582 = 12840"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = FENCE", "Answer": "8758 + 6587 = 15345"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "8582 + 7258 = 15840"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = DOZEN", "Answer": "8685 + 1568 = 10253"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAR = THEME", "Answer": "8978 + 1789 = 10767"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "8078 + 2780 = 10858"}
{"Question": "RARE + GEAR = LEGAL", "Answer": "9092 + 3209 = 12301"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAR = SALAD", "Answer": "9294 + 3429 = 12723"}
{"Question": "AREA + DEAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "9089 + 1890 = 10979"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAM = ADAPT", "Answer": "1921 + 8217 = 10138"}
{"Question": "AREA + DEAL = APPLY", "Answer": "1731 + 8314 = 10045"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FIVE = ERROR", "Answer": "1319 + 8731 = 10050"}
{"Question": "AREA + WEAK = ALLOW", "Answer": "1641 + 8417 = 10058"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LOVE = ERROR", "Answer": "1419 + 8641 = 10060"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAN = AWARE", "Answer": "1651 + 8514 = 10165"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAM = APART", "Answer": "1651 + 8517 = 10168"}
{"Question": "TREE + EARN = EVENT", "Answer": "8611 + 1567 = 10178"}
{"Question": "LOOK + YELL = LUCKY", "Answer": "1667 + 8911 = 10578"}
{"Question": "AREA + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "1371 + 8716 = 10087"}
{"Question": "SEED + KISS = SHAKE", "Answer": "1776 + 8511 = 10287"}
{"Question": "RARE + DOOR = AREA", "Answer": "2826 + 5442 = 8268"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TRIP = UPPER", "Answer": "2426 + 9842 = 12268"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SHOE = PHOTO", "Answer": "8622 + 2064 = 10686"}
{"Question": "NONE + IRON = RADIO", "Answer": "2624 + 8162 = 10786"}
{"Question": "NINE + SOON = ODDS", "Answer": "2123 + 5882 = 8005"}
{"Question": "EASE + USER = SURE", "Answer": "2682 + 5820 = 8502"}
{"Question": "HALL + LOAD = TOOTH", "Answer": "7922 + 2095 = 10017"}
{"Question": "THAT + RATE = PAPER", "Answer": "3923 + 8235 = 12158"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SHOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "7433 + 3041 = 10474"}
{"Question": "SEEM + KISS = MUSIC", "Answer": "3551 + 6833 = 10384"}
{"Question": "LESS + STEP = APPLE", "Answer": "8533 + 3752 = 12285"}
{"Question": "AREA + DEAL = SLIDE", "Answer": "3953 + 8532 = 12485"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "3583 + 9834 = 13417"}
{"Question": "LOOK + BALL = ORDER", "Answer": "4118 + 7944 = 12062"}
{"Question": "NINE + TWIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "4246 + 7924 = 12170"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIN = BEER", "Answer": "4348 + 2534 = 6882"}
{"Question": "NONE + IRON = HELLO", "Answer": "4642 + 7364 = 12006"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAN = TENT", "Answer": "4984 + 1842 = 6826"}
{"Question": "TENT + INTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "4584 + 7842 = 12426"}
{"Question": "NONE + IRON = FEWER", "Answer": "4842 + 7684 = 12526"}
{"Question": "TENT + INTO = HONOR", "Answer": "4984 + 7842 = 12826"}
{"Question": "PIPE + CHIP = SPEED", "Answer": "4842 + 9384 = 14226"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LIVE = UNTIL", "Answer": "5253 + 8725 = 13978"}
{"Question": "BALL + LEAD = SALES", "Answer": "9455 + 5046 = 14501"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAT = RATE", "Answer": "5865 + 2651 = 8516"}
{"Question": "THAT + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "5375 + 1752 = 7127"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SLOW = LABEL", "Answer": "9755 + 5176 = 14931"}
{"Question": "THAT + DATE = IDEA", "Answer": "5285 + 1853 = 7138"}
{"Question": "SEED + MASS = AIDE", "Answer": "5883 + 1755 = 7638"}
{"Question": "RARE + STAR = AREA", "Answer": "5853 + 2685 = 8538"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "5685 + 4853 = 10538"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "5685 + 7853 = 13538"}
{"Question": "SEED + MASS = ASIDE", "Answer": "5883 + 9155 = 15038"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FIVE = PROOF", "Answer": "6268 + 4726 = 10994"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIN = FIBER", "Answer": "6269 + 5826 = 12095"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TRIP = ENTER", "Answer": "6561 + 3756 = 10317"}
{"Question": "TALL + LEAN = ENTER", "Answer": "7566 + 6153 = 13719"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LADY = EAGER", "Answer": "6156 + 9562 = 15718"}
{"Question": "THAT + GATE = EAGER", "Answer": "6356 + 9561 = 15917"}
{"Question": "THAT + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "6876 + 3761 = 10637"}
{"Question": "NINE + MAIN = ARMED", "Answer": "6764 + 9176 = 15940"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SHOE = ASSET", "Answer": "9766 + 6873 = 16639"}
{"Question": "SEEK + MASS = ASIDE", "Answer": "6882 + 9166 = 16048"}
{"Question": "RARE + DOOR = BREAD", "Answer": "6463 + 9886 = 16349"}
{"Question": "SEED + BOSS = ERROR", "Answer": "7113 + 2977 = 10090"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SHIP = IRISH", "Answer": "7173 + 9017 = 16190"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SAVE = BASIS", "Answer": "7279 + 6327 = 13606"}
{"Question": "TENT + INTO = LOOSE", "Answer": "7327 + 9276 = 16603"}
{"Question": "EASE + USED = ASIDE", "Answer": "7137 + 6370 = 13507"}
{"Question": "NONE + IRON = EAGER", "Answer": "7471 + 2847 = 10318"}
{"Question": "SOON + MESS = LEVEL", "Answer": "7554 + 6377 = 13931"}
{"Question": "THAT + LATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "7157 + 9572 = 16729"}
{"Question": "KISS + SPIN = PINK", "Answer": "1677 + 7964 = 9641"}
{"Question": "NINE + THIN = EIGHT", "Answer": "7671 + 8367 = 16038"}
{"Question": "SEEM + KISS = MOVIE", "Answer": "7881 + 2577 = 10458"}
{"Question": "NINE + GAIN = PAPER", "Answer": "7876 + 4287 = 12163"}
{"Question": "MASS + STAR = TERMS", "Answer": "5877 + 7180 = 13057"}
{"Question": "NINE + JOIN = ORDER", "Answer": "7876 + 5187 = 13063"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SLIP = CLASS", "Answer": "7879 + 6487 = 14366"}
{"Question": "ONTO + STOP = POINT", "Answer": "7587 + 9871 = 17458"}
{"Question": "NINE + THIN = TOOTH", "Answer": "8289 + 1728 = 10017"}
{"Question": "THAT + DATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8528 + 4287 = 12815"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "8528 + 7280 = 15808"}
{"Question": "SEED + MASS = TASTE", "Answer": "8224 + 7588 = 15812"}
{"Question": "BOSS + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "4388 + 8931 = 13319"}
{"Question": "ONTO + STOP = APART", "Answer": "8738 + 6385 = 15123"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIN = ENTER", "Answer": "8381 + 9638 = 18019"}
{"Question": "NINE + SKIN = SALES", "Answer": "8483 + 1748 = 10231"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SLIP = LEVEL", "Answer": "8483 + 5148 = 13631"}
{"Question": "NINE + GAIN = LEVEL", "Answer": "8483 + 5248 = 13731"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LOVE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8489 + 7648 = 16137"}
{"Question": "PASS + SEAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1588 + 8654 = 10242"}
{"Question": "AREA + SEAT = GRASS", "Answer": "8258 + 4586 = 12844"}
{"Question": "LOOK + BILL = BASIS", "Answer": "8664 + 1588 = 10252"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SLIP = SHALL", "Answer": "8687 + 1568 = 10255"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LIVE = LUNCH", "Answer": "8684 + 1768 = 10452"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TRIP = TOWER", "Answer": "8786 + 1478 = 10264"}
{"Question": "PULL + LOUD = PRIOR", "Answer": "1788 + 8672 = 10460"}
{"Question": "EVEN + MOVE = MINOR", "Answer": "8784 + 1678 = 10462"}
{"Question": "SEED + MISS = MOVIE", "Answer": "8779 + 1688 = 10467"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIN = PAPER", "Answer": "8786 + 4378 = 13164"}
{"Question": "SEED + KISS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8779 + 4388 = 13167"}
{"Question": "NINE + GAIN = LEGAL", "Answer": "8783 + 4678 = 13461"}
{"Question": "EVER + FIVE = IRAQI", "Answer": "8783 + 5178 = 13961"}
{"Question": "EVER + SAVE = FRESH", "Answer": "8784 + 6078 = 14862"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LADY = CYCLE", "Answer": "8378 + 6785 = 15163"}
{"Question": "AREA + HEAD = DEATH", "Answer": "8078 + 9781 = 17859"}
{"Question": "BABY + GRAB = TREAT", "Answer": "9392 + 5439 = 14831"}
{"Question": "SEED + BOSS = LEVEL", "Answer": "9442 + 5399 = 14841"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = DOUBT", "Answer": "1581 + 8715 = 10296"}
{"Question": "TELL + LATE = FLAT", "Answer": "6422 + 2864 = 9286"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = AGAIN", "Answer": "2572 + 7625 = 10197"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALE = FINAL", "Answer": "7522 + 2975 = 10497"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = RATIO", "Answer": "3563 + 6835 = 10398"}
{"Question": "TELL + LATE = BLOOD", "Answer": "9533 + 3695 = 13228"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = CHEEK", "Answer": "4284 + 8942 = 13226"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = CATCH", "Answer": "4574 + 7845 = 12419"}
{"Question": "MESS + SAME = ADMIT", "Answer": "8644 + 4186 = 12830"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = EMPTY", "Answer": "5175 + 7851 = 13026"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = GIVEN", "Answer": "5385 + 8653 = 14038"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = EXTRA", "Answer": "6176 + 7861 = 14037"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = CLEAN", "Answer": "6286 + 8962 = 15248"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = PAPER", "Answer": "7257 + 5872 = 13129"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = READY", "Answer": "7697 + 9276 = 16973"}
{"Question": "TEST + SITE = PITCH", "Answer": "8278 + 7582 = 15860"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8358 + 5283 = 13641"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "8458 + 5384 = 13842"}
{"Question": "TELL + LATE = APPLY", "Answer": "9588 + 8195 = 17783"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = WOMAN", "Answer": "8648 + 4286 = 12934"}
{"Question": "TENT + NOTE = LATIN", "Answer": "8758 + 5087 = 13845"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALE = AWFUL", "Answer": "5788 + 8157 = 13945"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SELF = FLEE", "Answer": "8711 + 1089 = 9800"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = IDEA", "Answer": "1541 + 4613 = 6154"}
{"Question": "FILL + LEFT = ISSUE", "Answer": "8144 + 4086 = 12230"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = IRAQI", "Answer": "4684 + 8147 = 12831"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = IRISH", "Answer": "4984 + 8142 = 13126"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "5244 + 4951 = 10195"}
{"Question": "CELL + LACK = TABLE", "Answer": "9244 + 4398 = 13642"}
{"Question": "KICK + CAKE = PAPER", "Answer": "4784 + 8342 = 13126"}
{"Question": "ELSE + STEP = REPLY", "Answer": "4394 + 9842 = 14236"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = THESE", "Answer": "4684 + 8942 = 13626"}
{"Question": "TELL + LOTS = EXIST", "Answer": "7155 + 5872 = 13027"}
{"Question": "PIPE + EVEN = IMPLY", "Answer": "8185 + 5657 = 13842"}
{"Question": "EASE + STEP = APART", "Answer": "5185 + 8954 = 14139"}
{"Question": "TALL + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "7855 + 5371 = 13226"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALT = DELAY", "Answer": "8355 + 5487 = 13842"}
{"Question": "NONE + EVER = HELLO", "Answer": "9795 + 5652 = 15447"}
{"Question": "THAT + AUTO = COACH", "Answer": "5765 + 6852 = 12617"}
{"Question": "EASE + STEP = ADOPT", "Answer": "6176 + 7064 = 13240"}
{"Question": "MASS + SOME = ARMED", "Answer": "7166 + 6574 = 13740"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = IMAGE", "Answer": "6576 + 7169 = 13745"}
{"Question": "KICK + CAKE = IDEAL", "Answer": "6186 + 8567 = 14753"}
{"Question": "TALL + LOTS = ADAPT", "Answer": "8166 + 6982 = 15148"}
{"Question": "FALL + LEFT = TASTE", "Answer": "5266 + 6751 = 12017"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALT = WHEEL", "Answer": "8466 + 6982 = 15448"}
{"Question": "RARE + EVEN = AVOID", "Answer": "5157 + 7279 = 12436"}
{"Question": "NINE + EVER = VIRUS", "Answer": "6367 + 7175 = 13542"}
{"Question": "EASE + STEP = AGENT", "Answer": "7167 + 6578 = 13745"}
{"Question": "WELL + LAWN = ANGLE", "Answer": "9377 + 7196 = 16573"}
{"Question": "PIPE + EVEN = INNER", "Answer": "9197 + 7476 = 16673"}
{"Question": "KICK + CAKE = BASIS", "Answer": "7357 + 5279 = 12636"}
{"Question": "EASE + STEP = BASIS", "Answer": "7367 + 6279 = 13646"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = LEAST", "Answer": "7587 + 8276 = 15863"}
{"Question": "SELL + LIST = TASTE", "Answer": "4877 + 7541 = 12418"}
{"Question": "RARE + EVEN = AGENT", "Answer": "5158 + 8684 = 13842"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALT = METAL", "Answer": "4288 + 8346 = 12634"}
{"Question": "FALL + LIFE = SALES", "Answer": "4288 + 8543 = 12831"}
{"Question": "KICK + CAKE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8258 + 5483 = 13741"}
{"Question": "RARE + EVEN = BASIS", "Answer": "6468 + 8289 = 14757"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = MEDIA", "Answer": "8358 + 5487 = 13845"}
{"Question": "LESS + SALT = WASTE", "Answer": "6388 + 8465 = 14853"}
{"Question": "LOSS + SELF = REFER", "Answer": "6788 + 8563 = 15351"}
{"Question": "DEAD + AIDS = LEGAL", "Answer": "9459 + 5392 = 14851"}
{"Question": "EASE + TREE = EXTRA", "Answer": "1261 + 9711 = 10972"}
{"Question": "EASE + TREE = ASSET", "Answer": "3103 + 6933 = 10036"}
{"Question": "EASE + FLEE = USUAL", "Answer": "3523 + 8633 = 12156"}
{"Question": "EASE + TREE = MOTOR", "Answer": "6576 + 8266 = 14842"}
{"Question": "EASE + TREE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8348 + 1788 = 10136"}
{"Question": "EDGE + TREE = GREAT", "Answer": "8318 + 6488 = 14806"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TREE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8638 + 1488 = 10126"}
{"Question": "EASE + FREE = FINAL", "Answer": "8458 + 1788 = 10246"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = APPLE", "Answer": "1341 + 8713 = 10054"}
{"Question": "ONTO + UPON = OCCUR", "Answer": "1471 + 8614 = 10085"}
{"Question": "PIPE + HELP = PAPER", "Answer": "1714 + 8431 = 10145"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = APART", "Answer": "1541 + 8615 = 10156"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = ABUSE", "Answer": "1671 + 8916 = 10587"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = TEST", "Answer": "1751 + 6817 = 8568"}
{"Question": "TENT + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1731 + 8417 = 10148"}
{"Question": "NINE + LEAN = NOVEL", "Answer": "1517 + 8761 = 10278"}
{"Question": "LESS + SIDE = FIELD", "Answer": "8422 + 2064 = 10486"}
{"Question": "THAT + MYTH = PARTY", "Answer": "2602 + 7826 = 10428"}
{"Question": "LESS + SHOE = WHEEL", "Answer": "8622 + 2046 = 10668"}
{"Question": "ONTO + IRON = COLOR", "Answer": "2602 + 9826 = 12428"}
{"Question": "TENT + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "2752 + 6927 = 9679"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "3283 + 9132 = 12415"}
{"Question": "ONTO + IRON = ENTER", "Answer": "3283 + 9532 = 12815"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = CHART", "Answer": "3523 + 6835 = 10358"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = TOSS", "Answer": "3873 + 1538 = 5411"}
{"Question": "TEST + NOTE = SOON", "Answer": "3963 + 2039 = 6002"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = TREND", "Answer": "4234 + 8142 = 12376"}
{"Question": "TENT + DATE = AREA", "Answer": "4394 + 2743 = 7137"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CODE = ONION", "Answer": "4864 + 7148 = 12012"}
{"Question": "TENT + GATE = ANGER", "Answer": "4834 + 9148 = 13982"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ONCE = NEWLY", "Answer": "5851 + 9175 = 15026"}
{"Question": "EVER + TRUE = FRUIT", "Answer": "5652 + 7295 = 12947"}
{"Question": "BELL + LATE = ASSET", "Answer": "9255 + 5172 = 14427"}
{"Question": "ONTO + IRON = PAINT", "Answer": "5275 + 9652 = 14927"}
{"Question": "TENT + VOTE = OVEN", "Answer": "5385 + 1753 = 7138"}
{"Question": "ONTO + IRON = COUNT", "Answer": "5385 + 9653 = 15038"}
{"Question": "KNEE + EARN = BREAK", "Answer": "4955 + 5609 = 10564"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = RANGE", "Answer": "6176 + 9861 = 16037"}
{"Question": "MESS + SHOE = HELLO", "Answer": "7366 + 6193 = 13559"}
{"Question": "TENT + VOTE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6586 + 9365 = 15951"}
{"Question": "TENT + VOTE = ONION", "Answer": "6846 + 7168 = 14014"}
{"Question": "TENT + RATE = ANGER", "Answer": "6926 + 5169 = 12095"}
{"Question": "YELL + LAKE = ESSAY", "Answer": "8177 + 7361 = 15538"}
{"Question": "TENT + BITE = INNER", "Answer": "7357 + 8173 = 15530"}
{"Question": "TEST + DATA = SHADE", "Answer": "7017 + 9373 = 16390"}
{"Question": "NINE + LEAN = BALL", "Answer": "7874 + 1437 = 9311"}
{"Question": "LESS + SHOE = HEEL", "Answer": "1477 + 7964 = 9441"}
{"Question": "NINE + LEAN = SHALL", "Answer": "7875 + 2547 = 10422"}
{"Question": "EASE + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "7537 + 4875 = 12412"}
{"Question": "TENT + DATA = ENTER", "Answer": "7137 + 6575 = 13712"}
{"Question": "TENT + RATE = LATER", "Answer": "7687 + 3076 = 10763"}
{"Question": "TENT + RATE = PAPER", "Answer": "7807 + 5378 = 13185"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = TABLE", "Answer": "7857 + 9178 = 17035"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FUEL = SHELF", "Answer": "7917 + 6879 = 14796"}
{"Question": "TEST + DATE = ASSET", "Answer": "8028 + 4180 = 12208"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEAN = HONOR", "Answer": "8582 + 7268 = 15850"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEAN = LEVEL", "Answer": "8283 + 5348 = 13631"}
{"Question": "CELL + LAKE = CHECK", "Answer": "1488 + 8924 = 10412"}
{"Question": "TEST + DATE = SALAD", "Answer": "8418 + 2084 = 10502"}
{"Question": "TENT + LATE = PANEL", "Answer": "8458 + 2084 = 10542"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = VISIT", "Answer": "8468 + 7284 = 15752"}
{"Question": "NINE + MEAN = MUSIC", "Answer": "8685 + 1578 = 10263"}
{"Question": "LESS + SITE = VISIT", "Answer": "4588 + 8235 = 12823"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8538 + 7285 = 15823"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = CRAFT", "Answer": "8508 + 7385 = 15893"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = SCOPE", "Answer": "8648 + 1586 = 10234"}
{"Question": "EVER + TRUE = THIRD", "Answer": "8586 + 1678 = 10264"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HIDE = COACH", "Answer": "8628 + 4586 = 13214"}
{"Question": "EVER + TRUE = ONION", "Answer": "8386 + 5628 = 14014"}
{"Question": "ONTO + UPON = ENTER", "Answer": "8628 + 7586 = 16214"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FUEL = FOCUS", "Answer": "8758 + 1487 = 10245"}
{"Question": "MESS + SHOE = MONTH", "Answer": "1788 + 8507 = 10295"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = SHOOT", "Answer": "8748 + 1587 = 10335"}
{"Question": "TENT + CITE = CLOCK", "Answer": "8728 + 1687 = 10415"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ONCE = OUGHT", "Answer": "8687 + 1738 = 10425"}
{"Question": "EVER + TRUE = TOUCH", "Answer": "8687 + 1748 = 10435"}
{"Question": "ONTO + IRON = CROSS", "Answer": "8768 + 2087 = 10855"}
{"Question": "AREA + STAR = CLASS", "Answer": "8768 + 5087 = 13855"}
{"Question": "TEST + LATE = USUAL", "Answer": "8748 + 5387 = 14135"}
{"Question": "HELL + LATE = CATCH", "Answer": "5788 + 8427 = 14215"}
{"Question": "TEXT + DATA = SENSE", "Answer": "8528 + 6787 = 15315"}
{"Question": "TELL + LOSE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1988 + 8029 = 10017"}
{"Question": "TEST + DATA = SPEED", "Answer": "8018 + 7989 = 16007"}
{"Question": "AREA + ELSE = IDEAL", "Answer": "7327 + 2952 = 10279"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GANG = SPEED", "Answer": "7927 + 2852 = 10779"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NAME = AMONG", "Answer": "4948 + 8134 = 13082"}
{"Question": "NONE + EARN = LOCAL", "Answer": "4247 + 7834 = 12081"}
{"Question": "AREA + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "8948 + 4234 = 13182"}
{"Question": "NONE + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "5154 + 4895 = 10049"}
{"Question": "PASS + STOP = TODAY", "Answer": "7955 + 5137 = 13092"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NAME = ALONG", "Answer": "5958 + 8125 = 14083"}
{"Question": "NONE + EARN = ACTOR", "Answer": "5958 + 8135 = 14093"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAT = CABIN", "Answer": "7257 + 5835 = 13092"}
{"Question": "TALL + LIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7855 + 5317 = 13172"}
{"Question": "MESS + SWIM = BIBLE", "Answer": "8355 + 5748 = 14103"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "5457 + 7935 = 13392"}
{"Question": "NONE + EARN = MORAL", "Answer": "5458 + 8605 = 14063"}
{"Question": "THAT + AREA = WHERE", "Answer": "8458 + 5935 = 14393"}
{"Question": "THAT + AREA = RATE", "Answer": "2652 + 5875 = 8527"}
{"Question": "EVER + RACE = OCEAN", "Answer": "5657 + 7935 = 13592"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NAME = CREAM", "Answer": "5658 + 8935 = 14593"}
{"Question": "NINE + EARN = BREAD", "Answer": "5857 + 7935 = 13792"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SALT = LOCAL", "Answer": "5266 + 6815 = 12081"}
{"Question": "NINE + EARN = FRUIT", "Answer": "6268 + 8756 = 15024"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TEST = ASIAN", "Answer": "7367 + 6846 = 14213"}
{"Question": "NINE + EARN = RADIO", "Answer": "6867 + 7416 = 14283"}
{"Question": "EVEN + NOSE = SOUND", "Answer": "6768 + 8516 = 15284"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GANG = ASIAN", "Answer": "6876 + 7137 = 14013"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GANG = INDEX", "Answer": "6176 + 7847 = 14023"}
{"Question": "PASS + SOUP = RURAL", "Answer": "6277 + 7846 = 14123"}
{"Question": "LESS + SOIL = VIDEO", "Answer": "8477 + 7568 = 16045"}
{"Question": "NINE + EARN = TIRED", "Answer": "7678 + 8407 = 16085"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAT = CHAIN", "Answer": "8578 + 7627 = 16205"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SHIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1088 + 8931 = 10019"}
{"Question": "PASS + STEP = TREAT", "Answer": "3988 + 8103 = 12091"}
{"Question": "EVER + RACE = RURAL", "Answer": "8781 + 1358 = 10139"}
{"Question": "PASS + SLIP = USUAL", "Answer": "9388 + 8749 = 18137"}
{"Question": "EVER + RATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8785 + 5428 = 14213"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TEST = LEMON", "Answer": "6486 + 8578 = 15064"}
{"Question": "THAT + AREA = IRISH", "Answer": "7587 + 8608 = 16195"}
{"Question": "NONE + EARN = RADIO", "Answer": "8587 + 7618 = 16205"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SHUT = COUCH", "Answer": "7688 + 8527 = 16215"}
{"Question": "HELL + LOSS = SHOE", "Answer": "2044 + 4166 = 6210"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SHOT = HERE", "Answer": "4584 + 1648 = 6232"}
{"Question": "EVER + CARE = VIRUS", "Answer": "5158 + 7685 = 12843"}
{"Question": "NINE + OVEN = AVOID", "Answer": "5458 + 7285 = 12743"}
{"Question": "NONE + THEN = FIFTH", "Answer": "5758 + 4385 = 10143"}
{"Question": "NINE + OPEN = PILOT", "Answer": "6067 + 4176 = 10243"}
{"Question": "MALL + LESS = ARMED", "Answer": "7166 + 6588 = 13754"}
{"Question": "EVER + FIRE = VIRUS", "Answer": "6167 + 9576 = 15743"}
{"Question": "EVER + CARE = TREAT", "Answer": "6365 + 9256 = 15621"}
{"Question": "TALL + LESS = EXTRA", "Answer": "5377 + 7166 = 12543"}
{"Question": "NINE + OPEN = PIANO", "Answer": "7379 + 6197 = 13576"}
{"Question": "ONTO + PLOT = LEARN", "Answer": "7257 + 9175 = 16432"}
{"Question": "NINE + THEN = FIFTY", "Answer": "7276 + 4867 = 12143"}
{"Question": "PASS + SELL = HAPPY", "Answer": "6377 + 7288 = 13665"}
{"Question": "PIPE + STEP = CHEST", "Answer": "7278 + 6587 = 13865"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOTS = ISSUE", "Answer": "7367 + 9276 = 16643"}
{"Question": "EVER + CARE = BREAD", "Answer": "7276 + 9467 = 16743"}
{"Question": "RARE + USER = SHRUG", "Answer": "8685 + 4158 = 12843"}
{"Question": "NINE + THEN = HONOR", "Answer": "8684 + 5148 = 13832"}
{"Question": "BALL + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1388 + 8799 = 10187"}
{"Question": "EVER + HIRE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8786 + 4368 = 13154"}
{"Question": "FILL + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "4388 + 8799 = 13187"}
{"Question": "NONE + THEN = MONTH", "Answer": "8386 + 5468 = 13854"}
{"Question": "NINE + THEN = TOUCH", "Answer": "8786 + 1468 = 10254"}
{"Question": "PIPE + STEP = FIFTH", "Answer": "8685 + 7458 = 16143"}
{"Question": "MISS + SELL = MOVIE", "Answer": "1688 + 8577 = 10265"}
{"Question": "NINE + OPEN = RIVER", "Answer": "9492 + 5329 = 14821"}
{"Question": "AREA + THAN = APART", "Answer": "1541 + 8617 = 10158"}
{"Question": "TENT + LOTS = TITLE", "Answer": "1571 + 8614 = 10185"}
{"Question": "EASE + THEM = ASSET", "Answer": "2102 + 7925 = 10027"}
{"Question": "CELL + LUNG = UNCLE", "Answer": "8722 + 2105 = 10827"}
{"Question": "ARAB + IDEA = RARE", "Answer": "2925 + 6372 = 9297"}
{"Question": "NINE + WARN = AREA", "Answer": "2625 + 4732 = 7357"}
{"Question": "EVEN + GAME = AMONG", "Answer": "3935 + 8123 = 12058"}
{"Question": "LESS + SKIN = KNIFE", "Answer": "9533 + 3172 = 12705"}
{"Question": "LESS + SNAP = ASSET", "Answer": "9533 + 3817 = 13350"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SELF = ELITE", "Answer": "8944 + 4137 = 13081"}
{"Question": "BILL + LOAD = RADIO", "Answer": "7644 + 4925 = 12569"}
{"Question": "PIPE + CROP = UPPER", "Answer": "4742 + 9684 = 14426"}
{"Question": "GANG + HUGE = UNION", "Answer": "5925 + 6157 = 12082"}
{"Question": "FULL + LONG = UNION", "Answer": "7155 + 5938 = 13093"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LEAF = OFFER", "Answer": "9155 + 5274 = 14429"}
{"Question": "NINE + BURN = UNDER", "Answer": "5852 + 9175 = 15027"}
{"Question": "KISS + SHOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "7655 + 5294 = 12949"}
{"Question": "NINE + THAN = DEATH", "Answer": "5453 + 7825 = 13278"}
{"Question": "EVER + SHOE = HERO", "Answer": "5654 + 2895 = 8549"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BITE = VISIT", "Answer": "6167 + 4036 = 10203"}
{"Question": "EVEN + TIME = VISIT", "Answer": "6168 + 4036 = 10204"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LIFE = OFFER", "Answer": "3166 + 6907 = 10073"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SPIN = POINT", "Answer": "9566 + 6173 = 15739"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LEFT = OFFER", "Answer": "5177 + 7028 = 12205"}
{"Question": "NONE + SPIN = PRESS", "Answer": "7476 + 3157 = 10633"}
{"Question": "EVER + CODE = ONION", "Answer": "7875 + 4137 = 12012"}
{"Question": "EASE + OPEN = PRIOR", "Answer": "7867 + 4175 = 12042"}
{"Question": "EVER + BONE = ONION", "Answer": "7876 + 5137 = 13013"}
{"Question": "EVER + HUGE = UNION", "Answer": "7876 + 5147 = 13023"}
{"Question": "LESS + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "6577 + 7138 = 13715"}
{"Question": "ELSE + IDEA = LEGAL", "Answer": "7167 + 9874 = 17041"}
{"Question": "NONE + TURN = MOTOR", "Answer": "7378 + 6257 = 13635"}
{"Question": "EASE + OPEN = SPEND", "Answer": "7217 + 8579 = 15796"}
{"Question": "CELL + LAST = SLICE", "Answer": "9277 + 7815 = 17092"}
{"Question": "ELSE + IDEA = USUAL", "Answer": "7507 + 2678 = 10185"}
{"Question": "KISS + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6577 + 7841 = 14418"}
{"Question": "ROLL + LACK = COLOR", "Answer": "2088 + 8714 = 10802"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ITEM = SMELL", "Answer": "8018 + 4782 = 12800"}
{"Question": "ELSE + CHEF = SHELL", "Answer": "8018 + 9782 = 17800"}
{"Question": "BELL + LAST = SALES", "Answer": "9088 + 8713 = 17801"}
{"Question": "ONTO + GROW = WRONG", "Answer": "8028 + 9781 = 17809"}
{"Question": "TOSS + SLIP = ELITE", "Answer": "6288 + 8473 = 14761"}
{"Question": "TEST + INTO = ISSUE", "Answer": "8308 + 1785 = 10093"}
{"Question": "BELL + LACK = BIBLE", "Answer": "1388 + 8795 = 10183"}
{"Question": "FLEE + EACH = CIVIL", "Answer": "2588 + 8317 = 10905"}
{"Question": "TENT + AUTO = AGREE", "Answer": "8458 + 1786 = 10244"}
{"Question": "EDGE + STEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "8408 + 5789 = 14197"}
{"Question": "TENT + AUTO = SENSE", "Answer": "8428 + 5786 = 14214"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BIKE = BASIS", "Answer": "8584 + 1678 = 10262"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FATE = FLOAT", "Answer": "8589 + 1678 = 10267"}
{"Question": "NONE + PLAN = PRIOR", "Answer": "8582 + 1768 = 10350"}
{"Question": "KICK + TAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "8768 + 1583 = 10351"}
{"Question": "BABY + CLUB = CHEAP", "Answer": "8584 + 1768 = 10352"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = EDGE", "Answer": "1713 + 1330 = 3043"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PEER = HERE", "Answer": "2928 + 2880 = 5808"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEED = ONTO", "Answer": "3736 + 3661 = 7397"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = HERE", "Answer": "3938 + 3880 = 7818"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PEER = CARRY", "Answer": "5653 + 5339 = 10992"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = COLOR", "Answer": "5254 + 5449 = 10703"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = FENCE", "Answer": "6462 + 6220 = 12682"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PEER = REPLY", "Answer": "6462 + 6221 = 12683"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = MEDIA", "Answer": "6963 + 6332 = 13295"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = CIVIL", "Answer": "6265 + 6559 = 12824"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = SENSE", "Answer": "7274 + 7440 = 14714"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PEER = SENSE", "Answer": "7374 + 7440 = 14814"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = AGAIN", "Answer": "8486 + 8662 = 17148"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = ERROR", "Answer": "9691 + 9117 = 18808"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEED = OTHER", "Answer": "9193 + 9337 = 18530"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEED = MODEL", "Answer": "9096 + 9667 = 18763"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = IDEA", "Answer": "1315 + 1538 = 2853"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = ALLY", "Answer": "2423 + 2347 = 4770"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = DATA", "Answer": "2729 + 2978 = 5707"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = FADE", "Answer": "2829 + 2980 = 5809"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = BILL", "Answer": "3830 + 3081 = 6911"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = DATA", "Answer": "3639 + 3967 = 7606"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = BAKE", "Answer": "3839 + 3980 = 7819"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = FLOOR", "Answer": "5256 + 5629 = 10885"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = ELECT", "Answer": "6961 + 6193 = 13154"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = SENSE", "Answer": "6562 + 6250 = 12812"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = LEVEL", "Answer": "6562 + 6259 = 12821"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = LARGE", "Answer": "6264 + 6420 = 12684"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = LABOR", "Answer": "6265 + 6521 = 12786"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = BLOOD", "Answer": "6465 + 6543 = 13008"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = APPLY", "Answer": "7173 + 7319 = 14492"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = TASTE", "Answer": "7473 + 7340 = 14813"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = TERMS", "Answer": "7274 + 7429 = 14703"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = FEWER", "Answer": "7875 + 7582 = 15457"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = AFTER", "Answer": "7179 + 7918 = 15097"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = EARLY", "Answer": "8681 + 8164 = 16845"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = LABEL", "Answer": "8786 + 8675 = 17461"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = HELLO", "Answer": "8487 + 8742 = 17229"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = ADAPT", "Answer": "8189 + 8917 = 17106"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = ASIAN", "Answer": "9193 + 9317 = 18510"}
{"Question": "RARE + READ = TODAY", "Answer": "9096 + 9607 = 18703"}
{"Question": "RARE + REAL = APPLE", "Answer": "9196 + 9610 = 18806"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = BEER", "Answer": "2825 + 2513 = 5338"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEWS = LESS", "Answer": "3930 + 3081 = 7011"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEXT = TEST", "Answer": "3930 + 3087 = 7017"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEXT = ONTO", "Answer": "3735 + 3592 = 7327"}
{"Question": "RARE + REST = STAR", "Answer": "4345 + 4589 = 8934"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = EAGER", "Answer": "5051 + 5164 = 10215"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = CLEAN", "Answer": "5452 + 5206 = 10658"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = SALAD", "Answer": "5053 + 5349 = 10402"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = ALTER", "Answer": "5156 + 5609 = 10765"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = BELOW", "Answer": "6761 + 6192 = 12953"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = SENSE", "Answer": "6362 + 6250 = 12612"}
{"Question": "RARE + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "6462 + 6231 = 12693"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "6562 + 6284 = 12846"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = BEGIN", "Answer": "6562 + 6294 = 12856"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = SALES", "Answer": "6367 + 6704 = 13071"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEAR = ORDER", "Answer": "7170 + 7034 = 14204"}
{"Question": "NONE + NECK = ERROR", "Answer": "7271 + 7153 = 14424"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = COLOR", "Answer": "7273 + 7369 = 14642"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = SEVEN", "Answer": "7475 + 7582 = 15057"}
{"Question": "RARE + REST = METER", "Answer": "7675 + 7582 = 15257"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEXT = OTHER", "Answer": "7178 + 7804 = 14982"}
{"Question": "NONE + NEXT = OFTEN", "Answer": "7178 + 7809 = 14987"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7278 + 7810 = 15088"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = CABIN", "Answer": "7378 + 7859 = 15237"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "7379 + 7915 = 15294"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = LABEL", "Answer": "7579 + 7912 = 15491"}
{"Question": "RARE + RELY = LATER", "Answer": "7579 + 7918 = 15497"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = RADIO", "Answer": "8482 + 8261 = 16743"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PEAK = RAPID", "Answer": "8483 + 8362 = 16845"}
{"Question": "NONE + NECK = OCCUR", "Answer": "8184 + 8469 = 16653"}
{"Question": "RARE + REST = WASTE", "Answer": "8784 + 8420 = 17204"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEWS = FEWER", "Answer": "8086 + 8679 = 16765"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "8586 + 8627 = 17213"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = RELAX", "Answer": "8187 + 8796 = 16983"}
{"Question": "NINE + NEXT = UNTIL", "Answer": "9794 + 9482 = 19276"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = SHELL", "Answer": "9096 + 9637 = 18733"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ABLE = HAPPY", "Answer": "9796 + 9652 = 19448"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = ODDS", "Answer": "3448 + 6434 = 9882"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = JUDGE", "Answer": "3550 + 8535 = 12085"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = TIGHT", "Answer": "6883 + 7868 = 14751"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = IMAGE", "Answer": "7220 + 9272 = 16492"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7554 + 6575 = 14129"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = STATE", "Answer": "8660 + 5686 = 14346"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = ERROR", "Answer": "9112 + 4191 = 13303"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = FEWER", "Answer": "9228 + 3292 = 12520"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = ASSET", "Answer": "9228 + 6292 = 15520"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = GHOST", "Answer": "9335 + 1393 = 10728"}
{"Question": "NEED + GENE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9338 + 4393 = 13731"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = TIGHT", "Answer": "8616 + 1655 = 10271"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = TODAY", "Answer": "8919 + 1977 = 10896"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = CROSS", "Answer": "7434 + 3488 = 10922"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = EVENT", "Answer": "6535 + 3588 = 10123"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = METER", "Answer": "9252 + 5288 = 14540"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = LEAD", "Answer": "1464 + 6477 = 7941"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = FLAT", "Answer": "1272 + 7255 = 8527"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = BREAD", "Answer": "4676 + 7688 = 12364"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = BLOOD", "Answer": "9282 + 8277 = 17559"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALL = CABLE", "Answer": "3292 + 9288 = 12580"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = THIRD", "Answer": "9212 + 1247 = 10459"}
{"Question": "DATA + FADE = DRESS", "Answer": "1252 + 9214 = 10466"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAKE = TIRED", "Answer": "9212 + 1267 = 10479"}
{"Question": "BABY + DATA = BREAD", "Answer": "1415 + 9434 = 10849"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "8717 + 1754 = 10471"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = TRUTH", "Answer": "8717 + 1796 = 10513"}
{"Question": "HERE + REST = EARTH", "Answer": "8121 + 2157 = 10278"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATA = MOTOR", "Answer": "2329 + 8373 = 10702"}
{"Question": "HERE + READ = AREA", "Answer": "5131 + 3187 = 8318"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAKE = NAKED", "Answer": "9232 + 3247 = 12479"}
{"Question": "HERE + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "7434 + 3469 = 10903"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATA = GREAT", "Answer": "3836 + 9848 = 13684"}
{"Question": "DATA + TANK = ASIAN", "Answer": "8141 + 4176 = 12317"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "8242 + 4215 = 12457"}
{"Question": "HERE + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "8242 + 4231 = 12473"}
{"Question": "DATA + TANK = KNEE", "Answer": "5343 + 4379 = 9722"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "8343 + 4372 = 12715"}
{"Question": "DATA + TANK = NAKED", "Answer": "9343 + 4316 = 13659"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALE = VITAL", "Answer": "8747 + 4725 = 13472"}
{"Question": "HERE + READ = ORDER", "Answer": "9848 + 4836 = 14684"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATA = LABEL", "Answer": "5259 + 7232 = 12491"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEWS = FEWER", "Answer": "8353 + 5379 = 13732"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALE = LEAD", "Answer": "3454 + 5489 = 8943"}
{"Question": "DATA + LADY = CIVIL", "Answer": "5696 + 8652 = 14348"}
{"Question": "DATA + FADE = TREAT", "Answer": "5717 + 6754 = 12471"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATA = TREAT", "Answer": "5754 + 9717 = 15471"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATA = AHEAD", "Answer": "6163 + 4151 = 10314"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAKE = ELECT", "Answer": "3565 + 6581 = 10146"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "7565 + 6541 = 14106"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEAR = SERVE", "Answer": "8565 + 6530 = 15095"}
{"Question": "HERE + REAL = SALES", "Answer": "3767 + 6704 = 10471"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEWS = SWING", "Answer": "3272 + 7201 = 10473"}
{"Question": "HERE + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "6575 + 7582 = 14157"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "4676 + 7630 = 12306"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEWS = SEVEN", "Answer": "8676 + 7691 = 16367"}
{"Question": "BABY + DATA = SALAD", "Answer": "7672 + 8696 = 16368"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "4979 + 7912 = 12891"}
{"Question": "GENE + NECK = FEWER", "Answer": "5383 + 8349 = 13732"}
{"Question": "DATA + TALK = LEVEL", "Answer": "2484 + 8417 = 10901"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAKE = PAPER", "Answer": "6585 + 8542 = 15127"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "7585 + 8506 = 16091"}
{"Question": "HERE + REST = FIFTH", "Answer": "7585 + 8542 = 16127"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "7585 + 8564 = 16149"}
{"Question": "DATA + TASK = USUAL", "Answer": "7585 + 8569 = 16154"}
{"Question": "DATA + LADY = LEGAL", "Answer": "8676 + 1685 = 10361"}
{"Question": "HERE + RELY = HOTEL", "Answer": "1787 + 8792 = 10579"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = DEPTH", "Answer": "1787 + 8796 = 10583"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = LIGHT", "Answer": "3787 + 8721 = 12508"}
{"Question": "HERE + READ = CATCH", "Answer": "3787 + 8726 = 12513"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = DELAY", "Answer": "1292 + 9235 = 10527"}
{"Question": "GENE + NEAR = GUARD", "Answer": "1292 + 9254 = 10546"}
{"Question": "BABY + DATA = TASTE", "Answer": "9298 + 3212 = 12510"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAPE = HAPPY", "Answer": "3292 + 9258 = 12550"}
{"Question": "BABY + DATA = TOOTH", "Answer": "9298 + 6212 = 15510"}
{"Question": "DATA + TAIL = FLOAT", "Answer": "8292 + 9237 = 17529"}
{"Question": "HERE + READ = GHOST", "Answer": "7696 + 9652 = 17348"}
{"Question": "HERE + READ = WHICH", "Answer": "8696 + 9652 = 18348"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = SEEM", "Answer": "1012 + 4212 = 5224"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = ARMY", "Answer": "1516 + 3616 = 5132"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = AREA", "Answer": "2824 + 5424 = 8248"}
{"Question": "NONE + GENE = LEMON", "Answer": "4842 + 7242 = 12084"}
{"Question": "NONE + GENE = ERROR", "Answer": "5051 + 7151 = 12202"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = FIGHT", "Answer": "5254 + 7454 = 12708"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = HERE", "Answer": "6960 + 1060 = 8020"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = CIVIL", "Answer": "6365 + 7565 = 13930"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = SHOE", "Answer": "7170 + 2070 = 9240"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7471 + 9171 = 16642"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = ENJOY", "Answer": "7871 + 9171 = 17042"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = RANGE", "Answer": "8780 + 6080 = 14860"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = ENEMY", "Answer": "8981 + 6181 = 15162"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = GUESS", "Answer": "8983 + 1383 = 10366"}
{"Question": "NONE + GENE = GRAIN", "Answer": "8784 + 1484 = 10268"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "8285 + 7585 = 15870"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = LIMIT", "Answer": "8385 + 9585 = 17970"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = HUMAN", "Answer": "8786 + 1686 = 10472"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = HONEY", "Answer": "8587 + 1787 = 10374"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = GHOST", "Answer": "9392 + 1292 = 10684"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = WHICH", "Answer": "9792 + 4292 = 14084"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = GLASS", "Answer": "9294 + 1494 = 10788"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = PIANO", "Answer": "9295 + 3595 = 12890"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERE = CARRY", "Answer": "9395 + 4595 = 13990"}
{"Question": "NINE + GENE = ALONG", "Answer": "9097 + 4797 = 13894"}
{"Question": "RARE + MERE = MARRY", "Answer": "9098 + 1898 = 10996"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = CARE", "Answer": "1513 + 8318 = 9831"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = ALLOW", "Answer": "1418 + 8614 = 10032"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "1618 + 8416 = 10034"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = ASSET", "Answer": "1718 + 8317 = 10035"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = ALBUM", "Answer": "1719 + 9217 = 10936"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = INTO", "Answer": "1219 + 3913 = 5132"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = INNER", "Answer": "2725 + 9529 = 12254"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = IRISH", "Answer": "3238 + 8932 = 12170"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = MEDIA", "Answer": "3439 + 9234 = 12673"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = RACE", "Answer": "3935 + 5439 = 9374"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "4842 + 9249 = 14091"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = CYCLE", "Answer": "4845 + 5348 = 10193"}
{"Question": "NINE + TENT = EAGER", "Answer": "5651 + 9159 = 14810"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "5459 + 9054 = 14513"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = SENSE", "Answer": "5657 + 7356 = 13013"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = ONION", "Answer": "5658 + 8356 = 14014"}
{"Question": "NINE + TENT = BEAT", "Answer": "6960 + 1061 = 8021"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = OFTEN", "Answer": "6162 + 4264 = 10426"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = OFFER", "Answer": "6163 + 9369 = 15532"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "6369 + 9263 = 15632"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = SEVEN", "Answer": "6567 + 7365 = 13932"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = GENE", "Answer": "6961 + 1069 = 8030"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = DEEP", "Answer": "6961 + 1369 = 8330"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = DATA", "Answer": "7170 + 2072 = 9242"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = MOTOR", "Answer": "7572 + 8278 = 15850"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "7473 + 3174 = 10647"}
{"Question": "NINE + TENT = METER", "Answer": "7275 + 8578 = 15853"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = OWNER", "Answer": "7175 + 9579 = 16754"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = GRASS", "Answer": "7276 + 9679 = 16955"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = PRIOR", "Answer": "7578 + 2872 = 10450"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = UNION", "Answer": "7578 + 9879 = 17457"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = ALLOW", "Answer": "8782 + 1281 = 10063"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = SALES", "Answer": "8289 + 9782 = 18071"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = ADAPT", "Answer": "8783 + 1381 = 10164"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "8385 + 5483 = 13868"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = MONTH", "Answer": "8483 + 6386 = 14869"}
{"Question": "NINE + TENT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8583 + 6386 = 14969"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = CHEAP", "Answer": "8483 + 7387 = 15870"}
{"Question": "NINE + TENT = BIRTH", "Answer": "8583 + 7387 = 15970"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = APART", "Answer": "8486 + 1681 = 10167"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = ANGRY", "Answer": "8586 + 1681 = 10267"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = APPLE", "Answer": "8287 + 1781 = 10068"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = ABOVE", "Answer": "8687 + 1781 = 10468"}
{"Question": "NONE + TENT = HELLO", "Answer": "9592 + 3293 = 12885"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = CHASE", "Answer": "9294 + 4692 = 13986"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = FRAME", "Answer": "9094 + 5495 = 14589"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAR = ESSAY", "Answer": "9598 + 8195 = 17793"}
{"Question": "EVER + AREA = GREEN", "Answer": "9296 + 7697 = 16993"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "1216 + 8912 = 10128"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = APART", "Answer": "1217 + 8912 = 10129"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "1314 + 8713 = 10027"}
{"Question": "ARAB + WEAR = ALLOW", "Answer": "1315 + 8713 = 10028"}
{"Question": "RARE + VERY = RIVER", "Answer": "1613 + 9318 = 10931"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TEAR = ADAPT", "Answer": "1513 + 8615 = 10128"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEND = ONTO", "Answer": "1516 + 3619 = 5135"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GEAR = ANGLE", "Answer": "1715 + 9217 = 10932"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEND = VIDEO", "Answer": "2425 + 8529 = 10954"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "2823 + 9528 = 12351"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = RARE", "Answer": "3631 + 2736 = 6367"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERO = AREA", "Answer": "3637 + 2739 = 6376"}
{"Question": "RARE + TERM = LATER", "Answer": "3237 + 9736 = 12973"}
{"Question": "RARE + HERO = LOCAL", "Answer": "3739 + 8932 = 12671"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEND = HELLO", "Answer": "4543 + 9342 = 13885"}
{"Question": "NINE + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "5152 + 9250 = 14402"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = SENSE", "Answer": "5359 + 7253 = 12612"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "5458 + 9054 = 14512"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HEAR = COUCH", "Answer": "5856 + 4358 = 10214"}
{"Question": "NONE + MENU = COUCH", "Answer": "5358 + 7852 = 13210"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HEAR = COACH", "Answer": "5859 + 7658 = 13517"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEND = ONION", "Answer": "5158 + 9857 = 15015"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEND = DEAD", "Answer": "6960 + 1068 = 8028"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "6167 + 9861 = 16028"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEND = HONOR", "Answer": "6362 + 7268 = 13630"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = DRESS", "Answer": "6065 + 9568 = 15633"}
{"Question": "RARE + TERM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6068 + 7869 = 13937"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FEAR = DEER", "Answer": "6960 + 1269 = 8229"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "7279 + 5172 = 12451"}
{"Question": "RARE + VERY = LEVEL", "Answer": "7275 + 8576 = 15851"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEND = METER", "Answer": "7275 + 8579 = 15854"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = LABEL", "Answer": "7873 + 9478 = 17351"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = BRAIN", "Answer": "8281 + 4582 = 12863"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = TREAT", "Answer": "8582 + 4289 = 12871"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TEAR = TITLE", "Answer": "8384 + 1783 = 10167"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = CYCLE", "Answer": "8783 + 1385 = 10168"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FEAR = BRIEF", "Answer": "8381 + 4683 = 13064"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEND = LIMIT", "Answer": "8683 + 7384 = 16067"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HEAR = BEACH", "Answer": "8481 + 5384 = 13865"}
{"Question": "RARE + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "8384 + 6480 = 14864"}
{"Question": "ARAB + NEAR = BRAND", "Answer": "8481 + 6384 = 14865"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = GRASS", "Answer": "8482 + 6384 = 14866"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEND = FIFTH", "Answer": "8684 + 7489 = 16173"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEND = BRAIN", "Answer": "8685 + 1583 = 10268"}
{"Question": "AWAY + DRAW = IRAQI", "Answer": "8586 + 4285 = 12871"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = PRICE", "Answer": "8485 + 6583 = 15068"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = STATE", "Answer": "8485 + 7583 = 16068"}
{"Question": "NINE + SEND = START", "Answer": "8586 + 1684 = 10270"}
{"Question": "NINE + SEND = STUDY", "Answer": "8586 + 1687 = 10273"}
{"Question": "NINE + DENY = DOZEN", "Answer": "8786 + 1682 = 10468"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEND = BADLY", "Answer": "8487 + 1782 = 10269"}
{"Question": "NINE + SEND = SALES", "Answer": "8587 + 1784 = 10371"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = SHIRT", "Answer": "8789 + 1687 = 10476"}
{"Question": "EVER + CREW = AWARD", "Answer": "8387 + 6785 = 15172"}
{"Question": "NONE + MENU = UNION", "Answer": "8687 + 9781 = 18468"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STAR = SHEET", "Answer": "9293 + 1592 = 10885"}
{"Question": "NONE + MENU = COUNT", "Answer": "9592 + 6298 = 15890"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAR = LEGAL", "Answer": "9596 + 3295 = 12891"}
{"Question": "PEER + ROPE = CROP", "Answer": "1338 + 8513 = 9851"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = FIELD", "Answer": "1779 + 9017 = 10796"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = FULLY", "Answer": "1779 + 9217 = 10996"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NOTE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1998 + 8019 = 10017"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NOTE = HONOR", "Answer": "2778 + 8027 = 10805"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NOTE = LIMIT", "Answer": "3667 + 7236 = 10903"}
{"Question": "DEER + RIDE = APART", "Answer": "5228 + 8952 = 14180"}
{"Question": "DEER + RIDE = CIVIL", "Answer": "5667 + 7256 = 12923"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = SELF", "Answer": "6551 + 1965 = 8516"}
{"Question": "MEET + TIME = FIFTH", "Answer": "6885 + 5268 = 12153"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = APPLY", "Answer": "7664 + 4576 = 12240"}
{"Question": "MEET + TIME = TOOTH", "Answer": "8331 + 1683 = 10014"}
{"Question": "DEER + RIDE = RURAL", "Answer": "8441 + 1684 = 10125"}
{"Question": "DEER + RIDE = RAPID", "Answer": "8771 + 1587 = 10358"}
{"Question": "DEER + RIDE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9556 + 6295 = 15851"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = REFER", "Answer": "9556 + 6395 = 15951"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFE = INNER", "Answer": "9558 + 8195 = 17753"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NOTE = METER", "Answer": "9667 + 7296 = 16963"}
{"Question": "MEET + HOME = MATCH", "Answer": "1227 + 9512 = 10739"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DEAL = ASSET", "Answer": "1449 + 8614 = 10063"}
{"Question": "SOON + ALSO = STEEL", "Answer": "1448 + 9214 = 10662"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1553 + 8615 = 10168"}
{"Question": "ALLY + REAL = AWARE", "Answer": "1669 + 8516 = 10185"}
{"Question": "KEEP + CAKE = KNOCK", "Answer": "1665 + 8716 = 10381"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SAFE = FULLY", "Answer": "1668 + 9216 = 10884"}
{"Question": "BEER + TUBE = BIRTH", "Answer": "1772 + 8517 = 10289"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DEAL = ASIDE", "Answer": "1772 + 8917 = 10689"}
{"Question": "SELL + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "2655 + 7520 = 10175"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEER = ONION", "Answer": "2128 + 9884 = 12012"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERO = EARTH", "Answer": "3225 + 7132 = 10357"}
{"Question": "SEEM + NOSE = LEMON", "Answer": "3227 + 9532 = 12759"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DEER = RAPID", "Answer": "3835 + 6551 = 10386"}
{"Question": "PEER + TYPE = CARRY", "Answer": "3559 + 7435 = 10994"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AIDE = LEGAL", "Answer": "4229 + 7842 = 12071"}
{"Question": "ALLY + COAL = ELECT", "Answer": "4228 + 7942 = 12170"}
{"Question": "DEER + MODE = TERMS", "Answer": "5226 + 7452 = 12678"}
{"Question": "ALLY + DEAL = SLIDE", "Answer": "5224 + 7652 = 12876"}
{"Question": "RARE + MEET = ACTOR", "Answer": "5152 + 9223 = 14375"}
{"Question": "RARE + MEET = TERMS", "Answer": "5253 + 8331 = 13584"}
{"Question": "DEEP + HIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "5448 + 9054 = 14502"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERO = METER", "Answer": "5669 + 7256 = 12925"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEER = SORRY", "Answer": "5457 + 8772 = 14229"}
{"Question": "PEER + TAPE = EARTH", "Answer": "6114 + 7361 = 13475"}
{"Question": "TEEN + RATE = ENTRY", "Answer": "6113 + 7561 = 13674"}
{"Question": "PEER + TYPE = EMPTY", "Answer": "6114 + 7561 = 13675"}
{"Question": "TOOL + AUTO = ELECT", "Answer": "6224 + 7962 = 14186"}
{"Question": "DEER + AIDE = BREAD", "Answer": "6224 + 8062 = 14286"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NEED = SENSE", "Answer": "6365 + 9550 = 15915"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEEP = MEDIA", "Answer": "6365 + 9558 = 15923"}
{"Question": "TOOL + INTO = LATIN", "Answer": "6771 + 3867 = 10638"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERO = OTHER", "Answer": "7116 + 9871 = 16987"}
{"Question": "DATA + TEAM = MARRY", "Answer": "5373 + 7631 = 13004"}
{"Question": "MEET + NAME = HUMAN", "Answer": "7449 + 3274 = 10723"}
{"Question": "TEEN + BITE = UNTIL", "Answer": "7446 + 9274 = 16720"}
{"Question": "SEED + BASE = ODDS", "Answer": "7552 + 1675 = 9227"}
{"Question": "NINE + SEEM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7375 + 6559 = 13934"}
{"Question": "TEEN + CITE = KNOCK", "Answer": "7883 + 6078 = 13961"}
{"Question": "FEEL + WIFE = RIFLE", "Answer": "8220 + 7582 = 15802"}
{"Question": "SEED + CASE = BASIS", "Answer": "8226 + 7582 = 15808"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "8335 + 1983 = 10318"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERO = TOOTH", "Answer": "8331 + 4983 = 13314"}
{"Question": "TOOL + AUTO = CLOCK", "Answer": "8334 + 5983 = 14317"}
{"Question": "NINE + FEEL = FULLY", "Answer": "8784 + 1442 = 10226"}
{"Question": "SELL + ALSO = HONOR", "Answer": "8544 + 3482 = 12026"}
{"Question": "SELL + ALSO = COLOR", "Answer": "8944 + 3482 = 12426"}
{"Question": "SOON + ALSO = APPLE", "Answer": "8557 + 1485 = 10042"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SAFE = SHELF", "Answer": "8553 + 1985 = 10538"}
{"Question": "TOOL + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8662 + 1386 = 10048"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEEN = TOTAL", "Answer": "8486 + 1663 = 10149"}
{"Question": "DEER + WIDE = WORLD", "Answer": "8662 + 1586 = 10248"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TEEN = TROOP", "Answer": "8786 + 1662 = 10448"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEEN = THEIR", "Answer": "8986 + 1662 = 10648"}
{"Question": "PIPE + BEER = TROOP", "Answer": "8786 + 3662 = 12448"}
{"Question": "DEER + CODE = FORCE", "Answer": "8660 + 4386 = 13046"}
{"Question": "DATA + TEAR = GRADE", "Answer": "4686 + 8963 = 13649"}
{"Question": "NINE + HEEL = BENCH", "Answer": "8087 + 9772 = 17859"}
{"Question": "ROOM + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "9118 + 3091 = 12209"}
{"Question": "MEET + COME = CATCH", "Answer": "9226 + 1392 = 10618"}
{"Question": "DATA + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "3292 + 9624 = 12916"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEER = TIRED", "Answer": "9592 + 6228 = 15820"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "9225 + 7692 = 16917"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEER = BIRTH", "Answer": "9093 + 1334 = 10427"}
{"Question": "DEEP + RIDE = RAPID", "Answer": "9336 + 1293 = 10629"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SEED = STRIP", "Answer": "9394 + 1445 = 10839"}
{"Question": "NONE + DEEP = VIDEO", "Answer": "9294 + 7448 = 16742"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SAFE = SALES", "Answer": "9556 + 1095 = 10651"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEEP = RIVER", "Answer": "9295 + 3556 = 12851"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEER = TIRED", "Answer": "9295 + 3558 = 12853"}
{"Question": "SEEM + RISE = TERMS", "Answer": "9554 + 6095 = 15649"}
{"Question": "TEEN + RATE = LATER", "Answer": "9667 + 3296 = 12963"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEEP = UPPER", "Answer": "9096 + 8667 = 17763"}
{"Question": "MEET + HOME = OTHER", "Answer": "9667 + 8196 = 17863"}
{"Question": "FREE + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "9177 + 8794 = 17971"}
{"Question": "THIN + INTO = IRISH", "Answer": "8714 + 1483 = 10197"}
{"Question": "RATE + TERM = AREA", "Answer": "5827 + 2751 = 8578"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARAB = CHECK", "Answer": "3735 + 8584 = 12319"}
{"Question": "EACH + CHEF = LABEL", "Answer": "3295 + 9536 = 12831"}
{"Question": "THIN + INTO = SHIFT", "Answer": "4285 + 8549 = 12834"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DEAL = BLOOD", "Answer": "4685 + 8543 = 13228"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DEAL = IRAQI", "Answer": "8146 + 4685 = 12831"}
{"Question": "NAME + MENU = ADMIT", "Answer": "4186 + 8649 = 12835"}
{"Question": "TWIN + INTO = SHOOT", "Answer": "8546 + 4682 = 13228"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "4786 + 8642 = 13428"}
{"Question": "THIN + INTO = EVENT", "Answer": "5783 + 8352 = 14135"}
{"Question": "FILE + LEFT = SALES", "Answer": "8054 + 5487 = 13541"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DEAL = VIDEO", "Answer": "5384 + 8456 = 13840"}
{"Question": "THIN + INTO = GHOST", "Answer": "5276 + 7659 = 12935"}
{"Question": "ABLE + LEAN = BRAND", "Answer": "8156 + 5684 = 13840"}
{"Question": "RATE + TERM = ACTOR", "Answer": "5186 + 8659 = 13845"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARAB = HELLO", "Answer": "5756 + 9692 = 15448"}
{"Question": "SURE + REST = OTHER", "Answer": "6873 + 7364 = 14237"}
{"Question": "THIN + INTO = FRONT", "Answer": "6784 + 8462 = 15246"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARAB = CHART", "Answer": "8085 + 6567 = 14652"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARAB = DRIVE", "Answer": "8485 + 6563 = 15048"}
{"Question": "FILE + LEFT = METAL", "Answer": "6785 + 8563 = 15348"}
{"Question": "RATE + TERM = ADMIT", "Answer": "8167 + 6789 = 14956"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "8675 + 7582 = 16257"}
{"Question": "EACH + CHEF = OFFER", "Answer": "8096 + 9687 = 17783"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ONTO = THOSE", "Answer": "1445 + 9519 = 10964"}
{"Question": "GOOD + EDGE = GUESS", "Answer": "1336 + 9619 = 10955"}
{"Question": "GOOD + EDGE = DRESS", "Answer": "2771 + 8128 = 10899"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = MAYBE", "Answer": "2729 + 9667 = 12396"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = RACE", "Answer": "3935 + 5449 = 9384"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MERE = TOTAL", "Answer": "3228 + 8939 = 12167"}
{"Question": "GOOD + EDGE = LABEL", "Answer": "5887 + 4754 = 10641"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = MEDIA", "Answer": "5758 + 8447 = 14205"}
{"Question": "POST + STOP = TASTE", "Answer": "9461 + 6149 = 15610"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ONTO = ENJOY", "Answer": "6114 + 8468 = 14582"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = FRAME", "Answer": "6468 + 8224 = 14692"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = FULLY", "Answer": "6768 + 8227 = 14995"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MERE = PAPER", "Answer": "6227 + 7969 = 14196"}
{"Question": "GOOD + EDGE = PRESS", "Answer": "7883 + 2372 = 10255"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = SENSE", "Answer": "7875 + 5338 = 13213"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MERE = TOOTH", "Answer": "7335 + 5979 = 13314"}
{"Question": "NAME + MEAN = LEMON", "Answer": "2780 + 8072 = 10852"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAR = ENTRY", "Answer": "4681 + 8164 = 12845"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAD = LATER", "Answer": "8482 + 6246 = 14728"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = DRAMA", "Answer": "8385 + 5443 = 13828"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "5384 + 8435 = 13819"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAD = DOZEN", "Answer": "8785 + 1571 = 10356"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAD = UNDER", "Answer": "8785 + 3573 = 12358"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "6791 + 9176 = 15967"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAD = ENTER", "Answer": "9291 + 8128 = 17419"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEER = GRASS", "Answer": "9293 + 3662 = 12955"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "9554 + 4393 = 13947"}
{"Question": "NAME + MEAN = INNER", "Answer": "2695 + 9562 = 12257"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAD = LEGAL", "Answer": "9295 + 6526 = 15821"}
{"Question": "GOOD + EDGE = EAGER", "Answer": "9226 + 1691 = 10917"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAR = METAL", "Answer": "7296 + 9627 = 16923"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "9117 + 8798 = 17915"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MERE = ALBUM", "Answer": "1517 + 9252 = 10769"}
{"Question": "CAST + STAR = SERVE", "Answer": "9413 + 1347 = 10760"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERE = AFTER", "Answer": "1218 + 9424 = 10642"}
{"Question": "DATE + TEAR = AREA", "Answer": "2315 + 1538 = 3853"}
{"Question": "TEEN + INTO = THOSE", "Answer": "1225 + 9517 = 10742"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = EARN", "Answer": "1612 + 3556 = 5168"}
{"Question": "ROOF + HERE = AREA", "Answer": "1553 + 7616 = 9169"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = AWARD", "Answer": "1612 + 8556 = 10168"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = APART", "Answer": "1613 + 8556 = 10169"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TOUR = THREE", "Answer": "9216 + 1628 = 10844"}
{"Question": "VAST + STAR = SERVE", "Answer": "8617 + 1763 = 10380"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAR = THREE", "Answer": "8621 + 2167 = 10788"}
{"Question": "REST + STEP = APART", "Answer": "7526 + 2650 = 10176"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERE = EAGER", "Answer": "3837 + 9181 = 13018"}
{"Question": "SAFE + FEAR = TERMS", "Answer": "9532 + 3257 = 12789"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAM = ARMY", "Answer": "4835 + 3581 = 8416"}
{"Question": "TEEN + DATA = FENCE", "Answer": "3227 + 9535 = 12762"}
{"Question": "RARE + YEAH = THREE", "Answer": "3538 + 6850 = 10388"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAT = TIRED", "Answer": "3538 + 6851 = 10389"}
{"Question": "MATH + THAN = AGENT", "Answer": "7138 + 3815 = 10953"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAR = TREND", "Answer": "8641 + 4162 = 12803"}
{"Question": "MERE + ARMY = LEGAL", "Answer": "4232 + 8349 = 12581"}
{"Question": "TEEN + INTO = VOICE", "Answer": "4553 + 8342 = 12895"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAM = MAKER", "Answer": "8347 + 4731 = 13078"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAR = LABEL", "Answer": "7248 + 4823 = 12071"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TOUR = RURAL", "Answer": "7249 + 4921 = 12170"}
{"Question": "LIST + STIR = BIBLE", "Answer": "7249 + 4926 = 12175"}
{"Question": "LATE + TEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "7251 + 5123 = 12374"}
{"Question": "MALE + LEAF = REFER", "Answer": "7652 + 5269 = 12921"}
{"Question": "RARE + LEAD = BADLY", "Answer": "5452 + 9246 = 14698"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = EDGE", "Answer": "5354 + 1773 = 7127"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = BLOOD", "Answer": "5854 + 6482 = 12336"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = HELLO", "Answer": "5754 + 8472 = 14226"}
{"Question": "TEEN + INTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "5886 + 7653 = 13539"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "5157 + 9718 = 14875"}
{"Question": "RARE + HEAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "5259 + 7928 = 13187"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "5359 + 7932 = 13291"}
{"Question": "RICH + CHIP = APART", "Answer": "8259 + 5924 = 14183"}
{"Question": "DATE + TEAM = ENTER", "Answer": "7461 + 6149 = 13610"}
{"Question": "CAST + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "8461 + 6149 = 14610"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAM = EAGER", "Answer": "9561 + 6158 = 15719"}
{"Question": "SAFE + FEAR = TASTE", "Answer": "9563 + 6350 = 15913"}
{"Question": "TOOL + DATA = SALAD", "Answer": "6883 + 7464 = 14347"}
{"Question": "RARE + MEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "6264 + 8421 = 14685"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAN = PAPER", "Answer": "6269 + 5927 = 12196"}
{"Question": "RARE + WEAK = CREW", "Answer": "7472 + 1249 = 8721"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6872 + 7284 = 14156"}
{"Question": "INTO + TONE = UNION", "Answer": "8572 + 7253 = 15825"}
{"Question": "BASE + SEAT = METER", "Answer": "6573 + 7359 = 13932"}
{"Question": "RARE + HEAT = OTHER", "Answer": "7875 + 4582 = 12457"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERE = DEATH", "Answer": "7273 + 8525 = 15798"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "7179 + 2913 = 10092"}
{"Question": "ROOM + HERE = OFFER", "Answer": "7118 + 2979 = 10097"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAM = EXTRA", "Answer": "4681 + 8165 = 12846"}
{"Question": "INTO + TONE = ONION", "Answer": "5381 + 8132 = 13513"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "1982 + 8297 = 10279"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = BLADE", "Answer": "8381 + 2443 = 10824"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = TIRED", "Answer": "8483 + 2349 = 10832"}
{"Question": "MERE + ARMY = ASSET", "Answer": "8454 + 1589 = 10043"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERE = CRACK", "Answer": "8382 + 5434 = 13816"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TOUR = MORAL", "Answer": "5784 + 8472 = 14256"}
{"Question": "RATE + TEAM = PAPER", "Answer": "7684 + 8463 = 16147"}
{"Question": "MERE + ARMY = AFTER", "Answer": "8575 + 1782 = 10357"}
{"Question": "MALE + LEAD = MODEL", "Answer": "1785 + 8573 = 10358"}
{"Question": "BASE + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "4285 + 8520 = 12805"}
{"Question": "HATE + TEAM = CATCH", "Answer": "4285 + 8529 = 12814"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TOUR = GREAT", "Answer": "4685 + 8563 = 13248"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERE = FEWER", "Answer": "8782 + 6575 = 15357"}
{"Question": "EAST + STAR = ELITE", "Answer": "1786 + 8675 = 10461"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = COLOR", "Answer": "8586 + 4652 = 13238"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "8229 + 5686 = 13915"}
{"Question": "FADE + DEAL = FULLY", "Answer": "1487 + 8742 = 10229"}
{"Question": "RARE + SEAT = SKILL", "Answer": "8487 + 1746 = 10233"}
{"Question": "RARE + WEAK = WHICH", "Answer": "8687 + 1763 = 10450"}
{"Question": "RARE + SEAT = STATE", "Answer": "8289 + 1920 = 10209"}
{"Question": "RARE + BEAN = EAGER", "Answer": "9291 + 3128 = 12419"}
{"Question": "RARE + HEAT = HOTEL", "Answer": "9392 + 1236 = 10628"}
{"Question": "SOUP + UPON = STUFF", "Answer": "1692 + 9263 = 10955"}
{"Question": "RARE + MEAL = SALAD", "Answer": "9592 + 6258 = 15850"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HERE = FORTH", "Answer": "9665 + 7292 = 16957"}
{"Question": "CASE + SEAT = OCCUR", "Answer": "3894 + 9482 = 13376"}
{"Question": "REST + STEP = AGREE", "Answer": "7294 + 9428 = 16722"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEER = LEVEL", "Answer": "9596 + 3225 = 12821"}
{"Question": "RARE + DEAL = SALAD", "Answer": "9295 + 3528 = 12823"}
{"Question": "INTO + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "3296 + 9621 = 12917"}
{"Question": "TEEN + DATA = INNER", "Answer": "9007 + 8696 = 17703"}
{"Question": "PIPE + GENE = PANEL", "Answer": "1913 + 8323 = 10236"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = RURAL", "Answer": "1516 + 8636 = 10152"}
{"Question": "PIPE + GENE = PAPER", "Answer": "1516 + 8646 = 10162"}
{"Question": "NONE + MERE = FROM", "Answer": "1017 + 4787 = 5804"}
{"Question": "PIPE + HERE = PROOF", "Answer": "1517 + 8707 = 10224"}
{"Question": "GENE + URGE = GREEN", "Answer": "1868 + 9018 = 10886"}
{"Question": "HERE + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8121 + 2791 = 10912"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLE = COLOR", "Answer": "8626 + 2076 = 10702"}
{"Question": "PIPE + GENE = BEGIN", "Answer": "3732 + 9242 = 12974"}
{"Question": "GENE + NOSE = ODDS", "Answer": "2434 + 3684 = 6118"}
{"Question": "GENE + NOTE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9535 + 3285 = 12820"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = COLOR", "Answer": "3038 + 7868 = 10906"}
{"Question": "HERE + RATE = ACTOR", "Answer": "6242 + 4132 = 10374"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = COLOR", "Answer": "4742 + 8292 = 13034"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "4147 + 8727 = 12874"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = HONOR", "Answer": "4047 + 9787 = 13834"}
{"Question": "GENE + WAGE = AWAY", "Answer": "5424 + 1754 = 7178"}
{"Question": "HERE + RISE = BASIS", "Answer": "7454 + 5384 = 12838"}
{"Question": "MERE + SAME = DRESS", "Answer": "5434 + 8054 = 13488"}
{"Question": "MERE + SAME = BASIS", "Answer": "5474 + 8354 = 13828"}
{"Question": "MERE + NAME = SEVEN", "Answer": "5494 + 8754 = 14248"}
{"Question": "MERE + TIME = FIFTH", "Answer": "5909 + 6259 = 12168"}
{"Question": "HERE + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "9363 + 6173 = 15536"}
{"Question": "GENE + HUGE = THEN", "Answer": "6484 + 2764 = 9248"}
{"Question": "GENE + NOTE = METER", "Answer": "9565 + 6285 = 15850"}
{"Question": "GENE + WAGE = FEWER", "Answer": "6585 + 9365 = 15950"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = ONION", "Answer": "6168 + 9848 = 16016"}
{"Question": "MERE + TIME = EARTH", "Answer": "7161 + 3471 = 10632"}
{"Question": "NINE + HERE = EIGHT", "Answer": "7371 + 6191 = 13562"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = ANGRY", "Answer": "7172 + 3202 = 10374"}
{"Question": "GENE + URGE = ANGER", "Answer": "7252 + 8472 = 15724"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = OFFER", "Answer": "7173 + 8363 = 15536"}
{"Question": "GENE + URGE = HONOR", "Answer": "7434 + 2874 = 10308"}
{"Question": "NONE + MERE = HONOR", "Answer": "7076 + 3626 = 10702"}
{"Question": "NINE + HERE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7078 + 3828 = 10906"}
{"Question": "HERE + RATE = CATCH", "Answer": "6878 + 7438 = 14316"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = ERROR", "Answer": "8081 + 4121 = 12202"}
{"Question": "MERE + TIME = TOOTH", "Answer": "8232 + 1782 = 10014"}
{"Question": "PIPE + GENE = GREEN", "Answer": "8982 + 1242 = 10224"}
{"Question": "HERE + RIDE = TIRED", "Answer": "7282 + 8542 = 15824"}
{"Question": "GENE + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8353 + 1683 = 10036"}
{"Question": "MERE + RACE = TERMS", "Answer": "5383 + 8473 = 13856"}
{"Question": "PIPE + GENE = INNER", "Answer": "8183 + 7353 = 15536"}
{"Question": "MERE + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1484 + 8724 = 10208"}
{"Question": "NINE + HERE = HUMAN", "Answer": "8784 + 1454 = 10238"}
{"Question": "GENE + NAME = GIVEN", "Answer": "1484 + 8764 = 10248"}
{"Question": "GENE + NICE = GRAIN", "Answer": "1484 + 8794 = 10278"}
{"Question": "GENE + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "1484 + 8964 = 10448"}
{"Question": "NINE + HERE = SEVEN", "Answer": "8784 + 5464 = 14248"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = UNDER", "Answer": "8584 + 7464 = 16048"}
{"Question": "GENE + PAGE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8545 + 1685 = 10230"}
{"Question": "GENE + URGE = UNION", "Answer": "8505 + 1785 = 10290"}
{"Question": "GENE + NOSE = HONOR", "Answer": "4585 + 8235 = 12820"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "7585 + 8605 = 16190"}
{"Question": "GENE + PAGE = ANGER", "Answer": "8676 + 9186 = 17862"}
{"Question": "NINE + MERE = HONOR", "Answer": "8087 + 5747 = 13834"}
{"Question": "RARE + GENE = PAPER", "Answer": "8289 + 3909 = 12198"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = HUMOR", "Answer": "9392 + 1242 = 10634"}
{"Question": "MERE + RULE = MORAL", "Answer": "1292 + 9642 = 10934"}
{"Question": "MERE + RACE = MORAL", "Answer": "1292 + 9672 = 10964"}
{"Question": "NONE + MERE = MINOR", "Answer": "9593 + 1363 = 10956"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROPE = PORCH", "Answer": "6393 + 9513 = 15906"}
{"Question": "MERE + NAME = ONION", "Answer": "9424 + 8594 = 18018"}
{"Question": "MERE + RACE = CATCH", "Answer": "3595 + 9215 = 12810"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERE = SORRY", "Answer": "9295 + 3585 = 12880"}
{"Question": "MERE + RULE = HELLO", "Answer": "6595 + 9285 = 15880"}
{"Question": "MERE + RATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8696 + 9016 = 17712"}
{"Question": "HERE + RICE = CATCH", "Answer": "4797 + 9017 = 13814"}
{"Question": "TEST + SIDE = SOLID", "Answer": "9319 + 1423 = 10742"}
{"Question": "DATE + TEND = TODAY", "Answer": "9613 + 1349 = 10962"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHOE = SALAD", "Answer": "9419 + 1284 = 10703"}
{"Question": "REST + STAR = TREE", "Answer": "3815 + 1573 = 5388"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEST = STAR", "Answer": "1916 + 5675 = 7591"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ABLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "8718 + 1307 = 10025"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAN = TRUTH", "Answer": "8718 + 1597 = 10315"}
{"Question": "TEST + SALE = SALAD", "Answer": "9719 + 1087 = 10806"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GLAD = GUESS", "Answer": "9719 + 1247 = 10966"}
{"Question": "PAST + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "8021 + 2198 = 10219"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEAD = EARN", "Answer": "2027 + 5785 = 7812"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GOLD = MODEL", "Answer": "8728 + 2057 = 10785"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DEAD = APPLY", "Answer": "2527 + 9719 = 12246"}
{"Question": "TEST + SAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9239 + 3582 = 12821"}
{"Question": "ACID + IDEA = SEIZE", "Answer": "8934 + 3428 = 12362"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TURN = ACTOR", "Answer": "8638 + 3746 = 12384"}
{"Question": "REST + STIR = ISSUE", "Answer": "9637 + 3719 = 13356"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEST = SOON", "Answer": "3239 + 4984 = 8223"}
{"Question": "TENT + NAME = PAPER", "Answer": "8938 + 3259 = 12197"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SOIL = ODDS", "Answer": "3143 + 4861 = 8004"}
{"Question": "NONE + DEAD = VIDEO", "Answer": "4345 + 8508 = 12853"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SOIL = RIVER", "Answer": "5645 + 4706 = 10351"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAN = SHOOT", "Answer": "8648 + 4236 = 12884"}
{"Question": "TEST + SALE = LATER", "Answer": "9649 + 4316 = 13965"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "5452 + 7297 = 12749"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GENE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8258 + 5303 = 13561"}
{"Question": "YEAR + ARMY = RARE", "Answer": "1857 + 5721 = 7578"}
{"Question": "RARE + TENT = ANGER", "Answer": "5158 + 7827 = 12985"}
{"Question": "TEST + SOME = METAL", "Answer": "7367 + 6413 = 13780"}
{"Question": "YEAR + ARMY = STATE", "Answer": "9263 + 6389 = 15652"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TURN = ENTER", "Answer": "9569 + 6045 = 15614"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEAD = ASSET", "Answer": "6468 + 5815 = 12283"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THIN = NIGHT", "Answer": "6176 + 7031 = 13207"}
{"Question": "MATH + THEM = HABIT", "Answer": "6371 + 7126 = 13497"}
{"Question": "RARE + TENT = EAGER", "Answer": "7371 + 6146 = 13517"}
{"Question": "RARE + TENT = LATIN", "Answer": "7372 + 6286 = 13658"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEST = BASIS", "Answer": "7572 + 6286 = 13858"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TENT = INNER", "Answer": "7174 + 9469 = 16643"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAN = EARTH", "Answer": "2672 + 7806 = 10478"}
{"Question": "PUSH + SHIP = ONION", "Answer": "2478 + 7832 = 10310"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SOIL = ORDER", "Answer": "4874 + 7168 = 12042"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THEN = SENSE", "Answer": "5875 + 7938 = 13813"}
{"Question": "DATA + TEND = SENSE", "Answer": "6878 + 7436 = 14314"}
{"Question": "NONE + DEAD = ONION", "Answer": "7178 + 9839 = 17017"}
{"Question": "HERE + RUSH = SUPER", "Answer": "8979 + 7618 = 16597"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEST = ASSET", "Answer": "8180 + 4024 = 12204"}
{"Question": "ACID + IDEA = DRIVE", "Answer": "4681 + 8154 = 12835"}
{"Question": "REST + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "5681 + 8135 = 13816"}
{"Question": "RARE + TENT = UNDER", "Answer": "8082 + 6246 = 14328"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ONTO = STONE", "Answer": "8382 + 6246 = 14628"}
{"Question": "RARE + TENT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8783 + 1391 = 10174"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEST = TOWER", "Answer": "8784 + 1461 = 10245"}
{"Question": "NINE + DEAD = READY", "Answer": "8284 + 6476 = 14760"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEST = TOOTH", "Answer": "8485 + 1531 = 10016"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TURN = OCCUR", "Answer": "1581 + 8465 = 10046"}
{"Question": "REST + STAR = ROUTE", "Answer": "1685 + 8571 = 10256"}
{"Question": "REST + STAR = AGREE", "Answer": "4985 + 8514 = 13499"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TENT = TRAIN", "Answer": "8586 + 1671 = 10257"}
{"Question": "DATA + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "4686 + 8124 = 12810"}
{"Question": "TALE + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "1387 + 8751 = 10138"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEST = TRAIN", "Answer": "8487 + 1761 = 10248"}
{"Question": "PAST + STOP = TOOTH", "Answer": "3091 + 9123 = 12214"}
{"Question": "DATE + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "3791 + 9123 = 12914"}
{"Question": "REST + STIR = TASTE", "Answer": "6791 + 9126 = 15917"}
{"Question": "DATA + TEND = ASSET", "Answer": "8191 + 9568 = 17759"}
{"Question": "RARE + TEST = ENTER", "Answer": "9691 + 8128 = 17819"}
{"Question": "HERE + RICH = INNER", "Answer": "6393 + 9146 = 15539"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ONTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "9894 + 2432 = 12326"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THEN = COACH", "Answer": "3593 + 9825 = 13418"}
{"Question": "EVEN + ONTO = SORRY", "Answer": "9796 + 2652 = 12448"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THAN = FORTH", "Answer": "2692 + 9806 = 12498"}
{"Question": "REST + STAR = FRAME", "Answer": "2896 + 9652 = 12548"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEST = ASIAN", "Answer": "9096 + 3623 = 12719"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THEN = ENTER", "Answer": "7697 + 9216 = 16913"}
{"Question": "COAL + ALSO = LACK", "Answer": "1768 + 6847 = 8615"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOIL = LOVER", "Answer": "5172 + 7291 = 12463"}
{"Question": "URGE + GEAR = REACH", "Answer": "6173 + 7351 = 13524"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOIL = LEMON", "Answer": "9172 + 7251 = 16423"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOIL = PRIOR", "Answer": "8273 + 7362 = 15635"}
{"Question": "HERO + ROLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "9273 + 7362 = 16635"}
{"Question": "HERO + ROLE = ALTER", "Answer": "9374 + 7463 = 16837"}
{"Question": "JOIN + INTO = POINT", "Answer": "4285 + 8572 = 12857"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERO = MINOR", "Answer": "8582 + 6275 = 14857"}
{"Question": "NONE + HERO = BENCH", "Answer": "8285 + 7562 = 15847"}
{"Question": "URGE + GEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "6784 + 8457 = 15241"}
{"Question": "MESS + COME = MUSIC", "Answer": "1277 + 9512 = 10789"}
{"Question": "NONE + TELL = ONTO", "Answer": "1813 + 6355 = 8168"}
{"Question": "ROLL + HERO = REFER", "Answer": "1388 + 9013 = 10401"}
{"Question": "RARE + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "1514 + 7945 = 9459"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = THEIR", "Answer": "8515 + 1722 = 10237"}
{"Question": "CELL + RICE = CARRY", "Answer": "1577 + 9415 = 10992"}
{"Question": "BOAT + AUTO = APPLE", "Answer": "8617 + 1476 = 10093"}
{"Question": "LESS + MALE = LIMIT", "Answer": "1688 + 9216 = 10904"}
{"Question": "TELL + NOTE = ONTO", "Answer": "1799 + 4617 = 6416"}
{"Question": "SELL + BASE = SALAD", "Answer": "1788 + 9017 = 10805"}
{"Question": "CELL + RACE = AREA", "Answer": "1866 + 2418 = 4284"}
{"Question": "TOSS + INTO = TRAIN", "Answer": "1966 + 8519 = 10485"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLL = MOTOR", "Answer": "8525 + 2077 = 10602"}
{"Question": "DATA + TOSS = RADIO", "Answer": "9232 + 3755 = 12987"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = SENSE", "Answer": "9535 + 3277 = 12812"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "9535 + 3288 = 12823"}
{"Question": "TOSS + INTO = SKIN", "Answer": "4677 + 2346 = 7023"}
{"Question": "CELL + PACE = SLEEP", "Answer": "4622 + 8046 = 12668"}
{"Question": "DEAL + ABLE = BLOOD", "Answer": "9643 + 4136 = 13779"}
{"Question": "RARE + LESS = COLOR", "Answer": "4246 + 9688 = 13934"}
{"Question": "NINE + BELL = FIBER", "Answer": "4346 + 9622 = 13968"}
{"Question": "CELL + ONCE = ALLOW", "Answer": "4733 + 8647 = 13380"}
{"Question": "NONE + BELL = ONION", "Answer": "4148 + 9866 = 14014"}
{"Question": "RARE + IDEA = TREAT", "Answer": "4843 + 9538 = 14381"}
{"Question": "LESS + ABLE = ESSAY", "Answer": "5133 + 8251 = 13384"}
{"Question": "TELL + CITE = ELECT", "Answer": "5144 + 9051 = 14195"}
{"Question": "NINE + CELL = BEGIN", "Answer": "5852 + 6233 = 12085"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = EAGER", "Answer": "7252 + 5166 = 12418"}
{"Question": "RARE + MESS = USUAL", "Answer": "5952 + 8244 = 14196"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = BREAD", "Answer": "9252 + 5477 = 14729"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = SLIDE", "Answer": "9252 + 5644 = 14896"}
{"Question": "BELT + LATE = CATCH", "Answer": "7356 + 5263 = 12619"}
{"Question": "TOSS + INTO = UNION", "Answer": "5488 + 7254 = 12742"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = PAPER", "Answer": "8454 + 5722 = 14176"}
{"Question": "RARE + LESS = USER", "Answer": "6361 + 2155 = 8516"}
{"Question": "RARE + BELL = EAGER", "Answer": "6061 + 4155 = 10216"}
{"Question": "RARE + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "6261 + 4155 = 10416"}
{"Question": "RARE + IDEA = BASIS", "Answer": "6268 + 5782 = 12050"}
{"Question": "TELL + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "6255 + 7362 = 13617"}
{"Question": "BELT + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "7462 + 6824 = 14286"}
{"Question": "NINE + HELL = FIFTH", "Answer": "6268 + 5877 = 12145"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = ASSET", "Answer": "8171 + 7366 = 15537"}
{"Question": "NINE + BELL = ENJOY", "Answer": "7871 + 9155 = 17026"}
{"Question": "NONE + CELL = BELOW", "Answer": "7372 + 5266 = 12638"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLL = PAPER", "Answer": "6272 + 7855 = 14127"}
{"Question": "RARE + BELL = ALTER", "Answer": "7172 + 8255 = 15427"}
{"Question": "NINE + TELL = SPLIT", "Answer": "7372 + 8266 = 15638"}
{"Question": "RARE + SELL = BASIS", "Answer": "7572 + 8266 = 15838"}
{"Question": "RARE + WELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7173 + 8355 = 15528"}
{"Question": "MESS + TIME = ASSET", "Answer": "7366 + 9273 = 16639"}
{"Question": "RARE + LESS = ASSET", "Answer": "7174 + 9466 = 16640"}
{"Question": "REAL + ABLE = LEARN", "Answer": "8571 + 7215 = 15786"}
{"Question": "NINE + SELL = CROSS", "Answer": "7678 + 2844 = 10522"}
{"Question": "TELL + RATE = APART", "Answer": "7988 + 6179 = 14167"}
{"Question": "TELL + NOTE = EVENT", "Answer": "8177 + 5981 = 14158"}
{"Question": "TOSS + INTO = ONION", "Answer": "8133 + 6481 = 14614"}
{"Question": "CELL + ONCE = OFFER", "Answer": "8244 + 1782 = 10026"}
{"Question": "PIPE + CELL = CHEAP", "Answer": "8982 + 1266 = 10248"}
{"Question": "MESS + NAME = ASIAN", "Answer": "8233 + 5182 = 13415"}
{"Question": "LESS + TALE = ASSET", "Answer": "8244 + 6182 = 14426"}
{"Question": "RARE + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "8283 + 7432 = 15715"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SELL = SWEEP", "Answer": "8983 + 1355 = 10338"}
{"Question": "NINE + BELL = SEVEN", "Answer": "8683 + 4355 = 13038"}
{"Question": "PIPE + BELL = SLEEP", "Answer": "8983 + 6355 = 15338"}
{"Question": "RARE + BELL = ORDER", "Answer": "8683 + 9355 = 18038"}
{"Question": "NINE + LESS = LABEL", "Answer": "8785 + 1566 = 10351"}
{"Question": "RARE + BELL = SALES", "Answer": "8085 + 2566 = 10651"}
{"Question": "LESS + PILE = PAPER", "Answer": "8677 + 1486 = 10163"}
{"Question": "RARE + CELL = COLOR", "Answer": "8586 + 1622 = 10208"}
{"Question": "RARE + HELL = HONOR", "Answer": "8786 + 1622 = 10408"}
{"Question": "TELL + DATE = ALTER", "Answer": "8677 + 9186 = 17863"}
{"Question": "NINE + TELL = FIFTH", "Answer": "8387 + 4755 = 13142"}
{"Question": "NINE + SELL = SOLAR", "Answer": "9392 + 1266 = 10658"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TELL = TROOP", "Answer": "9392 + 1277 = 10669"}
{"Question": "CELL + ONCE = OFTEN", "Answer": "9233 + 1592 = 10825"}
{"Question": "NINE + BELL = BUNCH", "Answer": "9692 + 1255 = 10947"}
{"Question": "NONE + LESS = HOTEL", "Answer": "9492 + 5233 = 14725"}
{"Question": "DATA + TELL = HELLO", "Answer": "6292 + 9588 = 15880"}
{"Question": "RARE + BELL = FLOOR", "Answer": "9392 + 8277 = 17669"}
{"Question": "NINE + SELL = ASSET", "Answer": "9893 + 2344 = 12237"}
{"Question": "RARE + TELL = ALTER", "Answer": "9194 + 6455 = 15649"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROLL = OFFER", "Answer": "7494 + 9155 = 16649"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = UNDER", "Answer": "7494 + 9288 = 16782"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = REFER", "Answer": "8494 + 9177 = 17671"}
{"Question": "TELL + CITE = CATCH", "Answer": "9522 + 1395 = 10917"}
{"Question": "TOSS + INTO = VISIT", "Answer": "9544 + 3895 = 13439"}
{"Question": "TELL + DATE = CATCH", "Answer": "9522 + 4395 = 13917"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = LATER", "Answer": "6595 + 9388 = 15983"}
{"Question": "TRUE + USER = SHEET", "Answer": "4698 + 9186 = 13884"}
{"Question": "DATA + TREE = METER", "Answer": "3898 + 9022 = 12920"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TYPE = AGENT", "Answer": "1512 + 9237 = 10749"}
{"Question": "REST + STOP = SUPER", "Answer": "9512 + 1247 = 10759"}
{"Question": "DISH + SHOE = SPEED", "Answer": "9512 + 1267 = 10779"}
{"Question": "DATA + SIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "1282 + 9517 = 10799"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOFT = SHALL", "Answer": "9712 + 1265 = 10977"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TYPE = ASSET", "Answer": "1713 + 8345 = 10058"}
{"Question": "PIPE + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "1615 + 8543 = 10158"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOME = SHELL", "Answer": "8715 + 1562 = 10277"}
{"Question": "RICH + CHEF = CIVIL", "Answer": "9015 + 1587 = 10602"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOME = SMELL", "Answer": "9215 + 1507 = 10722"}
{"Question": "ARMY + MYTH = METER", "Answer": "9215 + 1587 = 10802"}
{"Question": "HERE + ROAD = RADIO", "Answer": "9515 + 1308 = 10823"}
{"Question": "RARE + LEFT = RURAL", "Answer": "1516 + 8642 = 10158"}
{"Question": "COME + MEAT = MOTOR", "Answer": "9016 + 1687 = 10703"}
{"Question": "FIRE + READ = RADIO", "Answer": "9216 + 1608 = 10824"}
{"Question": "BABY + HERE = BUYER", "Answer": "1218 + 9646 = 10864"}
{"Question": "DATA + TYPE = TODAY", "Answer": "9616 + 1347 = 10963"}
{"Question": "EVER + DRAW = WAVE", "Answer": "1017 + 3784 = 4801"}
{"Question": "IRON + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8317 + 1706 = 10023"}
{"Question": "IRON + ONCE = OFFER", "Answer": "8317 + 1746 = 10063"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOME = SMALL", "Answer": "9217 + 1705 = 10922"}
{"Question": "REAL + ALSO = AWARE", "Answer": "8219 + 1963 = 10182"}
{"Question": "LIST + STEP = TITLE", "Answer": "8021 + 2165 = 10186"}
{"Question": "EAST + STIR = TREAT", "Answer": "8721 + 2150 = 10871"}
{"Question": "LEAF + AIDE = FIELD", "Answer": "8521 + 2065 = 10586"}
{"Question": "DATA + TONE = OCEAN", "Answer": "8626 + 2137 = 10763"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HOUR = COACH", "Answer": "3235 + 7082 = 10317"}
{"Question": "DATA + TERM = EAGER", "Answer": "9232 + 3186 = 12418"}
{"Question": "IDEA + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "9532 + 3281 = 12813"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HOUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "3237 + 9582 = 12819"}
{"Question": "PAIN + IDEA = RAPID", "Answer": "9235 + 3702 = 12937"}
{"Question": "DENY + NAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "9235 + 3712 = 12947"}
{"Question": "DATA + TIME = LIMIT", "Answer": "7535 + 3068 = 10603"}
{"Question": "DATA + TYPE = ENEMY", "Answer": "8535 + 3641 = 12176"}
{"Question": "NONE + BEAR = ONION", "Answer": "3138 + 9875 = 13013"}
{"Question": "CASH + SHIP = HAPPY", "Answer": "6041 + 4182 = 10223"}
{"Question": "RARE + NEWS = ESSAY", "Answer": "4041 + 8162 = 12203"}
{"Question": "TIME + MEAN = ENTER", "Answer": "8641 + 4172 = 12813"}
{"Question": "CROP + OVER = PRICE", "Answer": "7241 + 4832 = 12073"}
{"Question": "NONE + TEAM = ONTO", "Answer": "4746 + 2681 = 7427"}
{"Question": "CORE + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "9246 + 4618 = 13864"}
{"Question": "INTO + TOUR = UNION", "Answer": "9346 + 4617 = 13963"}
{"Question": "PURE + REST = SUPER", "Answer": "9346 + 4618 = 13964"}
{"Question": "EAST + STIR = RAISE", "Answer": "8347 + 4701 = 13048"}
{"Question": "NONE + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "4347 + 8761 = 13108"}
{"Question": "STAR + ARMY = MASS", "Answer": "1548 + 4863 = 6411"}
{"Question": "NONE + ALSO = ESSAY", "Answer": "4941 + 7329 = 12270"}
{"Question": "SKIN + INTO = TOSS", "Answer": "3051 + 5182 = 8233"}
{"Question": "BOTH + THEM = HONOR", "Answer": "7251 + 5169 = 12420"}
{"Question": "HERO + ROAD = OTHER", "Answer": "8751 + 5124 = 13875"}
{"Question": "DATA + THEM = AHEAD", "Answer": "9151 + 5468 = 14619"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "5651 + 9147 = 14798"}
{"Question": "EVER + GROW = AWARE", "Answer": "5753 + 6382 = 12135"}
{"Question": "TYPE + PLAY = LABEL", "Answer": "7358 + 5123 = 12481"}
{"Question": "DATA + TUBE = LABEL", "Answer": "7353 + 5928 = 13281"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SOFT = TOOTH", "Answer": "7953 + 5361 = 13314"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "5253 + 9364 = 14617"}
{"Question": "DATA + TURN = ENTER", "Answer": "7454 + 5062 = 12516"}
{"Question": "AWAY + CREW = REACH", "Answer": "5452 + 8134 = 13586"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SNAP = PAUSE", "Answer": "5254 + 8431 = 13685"}
{"Question": "DATA + TOUR = ROUND", "Answer": "7656 + 5291 = 12947"}
{"Question": "DATE + TERM = ARMED", "Answer": "7158 + 5829 = 12987"}
{"Question": "MYTH + THEN = ENEMY", "Answer": "7259 + 5913 = 13172"}
{"Question": "HERE + RING = EIGHT", "Answer": "4161 + 6082 = 10243"}
{"Question": "BEST + STAR = TRACK", "Answer": "8261 + 6134 = 14395"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STIR = TRUST", "Answer": "6368 + 7103 = 13471"}
{"Question": "STIR + IRON = TOOTH", "Answer": "9163 + 6354 = 15517"}
{"Question": "NONE + TERM = OFFER", "Answer": "6163 + 9374 = 15537"}
{"Question": "DATA + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "9363 + 6251 = 15614"}
{"Question": "BEND + NOSE = ODDS", "Answer": "1463 + 6874 = 8337"}
{"Question": "NONE + TERM = HONOR", "Answer": "6065 + 4538 = 10603"}
{"Question": "NONE + ALSO = IDEAL", "Answer": "6569 + 7405 = 13974"}
{"Question": "CROP + OPEN = PIECE", "Answer": "3471 + 7165 = 10636"}
{"Question": "ITEM + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "5176 + 7241 = 12417"}
{"Question": "AWAY + SHOW = WHERE", "Answer": "7173 + 5291 = 12464"}
{"Question": "DATA + THIS = ASIDE", "Answer": "5171 + 7682 = 12853"}
{"Question": "SHIT + ITEM = THERE", "Answer": "6371 + 7154 = 13525"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TERM = ENTER", "Answer": "7671 + 8143 = 15814"}
{"Question": "AWAY + GROW = WHERE", "Answer": "7173 + 9251 = 16424"}
{"Question": "EVER + DATA = TRADE", "Answer": "7075 + 8212 = 15287"}
{"Question": "BOTH + THIS = ONION", "Answer": "8172 + 7243 = 15415"}
{"Question": "SALE + LEFT = FALSE", "Answer": "8572 + 7210 = 15782"}
{"Question": "CITY + TYPE = PITCH", "Answer": "8572 + 7214 = 15786"}
{"Question": "BABY + HERE = ARAB", "Answer": "7974 + 1323 = 9297"}
{"Question": "EVER + DRAG = TRADE", "Answer": "7573 + 6394 = 13967"}
{"Question": "ROLE + LEAF = OFFER", "Answer": "8173 + 7365 = 15538"}
{"Question": "STOP + OPEN = THESE", "Answer": "3174 + 7462 = 10636"}
{"Question": "ITEM + EAST = ASIAN", "Answer": "6478 + 7134 = 13612"}
{"Question": "DATA + TONE = METER", "Answer": "9474 + 7286 = 16760"}
{"Question": "SPIN + INTO = POINT", "Answer": "6175 + 7583 = 13758"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARMY = TREAT", "Answer": "7275 + 8506 = 15781"}
{"Question": "VERY + RISE = SERVE", "Answer": "8570 + 7215 = 15785"}
{"Question": "TAIL + IDEA = ELITE", "Answer": "9576 + 7215 = 16791"}
{"Question": "FISH + SHOE = REFER", "Answer": "9375 + 7586 = 16961"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TYPE = LEVEL", "Answer": "7078 + 6853 = 13931"}
{"Question": "BASE + SEND = ASIAN", "Answer": "9178 + 7835 = 17013"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GENE = LABEL", "Answer": "7573 + 9808 = 17381"}
{"Question": "EVER + DATA = TREAT", "Answer": "7872 + 4919 = 12791"}
{"Question": "NONE + WEAK = KNOW", "Answer": "8582 + 1269 = 9851"}
{"Question": "DATA + TIRE = LATER", "Answer": "4282 + 8597 = 12879"}
{"Question": "NINE + HERO = MINOR", "Answer": "8582 + 7264 = 15846"}
{"Question": "INTO + TURN = ERROR", "Answer": "9285 + 8472 = 17757"}
{"Question": "EVER + DATA = BREAD", "Answer": "8587 + 9242 = 17829"}
{"Question": "RELY + LAKE = RURAL", "Answer": "1385 + 8793 = 10178"}
{"Question": "TEAM + ABLE = LIMIT", "Answer": "2389 + 8513 = 10902"}
{"Question": "DEAL + ALSO = STATE", "Answer": "2384 + 8419 = 10803"}
{"Question": "MYTH + THAN = ENEMY", "Answer": "3684 + 8452 = 12136"}
{"Question": "NONE + YEAH = HONEY", "Answer": "8384 + 5461 = 13845"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "5784 + 8462 = 14246"}
{"Question": "CROP + OVER = PROVE", "Answer": "6481 + 8354 = 14835"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SNAP = STATE", "Answer": "8685 + 1523 = 10208"}
{"Question": "NINE + DATA = DRESS", "Answer": "8682 + 1595 = 10277"}
{"Question": "HERE + RAIN = HONOR", "Answer": "1585 + 8723 = 10308"}
{"Question": "DATA + TURN = REFER", "Answer": "2585 + 8316 = 10901"}
{"Question": "NINE + DESK = SALAD", "Answer": "8385 + 2517 = 10902"}
{"Question": "BEST + SAME = MOTOR", "Answer": "2589 + 8315 = 10904"}
{"Question": "TYPE + PRAY = METER", "Answer": "3582 + 8745 = 12327"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DEAR = RAPID", "Answer": "8285 + 6541 = 14826"}
{"Question": "SKIN + INTO = KNOCK", "Answer": "7185 + 8506 = 15691"}
{"Question": "EVER + GRAB = ARGUE", "Answer": "8285 + 7513 = 15798"}
{"Question": "AWAY + HERE = REACH", "Answer": "8382 + 7515 = 15897"}
{"Question": "IDEA + EAST = BASIS", "Answer": "7385 + 8594 = 15979"}
{"Question": "HERE + RING = INNER", "Answer": "9585 + 8173 = 17758"}
{"Question": "BEAR + ARMY = MAYBE", "Answer": "9785 + 8512 = 18297"}
{"Question": "FAIR + IRON = FENCE", "Answer": "1786 + 8634 = 10420"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TYPE = TIGHT", "Answer": "8786 + 1635 = 10421"}
{"Question": "BEST + SOME = MOTOR", "Answer": "2687 + 8016 = 10703"}
{"Question": "HERO + RULE = COLOR", "Answer": "3682 + 8746 = 12428"}
{"Question": "ARAB + USER = STATE", "Answer": "8687 + 4136 = 12823"}
{"Question": "MERE + CAMP = ARMED", "Answer": "8676 + 9184 = 17860"}
{"Question": "ROAD + ALSO = RURAL", "Answer": "1786 + 8397 = 10183"}
{"Question": "NONE + PEAK = PRIOR", "Answer": "8487 + 1753 = 10240"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SNOW = START", "Answer": "8487 + 1763 = 10250"}
{"Question": "RARE + LEFT = LOCAL", "Answer": "8587 + 1764 = 10351"}
{"Question": "WEST + SHOE = WORTH", "Answer": "1789 + 8607 = 10396"}
{"Question": "ARAB + OVER = ONION", "Answer": "8783 + 1627 = 10410"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TONE = ASIAN", "Answer": "1687 + 8725 = 10412"}
{"Question": "TIME + MENU = TRUST", "Answer": "1687 + 8734 = 10421"}
{"Question": "SIDE + DEAR = START", "Answer": "1687 + 8743 = 10430"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TYPE = TREAT", "Answer": "8687 + 1794 = 10481"}
{"Question": "NINE + READ = RADIO", "Answer": "8987 + 1706 = 10693"}
{"Question": "HOLE + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "4387 + 8721 = 13108"}
{"Question": "RARE + HELP = PAPER", "Answer": "8387 + 4791 = 13178"}
{"Question": "NONE + ALSO = LEVEL", "Answer": "8784 + 6157 = 14941"}
{"Question": "SIDE + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "1389 + 8902 = 10291"}
{"Question": "MERE + CAMP = PAPER", "Answer": "8909 + 3281 = 12190"}
{"Question": "THUS + USER = IRISH", "Answer": "4289 + 8903 = 13192"}
{"Question": "DATA + CODE = CHEST", "Answer": "9282 + 1396 = 10678"}
{"Question": "NINE + MEAT = MONTH", "Answer": "9692 + 1243 = 10935"}
{"Question": "GAIN + IDEA = GUIDE", "Answer": "1295 + 9672 = 10967"}
{"Question": "NINE + BEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "9592 + 3287 = 12879"}
{"Question": "POLE + LEAD = HELLO", "Answer": "3792 + 9205 = 12997"}
{"Question": "INTO + THAN = SHOOT", "Answer": "5297 + 9482 = 14779"}
{"Question": "LEFT + FACE = CATCH", "Answer": "6298 + 9512 = 15810"}
{"Question": "HIRE + REST = OTHER", "Answer": "8592 + 9237 = 17829"}
{"Question": "CARE + REST = CATCH", "Answer": "1093 + 9324 = 10417"}
{"Question": "EVER + ARMY = AHEAD", "Answer": "9593 + 1324 = 10917"}
{"Question": "NINE + LEFT = ALLOW", "Answer": "9893 + 2364 = 12257"}
{"Question": "NINE + TEAR = START", "Answer": "9894 + 6432 = 16326"}
{"Question": "ARAB + STIR = VISIT", "Answer": "9498 + 7264 = 16762"}
{"Question": "NONE + LEFT = ALLOW", "Answer": "9695 + 2573 = 12268"}
{"Question": "EVEN + UNIT = FULLY", "Answer": "9796 + 3652 = 13448"}
{"Question": "PLUS + USED = APPLE", "Answer": "4796 + 9682 = 14478"}
{"Question": "EVEN + INTO = TOOTH", "Answer": "9096 + 8617 = 17713"}
{"Question": "RARE + RARE = DEAD", "Answer": "1316 + 1316 = 2632"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BEER", "Answer": "1613 + 1613 = 3226"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = EASE", "Answer": "2127 + 2127 = 4254"}
{"Question": "NINE + NINE = MOON", "Answer": "2721 + 2721 = 5442"}
{"Question": "NINE + NINE = DIET", "Answer": "3037 + 3037 = 6074"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = ONTO", "Answer": "3438 + 3438 = 6876"}
{"Question": "RARE + RARE = BEAN", "Answer": "3632 + 3632 = 7264"}
{"Question": "BABY + BABY = ARMY", "Answer": "3730 + 3730 = 7460"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = DEER", "Answer": "3834 + 3834 = 7668"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BACK", "Answer": "4248 + 4248 = 8496"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = TENT", "Answer": "4249 + 4249 = 8498"}
{"Question": "BABY + BABY = GRAB", "Answer": "4842 + 4842 = 9684"}
{"Question": "BABY + BABY = ALLY", "Answer": "4940 + 4940 = 9880"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = ENTER", "Answer": "5457 + 5457 = 10914"}
{"Question": "NINE + NINE = THEIR", "Answer": "6367 + 6367 = 12734"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = FLOOR", "Answer": "7276 + 7276 = 14552"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = AGENT", "Answer": "7375 + 7375 = 14750"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = TRIBE", "Answer": "7475 + 7475 = 14950"}
{"Question": "NINE + NINE = BIBLE", "Answer": "7570 + 7570 = 15140"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = IRISH", "Answer": "7573 + 7573 = 15146"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BEGIN", "Answer": "7671 + 7671 = 15342"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = GUESS", "Answer": "7672 + 7672 = 15344"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = FIBER", "Answer": "7673 + 7673 = 15346"}
{"Question": "AWAY + AWAY = CRAZY", "Answer": "7870 + 7870 = 15740"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BEACH", "Answer": "7871 + 7871 = 15742"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = CLASS", "Answer": "7872 + 7872 = 15744"}
{"Question": "AWAY + AWAY = CYCLE", "Answer": "8086 + 8086 = 16172"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = VALUE", "Answer": "8189 + 8189 = 16378"}
{"Question": "RARE + RARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8286 + 8286 = 16572"}
{"Question": "EVER + EVER = PROOF", "Answer": "8386 + 8386 = 16772"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PIPE = TROOP", "Answer": "8389 + 8389 = 16778"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = ANGRY", "Answer": "8486 + 8486 = 16972"}
{"Question": "NONE + NONE = VIDEO", "Answer": "8487 + 8487 = 16974"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = DANCE", "Answer": "8489 + 8489 = 16978"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BIBLE", "Answer": "8581 + 8581 = 17162"}
{"Question": "BABY + BABY = DELAY", "Answer": "8680 + 8680 = 17360"}
{"Question": "RARE + RARE = EQUAL", "Answer": "8681 + 8681 = 17362"}
{"Question": "BABY + BABY = DAILY", "Answer": "8780 + 8780 = 17560"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = BRICK", "Answer": "8781 + 8781 = 17562"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = CROSS", "Answer": "8783 + 8783 = 17566"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVEN = MOVIE", "Answer": "8984 + 8984 = 17968"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = CLEAR", "Answer": "9296 + 9296 = 18592"}
{"Question": "EVER + EVER = GREEN", "Answer": "9498 + 9498 = 18996"}
{"Question": "NINE + NINE = ENEMY", "Answer": "9591 + 9591 = 19182"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARAB = LABOR", "Answer": "9693 + 9693 = 19386"}
{"Question": "NONE + NONE = ENJOY", "Answer": "9891 + 9891 = 19782"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = FORCE", "Answer": "6467 + 6469 = 12936"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = NURSE", "Answer": "6761 + 6765 = 13526"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = NOISE", "Answer": "6861 + 6865 = 13726"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = ARGUE", "Answer": "7672 + 7675 = 15347"}
{"Question": "EVER + EVEN = AGENT", "Answer": "7872 + 7874 = 15746"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = THERE", "Answer": "7873 + 7874 = 15747"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = TREND", "Answer": "7874 + 7875 = 15749"}
{"Question": "EVER + EVEN = START", "Answer": "8287 + 8289 = 16576"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = IRAQI", "Answer": "8485 + 8486 = 16971"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = TIRED", "Answer": "9395 + 9397 = 18792"}
{"Question": "EVER + EVEN = FENCE", "Answer": "9794 + 9795 = 19589"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EVER = SERVE", "Answer": "9892 + 9897 = 19789"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = FAIL", "Answer": "3930 + 3988 = 7918"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = TREAT", "Answer": "5453 + 5488 = 10941"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = RURAL", "Answer": "6560 + 6599 = 13159"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = ELITE", "Answer": "6768 + 6733 = 13501"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = REFER", "Answer": "8284 + 8277 = 16561"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = CLIMB", "Answer": "8382 + 8366 = 16748"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = FALSE", "Answer": "8784 + 8755 = 17539"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = SALES", "Answer": "8786 + 8755 = 17541"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = STYLE", "Answer": "9397 + 9355 = 18752"}
{"Question": "BABY + BALL = HELLO", "Answer": "9395 + 9377 = 18772"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = EAST", "Answer": "1012 + 1042 = 2054"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = POET", "Answer": "1018 + 1068 = 2086"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = TEST", "Answer": "1316 + 1326 = 2642"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PILE = FLEE", "Answer": "1410 + 1490 = 2900"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = TENT", "Answer": "2327 + 2397 = 4724"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = BEAT", "Answer": "2928 + 2968 = 5896"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = AREA", "Answer": "3138 + 3148 = 6286"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PINE = EVEN", "Answer": "3436 + 3426 = 6862"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = DEAD", "Answer": "3438 + 3408 = 6846"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = TREE", "Answer": "3530 + 3570 = 7100"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = TREE", "Answer": "3630 + 3670 = 7300"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = AIDE", "Answer": "3930 + 3980 = 7910"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOSE = SEND", "Answer": "4745 + 4795 = 9540"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = SENSE", "Answer": "5250 + 5260 = 10510"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = ISSUE", "Answer": "6160 + 6130 = 12290"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOSE = OFFER", "Answer": "6167 + 6107 = 12274"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PINE = INNER", "Answer": "6169 + 6129 = 12298"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = CATCH", "Answer": "6264 + 6254 = 12518"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = TERMS", "Answer": "6362 + 6312 = 12674"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = THEME", "Answer": "6560 + 6520 = 13080"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = SCENE", "Answer": "6560 + 6530 = 13090"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = METER", "Answer": "6863 + 6873 = 13736"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = CHIEF", "Answer": "7079 + 7019 = 14098"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PILE = CLOCK", "Answer": "7273 + 7243 = 14516"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = OCEAN", "Answer": "7275 + 7245 = 14520"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = ASSET", "Answer": "7278 + 7208 = 14486"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOSE = SORRY", "Answer": "7473 + 7413 = 14886"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = FIBER", "Answer": "7476 + 7486 = 14962"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PILE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7478 + 7468 = 14946"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = TOWER", "Answer": "7579 + 7519 = 15098"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = THREE", "Answer": "7870 + 7830 = 15700"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PINE = BEGIN", "Answer": "7875 + 7805 = 15680"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = BASIS", "Answer": "7974 + 7924 = 15898"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = OTHER", "Answer": "8185 + 8165 = 16350"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOSE = OFTEN", "Answer": "8189 + 8109 = 16298"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = ACTOR", "Answer": "8189 + 8169 = 16358"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "8285 + 8215 = 16500"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = METER", "Answer": "8386 + 8376 = 16762"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = ALLOW", "Answer": "8387 + 8307 = 16694"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = INNER", "Answer": "8389 + 8309 = 16698"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "8389 + 8379 = 16768"}
{"Question": "NINE + NICE = FEWER", "Answer": "8486 + 8476 = 16962"}
{"Question": "NONE + NOTE = ELECT", "Answer": "8581 + 8521 = 17102"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = VOTER", "Answer": "8589 + 8509 = 17098"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = TASTE", "Answer": "8780 + 8730 = 17510"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = LEAST", "Answer": "8987 + 8947 = 17934"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9193 + 9123 = 18316"}
{"Question": "RARE + RACE = ONION", "Answer": "9394 + 9324 = 18718"}
{"Question": "RARE + RATE = THREE", "Answer": "9490 + 9410 = 18900"}
{"Question": "RARE + RANK = NEAR", "Answer": "1418 + 1423 = 2841"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = BALL", "Answer": "3930 + 3981 = 7911"}
{"Question": "BABY + BAKE = EASE", "Answer": "3930 + 3987 = 7917"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = LEGAL", "Answer": "5350 + 5381 = 10731"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = ALLOW", "Answer": "6165 + 6132 = 12297"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PICK = INNER", "Answer": "6167 + 6108 = 12275"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = SALES", "Answer": "6267 + 6204 = 12471"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIN = FENCE", "Answer": "6563 + 6520 = 13083"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = SHELL", "Answer": "6560 + 6528 = 13088"}
{"Question": "RARE + RANK = OWNER", "Answer": "6567 + 6509 = 13076"}
{"Question": "RARE + RANK = ENTER", "Answer": "7271 + 7246 = 14517"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PINK = ENTER", "Answer": "7271 + 7248 = 14519"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = OFFER", "Answer": "7278 + 7209 = 14487"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = INNER", "Answer": "7279 + 7218 = 14497"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = SALAD", "Answer": "7473 + 7469 = 14942"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = FEWER", "Answer": "7675 + 7682 = 15357"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = CLEAN", "Answer": "7673 + 7695 = 15368"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIN = NEVER", "Answer": "8687 + 8691 = 17378"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PINK = SEVEN", "Answer": "8687 + 8692 = 17379"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIN = ENTER", "Answer": "9391 + 9328 = 18719"}
{"Question": "BABY + BASE = DRESS", "Answer": "9395 + 9327 = 18722"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARMY = CABIN", "Answer": "9693 + 9682 = 19375"}
{"Question": "RARE + RAIL = DRESS", "Answer": "9693 + 9684 = 19377"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARMY = MAYOR", "Answer": "9792 + 9715 = 19507"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ARMY = LAYER", "Answer": "9792 + 9745 = 19537"}
{"Question": "NINE + NONE = INTO", "Answer": "1314 + 1814 = 3128"}
{"Question": "NINE + NONE = BEGIN", "Answer": "6263 + 6763 = 13026"}
{"Question": "NONE + NINE = OFFER", "Answer": "7175 + 7275 = 14450"}
{"Question": "NINE + NONE = HONEY", "Answer": "7275 + 7475 = 14750"}
{"Question": "NONE + NINE = FIELD", "Answer": "7378 + 7478 = 14856"}
{"Question": "NINE + NONE = SOLID", "Answer": "7473 + 7573 = 15046"}
{"Question": "NONE + NINE = PIECE", "Answer": "8280 + 8780 = 17060"}
{"Question": "NONE + NINE = HELLO", "Answer": "8286 + 8486 = 16772"}
{"Question": "NONE + NINE = EIGHT", "Answer": "8581 + 8781 = 17362"}
{"Question": "NINE + NONE = MOVIE", "Answer": "8680 + 8780 = 17460"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ARAB = BRAIN", "Answer": "7279 + 7471 = 14750"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ALLY = LADY", "Answer": "1810 + 1330 = 3140"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ALLY = STEEL", "Answer": "6562 + 6442 = 13004"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ALLY = FUNNY", "Answer": "6560 + 6880 = 13440"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ALLY = CLOCK", "Answer": "7073 + 7443 = 14516"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ALLY = ERROR", "Answer": "9094 + 9774 = 18868"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAIN = DEEP", "Answer": "3135 + 3418 = 6553"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAR = AREA", "Answer": "3639 + 3067 = 6706"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POOL = ROLL", "Answer": "3930 + 3881 = 7811"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROAD = EASE", "Answer": "3837 + 3980 = 7817"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "5159 + 5718 = 10877"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "5653 + 5269 = 10922"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "6263 + 6421 = 12684"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAIN = ENEMY", "Answer": "6261 + 6923 = 13184"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = VOTER", "Answer": "6569 + 6227 = 12796"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = FORTH", "Answer": "6468 + 6229 = 12697"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POOR = IRAQI", "Answer": "6169 + 6332 = 12501"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAIR = AGREE", "Answer": "6864 + 6180 = 13044"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = LATER", "Answer": "6364 + 6882 = 13246"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAIR = GREEN", "Answer": "6864 + 6583 = 13447"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROAD = ASSET", "Answer": "7179 + 7316 = 14495"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOM = OFFER", "Answer": "7379 + 7118 = 14497"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAIR = TROOP", "Answer": "7372 + 7635 = 15007"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAR = PROOF", "Answer": "7374 + 7635 = 15009"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOM = MORAL", "Answer": "7279 + 7441 = 14720"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "7472 + 7341 = 14813"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "7473 + 7045 = 14518"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOF = AFTER", "Answer": "7173 + 7664 = 14837"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAR = REFER", "Answer": "7870 + 7581 = 15451"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = METER", "Answer": "7375 + 7882 = 15257"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROAD = FEWER", "Answer": "7875 + 7482 = 15357"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "7874 + 7985 = 15859"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ALLY = BOARD", "Answer": "8381 + 8449 = 16830"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEAT = TITLE", "Answer": "8485 + 8641 = 17126"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEER = URBAN", "Answer": "8389 + 8446 = 16835"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = AFTER", "Answer": "9193 + 9446 = 18639"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROOT = TREAT", "Answer": "9490 + 9551 = 19041"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROAD = OFFER", "Answer": "9695 + 9164 = 18859"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = FEEL", "Answer": "3930 + 3188 = 7118"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = TASTE", "Answer": "5052 + 5866 = 10918"}
{"Question": "EVER + EARN = AGREE", "Answer": "5759 + 5196 = 10955"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLL = FLOOR", "Answer": "6064 + 6822 = 12886"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLL = SOLAR", "Answer": "6469 + 6277 = 12746"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POLL = BELOW", "Answer": "6463 + 6822 = 13285"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLL = ALTER", "Answer": "7172 + 7855 = 15027"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = ELITE", "Answer": "7876 + 7155 = 15031"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POET = TROOP", "Answer": "7976 + 7361 = 15337"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = RURAL", "Answer": "7670 + 7499 = 15169"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = LAYER", "Answer": "7573 + 7811 = 15384"}
{"Question": "EVER + EARN = DRIVE", "Answer": "8486 + 8062 = 16548"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8187 + 8466 = 16653"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POET = FIFTH", "Answer": "8784 + 8342 = 17126"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POET = TOOTH", "Answer": "8983 + 8731 = 17714"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLL = ORDER", "Answer": "9894 + 9155 = 19049"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLL = BREAD", "Answer": "9392 + 9844 = 19236"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "3238 + 3698 = 6936"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLE = MORAL", "Answer": "5459 + 5089 = 10548"}
{"Question": "NINE + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "6563 + 6173 = 12736"}
{"Question": "RARE + RIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "6167 + 6547 = 12714"}
{"Question": "NONE + NAME = OCEAN", "Answer": "6168 + 6708 = 12876"}
{"Question": "BABY + BUSY = ESSAY", "Answer": "6960 + 6430 = 13390"}
{"Question": "NONE + NAME = LEMON", "Answer": "6863 + 6423 = 13286"}
{"Question": "BABY + BUSY = ASIAN", "Answer": "7173 + 7043 = 14216"}
{"Question": "RARE + RICE = AGREE", "Answer": "7170 + 7530 = 14700"}
{"Question": "NINE + NAME = MAKER", "Answer": "7279 + 7419 = 14698"}
{"Question": "NONE + NAME = MONEY", "Answer": "7479 + 7319 = 14798"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ARMY = EVERY", "Answer": "7470 + 7690 = 15160"}
{"Question": "NINE + NAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "8086 + 8216 = 16302"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLE = COLOR", "Answer": "8089 + 8679 = 16768"}
{"Question": "RARE + RISE = ASSET", "Answer": "8185 + 8465 = 16650"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "8289 + 8619 = 16908"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROLE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8589 + 8369 = 16958"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PACE = CHEAP", "Answer": "8584 + 8914 = 17498"}
{"Question": "PIPE + POLE = HELLO", "Answer": "9098 + 9678 = 18776"}
{"Question": "NINE + NOSE = ISSUE", "Answer": "9190 + 9680 = 18870"}
{"Question": "BABY + BUSY = ASSET", "Answer": "9192 + 9682 = 18874"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEST = TABLE", "Answer": "5053 + 5471 = 10524"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "6365 + 6912 = 13277"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PORT = ERROR", "Answer": "6461 + 6932 = 13393"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "7274 + 7905 = 15179"}
{"Question": "RARE + ROCK = COVER", "Answer": "7279 + 7418 = 14697"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PLUS = STEEL", "Answer": "7873 + 7461 = 15334"}
{"Question": "ARAB + AUTO = TROOP", "Answer": "7473 + 7519 = 14992"}
{"Question": "EVEN + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7876 + 7541 = 15417"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PAST = STRIP", "Answer": "7872 + 7615 = 15487"}
{"Question": "BABY + BELT = ALTER", "Answer": "8183 + 8567 = 16750"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PANT = INNER", "Answer": "8185 + 8467 = 16652"}
{"Question": "BABY + BOWL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8189 + 8456 = 16645"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PART = TREAT", "Answer": "8480 + 8571 = 17051"}
{"Question": "PIPE + PARK = MAKER", "Answer": "8483 + 8752 = 17235"}
{"Question": "BABY + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "8784 + 8531 = 17315"}
{"Question": "RARE + RING = INNER", "Answer": "9697 + 9182 = 18879"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = ROUND", "Answer": "1419 + 9413 = 10832"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = TENT", "Answer": "1714 + 4712 = 6426"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = SOLAR", "Answer": "3738 + 8735 = 12473"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = NEED", "Answer": "6163 + 3169 = 9332"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = COLOR", "Answer": "6267 + 7269 = 13536"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = BAKE", "Answer": "6961 + 1960 = 8921"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = FUNNY", "Answer": "7279 + 9275 = 16554"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = FLOOR", "Answer": "7279 + 9278 = 16557"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = OWNER", "Answer": "7674 + 4673 = 12347"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = HAPPY", "Answer": "8385 + 5389 = 13774"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = CHEEK", "Answer": "8387 + 7389 = 15776"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = INDEX", "Answer": "8487 + 7485 = 15972"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = EVENT", "Answer": "8581 + 1586 = 10167"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "8586 + 6582 = 15168"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = EQUAL", "Answer": "8681 + 1684 = 10365"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = SALAD", "Answer": "8687 + 7682 = 16369"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "8786 + 6782 = 15568"}
{"Question": "RARE + EARN = ANGRY", "Answer": "9198 + 8197 = 17395"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = ODDS", "Answer": "1224 + 4217 = 5441"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = DEEP", "Answer": "1227 + 7214 = 8441"}
{"Question": "SOON + NOSE = SHEET", "Answer": "1229 + 9214 = 10443"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FORM = EVER", "Answer": "1334 + 4317 = 5651"}
{"Question": "SOON + NOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "1339 + 9316 = 10655"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = SHALL", "Answer": "1449 + 9417 = 10866"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = START", "Answer": "1778 + 8712 = 10490"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = SHAKE", "Answer": "1778 + 8719 = 10497"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOTS = STAFF", "Answer": "2779 + 9721 = 12500"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOTS = SALT", "Answer": "3115 + 5138 = 8253"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = ASIDE", "Answer": "3559 + 9536 = 13095"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MORE = OFFER", "Answer": "4118 + 8146 = 12264"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = HEART", "Answer": "4338 + 8342 = 12680"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FORM = LIMIT", "Answer": "4665 + 5643 = 10308"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = TALE", "Answer": "4771 + 1746 = 6517"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = EVEN", "Answer": "5223 + 3258 = 8481"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = STYLE", "Answer": "5339 + 9354 = 14693"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = OPEN", "Answer": "5771 + 1752 = 7523"}
{"Question": "NEED + TENT = ONTO", "Answer": "5776 + 2752 = 8528"}
{"Question": "SEED + TEST = VISIT", "Answer": "5770 + 6756 = 12526"}
{"Question": "WOOD + DOWN = FEWER", "Answer": "5776 + 6753 = 12529"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MORE = OVER", "Answer": "5882 + 2853 = 8735"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = STAGE", "Answer": "5886 + 6852 = 12738"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOTS = SPLIT", "Answer": "6775 + 5761 = 12536"}
{"Question": "SEEM + TEST = EMPTY", "Answer": "7116 + 9179 = 16295"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOCK = SHALL", "Answer": "7229 + 9270 = 16499"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = GUESS", "Answer": "7443 + 3479 = 10922"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = BIBLE", "Answer": "7552 + 2573 = 10125"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FORM = ENEMY", "Answer": "7556 + 6572 = 14128"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = ELECT", "Answer": "7558 + 8571 = 16129"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "7668 + 8671 = 16339"}
{"Question": "NEED + TENT = TITLE", "Answer": "8554 + 1581 = 10135"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FORM = FIFTH", "Answer": "8551 + 1586 = 10137"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOCK = TOTAL", "Answer": "8556 + 6580 = 15136"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FORM = FLAME", "Answer": "8661 + 1684 = 10345"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = LARGE", "Answer": "8661 + 1685 = 10346"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = APPLE", "Answer": "8664 + 4682 = 13346"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = CIVIL", "Answer": "8665 + 5680 = 14345"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOTS = VISIT", "Answer": "8665 + 5683 = 14348"}
{"Question": "SOON + NOSE = FEWER", "Answer": "8665 + 5684 = 14349"}
{"Question": "SEED + DESK = FENCE", "Answer": "8667 + 7689 = 16356"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOCK = HELLO", "Answer": "8775 + 5782 = 14557"}
{"Question": "NEED + DENY = DRESS", "Answer": "8991 + 1986 = 10977"}
{"Question": "SEED + TEST = ENTER", "Answer": "9117 + 3193 = 12310"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = OFFER", "Answer": "9114 + 4190 = 13304"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = ENTER", "Answer": "9117 + 7193 = 16310"}
{"Question": "NEED + DENY = LEVEL", "Answer": "9223 + 3298 = 12521"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = OTHER", "Answer": "9227 + 7296 = 16523"}
{"Question": "NEED + TENT = TRADE", "Answer": "9332 + 1391 = 10723"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = LATIN", "Answer": "9331 + 1397 = 10728"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "9445 + 5496 = 14941"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROPE = DRESS", "Answer": "9662 + 2693 = 12355"}
{"Question": "SOON + NOSE = INNER", "Answer": "9663 + 3695 = 13358"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = SOLID", "Answer": "9219 + 1249 = 10468"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = SKILL", "Answer": "9219 + 1269 = 10488"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = BASE", "Answer": "7417 + 1497 = 8914"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = FEEL", "Answer": "8418 + 1468 = 9886"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = AREA", "Answer": "2512 + 1542 = 4054"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = DEAD", "Answer": "1612 + 2652 = 4264"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = SCALE", "Answer": "8618 + 1628 = 10246"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8718 + 1758 = 10476"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = SHELL", "Answer": "8918 + 1948 = 10866"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = STEEL", "Answer": "8918 + 1968 = 10886"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = SPEAK", "Answer": "8918 + 1978 = 10896"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = USER", "Answer": "2421 + 1491 = 3912"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = SPEAK", "Answer": "2428 + 8418 = 10846"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = AREA", "Answer": "2623 + 3613 = 6236"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = HAPPY", "Answer": "3239 + 9209 = 12448"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = ELSE", "Answer": "4834 + 3804 = 8638"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = AREA", "Answer": "4834 + 3814 = 8648"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "6836 + 3826 = 10662"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = SHEET", "Answer": "4346 + 6316 = 10662"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAME = MARRY", "Answer": "9349 + 4319 = 13668"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = OFTEN", "Answer": "8548 + 4538 = 13086"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = ONION", "Answer": "4845 + 5865 = 10710"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = PLATE", "Answer": "8658 + 5628 = 14286"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = CAUSE", "Answer": "4854 + 5804 = 10658"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = SEVEN", "Answer": "8468 + 6478 = 14946"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = USUAL", "Answer": "9569 + 6589 = 16158"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = SOLAR", "Answer": "6763 + 3713 = 10476"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = SUPER", "Answer": "6768 + 8718 = 15486"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = ASIAN", "Answer": "3863 + 6853 = 10716"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7173 + 3143 = 10316"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = METER", "Answer": "5275 + 7245 = 12520"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = CLOCK", "Answer": "6476 + 7436 = 13912"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = INDEX", "Answer": "9679 + 7689 = 17368"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = STAIR", "Answer": "8084 + 4014 = 12098"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASE = LATER", "Answer": "8284 + 4264 = 12548"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "7387 + 8347 = 15734"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = CLASS", "Answer": "4584 + 8504 = 13088"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = PAPER", "Answer": "6586 + 8576 = 15162"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = AGAIN", "Answer": "7587 + 8517 = 16104"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAFE = ENTER", "Answer": "1781 + 8731 = 10512"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = EXTRA", "Answer": "3193 + 9163 = 12356"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = THREE", "Answer": "1291 + 9231 = 10522"}
{"Question": "TEST + SEAT = TRACE", "Answer": "1291 + 9251 = 10542"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALE = METAL", "Answer": "4794 + 9784 = 14578"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "4894 + 9814 = 14708"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEXT = STATE", "Answer": "4894 + 9854 = 14748"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = SORRY", "Answer": "9419 + 1466 = 10885"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = SUPER", "Answer": "8718 + 1755 = 10473"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = METER", "Answer": "9459 + 5488 = 14947"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = ISSUE", "Answer": "9759 + 5788 = 15547"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = CLOCK", "Answer": "8368 + 6344 = 14712"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = PHOTO", "Answer": "3473 + 7466 = 10939"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = ALTER", "Answer": "9479 + 7466 = 16945"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = EARTH", "Answer": "2182 + 8144 = 10326"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = REFER", "Answer": "6486 + 8455 = 14941"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = TRUTH", "Answer": "1781 + 8733 = 10514"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = TRACE", "Answer": "1781 + 8766 = 10547"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = TROOP", "Answer": "1291 + 9266 = 10557"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELL = APPLE", "Answer": "8398 + 9355 = 17753"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SOUL = STUFF", "Answer": "9217 + 1249 = 10466"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "9215 + 1279 = 10494"}
{"Question": "GOLD + LONG = LEVEL", "Answer": "9312 + 1389 = 10701"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GIRL = GRASS", "Answer": "9419 + 1403 = 10822"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MORE = MAJOR", "Answer": "9419 + 1423 = 10842"}
{"Question": "PIPE + HIGH = PRESS", "Answer": "1418 + 9459 = 10877"}
{"Question": "LOST + SOIL = STILL", "Answer": "9410 + 1489 = 10899"}
{"Question": "TALE + LAST = SEAT", "Answer": "2510 + 1542 = 4052"}
{"Question": "EARN + RATE = TEAR", "Answer": "2619 + 1642 = 4261"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SLOW = WELL", "Answer": "2612 + 1654 = 4266"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = AREA", "Answer": "3613 + 1652 = 5265"}
{"Question": "LATE + TAIL = TIGHT", "Answer": "8713 + 1708 = 10421"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PART = PRESS", "Answer": "8714 + 1708 = 10422"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SLIP = START", "Answer": "8718 + 1732 = 10450"}
{"Question": "LOST + SOIL = SEIZE", "Answer": "8712 + 1748 = 10460"}
{"Question": "PACE + CAMP = CHECK", "Answer": "8715 + 1798 = 10513"}
{"Question": "EAST + SAME = SMELL", "Answer": "8914 + 1908 = 10822"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = RATE", "Answer": "1421 + 2493 = 3914"}
{"Question": "TEND + NEXT = INDEX", "Answer": "9826 + 2859 = 12685"}
{"Question": "NOTE + TOWN = OFTEN", "Answer": "9130 + 3179 = 12309"}
{"Question": "RARE + EAST = LATER", "Answer": "3239 + 9254 = 12493"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PART = GREAT", "Answer": "8530 + 3528 = 12058"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = AREA", "Answer": "3632 + 2694 = 6326"}
{"Question": "DOWN + WORD = ERROR", "Answer": "8634 + 3628 = 12262"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAND = ORDER", "Answer": "6736 + 3724 = 10460"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = HEAR", "Answer": "4245 + 5279 = 9524"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = GREEN", "Answer": "4346 + 8318 = 12664"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MOST = SORRY", "Answer": "9349 + 4318 = 13667"}
{"Question": "LATE + TAIL = SHELL", "Answer": "7540 + 4537 = 12077"}
{"Question": "BABY + YARD = ARAB", "Answer": "4641 + 1623 = 6264"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MOST = ODDS", "Answer": "1641 + 4698 = 6339"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = AGENT", "Answer": "4642 + 5605 = 10247"}
{"Question": "TENT + NECK = KNEE", "Answer": "1741 + 4736 = 6477"}
{"Question": "RARE + GANG = AREA", "Answer": "4745 + 2712 = 7457"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELF = CLOSE", "Answer": "5845 + 4803 = 10648"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SLIP = RIVER", "Answer": "5945 + 4906 = 10851"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEWS = WASTE", "Answer": "7357 + 5316 = 12673"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOMB = HELLO", "Answer": "5354 + 9309 = 14663"}
{"Question": "NOTE + TOWN = SWEET", "Answer": "7458 + 5427 = 12885"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = LEVEL", "Answer": "5453 + 8478 = 13931"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOMB = MODEL", "Answer": "5457 + 9419 = 14876"}
{"Question": "NOTE + TOWN = BELOW", "Answer": "7653 + 5607 = 13260"}
{"Question": "RARE + GANG = OWNER", "Answer": "5658 + 7627 = 13285"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SOIL = VIDEO", "Answer": "7659 + 5637 = 13296"}
{"Question": "RARE + GANG = TREAT", "Answer": "5652 + 9609 = 15261"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PAST = SPEAK", "Answer": "9754 + 5719 = 15473"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MORE = GREEN", "Answer": "6956 + 5928 = 12884"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SLOW = ORDER", "Answer": "7957 + 5916 = 13873"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GIRL = RIGHT", "Answer": "7367 + 6312 = 13679"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOMB = MONEY", "Answer": "6368 + 7317 = 13685"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "9369 + 6375 = 15744"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = DEAD", "Answer": "6561 + 1597 = 8158"}
{"Question": "RARE + EAST = SALES", "Answer": "6568 + 8513 = 15081"}
{"Question": "RARE + EASY = MAYBE", "Answer": "6568 + 8530 = 15098"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GIRL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8568 + 6574 = 15142"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SOIL = HELLO", "Answer": "5762 + 6795 = 12557"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = CHEEK", "Answer": "6968 + 8915 = 15883"}
{"Question": "TALE + LAST = ASSET", "Answer": "6170 + 7136 = 13306"}
{"Question": "PACE + CAMP = HAPPY", "Answer": "5274 + 7285 = 12559"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = CHART", "Answer": "4674 + 7630 = 12304"}
{"Question": "RARE + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "7678 + 8630 = 16308"}
{"Question": "ROPE + POUR = COLOR", "Answer": "8670 + 7698 = 16368"}
{"Question": "ROPE + POUR = SUPER", "Answer": "5870 + 7835 = 13705"}
{"Question": "GIRL + RING = ONION", "Answer": "5978 + 7935 = 13913"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = CHEAP", "Answer": "7978 + 8916 = 16894"}
{"Question": "EACH + CARE = AFTER", "Answer": "7182 + 8197 = 15379"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = TIGHT", "Answer": "8287 + 4254 = 12541"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PANT = ENTER", "Answer": "5281 + 8235 = 13516"}
{"Question": "BABY + YARD = REFER", "Answer": "8382 + 2319 = 10701"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEND = THREE", "Answer": "2381 + 8352 = 10733"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = EIGHT", "Answer": "8381 + 5375 = 13756"}
{"Question": "NINE + KICK = BEGIN", "Answer": "8483 + 5465 = 13948"}
{"Question": "EARN + RACE = EVENT", "Answer": "1582 + 8541 = 10123"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELF = TOTAL", "Answer": "1581 + 8543 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TASK + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "1586 + 8571 = 10157"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = TITLE", "Answer": "1581 + 8594 = 10175"}
{"Question": "KICK + CITY = TITLE", "Answer": "6586 + 8517 = 15103"}
{"Question": "RARE + GANG = PAPER", "Answer": "8582 + 6546 = 15128"}
{"Question": "EASE + SALT = USUAL", "Answer": "9589 + 8567 = 18156"}
{"Question": "HIRE + RICH = HONOR", "Answer": "1687 + 8621 = 10308"}
{"Question": "TERM + REST = TASTE", "Answer": "1685 + 8631 = 10316"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GIRL = HELLO", "Answer": "1681 + 8653 = 10334"}
{"Question": "BABY + GANG = GREEN", "Answer": "8684 + 1651 = 10335"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEWS = THOSE", "Answer": "1681 + 8675 = 10356"}
{"Question": "POSE + SOUP = PRIOR", "Answer": "1689 + 8671 = 10360"}
{"Question": "GANG + NAME = GIVEN", "Answer": "1681 + 8697 = 10378"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MOST = ERROR", "Answer": "4684 + 8679 = 13363"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "5685 + 8634 = 14319"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = OTHER", "Answer": "8685 + 5673 = 14358"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELF = LEAVE", "Answer": "7687 + 8619 = 16306"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEAR = LEAVE", "Answer": "7687 + 8639 = 16326"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = RIVER", "Answer": "8684 + 7657 = 16341"}
{"Question": "EACH + CARE = ENTER", "Answer": "1782 + 8731 = 10513"}
{"Question": "TENT + NECK = TASTE", "Answer": "1781 + 8736 = 10517"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = EIGHT", "Answer": "8781 + 1742 = 10523"}
{"Question": "BABY + GANG = GIVEN", "Answer": "8783 + 1741 = 10524"}
{"Question": "TAPE + PART = TIRED", "Answer": "1783 + 8751 = 10534"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MOST = BASIS", "Answer": "1781 + 8754 = 10535"}
{"Question": "BABY + GANG = ONION", "Answer": "8789 + 3723 = 12512"}
{"Question": "RARE + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "9196 + 6173 = 15369"}
{"Question": "RARE + GANG = GUESS", "Answer": "9295 + 1271 = 10566"}
{"Question": "HIGH + GIFT = STAFF", "Answer": "7297 + 9236 = 16533"}
{"Question": "RARE + EACH = ENTER", "Answer": "9391 + 1328 = 10719"}
{"Question": "TENT + NEWS = ASIAN", "Answer": "5395 + 9324 = 14719"}
{"Question": "GIRL + RING = FLOOR", "Answer": "5394 + 9385 = 14779"}
{"Question": "TEST + SELF = TASTE", "Answer": "1491 + 9423 = 10914"}
{"Question": "TERM + REST = THREE", "Answer": "1493 + 9451 = 10944"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = CHEAP", "Answer": "9693 + 2682 = 12375"}
{"Question": "PACK + CAMP = UPPER", "Answer": "3692 + 9683 = 13375"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIGH = SHELL", "Answer": "9693 + 4684 = 14377"}
{"Question": "EASE + SAND = MEDIA", "Answer": "2792 + 9745 = 12537"}
{"Question": "HIDE + DISH = AHEAD", "Answer": "4795 + 9724 = 14519"}
{"Question": "HIRE + RICH = THEIR", "Answer": "4795 + 9784 = 14579"}
{"Question": "SEND + NEWS = ISSUE", "Answer": "5792 + 9745 = 15537"}
{"Question": "RARE + EAST = METER", "Answer": "9892 + 2837 = 12729"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = EASE", "Answer": "3831 + 1534 = 5365"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = START", "Answer": "3738 + 8634 = 12372"}
{"Question": "EVEN + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "4541 + 3843 = 8384"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAT = STAGE", "Answer": "4547 + 7942 = 12489"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOAT = ONION", "Answer": "5857 + 7156 = 13013"}
{"Question": "NONE + GANG = ONION", "Answer": "5156 + 9859 = 15015"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = REFER", "Answer": "6167 + 7364 = 13531"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAD = FEED", "Answer": "6960 + 1261 = 8221"}
{"Question": "NINE + GANG = BEGIN", "Answer": "7472 + 5075 = 12547"}
{"Question": "AWAY + THAT = WHITE", "Answer": "7178 + 5275 = 12453"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = HEART", "Answer": "7475 + 5273 = 12748"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAD = GRADE", "Answer": "7279 + 5475 = 12754"}
{"Question": "AWAY + DEAD = CYCLE", "Answer": "7273 + 5875 = 13148"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = BIBLE", "Answer": "8781 + 1382 = 10163"}
{"Question": "EVEN + AREA = APART", "Answer": "8482 + 1681 = 10163"}
{"Question": "EVEN + AREA = AWARE", "Answer": "8487 + 1681 = 10168"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = BUYER", "Answer": "8581 + 1684 = 10265"}
{"Question": "EVEN + AREA = ABOVE", "Answer": "8687 + 1581 = 10268"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEAN = OWNER", "Answer": "8783 + 3684 = 12467"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOAT = SOLAR", "Answer": "9294 + 4398 = 13692"}
{"Question": "EVEN + AREA = INNER", "Answer": "9296 + 7397 = 16693"}
{"Question": "COOK + KICK = CLASS", "Answer": "1448 + 8918 = 10366"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = SHEET", "Answer": "9719 + 1279 = 10998"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = USUAL", "Answer": "9839 + 3289 = 13128"}
{"Question": "COOK + KICK = BIBLE", "Answer": "4778 + 8348 = 13126"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = LATER", "Answer": "7157 + 5217 = 12374"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = ARAB", "Answer": "2352 + 5832 = 8184"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = LEAD", "Answer": "2852 + 5382 = 8234"}
{"Question": "COOK + KICK = TOOTH", "Answer": "7335 + 5975 = 13310"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = IDEAL", "Answer": "4874 + 7584 = 12458"}
{"Question": "COOK + KICK = TOPIC", "Answer": "8224 + 4084 = 12308"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = RURAL", "Answer": "3683 + 8463 = 12146"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = ENEMY", "Answer": "1781 + 8371 = 10152"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALE = EIGHT", "Answer": "1781 + 8671 = 10452"}
{"Question": "BABY + THAT = BIRTH", "Answer": "1619 + 8768 = 10387"}
{"Question": "SITE + THIS = TRUST", "Answer": "8613 + 1968 = 10581"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROOT = ENTRY", "Answer": "1918 + 8665 = 10583"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALT = SALES", "Answer": "9719 + 1072 = 10791"}
{"Question": "SOON + ELSE = STEEL", "Answer": "1773 + 9219 = 10992"}
{"Question": "RANK + NEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "8524 + 2058 = 10582"}
{"Question": "POSE + STOP = ASSET", "Answer": "9528 + 2759 = 12287"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BURY = MAYBE", "Answer": "2629 + 9864 = 12493"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MOST = TOOTH", "Answer": "2997 + 7021 = 10018"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROOM = MERE", "Answer": "3235 + 5118 = 8353"}
{"Question": "POST + SHOP = FORTH", "Answer": "9236 + 3529 = 12765"}
{"Question": "BABY + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "3439 + 8748 = 12187"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "3556 + 6830 = 10386"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOP = LOOSE", "Answer": "3559 + 9837 = 13396"}
{"Question": "BABY + THAT = EARTH", "Answer": "4349 + 8738 = 13087"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TURN = MONTH", "Answer": "4338 + 8942 = 13280"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BIRD = IRAQI", "Answer": "4349 + 9132 = 13481"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROOF = STATE", "Answer": "4346 + 6558 = 10904"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "4778 + 8643 = 13421"}
{"Question": "BABY + DEAD = AIDE", "Answer": "4849 + 3283 = 8132"}
{"Question": "RANK + NEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "8159 + 5718 = 13877"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIFT = RIFLE", "Answer": "5228 + 8354 = 13582"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOE = DESK", "Answer": "5661 + 1057 = 6718"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TEND = ERROR", "Answer": "4854 + 5186 = 10040"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5886 + 6251 = 12137"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOT = DEATH", "Answer": "6114 + 4268 = 10382"}
{"Question": "LADY + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "8165 + 6318 = 14483"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOW = AWARD", "Answer": "6338 + 8765 = 15103"}
{"Question": "BABY + THAT = CATCH", "Answer": "6465 + 8348 = 14813"}
{"Question": "POST + SHOP = TOOTH", "Answer": "8561 + 6958 = 15519"}
{"Question": "RARE + THAT = BIRTH", "Answer": "6765 + 3873 = 10638"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YEAR = TRAIL", "Answer": "6775 + 5862 = 12637"}
{"Question": "BABY + DEAD = CYCLE", "Answer": "6765 + 8378 = 15143"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "6887 + 7265 = 14152"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MOST = ERROR", "Answer": "7112 + 2978 = 10090"}
{"Question": "MOON + NAME = TREAT", "Answer": "7228 + 8073 = 15301"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TURN = ENTER", "Answer": "7445 + 5072 = 12517"}
{"Question": "DARK + READ = MAKER", "Answer": "8579 + 7358 = 15937"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOT = THIRD", "Answer": "7665 + 5271 = 12936"}
{"Question": "RARE + THAT = SHELL", "Answer": "7679 + 5265 = 12944"}
{"Question": "EASE + STAR = THREE", "Answer": "5875 + 7180 = 13055"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8224 + 4580 = 12804"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SALT = WASTE", "Answer": "7287 + 8520 = 15807"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SHOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "8227 + 7581 = 15808"}
{"Question": "TASK + SEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1384 + 8631 = 10015"}
{"Question": "BABY + THAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8385 + 1631 = 10016"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BORN = COLOR", "Answer": "8384 + 4239 = 12623"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8984 + 4331 = 13315"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TEND = ADOPT", "Answer": "5485 + 8043 = 13528"}
{"Question": "NEED + GANG = DANCE", "Answer": "8551 + 4284 = 12835"}
{"Question": "GOOD + HIGH = TIGHT", "Answer": "8557 + 4284 = 12841"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YEAH = HOTEL", "Answer": "8554 + 4381 = 12935"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BIRD = DRAMA", "Answer": "8587 + 7251 = 15838"}
{"Question": "LADY + DEAL = LOOSE", "Answer": "1682 + 8361 = 10043"}
{"Question": "EASE + SNAP = EVENT", "Answer": "1681 + 8462 = 10143"}
{"Question": "NEED + GANG = JUDGE", "Answer": "8662 + 4584 = 13246"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOOK = BUYER", "Answer": "8481 + 1773 = 10254"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RIDE = RATIO", "Answer": "8771 + 1586 = 10357"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "8772 + 2085 = 10857"}
{"Question": "BABY + DEAD = ORDER", "Answer": "8789 + 4674 = 13463"}
{"Question": "RISE + STIR = TIRED", "Answer": "9786 + 8179 = 17965"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TERM = OFFER", "Answer": "9113 + 3096 = 12209"}
{"Question": "SOON + TEST = TASTE", "Answer": "9225 + 1691 = 10916"}
{"Question": "DARK + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "3296 + 9123 = 12419"}
{"Question": "ALLY + THAT = SHELL", "Answer": "9228 + 4394 = 13622"}
{"Question": "EASE + STAR = GREAT", "Answer": "8298 + 9527 = 17825"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RIDE = RAPID", "Answer": "9331 + 1298 = 10629"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOOK = COLOR", "Answer": "9294 + 4338 = 13632"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TURN = INNER", "Answer": "9335 + 5094 = 14429"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9441 + 1398 = 10839"}
{"Question": "NEWS + WHEN = SHINE", "Answer": "3491 + 9243 = 12734"}
{"Question": "EASE + STAR = TREAT", "Answer": "6496 + 9145 = 15641"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TURN = THREE", "Answer": "9661 + 1294 = 10955"}
{"Question": "RARE + THAT = THEIR", "Answer": "9798 + 1071 = 10869"}
{"Question": "NONE + EDGE = GOOD", "Answer": "1815 + 5065 = 6880"}
{"Question": "TEST + SPOT = PIPE", "Answer": "6216 + 1756 = 7972"}
{"Question": "EASE + SITE = STEAL", "Answer": "9219 + 1709 = 10928"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOMB = ALLOW", "Answer": "1318 + 8758 = 10076"}
{"Question": "RARE + ELSE = RURAL", "Answer": "1518 + 8638 = 10156"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SHOE = HELL", "Answer": "4814 + 1674 = 6488"}
{"Question": "EASE + SURE = AREA", "Answer": "3623 + 2513 = 6136"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHIT = HIGH", "Answer": "3923 + 2653 = 6576"}
{"Question": "NINE + ELSE = LIMIT", "Answer": "3037 + 7167 = 10204"}
{"Question": "RARE + EDGE = AREA", "Answer": "3834 + 4514 = 8348"}
{"Question": "NONE + EASE = ODDS", "Answer": "4843 + 3163 = 8006"}
{"Question": "EASE + SURE = ARMED", "Answer": "8148 + 4938 = 13086"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8548 + 4638 = 13186"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BOMB = START", "Answer": "4845 + 5635 = 10480"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SHOE = MODEL", "Answer": "8648 + 4938 = 13586"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SOME = MODEL", "Answer": "7457 + 5217 = 12674"}
{"Question": "NINE + EASE = BASIS", "Answer": "5258 + 8368 = 13626"}
{"Question": "NINE + ELSE = STEEL", "Answer": "5357 + 7417 = 12774"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHUT = COUCH", "Answer": "4754 + 5864 = 10618"}
{"Question": "EASE + SIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7167 + 6547 = 13714"}
{"Question": "NONE + EASE = OCEAN", "Answer": "6168 + 8708 = 14876"}
{"Question": "NONE + EDGE = OCEAN", "Answer": "6168 + 8728 = 14896"}
{"Question": "NINE + ELSE = CLEAN", "Answer": "6368 + 8458 = 14826"}
{"Question": "EASE + SURE = GUESS", "Answer": "8368 + 6498 = 14866"}
{"Question": "EASE + SHOE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6076 + 7236 = 13312"}
{"Question": "TEST + SPOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "3473 + 7163 = 10636"}
{"Question": "RARE + EDGE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7178 + 8638 = 15816"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ACID = GUIDE", "Answer": "6276 + 7586 = 13862"}
{"Question": "NINE + ELSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "7379 + 9619 = 16998"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ACID = SENSE", "Answer": "8678 + 7538 = 16216"}
{"Question": "TEST + SOFT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1981 + 8031 = 10012"}
{"Question": "NINE + EASE = GIVEN", "Answer": "8284 + 4064 = 12348"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1781 + 8231 = 10012"}
{"Question": "EASE + SIDE = BASIS", "Answer": "4284 + 8574 = 12858"}
{"Question": "TEST + SHIT = WHITE", "Answer": "6286 + 8476 = 14762"}
{"Question": "RARE + EDGE = PAPER", "Answer": "8384 + 4764 = 13148"}
{"Question": "ELSE + SURE = RURAL", "Answer": "7487 + 8617 = 16104"}
{"Question": "RARE + ELSE = SWEAR", "Answer": "8984 + 4514 = 13498"}
{"Question": "RARE + ELSE = ASIAN", "Answer": "9193 + 3523 = 12716"}
{"Question": "TEST + SALT = WASTE", "Answer": "3693 + 9243 = 12936"}
{"Question": "NONE + EASE = HELLO", "Answer": "9693 + 3753 = 13446"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MESS = SEEM", "Answer": "5015 + 1866 = 6881"}
{"Question": "TAPE + POET = PRIOR", "Answer": "8912 + 1428 = 10340"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = EARN", "Answer": "2427 + 5075 = 7502"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BELL = START", "Answer": "3836 + 6544 = 10380"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BELL = REFER", "Answer": "4146 + 6055 = 10201"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BELL = PAPER", "Answer": "4749 + 9388 = 14137"}
{"Question": "KICK + CELL = LAKE", "Answer": "1051 + 5766 = 6817"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = RELAX", "Answer": "5352 + 7127 = 12479"}
{"Question": "TOWN + WANT = ALLOW", "Answer": "9256 + 5169 = 14425"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = BRAIN", "Answer": "5458 + 7287 = 12745"}
{"Question": "BABY + YELL = SALES", "Answer": "5458 + 8933 = 14391"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TREE = ROOT", "Answer": "1261 + 6855 = 8116"}
{"Question": "TYPE + POET = FIFTY", "Answer": "5368 + 6785 = 12153"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TELL = ELECT", "Answer": "5075 + 7122 = 12197"}
{"Question": "FACE + CHEF = AHEAD", "Answer": "5174 + 7245 = 12419"}
{"Question": "EVEN + GANG = ANGLE", "Answer": "7472 + 5125 = 12597"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = GRASS", "Answer": "7276 + 8568 = 15844"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROLL = SOLVE", "Answer": "7975 + 5322 = 13297"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TALL = UNION", "Answer": "6476 + 7588 = 14064"}
{"Question": "TOWN + WANT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1083 + 8931 = 10014"}
{"Question": "BABY + YELL = TASTE", "Answer": "8082 + 2533 = 10615"}
{"Question": "NOTE + THEN = HONOR", "Answer": "7586 + 8167 = 15753"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TREE = OCCUR", "Answer": "1281 + 8766 = 10047"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "8286 + 5365 = 13651"}
{"Question": "PIPE + AREA = AGAIN", "Answer": "8385 + 1751 = 10136"}
{"Question": "FACE + CHEF = LEGAL", "Answer": "6485 + 8756 = 15241"}
{"Question": "EVEN + GANG = GLOVE", "Answer": "8587 + 1671 = 10258"}
{"Question": "TAPE + POET = TROOP", "Answer": "1987 + 8571 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TREE = NEVER", "Answer": "7197 + 9366 = 16563"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TALL = OFTEN", "Answer": "1691 + 9255 = 10946"}
{"Question": "NINE + AREA = FIBER", "Answer": "9398 + 4284 = 13682"}
{"Question": "EVER + ROLL = ALIVE", "Answer": "9395 + 5244 = 14639"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TELL = OFTEN", "Answer": "1591 + 9344 = 10935"}
{"Question": "SALT + LOTS = ESSAY", "Answer": "2394 + 9842 = 12236"}
{"Question": "ONTO + TALL = LATIN", "Answer": "4594 + 9311 = 13905"}
{"Question": "DIRT + ROAD = RADIO", "Answer": "9218 + 1709 = 10927"}
{"Question": "EVER + ONTO = TENT", "Answer": "1312 + 5875 = 7187"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BOMB = ERROR", "Answer": "1312 + 8758 = 10070"}
{"Question": "BOMB + MARK = ORDER", "Answer": "8138 + 3924 = 12062"}
{"Question": "EVER + GANG = ANGRY", "Answer": "3836 + 9129 = 12965"}
{"Question": "EASE + STIR = TREAT", "Answer": "9839 + 3142 = 12981"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BITE = START", "Answer": "3638 + 8724 = 12362"}
{"Question": "PACE + CROP = TREAT", "Answer": "8043 + 4258 = 12301"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THIS = ASIAN", "Answer": "8048 + 4562 = 12610"}
{"Question": "EARN + ROLE = ALTER", "Answer": "8146 + 4938 = 13084"}
{"Question": "NINE + EAST = FIFTH", "Answer": "4247 + 7938 = 12185"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOMB = LABEL", "Answer": "4342 + 9579 = 13921"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BEST = STARE", "Answer": "4547 + 7912 = 12459"}
{"Question": "EVER + GANG = TREAT", "Answer": "4943 + 8508 = 13451"}
{"Question": "STAR + AIDS = IRAQI", "Answer": "8453 + 5108 = 13561"}
{"Question": "NONE + EACH = ORDER", "Answer": "5158 + 8926 = 14084"}
{"Question": "RARE + ONTO = ACTOR", "Answer": "5156 + 9239 = 14395"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GROW = AWARD", "Answer": "8258 + 5934 = 14192"}
{"Question": "PAST + SLIP = TOTAL", "Answer": "6351 + 5786 = 12137"}
{"Question": "EACH + COPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7359 + 5817 = 13176"}
{"Question": "THAT + ACID = WHICH", "Answer": "8458 + 5936 = 14394"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BIRD = ORDER", "Answer": "7956 + 5837 = 13793"}
{"Question": "TALE + LIST = ASSET", "Answer": "8160 + 6248 = 14408"}
{"Question": "RARE + ONTO = ENTER", "Answer": "7071 + 6346 = 13417"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TENT = ENTER", "Answer": "7478 + 6136 = 13614"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TENT = ENTER", "Answer": "7479 + 6136 = 13615"}
{"Question": "RING + NEAR = EAGER", "Answer": "6870 + 7146 = 14016"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOMB = PAPER", "Answer": "7273 + 4864 = 12137"}
{"Question": "ONTO + THIS = SHOOT", "Answer": "6276 + 7391 = 13667"}
{"Question": "NINE + BOMB = MONEY", "Answer": "7479 + 6316 = 13795"}
{"Question": "TURN + REST = INNER", "Answer": "5083 + 8245 = 13328"}
{"Question": "TYPE + PAST = ESSAY", "Answer": "9081 + 8679 = 17760"}
{"Question": "EVEN + THAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8286 + 1731 = 10017"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BIND = BEGIN", "Answer": "8781 + 1465 = 10246"}
{"Question": "EASE + SHIT = CATCH", "Answer": "5485 + 8732 = 14217"}
{"Question": "EASE + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "4784 + 8531 = 13315"}
{"Question": "TEST + SAND = TASTE", "Answer": "1891 + 9027 = 10918"}
{"Question": "TEST + SPIN = TROOP", "Answer": "1291 + 9483 = 10774"}
{"Question": "ARAB + BLOW = FLOOR", "Answer": "9294 + 4368 = 13662"}
{"Question": "EDGE + GROW = EAGER", "Answer": "1391 + 9524 = 10915"}
{"Question": "NINE + WINE = VIEW", "Answer": "1012 + 4012 = 5024"}
{"Question": "PIPE + WIPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "1217 + 9217 = 10434"}
{"Question": "RARE + DARE = AIDE", "Answer": "1310 + 2310 = 3620"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVER = ENTRY", "Answer": "1312 + 9312 = 10624"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = ALBUM", "Answer": "1418 + 9418 = 10836"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVEN = MOON", "Answer": "1610 + 2610 = 4220"}
{"Question": "PIPE + WIPE = POWER", "Answer": "1912 + 8912 = 10824"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARE = ERROR", "Answer": "2621 + 9621 = 12242"}
{"Question": "NONE + TONE = INTO", "Answer": "2623 + 4623 = 7246"}
{"Question": "NONE + BONE = ONTO", "Answer": "2628 + 3628 = 6256"}
{"Question": "PIPE + WIPE = SPEED", "Answer": "2724 + 9724 = 12448"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVEN = VOTE", "Answer": "2726 + 4726 = 7452"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = PHOTO", "Answer": "2823 + 7823 = 10646"}
{"Question": "NONE + BONE = ERROR", "Answer": "3631 + 8631 = 12262"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVER = DRAMA", "Answer": "3732 + 8732 = 12464"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = ROOF", "Answer": "3831 + 4831 = 8662"}
{"Question": "NINE + MINE = ITEM", "Answer": "3837 + 4837 = 8674"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = ERROR", "Answer": "4045 + 6045 = 10090"}
{"Question": "NONE + TONE = PHOTO", "Answer": "4045 + 9045 = 13090"}
{"Question": "NONE + TONE = MONTH", "Answer": "4243 + 8243 = 12486"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = DRAMA", "Answer": "4247 + 8247 = 12494"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = FIELD", "Answer": "4346 + 9346 = 13692"}
{"Question": "NINE + MINE = THEME", "Answer": "4540 + 8540 = 13080"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = ERROR", "Answer": "4641 + 7641 = 12282"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = BASIS", "Answer": "4641 + 9641 = 14282"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVER = FLOOR", "Answer": "4940 + 8940 = 13880"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = BLOOD", "Answer": "4941 + 5941 = 10882"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = TRUTH", "Answer": "5356 + 8356 = 13712"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = TOOTH", "Answer": "5659 + 7659 = 13318"}
{"Question": "PIPE + WIPE = ONION", "Answer": "5957 + 8957 = 14914"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = BELL", "Answer": "6061 + 3061 = 9122"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6365 + 9365 = 15730"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = BIBLE", "Answer": "6560 + 8560 = 15120"}
{"Question": "NINE + WINE = FEWER", "Answer": "6762 + 5762 = 12524"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = STATE", "Answer": "6860 + 5860 = 12720"}
{"Question": "RARE + DARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6864 + 7864 = 14728"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = AIDE", "Answer": "6960 + 1960 = 8920"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = FLOOR", "Answer": "7276 + 3276 = 10552"}
{"Question": "NONE + BONE = HELLO", "Answer": "7276 + 9276 = 16552"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVER = DRESS", "Answer": "7372 + 5372 = 12744"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = FINAL", "Answer": "7378 + 6378 = 13756"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = CYCLE", "Answer": "7570 + 4570 = 12140"}
{"Question": "NONE + TONE = ELECT", "Answer": "7571 + 2571 = 10142"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = TRIBE", "Answer": "7675 + 8675 = 16350"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = PROOF", "Answer": "8386 + 5386 = 13772"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = STEEL", "Answer": "8387 + 4387 = 12774"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = RIFLE", "Answer": "8480 + 6480 = 14960"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = BIBLE", "Answer": "8580 + 6580 = 15160"}
{"Question": "NINE + PINE = PAPER", "Answer": "8587 + 1587 = 10174"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARE = ESSAY", "Answer": "8681 + 4681 = 13362"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8682 + 7682 = 16364"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = LATER", "Answer": "8687 + 1687 = 10374"}
{"Question": "NINE + MINE = LEMON", "Answer": "8784 + 5784 = 14568"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARE = EXACT", "Answer": "8981 + 6981 = 15962"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARE = CLASS", "Answer": "8983 + 1983 = 10966"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = SKILL", "Answer": "8983 + 6983 = 15966"}
{"Question": "NONE + BONE = BROWN", "Answer": "8984 + 1984 = 10968"}
{"Question": "NINE + PINE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8985 + 1985 = 10970"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARE = BEACH", "Answer": "8986 + 7986 = 16972"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINE = IDEAL", "Answer": "9193 + 6193 = 15386"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVEN = VIDEO", "Answer": "9198 + 6198 = 15396"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = URBAN", "Answer": "9295 + 3295 = 12590"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = SUGAR", "Answer": "9296 + 5296 = 14592"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVEN = ORDER", "Answer": "9395 + 1395 = 10790"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVEN = OWNER", "Answer": "9397 + 1397 = 10794"}
{"Question": "NINE + FINE = FENCE", "Answer": "9490 + 1490 = 10980"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAB = GIANT", "Answer": "9493 + 1493 = 10986"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = RIVER", "Answer": "1213 + 9218 = 10431"}
{"Question": "RARE + PART = TROOP", "Answer": "2728 + 9721 = 12449"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVEN = NONE", "Answer": "3236 + 4237 = 7473"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "3631 + 9632 = 13263"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINK = SKILL", "Answer": "4046 + 8042 = 12088"}
{"Question": "NINE + RING = AGREE", "Answer": "4348 + 6340 = 10688"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = AREA", "Answer": "4749 + 2748 = 7497"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DRAG = BLOOD", "Answer": "4941 + 7946 = 12887"}
{"Question": "NONE + LONG = HELLO", "Answer": "4943 + 8946 = 13889"}
{"Question": "RARE + FARM = AHEAD", "Answer": "5153 + 9157 = 14310"}
{"Question": "RARE + PART = CATCH", "Answer": "5359 + 8357 = 13716"}
{"Question": "RARE + PART = TOOTH", "Answer": "5659 + 7651 = 13310"}
{"Question": "RARE + WARN = HONOR", "Answer": "5652 + 4653 = 10305"}
{"Question": "NINE + MIND = LEMON", "Answer": "5853 + 7852 = 13705"}
{"Question": "ARAB + WRAP = UPPER", "Answer": "6267 + 9265 = 15532"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIND = VIDEO", "Answer": "6463 + 8469 = 14932"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DRAW = FEWER", "Answer": "6465 + 7469 = 13934"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = PAPER", "Answer": "6562 + 8564 = 15126"}
{"Question": "RARE + WARM = FEWER", "Answer": "6762 + 5764 = 12526"}
{"Question": "NINE + RING = FEWER", "Answer": "6862 + 5863 = 12725"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIND = SEVEN", "Answer": "6862 + 5864 = 12726"}
{"Question": "NINE + RING = ANGER", "Answer": "6862 + 9867 = 16729"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINK = KICK", "Answer": "6960 + 1968 = 8928"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVER = DRIVE", "Answer": "7472 + 8475 = 15947"}
{"Question": "NINE + RING = LEARN", "Answer": "7672 + 4675 = 12347"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = UNDER", "Answer": "7674 + 2673 = 10347"}
{"Question": "RARE + WARN = INNER", "Answer": "7674 + 5673 = 13347"}
{"Question": "RARE + DARK = MAKER", "Answer": "7674 + 8673 = 16347"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVEN = TREAT", "Answer": "7872 + 4879 = 12751"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DRAG = GREEN", "Answer": "8389 + 5381 = 13770"}
{"Question": "RARE + DARK = NAKED", "Answer": "8487 + 6489 = 14976"}
{"Question": "RARE + YARD = DELAY", "Answer": "8684 + 5681 = 14365"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = CLEAR", "Answer": "8683 + 1685 = 10368"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINK = FIELD", "Answer": "8683 + 7689 = 16372"}
{"Question": "EVER + OVEN = SERVE", "Answer": "8683 + 9685 = 18368"}
{"Question": "NINE + LINK = LABEL", "Answer": "8687 + 1684 = 10371"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = COVER", "Answer": "8786 + 1782 = 10568"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = MEDIA", "Answer": "8782 + 3785 = 12567"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GRAY = LAYER", "Answer": "8782 + 9785 = 18567"}
{"Question": "NONE + LONG = BEGIN", "Answer": "8783 + 4785 = 13568"}
{"Question": "RARE + CARD = TREAT", "Answer": "8785 + 9786 = 18571"}
{"Question": "NINE + PINK = PRESS", "Answer": "9295 + 1293 = 10588"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OVER = PANEL", "Answer": "9295 + 7298 = 16593"}
{"Question": "NINE + KING = AGENT", "Answer": "9397 + 6395 = 15792"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DRAW = SWEAR", "Answer": "9398 + 6395 = 15793"}
{"Question": "NINE + TINY = AGENT", "Answer": "9397 + 5398 = 14795"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DRAG = GRASS", "Answer": "9497 + 5491 = 14988"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = CARRY", "Answer": "1228 + 9218 = 10446"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = AGREE", "Answer": "1332 + 9312 = 10644"}
{"Question": "COOK + ROCK = CHAIR", "Answer": "1664 + 8614 = 10278"}
{"Question": "SEEK + DESK = EDGE", "Answer": "1884 + 6814 = 8698"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = LEAVE", "Answer": "2115 + 8125 = 10240"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FORM = MAKER", "Answer": "2331 + 8321 = 10652"}
{"Question": "NEED + TEND = DATA", "Answer": "2449 + 7429 = 9878"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = BABY", "Answer": "2660 + 5620 = 8280"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = TOSS", "Answer": "3007 + 4037 = 7044"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = STEEL", "Answer": "3447 + 9437 = 12884"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = ODDS", "Answer": "3448 + 2438 = 5886"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = KILL", "Answer": "3886 + 2836 = 6722"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = DRESS", "Answer": "3991 + 6931 = 10922"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = DANCE", "Answer": "4221 + 9241 = 13462"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = CLASS", "Answer": "4223 + 8243 = 12466"}
{"Question": "ROOT + SORT = WORKS", "Answer": "4229 + 8249 = 12478"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = EDGE", "Answer": "4663 + 1643 = 6306"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = RATIO", "Answer": "4663 + 7643 = 12306"}
{"Question": "SEEK + DESK = WORKS", "Answer": "4882 + 5842 = 10724"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = BASIS", "Answer": "5338 + 7358 = 12696"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = HONOR", "Answer": "5774 + 6754 = 12528"}
{"Question": "SEEK + DESK = ODDS", "Answer": "6553 + 1563 = 8116"}
{"Question": "LOOK + FOLK = HEEL", "Answer": "6553 + 2563 = 9116"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = TOTAL", "Answer": "6559 + 8569 = 15128"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = CHEST", "Answer": "7220 + 9270 = 16490"}
{"Question": "NEED + TEND = ADMIT", "Answer": "7223 + 6273 = 13496"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FORM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7449 + 5479 = 12928"}
{"Question": "ROOM + FORM = ENEMY", "Answer": "7552 + 8572 = 16124"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = BLOOD", "Answer": "7662 + 8672 = 16334"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = SLEEP", "Answer": "7664 + 8674 = 16338"}
{"Question": "ROOT + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "7881 + 2871 = 10752"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PORT = OTHER", "Answer": "8114 + 6184 = 14298"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = LIMIT", "Answer": "8117 + 2187 = 10304"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PORT = METER", "Answer": "8449 + 5489 = 13938"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PORT = VOTER", "Answer": "8449 + 6489 = 14938"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PORT = ADAPT", "Answer": "8550 + 3580 = 12130"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8551 + 6581 = 15132"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = TITLE", "Answer": "8551 + 7581 = 16132"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = LIMIT", "Answer": "8660 + 5680 = 14340"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PLAY = PRESS", "Answer": "8662 + 1682 = 10344"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = FULLY", "Answer": "8773 + 5783 = 14556"}
{"Question": "LOOK + FOLK = STEEL", "Answer": "8774 + 3784 = 12558"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SOFT = MOTOR", "Answer": "9225 + 3295 = 12520"}
{"Question": "NEED + TEND = THREE", "Answer": "9226 + 1296 = 10522"}
{"Question": "NEED + TEND = ASSET", "Answer": "9228 + 6298 = 15526"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = PRIOR", "Answer": "9228 + 7298 = 16526"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEND = ORDER", "Answer": "9337 + 5397 = 14734"}
{"Question": "NEED + SEND = SINCE", "Answer": "9442 + 1492 = 10934"}
{"Question": "COOK + LOCK = LUCKY", "Answer": "9443 + 1493 = 10936"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PORT = FORTH", "Answer": "9443 + 5493 = 14936"}
{"Question": "LOOK + GOLF = FEEL", "Answer": "1223 + 7218 = 8441"}
{"Question": "SOON + LOSE = STEAL", "Answer": "1225 + 9214 = 10439"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEBT = RARE", "Answer": "1335 + 4318 = 5653"}
{"Question": "SEED + BEST = SHADE", "Answer": "1335 + 9318 = 10653"}
{"Question": "TOOL + NOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "1443 + 9418 = 10861"}
{"Question": "NONE + GOOD = EDGE", "Answer": "1518 + 6550 = 8068"}
{"Question": "POOL + COPE = PRESS", "Answer": "1665 + 8612 = 10277"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOF = OWNER", "Answer": "2123 + 8115 = 10238"}
{"Question": "FOOD + SOFT = ODDS", "Answer": "2336 + 1325 = 3661"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = FEED", "Answer": "2326 + 5339 = 7665"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOT = ONTO", "Answer": "2627 + 3669 = 6296"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOT = ENTRY", "Answer": "2721 + 9774 = 12495"}
{"Question": "TOOL + VOTE = LEVEL", "Answer": "2881 + 7820 = 10701"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOK = DOZEN", "Answer": "3236 + 9227 = 12463"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = SPEED", "Answer": "3438 + 7449 = 10887"}
{"Question": "MOON + COME = FENCE", "Answer": "3550 + 8532 = 12082"}
{"Question": "SEEM + REST = MOTOR", "Answer": "3771 + 6735 = 10506"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOT = ENTRY", "Answer": "3731 + 9775 = 13506"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOM = MONEY", "Answer": "4246 + 8221 = 12467"}
{"Question": "ROOM + PORT = METER", "Answer": "4661 + 5643 = 10304"}
{"Question": "DOOR + MODE = TERMS", "Answer": "5336 + 9354 = 14690"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOF = AREA", "Answer": "5651 + 3668 = 9319"}
{"Question": "WEEK + NEWS = SKILL", "Answer": "5882 + 6851 = 12733"}
{"Question": "NONE + FOOD = ORDER", "Answer": "6168 + 4112 = 10280"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEBT = WRITE", "Answer": "6223 + 7269 = 13492"}
{"Question": "MOON + COME = INNER", "Answer": "6224 + 8269 = 14493"}
{"Question": "SOON + ROSE = INNER", "Answer": "6775 + 8763 = 15538"}
{"Question": "SOON + HOST = TIGHT", "Answer": "7220 + 9271 = 16491"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOK = PIECE", "Answer": "7274 + 9220 = 16494"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOT = START", "Answer": "7270 + 9226 = 16496"}
{"Question": "NONE + POOL = CLEAN", "Answer": "7274 + 6223 = 13497"}
{"Question": "TOOL + NOTE = ELECT", "Answer": "7556 + 8571 = 16127"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = SORRY", "Answer": "7672 + 8663 = 16335"}
{"Question": "ROOT + MORE = TERMS", "Answer": "7881 + 5873 = 13754"}
{"Question": "ROOM + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "7885 + 6871 = 14756"}
{"Question": "POOL + HOPE = DEPTH", "Answer": "7882 + 6874 = 14756"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOF = INNER", "Answer": "7875 + 9884 = 17759"}
{"Question": "NONE + POOR = REPLY", "Answer": "8283 + 5221 = 13504"}
{"Question": "ROOF + BORN = INNER", "Answer": "8223 + 7285 = 15508"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOK = LEVEL", "Answer": "8382 + 4339 = 12721"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = TIRED", "Answer": "8483 + 2449 = 10932"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = WORLD", "Answer": "8487 + 6449 = 14936"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOOL = ELECT", "Answer": "8581 + 7556 = 16137"}
{"Question": "WOOD + BOWL = LEVEL", "Answer": "8660 + 5681 = 14341"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOF = FEWER", "Answer": "8684 + 5661 = 14345"}
{"Question": "SEED + REST = ROUTE", "Answer": "8662 + 1684 = 10346"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEBT = STATE", "Answer": "8662 + 5684 = 14346"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEBT = DIRTY", "Answer": "8663 + 1684 = 10347"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOK = CLEAN", "Answer": "8683 + 1665 = 10348"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOM = MARRY", "Answer": "8782 + 5771 = 14553"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOL = HELLO", "Answer": "8782 + 3775 = 12557"}
{"Question": "NONE + GOOD = GREEN", "Answer": "8785 + 1773 = 10558"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = GREEN", "Answer": "8785 + 4773 = 13558"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOOK = HELLO", "Answer": "8784 + 5773 = 14557"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOL = CHEEK", "Answer": "8785 + 1774 = 10559"}
{"Question": "LOOK + POLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "8774 + 9785 = 18559"}
{"Question": "ROOF + PORT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8992 + 1987 = 10979"}
{"Question": "NONE + DOOR = ORDER", "Answer": "9190 + 3112 = 12302"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOL = CHECK", "Answer": "9295 + 1223 = 10518"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOT = MOTOR", "Answer": "9298 + 3225 = 12523"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOOM = HUMOR", "Answer": "9298 + 7225 = 16523"}
{"Question": "NONE + COOL = BELOW", "Answer": "9395 + 6337 = 15732"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FLAT = STILL", "Answer": "9338 + 6395 = 15733"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROOM = HUMOR", "Answer": "9398 + 5337 = 14735"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = TRAIL", "Answer": "1644 + 8614 = 10258"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = THEME", "Answer": "1722 + 8712 = 10434"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = SPLIT", "Answer": "2411 + 8421 = 10832"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = RATIO", "Answer": "2633 + 7623 = 10256"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = SLOW", "Answer": "3288 + 5238 = 8526"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = VISIT", "Answer": "4377 + 8347 = 12724"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "5311 + 8351 = 13662"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = COLOR", "Answer": "5488 + 9458 = 14946"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = ERROR", "Answer": "5722 + 8752 = 14474"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = POLL", "Answer": "5966 + 2956 = 8922"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = MOTOR", "Answer": "7355 + 6375 = 13730"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = HELLO", "Answer": "8266 + 5286 = 13552"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = LEAVE", "Answer": "8655 + 1685 = 10340"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = LARGE", "Answer": "9244 + 1294 = 10538"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOTS = LATER", "Answer": "9433 + 1493 = 10926"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEFT = FLEE", "Answer": "7018 + 1082 = 8100"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACE = CHEEK", "Answer": "1233 + 9214 = 10447"}
{"Question": "TALL + DATE = TREND", "Answer": "1255 + 9214 = 10469"}
{"Question": "SELL + DESK = SHADE", "Answer": "1277 + 9215 = 10492"}
{"Question": "LOSS + COLD = LEVEL", "Answer": "1288 + 9213 = 10501"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACE = CHIEF", "Answer": "1344 + 9315 = 10659"}
{"Question": "ROLL + FORM = REFER", "Answer": "1488 + 9413 = 10901"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = LOSS", "Answer": "3419 + 1492 = 4911"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8512 + 1523 = 10035"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEFT = LOOSE", "Answer": "8516 + 1569 = 10085"}
{"Question": "ROLL + PORT = RATIO", "Answer": "1644 + 8612 = 10256"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = START", "Answer": "8913 + 1937 = 10850"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = UNDER", "Answer": "8914 + 1945 = 10859"}
{"Question": "SELL + REST = SORRY", "Answer": "1966 + 8917 = 10883"}
{"Question": "RARE + FALL = LEAF", "Answer": "1918 + 5977 = 7895"}
{"Question": "LESS + BELT = LABEL", "Answer": "1977 + 8914 = 10891"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = OWNER", "Answer": "2125 + 8133 = 10258"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOSS = OWNER", "Answer": "2129 + 8166 = 10295"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = LEVEL", "Answer": "8127 + 2174 = 10301"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = INNER", "Answer": "7526 + 2569 = 10095"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOSS = ONTO", "Answer": "2625 + 3611 = 6236"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = MOTOR", "Answer": "3436 + 9488 = 12924"}
{"Question": "NONE + POEM = ERROR", "Answer": "3531 + 6519 = 10050"}
{"Question": "NINE + KISS = ASSET", "Answer": "3635 + 8622 = 12257"}
{"Question": "ROLL + FORM = DRAMA", "Answer": "3644 + 9638 = 13282"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOSS = INTO", "Answer": "3639 + 1677 = 5316"}
{"Question": "SELL + DESK = TASTE", "Answer": "3677 + 8639 = 12316"}
{"Question": "PART + RATE = TROOP", "Answer": "9731 + 3718 = 13449"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = ENTER", "Answer": "3731 + 9788 = 13519"}
{"Question": "PASS + TAPE = ASSET", "Answer": "4122 + 8146 = 12268"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEBT = ELITE", "Answer": "4133 + 9148 = 13281"}
{"Question": "TALL + DATE = LATER", "Answer": "4211 + 8245 = 12456"}
{"Question": "RARE + MALL = TERMS", "Answer": "4243 + 9255 = 13498"}
{"Question": "NONE + POLL = SLEEP", "Answer": "4346 + 8322 = 12668"}
{"Question": "WELL + NEWS = TASTE", "Answer": "4366 + 8347 = 12713"}
{"Question": "LIST + SITE = ENTER", "Answer": "6347 + 4371 = 10718"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CORE = HONOR", "Answer": "4388 + 9346 = 13734"}
{"Question": "NONE + POET = MOTOR", "Answer": "4348 + 9387 = 13735"}
{"Question": "PART + RATE = TREAT", "Answer": "9541 + 4510 = 14051"}
{"Question": "SALT + LATE = CHEST", "Answer": "7543 + 4530 = 12073"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOSS = PANEL", "Answer": "4746 + 8722 = 13468"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = DEATH", "Answer": "4749 + 8733 = 13482"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CORE = ERROR", "Answer": "4733 + 9741 = 14474"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DIET = STATE", "Answer": "5746 + 4760 = 10506"}
{"Question": "TALL + DATE = MEDIA", "Answer": "4866 + 7842 = 12708"}
{"Question": "WELL + NEWS = ELSE", "Answer": "4877 + 3841 = 8718"}
{"Question": "LESS + BELT = TASTE", "Answer": "4877 + 5841 = 10718"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = OTHER", "Answer": "5152 + 9177 = 14329"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOSS = ORDER", "Answer": "5154 + 7188 = 12342"}
{"Question": "LOSS + POLE = HELLO", "Answer": "5299 + 8253 = 13552"}
{"Question": "BACK + CAKE = MAKER", "Answer": "8357 + 5372 = 13729"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "8357 + 5374 = 13731"}
{"Question": "BABY + CALL = SALAD", "Answer": "5359 + 8377 = 13736"}
{"Question": "LIST + SITE = HOTEL", "Answer": "9357 + 5372 = 14729"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = SOLAR", "Answer": "5358 + 9377 = 14735"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = WOMAN", "Answer": "7452 + 5421 = 12873"}
{"Question": "BABY + MALL = CLIMB", "Answer": "5453 + 7422 = 12875"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOSS = HOTEL", "Answer": "5457 + 9422 = 14879"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BOTH = HELLO", "Answer": "5433 + 7451 = 12884"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = EAGER", "Answer": "5451 + 7466 = 12917"}
{"Question": "MALL + GAME = EAGER", "Answer": "5466 + 9451 = 14917"}
{"Question": "MALL + NAME = CLEAN", "Answer": "5722 + 6754 = 12476"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FREE = STAFF", "Answer": "5756 + 4788 = 10544"}
{"Question": "TALK + LAKE = METAL", "Answer": "6853 + 5832 = 12685"}
{"Question": "LIST + SITE = METER", "Answer": "6857 + 5872 = 12729"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEFT = WASTE", "Answer": "8952 + 5927 = 14879"}
{"Question": "TALL + RATE = HEART", "Answer": "6022 + 8064 = 14086"}
{"Question": "EARN + RANK = PAPER", "Answer": "4067 + 6079 = 10146"}
{"Question": "BABY + MASS = ASIAN", "Answer": "6162 + 9155 = 15317"}
{"Question": "MASS + NAME = ASIAN", "Answer": "6155 + 9164 = 15319"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DIET = ESSAY", "Answer": "8261 + 6219 = 14480"}
{"Question": "NINE + HILL = FLESH", "Answer": "6264 + 7233 = 13497"}
{"Question": "TALK + LAKE = SALES", "Answer": "7362 + 6329 = 13691"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = ORDER", "Answer": "7368 + 6385 = 13753"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEBT = STATE", "Answer": "6388 + 9365 = 15753"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ROLE = SORRY", "Answer": "6411 + 8469 = 14880"}
{"Question": "BACK + CAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "8462 + 6429 = 14891"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = EAGER", "Answer": "6461 + 8455 = 14916"}
{"Question": "NINE + BILL = RIVER", "Answer": "6569 + 8522 = 15091"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEBT = METAL", "Answer": "6533 + 8560 = 15093"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACT = ELITE", "Answer": "6722 + 5769 = 12491"}
{"Question": "LESS + HELP = TASTE", "Answer": "6755 + 3762 = 10517"}
{"Question": "NINE + KILL = CHEEK", "Answer": "6765 + 3788 = 10553"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BORN = ERROR", "Answer": "6822 + 9864 = 16686"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALL = ENTER", "Answer": "6861 + 7855 = 14716"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CORE = OFFER", "Answer": "7155 + 6172 = 13327"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DIET = IRAQI", "Answer": "3176 + 7165 = 10341"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACE = ALTER", "Answer": "7166 + 9174 = 16340"}
{"Question": "LOSS + HOLE = OTHER", "Answer": "7188 + 3176 = 10364"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALL = ACTOR", "Answer": "7179 + 3188 = 10367"}
{"Question": "NINE + KILL = CHECK", "Answer": "7275 + 9244 = 16519"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9275 + 7256 = 16531"}
{"Question": "SELL + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "7266 + 5271 = 12537"}
{"Question": "COPE + POEM = LOCAL", "Answer": "5278 + 7283 = 12561"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = CLASS", "Answer": "5279 + 7298 = 12577"}
{"Question": "RARE + HALL = EARTH", "Answer": "7371 + 6355 = 13726"}
{"Question": "COPE + POET = DEPTH", "Answer": "9376 + 7364 = 16740"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BORN = SENSE", "Answer": "7433 + 5479 = 12912"}
{"Question": "LAWN + WANT = ENTER", "Answer": "6473 + 7439 = 13912"}
{"Question": "CALL + EACH = LABEL", "Answer": "7611 + 8670 = 16281"}
{"Question": "EARN + RANK = NAKED", "Answer": "8671 + 7612 = 16283"}
{"Question": "NONE + POEM = THEME", "Answer": "7673 + 4630 = 12303"}
{"Question": "LAWN + WANT = SENSE", "Answer": "4673 + 7639 = 12312"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACE = EAGER", "Answer": "7644 + 8671 = 16315"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEBT = SENSE", "Answer": "7644 + 8672 = 16316"}
{"Question": "WELL + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "7655 + 4671 = 12326"}
{"Question": "NINE + BILL = SEVEN", "Answer": "7672 + 4655 = 12327"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = ORDER", "Answer": "7672 + 9655 = 17327"}
{"Question": "NINE + BILL = CIVIL", "Answer": "7670 + 8699 = 16369"}
{"Question": "BABY + CALL = LOCAL", "Answer": "7870 + 6811 = 14681"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = ENTRY", "Answer": "7872 + 6811 = 14683"}
{"Question": "ROLL + MORE = LEMON", "Answer": "7811 + 6874 = 14685"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = ERROR", "Answer": "7871 + 9866 = 17737"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = INNER", "Answer": "7873 + 9866 = 17739"}
{"Question": "WELL + NEWS = SCENE", "Answer": "7988 + 5971 = 13959"}
{"Question": "CALL + RACE = ALTER", "Answer": "8144 + 6182 = 14326"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOSS = ERROR", "Answer": "8281 + 7244 = 15525"}
{"Question": "CALL + EACH = SALES", "Answer": "8255 + 4286 = 12541"}
{"Question": "NONE + POEM = EMPTY", "Answer": "8381 + 6314 = 14695"}
{"Question": "GIVE + VIEW = LEGAL", "Answer": "7385 + 8356 = 15741"}
{"Question": "LOSS + COLD = ERROR", "Answer": "8355 + 9382 = 17737"}
{"Question": "NINE + FILL = REFER", "Answer": "8385 + 7366 = 15751"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SLOW = FLOAT", "Answer": "5387 + 8372 = 13759"}
{"Question": "NONE + TOSS = COUNT", "Answer": "8386 + 5399 = 13785"}
{"Question": "DRUG + URGE = PRESS", "Answer": "6483 + 8439 = 14922"}
{"Question": "SIDE + DIET = BASIS", "Answer": "9486 + 8463 = 17949"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = GREAT", "Answer": "8487 + 6499 = 14986"}
{"Question": "CALL + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "8544 + 6582 = 15126"}
{"Question": "NEWS + WEST = TITLE", "Answer": "7584 + 8541 = 16125"}
{"Question": "ROLL + PORT = PAPER", "Answer": "8566 + 1582 = 10148"}
{"Question": "LESS + BELT = BIBLE", "Answer": "8599 + 1586 = 10185"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = FRONT", "Answer": "8685 + 7622 = 16307"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DIET = AHEAD", "Answer": "1683 + 8635 = 10318"}
{"Question": "SELL + REST = ROUTE", "Answer": "8644 + 1682 = 10326"}
{"Question": "WALK + LAKE = WHEEL", "Answer": "1685 + 8653 = 10338"}
{"Question": "BABY + TALL = TREAT", "Answer": "8684 + 1677 = 10361"}
{"Question": "NONE + POEM = PIANO", "Answer": "8689 + 1697 = 10386"}
{"Question": "RARE + HALL = HONOR", "Answer": "8786 + 1722 = 10508"}
{"Question": "BABY + MALL = MEDIA", "Answer": "8783 + 1744 = 10527"}
{"Question": "BABY + FALL = FENCE", "Answer": "8786 + 1744 = 10530"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLL = UPPER", "Answer": "8782 + 6744 = 15526"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = THEIR", "Answer": "8782 + 1755 = 10537"}
{"Question": "ROLL + SORT = SALES", "Answer": "8755 + 1786 = 10541"}
{"Question": "PART + RATE = METER", "Answer": "4785 + 8753 = 13538"}
{"Question": "BIRD + RIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "9785 + 8753 = 18538"}
{"Question": "NINE + BILL = BROWN", "Answer": "8782 + 1766 = 10548"}
{"Question": "CALL + FACT = STATE", "Answer": "8944 + 3982 = 12926"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOSS = BROWN", "Answer": "8982 + 1966 = 10948"}
{"Question": "RIDE + DIET = THIRD", "Answer": "5987 + 8971 = 14958"}
{"Question": "RARE + PASS = PAPER", "Answer": "9094 + 1055 = 10149"}
{"Question": "MALL + CAMP = APPLE", "Answer": "9177 + 4193 = 13370"}
{"Question": "HOPE + POET = OTHER", "Answer": "3198 + 9182 = 12380"}
{"Question": "RARE + CALL = CHEAP", "Answer": "9295 + 1233 = 10528"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALL = THEIR", "Answer": "9295 + 1244 = 10539"}
{"Question": "EARN + RANK = MAKER", "Answer": "3294 + 9245 = 12539"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = METER", "Answer": "9298 + 5244 = 14542"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BORN = INNER", "Answer": "9244 + 6295 = 15539"}
{"Question": "AIDE + DIET = STEAL", "Answer": "4295 + 9253 = 13548"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIET = CHEEK", "Answer": "9295 + 7258 = 16553"}
{"Question": "NONE + POLL = HELLO", "Answer": "9297 + 8255 = 17552"}
{"Question": "PASS + TAPE = TROOP", "Answer": "9266 + 1293 = 10559"}
{"Question": "CALL + EACH = HAPPY", "Answer": "9266 + 3291 = 12557"}
{"Question": "ROPE + POET = VOTER", "Answer": "3298 + 9285 = 12583"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIET = AFTER", "Answer": "9298 + 7285 = 16583"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIET = DRAMA", "Answer": "9395 + 1352 = 10747"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = BUYER", "Answer": "9394 + 1355 = 10749"}
{"Question": "NINE + VIEW = FEWER", "Answer": "9395 + 6357 = 15752"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TREE = FEWER", "Answer": "9398 + 6355 = 15753"}
{"Question": "RARE + BALL = INNER", "Answer": "9394 + 8355 = 17749"}
{"Question": "TALL + PATH = PILOT", "Answer": "9377 + 1392 = 10769"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIET = SPEED", "Answer": "9397 + 5378 = 14775"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIET = STEEL", "Answer": "9397 + 6375 = 15772"}
{"Question": "NINE + FILL = SHELF", "Answer": "9397 + 5388 = 14785"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEBT = STYLE", "Answer": "9388 + 6395 = 15783"}
{"Question": "NINE + HILL = HONEY", "Answer": "9492 + 1433 = 10925"}
{"Question": "TALL + RATE = WATER", "Answer": "9433 + 5492 = 14925"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALL = EARTH", "Answer": "9491 + 5466 = 14957"}
{"Question": "FIVE + VIEW = LEVEL", "Answer": "7496 + 9465 = 16961"}
{"Question": "FALL + SAFE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9677 + 3691 = 13368"}
{"Question": "CALL + RACE = ORDER", "Answer": "9833 + 5892 = 15725"}
{"Question": "NINE + FILL = OFFER", "Answer": "9892 + 7833 = 17725"}
{"Question": "SALT + LAST = SENSE", "Answer": "1395 + 9315 = 10710"}
{"Question": "CARE + RACE = CHECK", "Answer": "1397 + 9317 = 10714"}
{"Question": "NINE + PIPE = DEEP", "Answer": "1418 + 6468 = 7886"}
{"Question": "CARE + RACE = CHEST", "Answer": "1682 + 8612 = 10294"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALE = LIGHT", "Answer": "1684 + 8614 = 10298"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NINE = PHOTO", "Answer": "1712 + 8782 = 10494"}
{"Question": "NINE + PIPE = NORTH", "Answer": "1713 + 8783 = 10496"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NINE = OPEN", "Answer": "2127 + 4147 = 6274"}
{"Question": "NINE + PIPE = SPIN", "Answer": "2821 + 6861 = 9682"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FILE = EQUAL", "Answer": "2871 + 7821 = 10692"}
{"Question": "LAST + SALT = TRIAL", "Answer": "2971 + 7921 = 10892"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FILE = YIELD", "Answer": "3295 + 9235 = 12530"}
{"Question": "NINE + PIPE = DOZEN", "Answer": "4742 + 8782 = 13524"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALE = HEART", "Answer": "5984 + 8954 = 14938"}
{"Question": "NINE + PIPE = TROOP", "Answer": "6269 + 8289 = 14558"}
{"Question": "CARE + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "6584 + 8564 = 15148"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALE = HOTEL", "Answer": "6873 + 7863 = 14736"}
{"Question": "CARE + RACE = WHICH", "Answer": "7298 + 9278 = 16576"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALE = HELLO", "Answer": "7396 + 9376 = 16772"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "7574 + 8584 = 16158"}
{"Question": "NOTE + TONE = UNION", "Answer": "8794 + 9784 = 18578"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = YEAR", "Answer": "1418 + 2423 = 3841"}
{"Question": "FILM + LIFT = METAL", "Answer": "2871 + 7826 = 10697"}
{"Question": "SURE + RUSH = GUESS", "Answer": "3295 + 9238 = 12533"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALK = EVENT", "Answer": "4581 + 8547 = 13128"}
{"Question": "CORE + ROCK = PAPER", "Answer": "4582 + 8546 = 13128"}
{"Question": "RIDE + DIRT = ENTER", "Answer": "4671 + 7643 = 12314"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FILM = METAL", "Answer": "4783 + 8741 = 13524"}
{"Question": "BABY + RARE = COVER", "Answer": "4746 + 8782 = 13528"}
{"Question": "FILE + LIFT = METAL", "Answer": "4783 + 8745 = 13528"}
{"Question": "BABY + RARE = LABEL", "Answer": "5258 + 7273 = 12531"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FILM = SALES", "Answer": "5284 + 8257 = 13541"}
{"Question": "PORT + ROPE = THROW", "Answer": "5371 + 7359 = 12730"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RIDE = STRIP", "Answer": "5372 + 7358 = 12730"}
{"Question": "LATE + TALK = SHELL", "Answer": "5397 + 9358 = 14755"}
{"Question": "RACE + CARD = DRESS", "Answer": "5693 + 9651 = 15344"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RIDE = SPEED", "Answer": "5682 + 8653 = 14335"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = ENTER", "Answer": "5851 + 6864 = 12715"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RIDE = BIRTH", "Answer": "6374 + 7368 = 13742"}
{"Question": "NOSE + SONG = AGENT", "Answer": "6397 + 9365 = 15762"}
{"Question": "NOSE + SONG = AGAIN", "Answer": "6572 + 7564 = 14136"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = PAPER", "Answer": "6564 + 8582 = 15146"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = INNER", "Answer": "6764 + 8782 = 15546"}
{"Question": "TALK + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "6794 + 9765 = 16559"}
{"Question": "NAME + MANY = LEMON", "Answer": "6874 + 7862 = 14736"}
{"Question": "CORN + ROCK = BENCH", "Answer": "7295 + 9278 = 16573"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = LATER", "Answer": "7675 + 8682 = 16357"}
{"Question": "BABY + RARE = LAYER", "Answer": "7673 + 8685 = 16358"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = FRESH", "Answer": "8683 + 9692 = 18375"}
{"Question": "RARE + BABY = DRESS", "Answer": "8683 + 9694 = 18377"}
{"Question": "TALK + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "8794 + 9785 = 18579"}
{"Question": "BABY + VARY = BREAD", "Answer": "1218 + 9208 = 10426"}
{"Question": "NINE + FILE = NOVEL", "Answer": "1218 + 9268 = 10486"}
{"Question": "BABY + LADY = BUILD", "Answer": "1314 + 9384 = 10698"}
{"Question": "PIPE + FIRE = PRESS", "Answer": "1316 + 9306 = 10622"}
{"Question": "BABY + VARY = BRICK", "Answer": "1317 + 9307 = 10624"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAT = BASIS", "Answer": "9318 + 1308 = 10626"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TIME = PHOTO", "Answer": "1318 + 9378 = 10696"}
{"Question": "REST + SEAT = START", "Answer": "9410 + 1480 = 10890"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAT = BLADE", "Answer": "9412 + 1482 = 10894"}
{"Question": "NINE + TIRE = NORTH", "Answer": "1413 + 9483 = 10896"}
{"Question": "MALE + LAKE = LIMIT", "Answer": "9416 + 1486 = 10902"}
{"Question": "BEST + SEAT = SAUCE", "Answer": "9417 + 1407 = 10824"}
{"Question": "LOVE + VOTE = VIDEO", "Answer": "9417 + 1457 = 10874"}
{"Question": "BITE + TIRE = TREND", "Answer": "9418 + 1408 = 10826"}
{"Question": "BASE + SALE = STEEL", "Answer": "9418 + 1468 = 10886"}
{"Question": "CAST + SALT = SENSE", "Answer": "8615 + 1695 = 10310"}
{"Question": "PIPE + HIRE = PROOF", "Answer": "1617 + 8607 = 10224"}
{"Question": "PIPE + FIRE = PROOF", "Answer": "1619 + 8609 = 10228"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SOME = STEEL", "Answer": "8714 + 1734 = 10448"}
{"Question": "PACE + CAKE = CHEAP", "Answer": "8714 + 1764 = 10478"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIKE = NAKED", "Answer": "1716 + 8746 = 10462"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BELT = BLIND", "Answer": "8719 + 1709 = 10428"}
{"Question": "PIPE + FILE = PROOF", "Answer": "1719 + 8729 = 10448"}
{"Question": "BABY + EASY = BREAD", "Answer": "1916 + 8976 = 10892"}
{"Question": "COLD + LOUD = LUCKY", "Answer": "8917 + 1907 = 10824"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATE = TEAR", "Answer": "2021 + 6081 = 8102"}
{"Question": "UPON + OPEN = PHOTO", "Answer": "8126 + 2146 = 10272"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TIME = IMPLY", "Answer": "2127 + 8107 = 10234"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORE = OWNER", "Answer": "2127 + 8147 = 10274"}
{"Question": "PIPE + LIFE = IMPLY", "Answer": "2127 + 8157 = 10284"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLE = OWNER", "Answer": "2129 + 8169 = 10298"}
{"Question": "MOST + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "8321 + 2361 = 10682"}
{"Question": "RARE + DATE = ENTER", "Answer": "2421 + 8491 = 10912"}
{"Question": "PIPE + RISE = STRIP", "Answer": "2426 + 8416 = 10842"}
{"Question": "REST + SEAT = AGREE", "Answer": "8427 + 2417 = 10844"}
{"Question": "EARN + RAIN = SCENE", "Answer": "8429 + 2469 = 10898"}
{"Question": "WARN + RAIN = NEVER", "Answer": "7621 + 2681 = 10302"}
{"Question": "CORE + ROLE = ERROR", "Answer": "9621 + 2641 = 12262"}
{"Question": "EARN + RAIN = AREA", "Answer": "3628 + 2608 = 6236"}
{"Question": "VERY + RELY = EVER", "Answer": "4721 + 2751 = 7472"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NICE = SENSE", "Answer": "2820 + 7890 = 10710"}
{"Question": "BABY + VARY = ARAB", "Answer": "2821 + 5861 = 8682"}
{"Question": "RARE + TAKE = ENTER", "Answer": "2821 + 7891 = 10712"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = GREEN", "Answer": "2826 + 7836 = 10662"}
{"Question": "BABY + EASY = ARAB", "Answer": "2921 + 6971 = 9892"}
{"Question": "RARE + BAKE = AGREE", "Answer": "3130 + 9170 = 12300"}
{"Question": "NONE + CODE = OWNER", "Answer": "3132 + 7192 = 10324"}
{"Question": "RARE + CASE = BASIS", "Answer": "3237 + 9247 = 12484"}
{"Question": "CITY + TINY = PIECE", "Answer": "9237 + 3257 = 12494"}
{"Question": "LAWN + WARN = INNER", "Answer": "8632 + 3642 = 12274"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOSE = STEEL", "Answer": "3734 + 8714 = 12448"}
{"Question": "NINE + FIRE = AREA", "Answer": "3738 + 2748 = 6486"}
{"Question": "PIPE + AIDE = SPEED", "Answer": "3836 + 9826 = 13662"}
{"Question": "BABY + MANY = DRAMA", "Answer": "4045 + 8035 = 12080"}
{"Question": "NINE + FIVE = EVEN", "Answer": "4147 + 3127 = 7274"}
{"Question": "RISK + SINK = INNER", "Answer": "8149 + 4129 = 12278"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "9241 + 4231 = 13472"}
{"Question": "RATE + TAKE = EXTRA", "Answer": "9241 + 4251 = 13492"}
{"Question": "FADE + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "6245 + 4205 = 10450"}
{"Question": "FIRE + RIDE = TIRED", "Answer": "8245 + 4205 = 12450"}
{"Question": "GRAY + ARMY = COLOR", "Answer": "9246 + 4286 = 13532"}
{"Question": "BASE + SALE = LESS", "Answer": "5347 + 4397 = 9744"}
{"Question": "NINE + RICE = THERE", "Answer": "4540 + 7530 = 12070"}
{"Question": "NONE + HOLE = LEMON", "Answer": "4542 + 7512 = 12054"}
{"Question": "NINE + TIME = MEDIA", "Answer": "4543 + 8513 = 13056"}
{"Question": "NINE + RICE = CORN", "Answer": "4547 + 3587 = 8134"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORE = ERROR", "Answer": "4641 + 7621 = 12262"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = SEVEN", "Answer": "4642 + 7682 = 12324"}
{"Question": "RARE + BAKE = ARAB", "Answer": "4741 + 2731 = 7472"}
{"Question": "BASE + SAFE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9741 + 4731 = 14472"}
{"Question": "FATE + TALE = LEFT", "Answer": "1847 + 4867 = 6714"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIFE = FILL", "Answer": "4946 + 2976 = 7922"}
{"Question": "NONE + SOME = MESS", "Answer": "5051 + 2071 = 7122"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIKE = SKILL", "Answer": "5054 + 8034 = 13088"}
{"Question": "LATE + TAPE = APPLE", "Answer": "7150 + 5120 = 12270"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "5152 + 8132 = 13284"}
{"Question": "BABY + LADY = ADULT", "Answer": "5153 + 9143 = 14296"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLE = OFFER", "Answer": "5154 + 8194 = 13348"}
{"Question": "PIPE + FINE = INNER", "Answer": "5158 + 7128 = 12286"}
{"Question": "SITE + TIRE = DRESS", "Answer": "8254 + 5234 = 13488"}
{"Question": "NONE + CORE = HONOR", "Answer": "5258 + 7268 = 12526"}
{"Question": "NINE + TIME = EMPTY", "Answer": "5351 + 9341 = 14692"}
{"Question": "NINE + FIVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "5356 + 8376 = 13732"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "5359 + 8379 = 13738"}
{"Question": "LAWN + WARN = ENTER", "Answer": "8453 + 5463 = 13916"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "5453 + 8493 = 13946"}
{"Question": "MOST + SOFT = THEME", "Answer": "8651 + 5631 = 14282"}
{"Question": "BABY + VARY = ERROR", "Answer": "5752 + 8742 = 14494"}
{"Question": "RARE + CAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "5856 + 9826 = 15682"}
{"Question": "EACH + CASH = THEME", "Answer": "8954 + 5924 = 14878"}
{"Question": "NINE + PILE = SLEEP", "Answer": "5958 + 6928 = 12886"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FIRE = RIFLE", "Answer": "7360 + 6310 = 13670"}
{"Question": "PIPE + HIDE = DEPTH", "Answer": "6364 + 8314 = 14678"}
{"Question": "UPON + OPEN = SENSE", "Answer": "8367 + 6347 = 14714"}
{"Question": "NONE + MODE = WOMAN", "Answer": "6368 + 7358 = 13726"}
{"Question": "TIME + MINE = ENTER", "Answer": "9461 + 6451 = 15912"}
{"Question": "COST + SOFT = FOCUS", "Answer": "8463 + 6413 = 14876"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROSE = SORRY", "Answer": "6465 + 8415 = 14880"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEAF = FALL", "Answer": "2468 + 6498 = 8966"}
{"Question": "REST + SEAT = METER", "Answer": "8469 + 6479 = 14948"}
{"Question": "NINE + CITE = PIECE", "Answer": "6560 + 8520 = 15080"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = PIECE", "Answer": "6560 + 8530 = 15090"}
{"Question": "POLE + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "7864 + 6804 = 14668"}
{"Question": "BEST + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "5869 + 6829 = 12698"}
{"Question": "RARE + SALE = LEAST", "Answer": "7076 + 9016 = 16092"}
{"Question": "FINE + NICE = CHIEF", "Answer": "8079 + 7019 = 15098"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLE = SORRY", "Answer": "7273 + 5283 = 12556"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "7274 + 8214 = 15488"}
{"Question": "TRUE + URGE = FEWER", "Answer": "9276 + 7286 = 16562"}
{"Question": "PAGE + GAME = EAGER", "Answer": "6371 + 7341 = 13712"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLE = HONOR", "Answer": "7378 + 6358 = 13736"}
{"Question": "NOSE + SOME = MONEY", "Answer": "6379 + 7319 = 13698"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = BREAD", "Answer": "7479 + 6489 = 13968"}
{"Question": "HOST + SOFT = CATCH", "Answer": "8479 + 7439 = 15918"}
{"Question": "HATE + TAPE = DEPTH", "Answer": "4572 + 7502 = 12074"}
{"Question": "BASE + SALE = USUAL", "Answer": "9574 + 7584 = 17158"}
{"Question": "NINE + FIRE = AGREE", "Answer": "7670 + 4630 = 12300"}
{"Question": "BABY + LADY = DAILY", "Answer": "7670 + 8610 = 16280"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEAF = FEWER", "Answer": "8671 + 7691 = 16362"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIFE = FIELD", "Answer": "7672 + 8612 = 16284"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROLE = LOVER", "Answer": "7679 + 8619 = 16298"}
{"Question": "BABY + EASY = TASTE", "Answer": "7679 + 8639 = 16318"}
{"Question": "BABY + LADY = DELAY", "Answer": "7870 + 6810 = 14680"}
{"Question": "RATE + TAKE = ENTER", "Answer": "2871 + 7841 = 10712"}
{"Question": "VOTE + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "6871 + 7841 = 14712"}
{"Question": "BITE + TIRE = METER", "Answer": "5873 + 7863 = 13736"}
{"Question": "RARE + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "7876 + 2806 = 10682"}
{"Question": "CITY + TINY = ENTER", "Answer": "5876 + 7836 = 13712"}
{"Question": "MORE + ROLE = LEMON", "Answer": "8976 + 7916 = 16892"}
{"Question": "BASE + SALE = ALBUM", "Answer": "2187 + 8107 = 10294"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "8189 + 2109 = 10298"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAT = STAFF", "Answer": "9287 + 8257 = 17544"}
{"Question": "RARE + TAKE = LATER", "Answer": "8289 + 4209 = 12498"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIFE = RIFLE", "Answer": "8380 + 5370 = 13750"}
{"Question": "PAST + SALT = TROOP", "Answer": "2381 + 8391 = 10772"}
{"Question": "NINE + CITE = PITCH", "Answer": "8382 + 5372 = 13754"}
{"Question": "RISE + SITE = TERMS", "Answer": "6384 + 8314 = 14698"}
{"Question": "COST + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "5387 + 8347 = 13734"}
{"Question": "RARE + FACE = COLOR", "Answer": "8389 + 2319 = 10708"}
{"Question": "GRAY + ARMY = METER", "Answer": "2487 + 8417 = 10904"}
{"Question": "MALE + LATE = ELECT", "Answer": "9581 + 8521 = 18102"}
{"Question": "FACE + CARE = PAPER", "Answer": "6582 + 8542 = 15124"}
{"Question": "PURE + RULE = PAPER", "Answer": "1584 + 8564 = 10148"}
{"Question": "NINE + PILE = PAPER", "Answer": "8586 + 1576 = 10162"}
{"Question": "COLD + LOAD = ADAPT", "Answer": "7586 + 8516 = 16102"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAT = AWARD", "Answer": "4587 + 8517 = 13104"}
{"Question": "NINE + LIFE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8587 + 6517 = 15104"}
{"Question": "NINE + FIVE = GIVEN", "Answer": "8589 + 6509 = 15098"}
{"Question": "NINE + CITE = CATCH", "Answer": "8682 + 1632 = 10314"}
{"Question": "NINE + WIRE = FEWER", "Answer": "8682 + 3642 = 12324"}
{"Question": "COLD + LOAD = RADIO", "Answer": "5683 + 8643 = 14326"}
{"Question": "POST + SORT = PRESS", "Answer": "1684 + 8604 = 10288"}
{"Question": "SELF + LEAF = START", "Answer": "1685 + 8635 = 10320"}
{"Question": "NONE + POLE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8685 + 1675 = 10360"}
{"Question": "FACT + CAST = FENCE", "Answer": "1685 + 8695 = 10380"}
{"Question": "NINE + HIRE = FEWER", "Answer": "8782 + 3742 = 12524"}
{"Question": "BABY + LADY = LIMIT", "Answer": "8783 + 1723 = 10506"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "8783 + 6753 = 15536"}
{"Question": "RARE + BAKE = BUYER", "Answer": "8784 + 1764 = 10548"}
{"Question": "NONE + VOTE = SEVEN", "Answer": "8784 + 5764 = 14548"}
{"Question": "NINE + GIVE = BEGIN", "Answer": "8784 + 5794 = 14578"}
{"Question": "RARE + CAKE = CLOCK", "Answer": "8786 + 1726 = 10512"}
{"Question": "SAFE + FATE = LEAST", "Answer": "4983 + 8963 = 13946"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = ASIAN", "Answer": "8984 + 1934 = 10918"}
{"Question": "RATE + TAKE = HEART", "Answer": "5984 + 8974 = 14958"}
{"Question": "DATE + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "6985 + 8905 = 15890"}
{"Question": "CASE + SAKE = CRACK", "Answer": "1986 + 8926 = 10912"}
{"Question": "NONE + CODE = ORDER", "Answer": "9192 + 5132 = 14324"}
{"Question": "RARE + TAKE = EXTRA", "Answer": "9291 + 4201 = 13492"}
{"Question": "BEST + SEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "5291 + 9241 = 14532"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEST = SENSE", "Answer": "3296 + 9216 = 12512"}
{"Question": "NONE + POLE = HELLO", "Answer": "9296 + 7256 = 16552"}
{"Question": "RARE + HATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "9298 + 6218 = 15516"}
{"Question": "FACT + CAST = SENSE", "Answer": "7298 + 9218 = 16516"}
{"Question": "FACE + CARE = EAGER", "Answer": "4391 + 9321 = 13712"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "9391 + 7321 = 16712"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDE = AVOID", "Answer": "9392 + 1342 = 10734"}
{"Question": "NONE + POSE = PRESS", "Answer": "9397 + 1347 = 10744"}
{"Question": "NINE + SIDE = SENSE", "Answer": "9490 + 1420 = 10910"}
{"Question": "CITE + TIME = CATCH", "Answer": "1493 + 9423 = 10916"}
{"Question": "NONE + MODE = MINOR", "Answer": "9493 + 1453 = 10946"}
{"Question": "RARE + FATE = FIRST", "Answer": "9493 + 1463 = 10956"}
{"Question": "GRAY + ARMY = GLASS", "Answer": "1493 + 9473 = 10966"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIKE = BUNCH", "Answer": "9493 + 1483 = 10976"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SONG = STEEL", "Answer": "9214 + 1235 = 10449"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SICK = PRESS", "Answer": "1214 + 9285 = 10499"}
{"Question": "CASH + SALE = STEEL", "Answer": "9318 + 1346 = 10664"}
{"Question": "BABY + CAKE = BUYER", "Answer": "1612 + 8645 = 10257"}
{"Question": "DISH + SIGN = SENSE", "Answer": "8617 + 1693 = 10310"}
{"Question": "RARE + FAIL = RIVER", "Answer": "1712 + 8709 = 10421"}
{"Question": "PALM + LATE = LIMIT", "Answer": "8715 + 1794 = 10509"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIRT = TREND", "Answer": "2826 + 7801 = 10627"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROAD = OWNER", "Answer": "3132 + 7195 = 10327"}
{"Question": "STIR + ITEM = TRIBE", "Answer": "9132 + 3175 = 12307"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GROW = BROWN", "Answer": "3231 + 9247 = 12478"}
{"Question": "BABY + FAIR = ARAB", "Answer": "3435 + 1408 = 4843"}
{"Question": "FACT + CARE = TREAT", "Answer": "8531 + 3520 = 12051"}
{"Question": "TERM + READ = ORDER", "Answer": "9837 + 3846 = 13683"}
{"Question": "RELY + LEAN = ENTER", "Answer": "8146 + 4172 = 12318"}
{"Question": "STIR + ITEM = TERMS", "Answer": "9142 + 4137 = 13279"}
{"Question": "BABY + MALE = LABEL", "Answer": "4245 + 8216 = 12461"}
{"Question": "BABY + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "4348 + 9371 = 13719"}
{"Question": "HOST + SONG = TIGHT", "Answer": "7541 + 4530 = 12071"}
{"Question": "CORN + ROLE = FENCE", "Answer": "7540 + 4532 = 12072"}
{"Question": "RARE + CAST = ENTER", "Answer": "4641 + 5673 = 10314"}
{"Question": "ROSE + SOUP = UPPER", "Answer": "7645 + 4612 = 12257"}
{"Question": "NONE + FOUR = REFER", "Answer": "4740 + 5761 = 10501"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CREW = BEACH", "Answer": "4741 + 8739 = 13480"}
{"Question": "RACE + CAST = METER", "Answer": "8743 + 4795 = 13538"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIRD = FEWER", "Answer": "4743 + 8796 = 13539"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOTS = STEEL", "Answer": "4846 + 7821 = 12667"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TRUE = LABEL", "Answer": "4846 + 9805 = 14651"}
{"Question": "HATE + TAIL = EIGHT", "Answer": "7351 + 5324 = 12675"}
{"Question": "BOTH + TONE = HONOR", "Answer": "8351 + 5379 = 13730"}
{"Question": "BELT + LEAD = TRADE", "Answer": "9351 + 5372 = 14723"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIRT = THEIR", "Answer": "5357 + 9381 = 14738"}
{"Question": "RARE + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "5457 + 9418 = 14875"}
{"Question": "HELP + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "6751 + 5724 = 12475"}
{"Question": "HERO + READ = ORDER", "Answer": "9751 + 5724 = 15475"}
{"Question": "PALM + LATE = METER", "Answer": "6851 + 5872 = 12723"}
{"Question": "TALE + LAWN = ENTER", "Answer": "7851 + 5863 = 13714"}
{"Question": "RARE + LAWN = FEWER", "Answer": "5852 + 6873 = 12725"}
{"Question": "BABY + RATE = METER", "Answer": "5854 + 6872 = 12726"}
{"Question": "NINE + GIFT = OFTEN", "Answer": "5859 + 7836 = 13695"}
{"Question": "SOFT + FOUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "7261 + 6253 = 13514"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FIRM = SMELL", "Answer": "9264 + 6235 = 15499"}
{"Question": "NONE + ROAD = EAGER", "Answer": "6361 + 9358 = 15719"}
{"Question": "RARE + LADY = MEDIA", "Answer": "6365 + 9378 = 15743"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RING = TIGHT", "Answer": "8561 + 6530 = 15091"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DROP = BROAD", "Answer": "6561 + 8507 = 15068"}
{"Question": "HURT + RULE = OTHER", "Answer": "5762 + 6784 = 12546"}
{"Question": "TUBE + BURN = ENTER", "Answer": "7861 + 6854 = 14715"}
{"Question": "CORE + ROAD = ERROR", "Answer": "9861 + 6825 = 16686"}
{"Question": "RARE + GAIN = BEING", "Answer": "6862 + 5873 = 12735"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TRUE = HEART", "Answer": "6863 + 7824 = 14687"}
{"Question": "RARE + MATH = TERMS", "Answer": "6864 + 7815 = 14679"}
{"Question": "RARE + GAIN = EAGER", "Answer": "7271 + 5246 = 12517"}
{"Question": "WEST + SELF = FEWER", "Answer": "5279 + 7241 = 12520"}
{"Question": "RARE + PATH = HAPPY", "Answer": "7273 + 5281 = 12554"}
{"Question": "NONE + FORM = ERROR", "Answer": "7271 + 8254 = 15525"}
{"Question": "LOTS + TOWN = SENSE", "Answer": "9271 + 7245 = 16516"}
{"Question": "BABY + MALE = LAYER", "Answer": "7274 + 5219 = 12493"}
{"Question": "EAST + SAND = TASTE", "Answer": "6371 + 7345 = 13716"}
{"Question": "RARE + LAST = SALES", "Answer": "7379 + 6312 = 13691"}
{"Question": "RARE + TALK = LATER", "Answer": "7379 + 6318 = 13697"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAR = TRADE", "Answer": "6471 + 7493 = 13964"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDS = LEVEL", "Answer": "7473 + 6458 = 13931"}
{"Question": "TRIP + IRON = ENTER", "Answer": "9478 + 7436 = 16914"}
{"Question": "RARE + WAIT = ELITE", "Answer": "7671 + 4630 = 12301"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAR = START", "Answer": "4672 + 7630 = 12302"}
{"Question": "LIST + SIGH = TIGHT", "Answer": "8671 + 7630 = 16301"}
{"Question": "HERO + REAL = LEVEL", "Answer": "8670 + 7691 = 16361"}
{"Question": "PIPE + DIRT = ENTER", "Answer": "7671 + 2643 = 10314"}
{"Question": "TERM + REAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "4673 + 7651 = 12324"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIRT = ENTER", "Answer": "7671 + 9643 = 17314"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIRT = METER", "Answer": "7672 + 4653 = 12325"}
{"Question": "RARE + PAST = SUPER", "Answer": "7679 + 2618 = 10297"}
{"Question": "SAFE + FAIR = REFER", "Answer": "2870 + 7831 = 10701"}
{"Question": "CITY + TIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "2873 + 7841 = 10714"}
{"Question": "RATE + TANK = ENTER", "Answer": "6871 + 7845 = 14716"}
{"Question": "RATE + TAIL = METER", "Answer": "5873 + 7862 = 13735"}
{"Question": "STIR + ITEM = CRIME", "Answer": "5873 + 7896 = 13769"}
{"Question": "TERM + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "6873 + 7814 = 14687"}
{"Question": "GATE + TALK = LEGAL", "Answer": "8976 + 7915 = 16891"}
{"Question": "BEST + SELF = ELITE", "Answer": "9186 + 8175 = 17361"}
{"Question": "NINE + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "8283 + 4251 = 12534"}
{"Question": "CARD + RANK = DANCE", "Answer": "4281 + 8259 = 12540"}
{"Question": "RARE + TANK = ENTER", "Answer": "8281 + 5237 = 13518"}
{"Question": "HURT + RULE = TOOTH", "Answer": "7281 + 8236 = 15517"}
{"Question": "BABY + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "8284 + 7295 = 15579"}
{"Question": "VERY + REAL = LEAVE", "Answer": "5382 + 8371 = 13753"}
{"Question": "AIDS + DIET = STAGE", "Answer": "7381 + 8365 = 15746"}
{"Question": "BABY + EARN = LAYER", "Answer": "8387 + 5369 = 13756"}
{"Question": "RARE + BAND = ENTER", "Answer": "8481 + 5437 = 13918"}
{"Question": "FISH + SIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "5483 + 8429 = 13912"}
{"Question": "PURE + RUSH = PAPER", "Answer": "1582 + 8546 = 10128"}
{"Question": "BABY + FACT = CYCLE", "Answer": "8583 + 4519 = 13102"}
{"Question": "DEBT + BEAR = STARE", "Answer": "7586 + 8509 = 16095"}
{"Question": "DENY + NECK = CYCLE", "Answer": "7586 + 8519 = 16105"}
{"Question": "ARAB + URGE = EAGER", "Answer": "8685 + 9631 = 18316"}
{"Question": "SORT + ROLE = SALES", "Answer": "1689 + 8632 = 10321"}
{"Question": "BABY + CAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "8682 + 1653 = 10335"}
{"Question": "SIGN + GIFT = SENSE", "Answer": "1683 + 8627 = 10310"}
{"Question": "NINE + AIDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "8683 + 1629 = 10312"}
{"Question": "FARM + RAIN = FENCE", "Answer": "1687 + 8653 = 10340"}
{"Question": "RARE + VAST = VOTER", "Answer": "8685 + 1673 = 10358"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TINY = THEIR", "Answer": "8683 + 1679 = 10362"}
{"Question": "RARE + CAMP = UPPER", "Answer": "8685 + 4673 = 13358"}
{"Question": "TERM + REAL = TABLE", "Answer": "1687 + 8609 = 10296"}
{"Question": "RISE + SIGN = NEVER", "Answer": "3782 + 8741 = 12523"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "8786 + 5731 = 14517"}
{"Question": "NONE + LOAD = LABEL", "Answer": "8789 + 1702 = 10491"}
{"Question": "TEND + NEWS = TASTE", "Answer": "1782 + 8735 = 10517"}
{"Question": "NEWS + WEAR = NURSE", "Answer": "1782 + 8745 = 10527"}
{"Question": "SPOT + OPEN = SCENE", "Answer": "1782 + 8753 = 10535"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TRUE = THEIR", "Answer": "8782 + 1765 = 10547"}
{"Question": "TEND + NEAR = THREE", "Answer": "1782 + 8795 = 10577"}
{"Question": "NINE + BIRD = SEVEN", "Answer": "8782 + 3746 = 12528"}
{"Question": "NONE + WORD = FEWER", "Answer": "8784 + 5762 = 14546"}
{"Question": "MENU + NEWS = ISSUE", "Answer": "6782 + 8745 = 15527"}
{"Question": "BEND + NEAR = BLADE", "Answer": "1783 + 8754 = 10537"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TRUE = TOWER", "Answer": "8783 + 1764 = 10547"}
{"Question": "NONE + FORM = LEMON", "Answer": "8783 + 4795 = 13578"}
{"Question": "STIR + ITEM = SERVE", "Answer": "1784 + 8706 = 10490"}
{"Question": "RARE + FAIL = FIELD", "Answer": "8784 + 1709 = 10493"}
{"Question": "SEND + NEAR = START", "Answer": "1786 + 8754 = 10540"}
{"Question": "BABY + CARE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8784 + 1795 = 10579"}
{"Question": "RARE + GAIN = ANGER", "Answer": "9197 + 3182 = 12379"}
{"Question": "EARN + RAIL = ALTER", "Answer": "6194 + 9175 = 15369"}
{"Question": "HERO + READ = OFFER", "Answer": "6291 + 9238 = 15529"}
{"Question": "POSE + SORT = PRESS", "Answer": "1294 + 9205 = 10499"}
{"Question": "NONE + BOAT = AHEAD", "Answer": "9295 + 7218 = 16513"}
{"Question": "NINE + DISH = GUESS", "Answer": "9295 + 7238 = 16533"}
{"Question": "AWAY + SWIM = LIMIT", "Answer": "9298 + 7265 = 16563"}
{"Question": "NINE + RICH = CHECK", "Answer": "9397 + 6315 = 15712"}
{"Question": "NINE + FILM = SMELL", "Answer": "9397 + 6325 = 15722"}
{"Question": "NONE + COLD = HELLO", "Answer": "9395 + 6378 = 15773"}
{"Question": "KIND + NICE = CHECK", "Answer": "5398 + 9317 = 14715"}
{"Question": "ARAB + IRON = SINCE", "Answer": "9692 + 4683 = 14375"}
{"Question": "BABY + EARN = FENCE", "Answer": "9692 + 5683 = 15375"}
{"Question": "BABY + EAST = METER", "Answer": "9692 + 7683 = 17375"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = RURAL", "Answer": "1213 + 8913 = 10126"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OPEN = NERVE", "Answer": "2421 + 9621 = 12042"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = ERROR", "Answer": "2821 + 9421 = 12242"}
{"Question": "NINE + TONE = ONTO", "Answer": "2429 + 5829 = 8258"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = AREA", "Answer": "4849 + 3649 = 8498"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = AHEAD", "Answer": "5156 + 8456 = 13612"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = VISIT", "Answer": "5753 + 4653 = 10406"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = TOSS", "Answer": "6061 + 2861 = 8922"}
{"Question": "NINE + BONE = INDEX", "Answer": "6162 + 9862 = 16024"}
{"Question": "EVEN + OPEN = PEACE", "Answer": "6863 + 9163 = 16026"}
{"Question": "AWAY + GRAY = WATER", "Answer": "6164 + 9864 = 16028"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TYPE = IMPLY", "Answer": "6167 + 9467 = 15634"}
{"Question": "AWAY + OKAY = KILL", "Answer": "7072 + 1872 = 8944"}
{"Question": "NONE + LINE = BIBLE", "Answer": "7870 + 4270 = 12140"}
{"Question": "EVEN + THEN = NIGHT", "Answer": "7871 + 2471 = 10342"}
{"Question": "RARE + HIRE = EARTH", "Answer": "8081 + 2781 = 10862"}
{"Question": "NONE + LINE = HELLO", "Answer": "8085 + 7685 = 15770"}
{"Question": "PIPE + COPE = TOPIC", "Answer": "8786 + 2086 = 10872"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = FORCE", "Answer": "8380 + 6480 = 14860"}
{"Question": "RARE + TIRE = EARTH", "Answer": "8481 + 6381 = 14862"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TAPE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8386 + 1786 = 10172"}
{"Question": "NINE + BONE = ERROR", "Answer": "8581 + 3681 = 12262"}
{"Question": "NINE + TONE = THEIR", "Answer": "8682 + 1582 = 10264"}
{"Question": "RARE + SURE = GUESS", "Answer": "8783 + 6583 = 15366"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = SOUTH", "Answer": "8586 + 1786 = 10372"}
{"Question": "RARE + CORE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8684 + 1784 = 10468"}
{"Question": "EVER + USER = NERVE", "Answer": "8684 + 9784 = 18468"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = STYLE", "Answer": "9293 + 1093 = 10386"}
{"Question": "EVER + USER = DRESS", "Answer": "9094 + 5894 = 14988"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = SMART", "Answer": "9293 + 1693 = 10986"}
{"Question": "NONE + FINE = PIANO", "Answer": "9296 + 5496 = 14792"}
{"Question": "AWAY + GRAY = SUGAR", "Answer": "9596 + 8296 = 17892"}
{"Question": "NINE + TONE = COUNT", "Answer": "9297 + 4397 = 13694"}
{"Question": "PIPE + ROPE = ERROR", "Answer": "9391 + 2891 = 12282"}
{"Question": "AWAY + STAY = SHEET", "Answer": "9392 + 1492 = 10884"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "1315 + 8712 = 10027"}
{"Question": "AWAY + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "2426 + 8529 = 10955"}
{"Question": "RARE + BIRD = TREAT", "Answer": "3735 + 9836 = 13571"}
{"Question": "EVEN + USER = NERVE", "Answer": "4841 + 9543 = 14384"}
{"Question": "RARE + GIRL = LEGAL", "Answer": "4840 + 5741 = 10581"}
{"Question": "ARAB + WHAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "5259 + 8051 = 13310"}
{"Question": "RARE + DIRT = AHEAD", "Answer": "5158 + 7659 = 12817"}
{"Question": "NINE + HANG = EAGER", "Answer": "5651 + 7259 = 12910"}
{"Question": "RARE + HURT = CATCH", "Answer": "5258 + 7659 = 12917"}
{"Question": "EVER + ITEM = SMART", "Answer": "6062 + 9765 = 15827"}
{"Question": "EVER + STEP = APART", "Answer": "6362 + 8765 = 15127"}
{"Question": "RARE + BIRD = LABEL", "Answer": "7075 + 3276 = 10351"}
{"Question": "EVER + USED = DRESS", "Answer": "7273 + 6471 = 13744"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "7279 + 8571 = 15850"}
{"Question": "NINE + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "7273 + 6578 = 13851"}
{"Question": "NINE + RANK = PAPER", "Answer": "7875 + 4279 = 12154"}
{"Question": "NONE + LAND = MODEL", "Answer": "8087 + 2485 = 10572"}
{"Question": "EVER + ITEM = TREAT", "Answer": "8682 + 4189 = 12871"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEAL = BLADE", "Answer": "8281 + 6584 = 14865"}
{"Question": "RARE + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "8286 + 7581 = 15867"}
{"Question": "NINE + TANK = TREAT", "Answer": "8482 + 1789 = 10271"}
{"Question": "EVEN + POEM = PIANO", "Answer": "8587 + 1689 = 10276"}
{"Question": "LIST + SHIT = SOUTH", "Answer": "9213 + 1623 = 10836"}
{"Question": "LAST + SEAT = TALE", "Answer": "4215 + 1025 = 5240"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DIRT = RADIO", "Answer": "1442 + 9512 = 10954"}
{"Question": "SEEK + RISK = STRIP", "Answer": "1443 + 9513 = 10956"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HURT = RATIO", "Answer": "1447 + 9317 = 10764"}
{"Question": "BABY + PLAY = BIBLE", "Answer": "1512 + 8652 = 10164"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SHOE = STEAL", "Answer": "8514 + 1954 = 10468"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SHOE = SPEED", "Answer": "9517 + 1257 = 10774"}
{"Question": "SEEK + RISK = START", "Answer": "1665 + 8715 = 10380"}
{"Question": "NOSE + SHOE = SPEND", "Answer": "8712 + 1572 = 10284"}
{"Question": "EASY + STAY = SHEET", "Answer": "9716 + 1276 = 10992"}
{"Question": "BABY + OKAY = BLOOD", "Answer": "1718 + 9278 = 10996"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = GHOST", "Answer": "2527 + 8057 = 10584"}
{"Question": "ROOM + TERM = MAKER", "Answer": "2661 + 7821 = 10482"}
{"Question": "BABY + GRAY = CIVIL", "Answer": "2823 + 7583 = 10406"}
{"Question": "NEED + BOND = ONION", "Answer": "2886 + 9126 = 12012"}
{"Question": "JOIN + IRON = OWNER", "Answer": "7139 + 3819 = 10958"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GRAY = FLOOR", "Answer": "3227 + 9437 = 12664"}
{"Question": "CAST + SEAT = TEACH", "Answer": "7431 + 3041 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PRAY = SLEEP", "Answer": "4229 + 8549 = 12778"}
{"Question": "BABY + STAY = COAST", "Answer": "4345 + 8035 = 12380"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SOON = HORSE", "Answer": "4947 + 8337 = 13284"}
{"Question": "EVER + DOOR = SORRY", "Answer": "4548 + 9338 = 13886"}
{"Question": "ALLY + OKAY = MAYOR", "Answer": "4553 + 9843 = 14396"}
{"Question": "DUST + SHUT = TOOTH", "Answer": "5741 + 4271 = 10012"}
{"Question": "ALLY + STAY = LAST", "Answer": "4778 + 2648 = 7426"}
{"Question": "BABY + GRAY = RANGE", "Answer": "5254 + 7124 = 12378"}
{"Question": "BABY + OKAY = LABOR", "Answer": "5254 + 7324 = 12578"}
{"Question": "SEEK + TASK = WASTE", "Answer": "5226 + 8356 = 13582"}
{"Question": "TUBE + BLUE = WHEEL", "Answer": "9258 + 5628 = 14886"}
{"Question": "ALLY + PRAY = GRASS", "Answer": "5334 + 7254 = 12588"}
{"Question": "ALLY + STAY = CLASS", "Answer": "5334 + 8254 = 13588"}
{"Question": "LIST + SHIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7359 + 5839 = 13198"}
{"Question": "CARD + READ = DANCE", "Answer": "9451 + 5241 = 14692"}
{"Question": "FACT + COAT = STAFF", "Answer": "8264 + 6024 = 14288"}
{"Question": "LOOK + WALK = TOTAL", "Answer": "6228 + 5968 = 12196"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DEBT = ROUTE", "Answer": "6229 + 5869 = 12098"}
{"Question": "SEEK + TASK = VISIT", "Answer": "6337 + 4267 = 10604"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DEBT = HELLO", "Answer": "6442 + 8562 = 15004"}
{"Question": "EASY + STAY = TASTE", "Answer": "8469 + 6149 = 14618"}
{"Question": "CARD + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "9563 + 6153 = 15716"}
{"Question": "CAST + SEAT = TROOP", "Answer": "3861 + 6581 = 10442"}
{"Question": "EVER + DOOR = NERVE", "Answer": "6463 + 9883 = 16346"}
{"Question": "FOOT + LIFT = BIBLE", "Answer": "6887 + 5267 = 12154"}
{"Question": "ALLY + STAY = LEAST", "Answer": "7113 + 8673 = 15786"}
{"Question": "FAST + SEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "6379 + 7539 = 13918"}
{"Question": "NEED + SAND = DRESS", "Answer": "7551 + 2971 = 10522"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = CHEEK", "Answer": "7572 + 8652 = 16224"}
{"Question": "BABY + STAY = WASTE", "Answer": "7573 + 8253 = 15826"}
{"Question": "TUBE + BLUE = EVENT", "Answer": "2671 + 7461 = 10132"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GRAY = TRAIL", "Answer": "7668 + 3078 = 10746"}
{"Question": "COOK + LACK = TOTAL", "Answer": "7669 + 8479 = 16148"}
{"Question": "PAST + SEAT = TROOP", "Answer": "2871 + 7681 = 10552"}
{"Question": "FOOT + LEFT = TITLE", "Answer": "7881 + 5271 = 13152"}
{"Question": "FOOT + GIFT = RATIO", "Answer": "7884 + 2574 = 10458"}
{"Question": "COOK + LACK = HELLO", "Answer": "7884 + 5674 = 13558"}
{"Question": "FOOT + LEFT = STEEL", "Answer": "7992 + 4672 = 12664"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GRAY = LIMIT", "Answer": "8117 + 2387 = 10504"}
{"Question": "ALLY + STAY = LIMIT", "Answer": "8117 + 2487 = 10604"}
{"Question": "ROOM + TERM = OFFER", "Answer": "8119 + 4089 = 12208"}
{"Question": "FOOT + GIFT = STEEL", "Answer": "8223 + 4783 = 13006"}
{"Question": "NEED + BAND = SENSE", "Answer": "8226 + 4586 = 12812"}
{"Question": "SEEK + MASK = TASTE", "Answer": "8226 + 7586 = 15812"}
{"Question": "SEEK + TASK = TOOTH", "Answer": "8332 + 1682 = 10014"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PART = PHOTO", "Answer": "8442 + 1982 = 10424"}
{"Question": "NEED + LAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "8447 + 1587 = 10034"}
{"Question": "NEED + BAND = BIBLE", "Answer": "8447 + 1687 = 10134"}
{"Question": "COST + SHOT = THEME", "Answer": "7581 + 8651 = 16232"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = SPEAK", "Answer": "8582 + 1652 = 10234"}
{"Question": "FOOT + LEFT = STYLE", "Answer": "8552 + 3482 = 12034"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = SLEEP", "Answer": "8583 + 1753 = 10336"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DEBT = STATE", "Answer": "8553 + 4683 = 13236"}
{"Question": "LOOK + WALK = WHEEL", "Answer": "8554 + 1784 = 10338"}
{"Question": "BABY + GRAY = GUESS", "Answer": "8587 + 1657 = 10244"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = THESE", "Answer": "8680 + 4360 = 13040"}
{"Question": "SIGN + GAIN = NEVER", "Answer": "5681 + 8361 = 14042"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = SMELL", "Answer": "8682 + 1562 = 10244"}
{"Question": "TUBE + BLUE = GUESS", "Answer": "7682 + 8562 = 16244"}
{"Question": "EVER + POOR = PIANO", "Answer": "8583 + 1663 = 10246"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HURT = HELLO", "Answer": "8663 + 1783 = 10446"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SOON = SHINE", "Answer": "8584 + 1664 = 10248"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SOON = STONE", "Answer": "8984 + 1664 = 10648"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = FEWER", "Answer": "8685 + 7265 = 15950"}
{"Question": "GIRL + RAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "7685 + 8465 = 16150"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "8771 + 2081 = 10852"}
{"Question": "FOOT + GIFT = TITLE", "Answer": "8771 + 4381 = 13152"}
{"Question": "NOSE + SHOE = EVENT", "Answer": "5781 + 8371 = 14152"}
{"Question": "JOIN + IRON = NEVER", "Answer": "6781 + 8271 = 15052"}
{"Question": "COOK + BACK = BIBLE", "Answer": "8772 + 1382 = 10154"}
{"Question": "MOST + SHOT = MATCH", "Answer": "1782 + 8472 = 10254"}
{"Question": "COOK + NECK = NAKED", "Answer": "8773 + 1583 = 10356"}
{"Question": "BABY + PRAY = POWER", "Answer": "8783 + 1673 = 10456"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SOON = SINCE", "Answer": "8684 + 1774 = 10458"}
{"Question": "EVER + DOOR = GRADE", "Answer": "8284 + 5774 = 14058"}
{"Question": "FACT + COAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1786 + 8376 = 10162"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DIRT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8776 + 4386 = 13162"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOE = SENSE", "Answer": "9290 + 1620 = 10910"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HURT = CATCH", "Answer": "9223 + 6093 = 15316"}
{"Question": "LOOK + TALK = TASTE", "Answer": "9224 + 1094 = 10318"}
{"Question": "ALLY + OKAY = SKILL", "Answer": "9226 + 5496 = 14722"}
{"Question": "SEEK + RISK = AGREE", "Answer": "9226 + 8596 = 17822"}
{"Question": "COOK + NECK = LEMON", "Answer": "9227 + 4397 = 13624"}
{"Question": "GIRL + RAIL = BASIS", "Answer": "4298 + 9328 = 13626"}
{"Question": "LAST + SEAT = METAL", "Answer": "6298 + 9528 = 15826"}
{"Question": "JOIN + IRON = PRIOR", "Answer": "7298 + 9628 = 16926"}
{"Question": "POST + SHOT = DEPTH", "Answer": "8392 + 9432 = 17824"}
{"Question": "BABY + STAY = STYLE", "Answer": "9394 + 1034 = 10428"}
{"Question": "SEEK + RISK = FEWER", "Answer": "9337 + 4297 = 13634"}
{"Question": "ROOM + WARM = ALLOW", "Answer": "9338 + 6198 = 15536"}
{"Question": "NEED + MIND = MOVIE", "Answer": "9442 + 1392 = 10834"}
{"Question": "NEED + BOND = ORDER", "Answer": "9446 + 3196 = 12642"}
{"Question": "JOIN + IRON = COLOR", "Answer": "5496 + 9246 = 14742"}
{"Question": "EVEN + SOON = SHELL", "Answer": "9392 + 1552 = 10944"}
{"Question": "GIRL + RAIL = ANGLE", "Answer": "7594 + 9154 = 16748"}
{"Question": "BABY + GRAY = SUGAR", "Answer": "9596 + 8256 = 17852"}
{"Question": "LIST + SUIT = UNTIL", "Answer": "4597 + 9157 = 13754"}
{"Question": "NEED + SAND = SINCE", "Answer": "9663 + 1293 = 10956"}
{"Question": "ALLY + STAY = SHALL", "Answer": "9668 + 1298 = 10966"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TIRE = ASSET", "Answer": "1413 + 8645 = 10058"}
{"Question": "USER + EAST = EXTRA", "Answer": "9416 + 1347 = 10763"}
{"Question": "NINE + ODDS = SOON", "Answer": "1213 + 7558 = 8771"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SOFT = FALSE", "Answer": "1773 + 8614 = 10387"}
{"Question": "CAMP + MEAL = PEACE", "Answer": "8521 + 2059 = 10580"}
{"Question": "SEED + HOST = TOOTH", "Answer": "2996 + 7021 = 10017"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOAT = LABEL", "Answer": "3236 + 9725 = 12961"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOAT = LATER", "Answer": "3236 + 9527 = 12763"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SHIT = DEPTH", "Answer": "3432 + 8947 = 12379"}
{"Question": "USER + EAST = TREAT", "Answer": "6530 + 3851 = 10381"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HIDE = RADIO", "Answer": "3551 + 6834 = 10385"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOAT = ERROR", "Answer": "3531 + 9852 = 13383"}
{"Question": "RARE + OKAY = ERROR", "Answer": "3631 + 9762 = 13393"}
{"Question": "ROOM + DIRT = METER", "Answer": "3771 + 6432 = 10203"}
{"Question": "AWAY + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "3734 + 6571 = 10305"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AIDS = EASE", "Answer": "3887 + 4531 = 8418"}
{"Question": "BABY + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "4245 + 8123 = 12368"}
{"Question": "BABY + DEAL = CYCLE", "Answer": "4243 + 8926 = 13169"}
{"Question": "SOON + RISE = INNER", "Answer": "4223 + 9146 = 13369"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CROP = SPORT", "Answer": "4551 + 7942 = 12493"}
{"Question": "ODDS + PLOT = STEEL", "Answer": "4661 + 7342 = 12003"}
{"Question": "RARE + OKAY = HELLO", "Answer": "4642 + 7365 = 12007"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "4883 + 7542 = 12425"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MEET = STATE", "Answer": "4546 + 7882 = 12428"}
{"Question": "NINE + ROOT = METER", "Answer": "4642 + 7885 = 12527"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LADY = APPLE", "Answer": "5223 + 8159 = 13382"}
{"Question": "NINE + LOOK = HELLO", "Answer": "5653 + 8229 = 13882"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "7359 + 5032 = 12391"}
{"Question": "PART + REAL = ELITE", "Answer": "7359 + 5132 = 12491"}
{"Question": "NINE + TRIP = RIVER", "Answer": "5359 + 8132 = 13491"}
{"Question": "NINE + CHIP = BENCH", "Answer": "5354 + 9238 = 14592"}
{"Question": "EVEN + COOK = FENCE", "Answer": "5852 + 9443 = 15295"}
{"Question": "MUCH + CLUE = SHELL", "Answer": "8653 + 5269 = 13922"}
{"Question": "SOON + REST = METER", "Answer": "5668 + 7259 = 12927"}
{"Question": "NINE + TRIP = GREEN", "Answer": "5752 + 8473 = 14225"}
{"Question": "NONE + PLOT = SLEEP", "Answer": "5752 + 8476 = 14228"}
{"Question": "TOOL + RATE = METER", "Answer": "5884 + 7653 = 13537"}
{"Question": "EVER + MOOD = DRAMA", "Answer": "6364 + 8221 = 14585"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ALSO = MORAL", "Answer": "6221 + 8564 = 14785"}
{"Question": "EAST + SNAP = TASTE", "Answer": "9561 + 6058 = 15619"}
{"Question": "BABY + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "6562 + 9351 = 15913"}
{"Question": "INTO + TANK = ONION", "Answer": "9561 + 6354 = 15915"}
{"Question": "NINE + QUIT = ENTER", "Answer": "6561 + 9753 = 16314"}
{"Question": "BABY + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "6764 + 9173 = 15937"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIL = CLEAR", "Answer": "6863 + 5482 = 12345"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOAT = METER", "Answer": "6864 + 7382 = 14246"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERO = LABEL", "Answer": "6864 + 9587 = 16451"}
{"Question": "PIPE + STIR = APART", "Answer": "6867 + 9285 = 16152"}
{"Question": "ROOF + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "7115 + 8472 = 15587"}
{"Question": "ODDS + CROP = SPEED", "Answer": "7331 + 4672 = 12003"}
{"Question": "PLUS + UGLY = SLEEP", "Answer": "5371 + 7634 = 13005"}
{"Question": "RARE + ODDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "7175 + 9338 = 16513"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LOTS = SENSE", "Answer": "7443 + 6871 = 14314"}
{"Question": "NONE + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "7478 + 6941 = 14419"}
{"Question": "AUTO + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "6571 + 7352 = 13923"}
{"Question": "BABY + ROOM = MORAL", "Answer": "7273 + 8551 = 15824"}
{"Question": "ARAB + WIRE = FEWER", "Answer": "7573 + 4852 = 12425"}
{"Question": "RARE + LOAN = PANEL", "Answer": "7572 + 8056 = 15628"}
{"Question": "RARE + GOAL = COLOR", "Answer": "7578 + 6359 = 13937"}
{"Question": "ROOF + HIRE = FIFTH", "Answer": "7881 + 4273 = 12154"}
{"Question": "ARAB + GIRL = BLOOD", "Answer": "7871 + 4682 = 12553"}
{"Question": "COST + SHOP = PATCH", "Answer": "6879 + 7081 = 13960"}
{"Question": "TOOL + CITY = ELECT", "Answer": "7883 + 5274 = 13157"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DOOR = SERVE", "Answer": "7573 + 9884 = 17457"}
{"Question": "BABY + REAL = LAYER", "Answer": "8283 + 4021 = 12304"}
{"Question": "RARE + ODDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "8081 + 5223 = 13304"}
{"Question": "BABY + HEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "8285 + 4629 = 12914"}
{"Question": "STIR + INTO = FRONT", "Answer": "9387 + 8236 = 17623"}
{"Question": "RARE + WHAT = EARTH", "Answer": "8481 + 6342 = 14823"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DIRT = BRAIN", "Answer": "8481 + 6349 = 14830"}
{"Question": "GOOD + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8443 + 1582 = 10025"}
{"Question": "PIPE + SHIT = SLEEP", "Answer": "8482 + 1746 = 10228"}
{"Question": "NONE + PLOT = STEEL", "Answer": "8482 + 6745 = 15227"}
{"Question": "NINE + RAIL = PAPER", "Answer": "8482 + 7645 = 16127"}
{"Question": "FOOD + LIFE = REFER", "Answer": "8557 + 6284 = 14841"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DIRT = STATE", "Answer": "8589 + 6254 = 14843"}
{"Question": "NONE + GROW = FEWER", "Answer": "8584 + 6359 = 14943"}
{"Question": "NINE + TAIL = TREAT", "Answer": "8682 + 1569 = 10251"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERO = COLOR", "Answer": "8682 + 5364 = 14046"}
{"Question": "CAMP + MEAL = CYCLE", "Answer": "1689 + 8465 = 10154"}
{"Question": "POST + SHOE = DEPTH", "Answer": "9685 + 8267 = 17952"}
{"Question": "ARAB + ODDS = BRAND", "Answer": "8081 + 2776 = 10857"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CORE = BEACH", "Answer": "8781 + 5073 = 13854"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEEP = BLADE", "Answer": "8081 + 5776 = 13857"}
{"Question": "WEEK + BOWL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8772 + 1385 = 10157"}
{"Question": "NINE + SHIP = SMELL", "Answer": "8782 + 1473 = 10255"}
{"Question": "NINE + CHIP = CLEAN", "Answer": "8782 + 1476 = 10258"}
{"Question": "BABY + TEAR = THREE", "Answer": "8782 + 1573 = 10355"}
{"Question": "ARAB + HERO = HUMOR", "Answer": "8782 + 1675 = 10457"}
{"Question": "NINE + SUIT = GUESS", "Answer": "8782 + 5473 = 14255"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "8784 + 1573 = 10357"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FORM = FIBER", "Answer": "8784 + 1673 = 10457"}
{"Question": "NINE + SOIL = SHELF", "Answer": "8784 + 1675 = 10459"}
{"Question": "NINE + TRIP = TOWER", "Answer": "8786 + 1579 = 10365"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LOTS = LOOSE", "Answer": "8992 + 1087 = 10079"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TERM = OFFER", "Answer": "9112 + 3097 = 12209"}
{"Question": "PART + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "8192 + 9017 = 17209"}
{"Question": "RARE + GLAD = EAGER", "Answer": "9291 + 3028 = 12319"}
{"Question": "RARE + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "9291 + 3528 = 12819"}
{"Question": "PAGE + GRAB = EAGER", "Answer": "3291 + 9625 = 12916"}
{"Question": "STIR + INTO = ONION", "Answer": "7295 + 9621 = 16916"}
{"Question": "ROOT + BURN = ENTER", "Answer": "9223 + 7096 = 16319"}
{"Question": "RARE + FLAT = LATER", "Answer": "9493 + 5146 = 14639"}
{"Question": "BABY + HEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "9592 + 6351 = 15943"}
{"Question": "ROOF + PART = AFTER", "Answer": "9552 + 3197 = 12749"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AIDE = BREAD", "Answer": "9553 + 4096 = 13649"}
{"Question": "NINE + STIR = ASSET", "Answer": "9695 + 4762 = 14457"}
{"Question": "PAGE + GLAD = LEGAL", "Answer": "4793 + 9178 = 13971"}
{"Question": "FREE + SAFE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1422 + 8912 = 10334"}
{"Question": "NONE + TREE = ONTO", "Answer": "1613 + 4533 = 6146"}
{"Question": "TREE + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1644 + 8514 = 10158"}
{"Question": "TREE + DATE = THIRD", "Answer": "1544 + 8714 = 10258"}
{"Question": "NONE + FREE = ROOF", "Answer": "2128 + 6988 = 9116"}
{"Question": "TREE + SITE = IRISH", "Answer": "3044 + 7134 = 10178"}
{"Question": "NONE + FLEE = LEMON", "Answer": "4642 + 8122 = 12764"}
{"Question": "ROLL + GIRL = ORDER", "Answer": "4177 + 9847 = 14024"}
{"Question": "TREE + SITE = BASIS", "Answer": "4288 + 6348 = 10636"}
{"Question": "ROLL + GIRL = ERROR", "Answer": "4622 + 9842 = 14464"}
{"Question": "TREE + NOTE = RATIO", "Answer": "5122 + 8452 = 13574"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SAFE = LESS", "Answer": "5866 + 2756 = 8622"}
{"Question": "WELL + BOWL = SOLVE", "Answer": "6055 + 8465 = 14520"}
{"Question": "ROLL + GIRL = COLOR", "Answer": "6588 + 9268 = 15856"}
{"Question": "RARE + FLEE = CLEAR", "Answer": "6963 + 7433 = 14396"}
{"Question": "TREE + NOTE = ROOT", "Answer": "6988 + 2568 = 9556"}
{"Question": "KNEE + TAKE = EVENT", "Answer": "7811 + 2371 = 10182"}
{"Question": "FREE + SAFE = DRESS", "Answer": "7388 + 6478 = 13866"}
{"Question": "KNEE + MAKE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7611 + 8571 = 16182"}
{"Question": "NONE + TREE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8083 + 1933 = 10016"}
{"Question": "TREE + DATE = BREAD", "Answer": "8066 + 2586 = 10652"}
{"Question": "WALL + BOWL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8144 + 6284 = 14428"}
{"Question": "PIPE + FLEE = FINAL", "Answer": "9093 + 1633 = 10726"}
{"Question": "NINE + FREE = FINAL", "Answer": "9093 + 1833 = 10926"}
{"Question": "NINE + FLEE = FLOOR", "Answer": "9294 + 1044 = 10338"}
{"Question": "NINE + FLEE = FINAL", "Answer": "9094 + 1844 = 10938"}
{"Question": "TREE + BITE = METER", "Answer": "9055 + 6895 = 15950"}
{"Question": "TREE + NOTE = ONION", "Answer": "9822 + 4192 = 14014"}
{"Question": "KNEE + JOKE = ONION", "Answer": "9422 + 5192 = 14614"}
{"Question": "KNEE + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "9388 + 6198 = 15586"}
{"Question": "TREE + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "9788 + 6198 = 15986"}
{"Question": "NINE + TREE = FIBER", "Answer": "9496 + 5266 = 14762"}
{"Question": "NINE + TREE = AFTER", "Answer": "9596 + 8266 = 17862"}
{"Question": "NONE + FREE = BRIEF", "Answer": "9297 + 4377 = 13674"}
{"Question": "TREE + DATE = LATER", "Answer": "9688 + 3298 = 12986"}
{"Question": "TREE + NOTE = GREEN", "Answer": "9588 + 6298 = 15886"}
{"Question": "TREE + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "9522 + 4392 = 13914"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TREE = TOPIC", "Answer": "9394 + 1544 = 10938"}
{"Question": "ARAB + DEBT = AFTER", "Answer": "1214 + 9648 = 10862"}
{"Question": "SELL + BUSY = SOLVE", "Answer": "1355 + 9218 = 10573"}
{"Question": "AWAY + BOSS = ALLOW", "Answer": "1715 + 8322 = 10037"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SHOE = STEEL", "Answer": "8914 + 1645 = 10559"}
{"Question": "AWAY + LESS = WALL", "Answer": "2423 + 1788 = 4211"}
{"Question": "HEAD + AIDS = STATE", "Answer": "6837 + 3471 = 10308"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOSS = ERROR", "Answer": "3831 + 9522 = 13353"}
{"Question": "LAWN + WINE = PANEL", "Answer": "8342 + 4926 = 13268"}
{"Question": "PIPE + ROLL = INNER", "Answer": "5157 + 9322 = 14479"}
{"Question": "VOTE + THEN = HONOR", "Answer": "7256 + 5164 = 12420"}
{"Question": "HALF + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "7954 + 5241 = 13195"}
{"Question": "MASS + COME = LOCAL", "Answer": "5488 + 7253 = 12741"}
{"Question": "ARAB + TUBE = METER", "Answer": "5258 + 9684 = 14942"}
{"Question": "HALF + LIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7851 + 5316 = 13167"}
{"Question": "LOSS + HALF = TOTAL", "Answer": "5422 + 8753 = 14175"}
{"Question": "BABY + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "5756 + 8422 = 14178"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SHOE = COACH", "Answer": "9065 + 6853 = 15918"}
{"Question": "NONE + USER = YOURS", "Answer": "6068 + 4385 = 10453"}
{"Question": "LOSS + BELT = ELITE", "Answer": "6877 + 9164 = 16041"}
{"Question": "TYPE + POEM = EMPTY", "Answer": "7461 + 6213 = 13674"}
{"Question": "BABY + ROLL = MAYOR", "Answer": "6369 + 7588 = 13957"}
{"Question": "EVEN + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "6768 + 9583 = 16351"}
{"Question": "ROLL + EARN = SALES", "Answer": "7455 + 3076 = 10531"}
{"Question": "NONE + CHEF = LOCAL", "Answer": "7076 + 3265 = 10341"}
{"Question": "WALL + NEWS = FALSE", "Answer": "7566 + 8074 = 15640"}
{"Question": "RARE + BOSS = ORDER", "Answer": "7872 + 9155 = 17027"}
{"Question": "NONE + USER = SORRY", "Answer": "7276 + 5164 = 12440"}
{"Question": "RARE + TOSS = ASSET", "Answer": "7173 + 9466 = 16639"}
{"Question": "NINE + CREW = AWARD", "Answer": "7875 + 6254 = 14129"}
{"Question": "CELL + FACT = REFER", "Answer": "7688 + 9273 = 16961"}
{"Question": "PASS + TYPE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7922 + 4371 = 12293"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6874 + 7541 = 14415"}
{"Question": "WALL + DOWN = ALLOW", "Answer": "8122 + 4086 = 12208"}
{"Question": "NONE + THEM = TOOTH", "Answer": "8083 + 1936 = 10019"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LONG = LOOSE", "Answer": "8986 + 1062 = 10048"}
{"Question": "NINE + USER = VIRUS", "Answer": "8386 + 5064 = 13450"}
{"Question": "FULL + SAFE = GUESS", "Answer": "8255 + 4689 = 12944"}
{"Question": "ALSO + SHOE = WHEEL", "Answer": "4387 + 8276 = 12663"}
{"Question": "LEAD + AIDS = LOOSE", "Answer": "1684 + 8342 = 10026"}
{"Question": "MESS + ARMY = AWARE", "Answer": "8755 + 1382 = 10137"}
{"Question": "DIRT + RATE = MEDIA", "Answer": "9586 + 8367 = 17953"}
{"Question": "SEAT + AUTO = LOOSE", "Answer": "3785 + 8452 = 12237"}
{"Question": "TELL + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8466 + 1582 = 10048"}
{"Question": "PIPE + CALL = CHEAP", "Answer": "8782 + 1466 = 10248"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TOSS = TROOP", "Answer": "8982 + 1466 = 10448"}
{"Question": "EVER + WARM = WOMAN", "Answer": "8687 + 1572 = 10259"}
{"Question": "NINE + CREW = COLOR", "Answer": "8682 + 1725 = 10407"}
{"Question": "ALSO + STOP = ADOPT", "Answer": "1784 + 8642 = 10426"}
{"Question": "NINE + CREW = CLEAR", "Answer": "8684 + 1743 = 10427"}
{"Question": "EVER + PORT = PIANO", "Answer": "8685 + 1752 = 10437"}
{"Question": "EARN + RING = EAGER", "Answer": "1092 + 9627 = 10719"}
{"Question": "SELL + TASK = TASTE", "Answer": "9822 + 1096 = 10918"}
{"Question": "NINE + FUEL = FULLY", "Answer": "9294 + 1043 = 10337"}
{"Question": "WAIT + INTO = ASIAN", "Answer": "4192 + 9725 = 13917"}
{"Question": "FREE + GIFT = REFER", "Answer": "9133 + 4798 = 13931"}
{"Question": "RARE + THEN = AGENT", "Answer": "9194 + 7243 = 16437"}
{"Question": "QUIT + INTO = ONION", "Answer": "4592 + 9321 = 13913"}
{"Question": "SELL + CAST = TASTE", "Answer": "9322 + 6591 = 15913"}
{"Question": "CELL + SUCH = ISSUE", "Answer": "9866 + 4592 = 14458"}
{"Question": "RARE + NINE = RURAL", "Answer": "1913 + 8283 = 10196"}
{"Question": "RIDE + DARE = IDEA", "Answer": "1534 + 3814 = 5348"}
{"Question": "COPE + PACE = CHEAP", "Answer": "1584 + 8914 = 10498"}
{"Question": "REST + SORT = RATIO", "Answer": "1783 + 8613 = 10396"}
{"Question": "SALE + LOSE = ASIAN", "Answer": "2193 + 9823 = 12016"}
{"Question": "SORT + REST = HORSE", "Answer": "3298 + 9638 = 12936"}
{"Question": "ROPE + PURE = OCCUR", "Answer": "4152 + 5942 = 10094"}
{"Question": "RARE + NINE = MINOR", "Answer": "4547 + 8287 = 12834"}
{"Question": "SUCH + CASH = GUESS", "Answer": "4397 + 9247 = 13644"}
{"Question": "RARE + NINE = PAPER", "Answer": "4342 + 8782 = 13124"}
{"Question": "REST + SORT = AGREE", "Answer": "5487 + 8057 = 13544"}
{"Question": "SORT + REST = HOUSE", "Answer": "5496 + 9256 = 14752"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NONE = BEGIN", "Answer": "5354 + 8684 = 14038"}
{"Question": "NONE + PIPE = TOPIC", "Answer": "5356 + 8486 = 13842"}
{"Question": "LIST + SALT = BASIS", "Answer": "5489 + 8359 = 13848"}
{"Question": "NONE + PIPE = OFTEN", "Answer": "6163 + 7873 = 14036"}
{"Question": "SURE + RISE = GUESS", "Answer": "6598 + 9268 = 15866"}
{"Question": "PIPE + NONE = HONEY", "Answer": "6365 + 8485 = 14850"}
{"Question": "LIST + SALT = VITAL", "Answer": "6378 + 7468 = 13846"}
{"Question": "DARE + RIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "7085 + 8675 = 15760"}
{"Question": "LOST + SALT = HELLO", "Answer": "8296 + 9586 = 17882"}
{"Question": "SOFT + FAST = USUAL", "Answer": "8392 + 9782 = 18174"}
{"Question": "RACE + CORN = EAGER", "Answer": "5261 + 6754 = 12015"}
{"Question": "NINE + BABY = LABEL", "Answer": "5453 + 7278 = 12731"}
{"Question": "SING + NOSE = AGAIN", "Answer": "5273 + 7854 = 13127"}
{"Question": "NONE + ARAB = BOARD", "Answer": "5359 + 8481 = 13840"}
{"Question": "FOLK + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "5487 + 8651 = 14138"}
{"Question": "DARK + RIDE = NAKED", "Answer": "5482 + 8753 = 14235"}
{"Question": "DOWN + WIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "6278 + 7364 = 13642"}
{"Question": "PATH + TYPE = CHEAP", "Answer": "6374 + 7862 = 14236"}
{"Question": "SICK + COST = TOPIC", "Answer": "6487 + 8561 = 15048"}
{"Question": "BEST + SALT = SALAD", "Answer": "9716 + 1086 = 10802"}
{"Question": "BEST + SPOT = SHAPE", "Answer": "9216 + 1536 = 10752"}
{"Question": "BIRD + ROAD = RATIO", "Answer": "9217 + 1407 = 10624"}
{"Question": "EVER + STAR = EARTH", "Answer": "1517 + 9207 = 10724"}
{"Question": "BIRD + ROAD = RADIO", "Answer": "9218 + 1608 = 10826"}
{"Question": "AWAY + ONLY = ALONE", "Answer": "1718 + 9208 = 10926"}
{"Question": "SHOE + ONCE = OCEAN", "Answer": "9317 + 1407 = 10724"}
{"Question": "AWAY + BODY = ALLOW", "Answer": "1412 + 8652 = 10064"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DOWN = ERROR", "Answer": "1615 + 8425 = 10040"}
{"Question": "AWAY + RELY = ALLOW", "Answer": "1417 + 8607 = 10024"}
{"Question": "AWAY + BURY = ALLOW", "Answer": "1417 + 8637 = 10054"}
{"Question": "AWAY + DENY = ANGLE", "Answer": "1917 + 8407 = 10324"}
{"Question": "BABY + VERY = BUYER", "Answer": "1712 + 8542 = 10254"}
{"Question": "READ + ACID = AWARE", "Answer": "8613 + 1573 = 10186"}
{"Question": "URGE + GIVE = EVER", "Answer": "2814 + 1534 = 4348"}
{"Question": "RARE + GIVE = EAGER", "Answer": "2021 + 8791 = 10812"}
{"Question": "EAST + SPOT = PAPER", "Answer": "8027 + 2157 = 10184"}
{"Question": "MAIN + IRON = DRAMA", "Answer": "8427 + 2057 = 10484"}
{"Question": "BABY + RELY = ALTER", "Answer": "2129 + 8309 = 10438"}
{"Question": "REST + SHIT = THERE", "Answer": "7231 + 3041 = 10272"}
{"Question": "NONE + CARE = HONOR", "Answer": "3038 + 7268 = 10306"}
{"Question": "NONE + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "3136 + 9826 = 12962"}
{"Question": "PIPE + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "3534 + 9814 = 13348"}
{"Question": "NONE + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "3738 + 9648 = 13386"}
{"Question": "BABY + RELY = AWARE", "Answer": "4145 + 8035 = 12180"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LAWN = ANGLE", "Answer": "4942 + 7132 = 12074"}
{"Question": "RARE + ONCE = ACTOR", "Answer": "4147 + 8937 = 13084"}
{"Question": "COST + SHUT = TOUCH", "Answer": "9341 + 4251 = 13592"}
{"Question": "WEST + SORT = TOWER", "Answer": "9641 + 4321 = 13962"}
{"Question": "RARE + LOSE = COLOR", "Answer": "4547 + 9387 = 13934"}
{"Question": "THEY + EASY = ASSET", "Answer": "4952 + 5102 = 10054"}
{"Question": "BABY + UGLY = ALBUM", "Answer": "5153 + 7423 = 12576"}
{"Question": "IRON + OPEN = PRESS", "Answer": "7254 + 5134 = 12388"}
{"Question": "ROLE + LIFE = OFFER", "Answer": "8159 + 5239 = 13398"}
{"Question": "BELT + LAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8251 + 5361 = 13612"}
{"Question": "GIRL + REAL = LARGE", "Answer": "9351 + 5241 = 14592"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SITE = TOTAL", "Answer": "6258 + 5918 = 12176"}
{"Question": "NONE + TIRE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5258 + 7468 = 12726"}
{"Question": "BABY + TINY = LATIN", "Answer": "5259 + 7489 = 12748"}
{"Question": "HOUR + USER = SHOE", "Answer": "1354 + 5784 = 7138"}
{"Question": "COST + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8451 + 5721 = 14172"}
{"Question": "AWAY + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "5952 + 8432 = 14384"}
{"Question": "NONE + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "5459 + 8719 = 14178"}
{"Question": "NINE + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "5759 + 8439 = 14198"}
{"Question": "EVER + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "6763 + 9153 = 15916"}
{"Question": "RARE + BONE = ORDER", "Answer": "6863 + 9173 = 16036"}
{"Question": "NONE + FACE = OCEAN", "Answer": "6168 + 4708 = 10876"}
{"Question": "COST + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9361 + 6251 = 15612"}
{"Question": "RARE + COPE = PAPER", "Answer": "6268 + 5918 = 12186"}
{"Question": "PIPE + URGE = GROUP", "Answer": "6863 + 7413 = 14276"}
{"Question": "SHOE + ONCE = TOOTH", "Answer": "9864 + 6754 = 16618"}
{"Question": "HOST + SALT = TOOTH", "Answer": "2071 + 7941 = 10012"}
{"Question": "EVEN + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "7576 + 3026 = 10602"}
{"Question": "ROPE + PAGE = AGREE", "Answer": "6470 + 7130 = 13600"}
{"Question": "ONCE + CARE = NEVER", "Answer": "5173 + 7863 = 13036"}
{"Question": "RARE + CODE = ARMED", "Answer": "7173 + 9863 = 17036"}
{"Question": "LIFE + FADE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8174 + 7254 = 15428"}
{"Question": "THEN + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "3176 + 7426 = 10602"}
{"Question": "NINE + CASE = SINCE", "Answer": "7570 + 8210 = 15780"}
{"Question": "NINE + LAKE = PANEL", "Answer": "7478 + 6308 = 13786"}
{"Question": "LEFT + FACT = TOTAL", "Answer": "2471 + 7691 = 10162"}
{"Question": "EVEN + DOWN = WOUND", "Answer": "7479 + 8619 = 16098"}
{"Question": "EAST + SHIT = TASTE", "Answer": "2081 + 8731 = 10812"}
{"Question": "DIRT + REST = TIRED", "Answer": "2081 + 8791 = 10872"}
{"Question": "BEST + SHOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "5081 + 8231 = 13312"}
{"Question": "EAST + SHIT = CATCH", "Answer": "6485 + 8025 = 14510"}
{"Question": "TIME + MALE = LIMIT", "Answer": "2086 + 8716 = 10802"}
{"Question": "NONE + TIME = MINOR", "Answer": "8086 + 9716 = 17802"}
{"Question": "NINE + FACE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8087 + 2517 = 10604"}
{"Question": "BABY + JURY = URBAN", "Answer": "8685 + 9175 = 17860"}
{"Question": "HOLE + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "3284 + 8914 = 12198"}
{"Question": "RACE + CLUE = RURAL", "Answer": "1986 + 8206 = 10192"}
{"Question": "POST + SEAT = PAPER", "Answer": "1287 + 8907 = 10194"}
{"Question": "GIFT + FLAT = TITLE", "Answer": "4381 + 8791 = 13172"}
{"Question": "URGE + GIVE = EVERY", "Answer": "6381 + 8751 = 15132"}
{"Question": "BABY + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "8382 + 4912 = 13294"}
{"Question": "LIST + SEAT = APPLE", "Answer": "9382 + 8412 = 17794"}
{"Question": "THEY + EASY = SHELL", "Answer": "6485 + 8315 = 14800"}
{"Question": "COST + SHIT = CATCH", "Answer": "1782 + 8432 = 10214"}
{"Question": "NONE + TRUE = THEIR", "Answer": "8782 + 1452 = 10234"}
{"Question": "NINE + TRUE = THEIR", "Answer": "8782 + 1492 = 10274"}
{"Question": "DATE + TIME = MEDIA", "Answer": "3482 + 8912 = 12394"}
{"Question": "FAST + SHOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1483 + 8653 = 10136"}
{"Question": "BELT + LAST = BIBLE", "Answer": "1487 + 8697 = 10184"}
{"Question": "MOST + SHIT = THEME", "Answer": "7581 + 8691 = 16272"}
{"Question": "EVER + STAR = SHOOT", "Answer": "8583 + 1643 = 10226"}
{"Question": "VARY + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "6584 + 8914 = 15498"}
{"Question": "EVEN + PLAN = PANEL", "Answer": "8783 + 1603 = 10386"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CLUB = CIVIL", "Answer": "8783 + 1623 = 10406"}
{"Question": "EVER + STAR = SHIRT", "Answer": "8783 + 1653 = 10436"}
{"Question": "NINE + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "8783 + 4653 = 13436"}
{"Question": "OKAY + ARMY = MAYOR", "Answer": "9783 + 8613 = 18396"}
{"Question": "NINE + CAKE = CLEAN", "Answer": "8684 + 1794 = 10478"}
{"Question": "NINE + CARE = CREAM", "Answer": "8786 + 1906 = 10692"}
{"Question": "NINE + SHOE = SHELL", "Answer": "9293 + 1073 = 10366"}
{"Question": "CASE + SHOE = CATCH", "Answer": "1093 + 9623 = 10716"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CLUB = CRACK", "Answer": "9093 + 1823 = 10916"}
{"Question": "CAST + SOFT = CATCH", "Answer": "1094 + 9324 = 10418"}
{"Question": "LATE + TRUE = LATER", "Answer": "1094 + 9854 = 10948"}
{"Question": "RARE + NOSE = ONION", "Answer": "9893 + 6123 = 16016"}
{"Question": "SHUT + UNIT = SOUTH", "Answer": "1693 + 9243 = 10936"}
{"Question": "RARE + TYPE = HAPPY", "Answer": "9496 + 5276 = 14772"}
{"Question": "THIN + IRON = MOTOR", "Answer": "8596 + 9276 = 17872"}
{"Question": "HIRE + RACE = CATCH", "Answer": "4297 + 9317 = 13614"}
{"Question": "AWAY + THEY = SHEET", "Answer": "9297 + 4367 = 13664"}
{"Question": "NINE + CARE = EAGER", "Answer": "9391 + 5421 = 14812"}
{"Question": "SOFT + FLAT = SHELL", "Answer": "1392 + 9452 = 10844"}
{"Question": "AWAY + TINY = TRAIN", "Answer": "9592 + 1342 = 10934"}
{"Question": "ARAB + MUCH = ALBUM", "Answer": "1712 + 8546 = 10258"}
{"Question": "COLD + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "7243 + 4951 = 12194"}
{"Question": "BABY + LONG = ANGLE", "Answer": "5152 + 8637 = 13789"}
{"Question": "STAR + AIDE = TIRED", "Answer": "8154 + 5306 = 13460"}
{"Question": "NONE + WRAP = POWER", "Answer": "5253 + 7481 = 12734"}
{"Question": "FARM + RIDE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8451 + 5273 = 13724"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CHEF = BENCH", "Answer": "5251 + 8736 = 13987"}
{"Question": "EVEN + LIFT = TITLE", "Answer": "5854 + 7321 = 13175"}
{"Question": "PIPE + ALSO = SLEEP", "Answer": "5357 + 9418 = 14775"}
{"Question": "BABY + PLOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "5753 + 6421 = 12174"}
{"Question": "WHAT + ALSO = TOOTH", "Answer": "7451 + 5863 = 13314"}
{"Question": "ARAB + FIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "6169 + 7352 = 13521"}
{"Question": "ARAB + CODE = ORDER", "Answer": "6562 + 9173 = 15735"}
{"Question": "LOSE + SHIP = HELLO", "Answer": "8764 + 6123 = 14887"}
{"Question": "EAST + SLIP = APPLE", "Answer": "9164 + 6375 = 15539"}
{"Question": "ONCE + CARD = NEVER", "Answer": "4172 + 7853 = 12025"}
{"Question": "TERM + RAIL = ALTER", "Answer": "8672 + 7195 = 15867"}
{"Question": "TYPE + PALM = EMPTY", "Answer": "6471 + 7293 = 13764"}
{"Question": "BABY + ROLE = LAYER", "Answer": "7276 + 5419 = 12695"}
{"Question": "AWAY + REST = STARE", "Answer": "7378 + 9416 = 16794"}
{"Question": "NINE + PALM = LIMIT", "Answer": "8087 + 2516 = 10603"}
{"Question": "NINE + CAMP = CLEAN", "Answer": "8482 + 1796 = 10278"}
{"Question": "NONE + VARY = VIDEO", "Answer": "8485 + 1769 = 10254"}
{"Question": "EVER + MYTH = MARRY", "Answer": "8682 + 1543 = 10225"}
{"Question": "ARAB + SHOT = SOUTH", "Answer": "8786 + 1509 = 10295"}
{"Question": "EVER + STAY = SMART", "Answer": "8682 + 1745 = 10427"}
{"Question": "EVEN + FAIR = FINAL", "Answer": "8685 + 1907 = 10592"}
{"Question": "BABY + COST = CATCH", "Answer": "9093 + 1425 = 10518"}
{"Question": "ARAB + SHOE = REACH", "Answer": "9192 + 6745 = 15937"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = ODDS", "Answer": "2556 + 2562 = 5118"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = INTO", "Answer": "3112 + 3123 = 6235"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = MALL", "Answer": "4338 + 4384 = 8722"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = WOMAN", "Answer": "6224 + 6246 = 12470"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = LOCAL", "Answer": "6225 + 6256 = 12481"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = CLOCK", "Answer": "6992 + 6926 = 13918"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = KNOCK", "Answer": "7334 + 7347 = 14681"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = SORRY", "Answer": "7443 + 7437 = 14880"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = DOUBT", "Answer": "7552 + 7527 = 15079"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = TOTAL", "Answer": "7556 + 7567 = 15123"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = SMALL", "Answer": "7665 + 7657 = 15322"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = AGREE", "Answer": "7669 + 7697 = 15366"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = MOTOR", "Answer": "7886 + 7867 = 15753"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = AMONG", "Answer": "8006 + 8068 = 16074"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = DANCE", "Answer": "8224 + 8248 = 16472"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8552 + 8528 = 17080"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = AHEAD", "Answer": "8664 + 8648 = 17312"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = PRIOR", "Answer": "8669 + 8698 = 17367"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TENT = ENJOY", "Answer": "9118 + 9189 = 18307"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOMB = MARRY", "Answer": "9221 + 9219 = 18440"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = RIDE", "Answer": "1332 + 1381 = 2713"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = NINE", "Answer": "1332 + 1391 = 2723"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = TAPE", "Answer": "1443 + 1491 = 2934"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOMB = ONTO", "Answer": "2553 + 2582 = 5135"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = RARE", "Answer": "2886 + 2872 = 5758"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = EASE", "Answer": "3774 + 3753 = 7527"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = ELITE", "Answer": "5116 + 5135 = 10251"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "5338 + 5315 = 10653"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = READY", "Answer": "6221 + 6246 = 12467"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = READY", "Answer": "6223 + 6246 = 12469"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "6559 + 6506 = 13065"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = RAPID", "Answer": "6550 + 6536 = 13086"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = IRISH", "Answer": "6553 + 6576 = 13129"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOMB = TITLE", "Answer": "6551 + 6596 = 13147"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOMB = ADAPT", "Answer": "6552 + 6596 = 13148"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PHONE", "Answer": "6771 + 6726 = 13497"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PAUSE", "Answer": "6771 + 6736 = 13507"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PHASE", "Answer": "6771 + 6756 = 13527"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PRIDE", "Answer": "6771 + 6796 = 13567"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PRESS", "Answer": "6991 + 6986 = 13977"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = SINCE", "Answer": "7336 + 7317 = 14653"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = TRUST", "Answer": "7334 + 7357 = 14691"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOMB = TOTAL", "Answer": "7551 + 7597 = 15148"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOMB = CATCH", "Answer": "7663 + 7647 = 15310"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOMB = PRIOR", "Answer": "7668 + 7697 = 15365"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = SCENE", "Answer": "8002 + 8018 = 16020"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOMB = STORM", "Answer": "8006 + 8048 = 16054"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = VISIT", "Answer": "8220 + 8248 = 16468"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = CRACK", "Answer": "8336 + 8378 = 16714"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = SPACE", "Answer": "8557 + 8508 = 17065"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = PRIDE", "Answer": "8557 + 8528 = 17085"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = START", "Answer": "8669 + 8628 = 17297"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = SENSE", "Answer": "8779 + 8738 = 17517"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = LEVEL", "Answer": "8773 + 8798 = 17571"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = GRASS", "Answer": "9228 + 9249 = 18477"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAD = PROOF", "Answer": "9331 + 9329 = 18660"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = SORRY", "Answer": "9336 + 9329 = 18665"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "9445 + 9419 = 18864"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = STAFF", "Answer": "9558 + 9519 = 19077"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEXT = STATE", "Answer": "9556 + 9539 = 19095"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEST = STATE", "Answer": "9778 + 9719 = 19497"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = EVER", "Answer": "1201 + 1322 = 2523"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = AIDE", "Answer": "1321 + 1292 = 2613"}
{"Question": "TEST + TREE = STAR", "Answer": "1531 + 1655 = 3186"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = HEART", "Answer": "5025 + 5272 = 10297"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = ANGER", "Answer": "5205 + 5722 = 10927"}
{"Question": "TEXT + TREE = RELAX", "Answer": "6286 + 6122 = 12408"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = EAGER", "Answer": "6126 + 6292 = 12418"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = TRADE", "Answer": "6046 + 6414 = 12460"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = METER", "Answer": "6246 + 6474 = 12720"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = PHOTO", "Answer": "6876 + 6588 = 13464"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = STUDY", "Answer": "7827 + 7252 = 15079"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = TITLE", "Answer": "7927 + 7212 = 15139"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = REFER", "Answer": "7497 + 7144 = 14641"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = LABEL", "Answer": "7547 + 7404 = 14951"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = HELLO", "Answer": "7457 + 7535 = 14992"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = UNION", "Answer": "7857 + 7388 = 15245"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = ONION", "Answer": "7487 + 7828 = 15315"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = SENSE", "Answer": "7587 + 7828 = 15415"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = ORDER", "Answer": "7897 + 7588 = 15485"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = ORDER", "Answer": "7987 + 7808 = 15795"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = START", "Answer": "7987 + 7858 = 15845"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = ENTRY", "Answer": "8168 + 8711 = 16879"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = BLADE", "Answer": "8028 + 8252 = 16280"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = ESSAY", "Answer": "8148 + 8494 = 16642"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = CARRY", "Answer": "8368 + 8626 = 16994"}
{"Question": "TENT + TREE = MINOR", "Answer": "9369 + 9233 = 18602"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATA = ENTER", "Answer": "9149 + 9464 = 18613"}
{"Question": "TEST + TREE = STAIR", "Answer": "9819 + 9788 = 19607"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = ODDS", "Answer": "2742 + 2487 = 5229"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = ALLY", "Answer": "2752 + 2587 = 5339"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = EVER", "Answer": "2582 + 2875 = 5457"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = PHOTO", "Answer": "5245 + 5492 = 10737"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "5165 + 5681 = 10846"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = EAGER", "Answer": "6126 + 6291 = 12417"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = PARTY", "Answer": "6326 + 6253 = 12579"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = RIVER", "Answer": "6536 + 6315 = 12851"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = PAPER", "Answer": "6836 + 6348 = 13184"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = LATER", "Answer": "6936 + 6359 = 13295"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = FEWER", "Answer": "6246 + 6482 = 12728"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = CRACK", "Answer": "6976 + 6739 = 13715"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = REFER", "Answer": "7427 + 7214 = 14641"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = BRIEF", "Answer": "7937 + 7359 = 15296"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = RADIO", "Answer": "7347 + 7413 = 14760"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = LATER", "Answer": "7347 + 7483 = 14830"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = CROSS", "Answer": "7357 + 7543 = 14900"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = LABEL", "Answer": "7457 + 7584 = 15041"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = PAPER", "Answer": "7657 + 7506 = 15163"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = ASSET", "Answer": "8518 + 8135 = 16653"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8248 + 8472 = 16720"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARE = ASSET", "Answer": "9719 + 9157 = 18876"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DATE = ENTER", "Answer": "9149 + 9461 = 18610"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = WHERE", "Answer": "5725 + 5072 = 10797"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = ENEMY", "Answer": "6126 + 6012 = 12138"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = ALTER", "Answer": "6516 + 6122 = 12638"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = PLATE", "Answer": "6046 + 6422 = 12468"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = ERROR", "Answer": "6846 + 6477 = 13323"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = EARTH", "Answer": "7157 + 7215 = 14372"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = BUNCH", "Answer": "7357 + 7235 = 14592"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = WHICH", "Answer": "7547 + 7488 = 15035"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = PHOTO", "Answer": "7457 + 7522 = 14979"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = LEAVE", "Answer": "7587 + 7658 = 15245"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = PARTY", "Answer": "7857 + 7522 = 15379"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = EARTH", "Answer": "7957 + 7522 = 15479"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = CLASS", "Answer": "7967 + 7655 = 15622"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEN = HAPPY", "Answer": "7827 + 7182 = 15009"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = DEATH", "Answer": "8058 + 8522 = 16580"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALL = ALLOW", "Answer": "9619 + 9188 = 18807"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DIET = TAIL", "Answer": "1521 + 1753 = 3274"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALE = HEEL", "Answer": "2582 + 2864 = 5446"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = HERE", "Answer": "3551 + 3943 = 7494"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GANG = ONTO", "Answer": "3774 + 3523 = 7297"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TENT = ONTO", "Answer": "3774 + 3863 = 7637"}
{"Question": "TOOL + THAT = SALES", "Answer": "5226 + 5405 = 10631"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = SHARE", "Answer": "5229 + 5465 = 10694"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = ARMED", "Answer": "5330 + 5415 = 10745"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAKE = CHECK", "Answer": "5075 + 5738 = 10813"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = READY", "Answer": "5771 + 5085 = 10856"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THAT = ENTER", "Answer": "6112 + 6506 = 12618"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = ONION", "Answer": "6117 + 6896 = 13013"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARK = EAGER", "Answer": "6126 + 6293 = 12419"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "6426 + 6213 = 12639"}
{"Question": "TOOL + THAT = COACH", "Answer": "6229 + 6586 = 12815"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = FORCE", "Answer": "6332 + 6876 = 13208"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEM = NERVE", "Answer": "6316 + 6937 = 13253"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HAIR = TIGHT", "Answer": "6326 + 6935 = 13261"}
{"Question": "GANG + GOAL = HONOR", "Answer": "6476 + 6249 = 12725"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = CARRY", "Answer": "6558 + 6326 = 12884"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KICK = SCOPE", "Answer": "6559 + 6736 = 13295"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TEST = ASSET", "Answer": "6550 + 6836 = 13386"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TENT = NEWLY", "Answer": "6779 + 6316 = 13095"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TENT = BIBLE", "Answer": "6778 + 6406 = 13184"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAIL = IRISH", "Answer": "6476 + 6718 = 13194"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = RADIO", "Answer": "6771 + 6836 = 13607"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAKE = EXTRA", "Answer": "6876 + 6751 = 13627"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOMB = ONION", "Answer": "6887 + 6126 = 13013"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ONTO = NERVE", "Answer": "6887 + 6156 = 13043"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HAIR = RURAL", "Answer": "6846 + 6281 = 13127"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TENT = HELLO", "Answer": "6882 + 6346 = 13228"}
{"Question": "THAT + TALK = LEAVE", "Answer": "6986 + 6817 = 13803"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "7427 + 7236 = 14663"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HIGH = GLOVE", "Answer": "7225 + 7817 = 15042"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = AGREE", "Answer": "7338 + 7517 = 14855"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOMB = AWARE", "Answer": "7336 + 7827 = 15163"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THAT = HEAVY", "Answer": "7442 + 7167 = 14609"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAKE = SHEET", "Answer": "7547 + 7460 = 15007"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DARK = PAPER", "Answer": "7657 + 7503 = 15160"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ONTO = STONE", "Answer": "7661 + 7047 = 14708"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HIGH = BIBLE", "Answer": "7669 + 7527 = 15196"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THAT = COACH", "Answer": "7886 + 7327 = 15213"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ONTO = STAND", "Answer": "7881 + 7357 = 15238"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = TOTAL", "Answer": "8224 + 8958 = 17182"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOMB = MORAL", "Answer": "8339 + 8618 = 16957"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = SENSE", "Answer": "8339 + 8678 = 17017"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "8339 + 8708 = 17047"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ONTO = UNION", "Answer": "8339 + 8748 = 17087"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAD = PRIDE", "Answer": "8556 + 8428 = 16984"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "8553 + 8728 = 17281"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = BLOOD", "Answer": "8667 + 8328 = 16995"}
{"Question": "THAT + TAPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "8768 + 8615 = 17383"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AREA = CLEAR", "Answer": "8775 + 8308 = 17083"}
{"Question": "TENT + THEM = SENSE", "Answer": "8738 + 8579 = 17317"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THAT = STATE", "Answer": "9556 + 9839 = 19395"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TEST = STYLE", "Answer": "9668 + 9719 = 19387"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = POUND", "Answer": "8661 + 1667 = 10328"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOOL = THREE", "Answer": "8771 + 1773 = 10544"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEEP = DRESS", "Answer": "8991 + 1997 = 10988"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEEN = NINE", "Answer": "3882 + 2886 = 6768"}
{"Question": "MOOD + DOOR = ARMED", "Answer": "7882 + 2880 = 10762"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROOM = ARMED", "Answer": "9882 + 2887 = 12769"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEEN = ELITE", "Answer": "7113 + 3118 = 10231"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEED = HONOR", "Answer": "8663 + 3664 = 12327"}
{"Question": "KEEP + PEER = DRAMA", "Answer": "8773 + 3772 = 12545"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOOK = ADAPT", "Answer": "7554 + 4553 = 12107"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOOT = METER", "Answer": "7664 + 4663 = 12327"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEEP = PASS", "Answer": "3115 + 5118 = 8233"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = RAPID", "Answer": "6775 + 5771 = 12546"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = APPLE", "Answer": "9775 + 5772 = 15547"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOOT = THREE", "Answer": "7885 + 5881 = 13766"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MOOD = TOTAL", "Answer": "8556 + 6553 = 15109"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEER = RIFLE", "Answer": "5776 + 6771 = 12547"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOOD = INNER", "Answer": "8776 + 6772 = 15548"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOOK = ONLY", "Answer": "1886 + 6883 = 8769"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEED = ELITE", "Answer": "3117 + 7114 = 10231"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = BOARD", "Answer": "6447 + 7449 = 13896"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROOT = STUDY", "Answer": "9447 + 7446 = 16893"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROOF = FOUND", "Answer": "8667 + 7661 = 16328"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEEP = PRESS", "Answer": "8997 + 7991 = 16988"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEEP = APPLE", "Answer": "6228 + 8224 = 14452"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEER = LEARN", "Answer": "5338 + 8337 = 13675"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = GRADE", "Answer": "7338 + 8335 = 15673"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROOT = FORTH", "Answer": "6448 + 8449 = 14897"}
{"Question": "FOOT + TOOL = FULLY", "Answer": "1778 + 8775 = 10553"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOOT = VOTER", "Answer": "3229 + 9224 = 12453"}
{"Question": "KEEP + PEER = KNOCK", "Answer": "1339 + 9332 = 10671"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOOK = TOPIC", "Answer": "4339 + 9335 = 13674"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEER = ARGUE", "Answer": "5339 + 9334 = 14673"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEEP = SHADE", "Answer": "1449 + 9445 = 10894"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEEN = MONTH", "Answer": "1449 + 9448 = 10897"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOOL = ELITE", "Answer": "3449 + 9442 = 12891"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEER = READY", "Answer": "5449 + 9441 = 14890"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROOF = BOARD", "Answer": "5449 + 9446 = 14895"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAD = EVEN", "Answer": "2331 + 1301 = 3632"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = DRAFT", "Answer": "9331 + 1361 = 10692"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAD = DRINK", "Answer": "9441 + 1451 = 10892"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAD = ODDS", "Answer": "2551 + 1561 = 4112"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8551 + 1591 = 10142"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = TROOP", "Answer": "8661 + 1671 = 10332"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = DRESS", "Answer": "8991 + 1931 = 10922"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = ENTER", "Answer": "8112 + 2102 = 10214"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = INNER", "Answer": "7552 + 2502 = 10054"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = ONTO", "Answer": "1772 + 2752 = 4524"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "8663 + 3613 = 12276"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEST = STAGE", "Answer": "9663 + 3613 = 13276"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAD = GANG", "Answer": "2773 + 3753 = 6526"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAD = PANEL", "Answer": "6334 + 4304 = 10638"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7554 + 4594 = 12148"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = STAFF", "Answer": "8664 + 4624 = 13288"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAD = ELSE", "Answer": "3884 + 4854 = 8738"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = EASE", "Answer": "3884 + 4874 = 8758"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = STATE", "Answer": "9884 + 4864 = 14748"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = CHECK", "Answer": "5994 + 4924 = 10918"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = ONION", "Answer": "4885 + 5825 = 10710"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = READY", "Answer": "8556 + 6506 = 15062"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = ONION", "Answer": "5886 + 6826 = 12712"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = KNEE", "Answer": "1447 + 7497 = 8944"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAD = ALONE", "Answer": "6447 + 7417 = 13864"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAD = TASTE", "Answer": "9447 + 7467 = 16914"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = FIFTH", "Answer": "1558 + 8578 = 10136"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = FALSE", "Answer": "1668 + 8608 = 10276"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = FLAME", "Answer": "1668 + 8628 = 10296"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAD = STATE", "Answer": "1668 + 8638 = 10306"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = TASTE", "Answer": "5668 + 8648 = 14316"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = SENSE", "Answer": "7668 + 8648 = 16316"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAD = FENCE", "Answer": "7668 + 8658 = 16326"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEST = STATE", "Answer": "9668 + 8618 = 18286"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = FIBER", "Answer": "1778 + 8798 = 10576"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = FLOOR", "Answer": "1339 + 9329 = 10668"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = MOTOR", "Answer": "1449 + 9459 = 10908"}
{"Question": "MEET + TENT = MATCH", "Answer": "1449 + 9479 = 10928"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "5449 + 9489 = 14938"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = MORAL", "Answer": "9221 + 1242 = 10463"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = MUSIC", "Answer": "9441 + 1484 = 10925"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = BOMB", "Answer": "6771 + 1747 = 8518"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = ODDS", "Answer": "1338 + 8323 = 9661"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5338 + 8393 = 13731"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = CLASS", "Answer": "2448 + 8474 = 10922"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = SHRUG", "Answer": "1668 + 8626 = 10294"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = BASIS", "Answer": "5778 + 8727 = 14505"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MERE = SALAD", "Answer": "1339 + 9363 = 10702"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAF = FIFTH", "Answer": "1558 + 8571 = 10129"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEXT = DATA", "Answer": "1662 + 2651 = 4313"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOST = ONLY", "Answer": "1664 + 4681 = 6345"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROAD = READY", "Answer": "8661 + 1628 = 10289"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAF = FUNNY", "Answer": "1668 + 8671 = 10339"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROAD = DEATH", "Answer": "1778 + 8751 = 10529"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = DOUBT", "Answer": "1778 + 8761 = 10539"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEAM = DATA", "Answer": "3772 + 2753 = 6525"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = EARN", "Answer": "4772 + 2754 = 7526"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAF = APPLY", "Answer": "3556 + 6513 = 10069"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOUR = APART", "Answer": "3556 + 6583 = 10139"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOUR = ELITE", "Answer": "3778 + 8703 = 12481"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = CARE", "Answer": "3885 + 5873 = 9758"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROAD = AGREE", "Answer": "3886 + 6813 = 10699"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = SORRY", "Answer": "4775 + 5784 = 10559"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOST = SALES", "Answer": "4887 + 7814 = 12701"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = BADLY", "Answer": "5778 + 8745 = 14523"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOUR = COURT", "Answer": "6558 + 8506 = 15064"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9556 + 6509 = 16065"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEXT = STONE", "Answer": "6559 + 9536 = 16095"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = ASIDE", "Answer": "7558 + 8517 = 16075"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = SCORE", "Answer": "7558 + 8527 = 16085"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOST = SOUTH", "Answer": "8667 + 7618 = 16285"}
{"Question": "DEER + READ = GRADE", "Answer": "9667 + 7629 = 17296"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAF = ALLOW", "Answer": "9887 + 7819 = 17706"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOST = STAFF", "Answer": "8559 + 9518 = 18077"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = LIMIT", "Answer": "9221 + 1288 = 10509"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOSS = ALLY", "Answer": "2551 + 1566 = 4117"}
{"Question": "DOOR + WORD = ODDS", "Answer": "1556 + 3561 = 5117"}
{"Question": "POOR + ROLL = ODDS", "Answer": "4661 + 1677 = 6338"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = TASTE", "Answer": "8661 + 1655 = 10316"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = SALES", "Answer": "8442 + 2499 = 10941"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = ITEM", "Answer": "2113 + 3199 = 5312"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "7113 + 3199 = 10312"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = APART", "Answer": "8553 + 3577 = 12130"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = ENTER", "Answer": "8663 + 3655 = 12318"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = SALAD", "Answer": "8773 + 3755 = 12528"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LESS = SALE", "Answer": "1883 + 3855 = 5738"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LESS = ANGLE", "Answer": "6883 + 3855 = 10738"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = STATE", "Answer": "9883 + 3855 = 13738"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = LEVEL", "Answer": "6224 + 4277 = 10501"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOSS = SLIP", "Answer": "3225 + 5288 = 8513"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOSS = COLOR", "Answer": "7225 + 5299 = 12524"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = ASSET", "Answer": "9225 + 5244 = 14469"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SELF = ELITE", "Answer": "6115 + 9156 = 15271"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOSS = FORCE", "Answer": "8556 + 6533 = 15089"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = WASTE", "Answer": "5886 + 6877 = 12763"}
{"Question": "MEET + TELL = BLAME", "Answer": "8227 + 7255 = 15482"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = METER", "Answer": "5337 + 7388 = 12725"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = MOTOR", "Answer": "6337 + 7399 = 13736"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOSS = ADAPT", "Answer": "2557 + 7566 = 10123"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LESS = AWARE", "Answer": "2557 + 7588 = 10145"}
{"Question": "DOOR + WORD = AGREE", "Answer": "7663 + 4637 = 12300"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = FORTH", "Answer": "4228 + 8255 = 12483"}
{"Question": "DOOR + WORD = ALLOW", "Answer": "8229 + 7298 = 15527"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = GUARD", "Answer": "2338 + 8344 = 10682"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SELF = TASTE", "Answer": "8446 + 9468 = 17914"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1558 + 8566 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = ADAPT", "Answer": "4558 + 8566 = 13124"}
{"Question": "DOOR + WORD = TOTAL", "Answer": "8554 + 6548 = 15102"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = ELITE", "Answer": "9558 + 8533 = 18091"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = BADLY", "Answer": "1668 + 8677 = 10345"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = BELOW", "Answer": "1668 + 8699 = 10367"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = ASIAN", "Answer": "5668 + 8644 = 14312"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = COLOR", "Answer": "7668 + 8699 = 16367"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = CLASS", "Answer": "3778 + 8722 = 12500"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = AGREE", "Answer": "5778 + 8722 = 14500"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = BASIC", "Answer": "1229 + 9244 = 10473"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOSS = SORRY", "Answer": "3229 + 9211 = 12440"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = SOLID", "Answer": "3229 + 9244 = 12473"}
{"Question": "ROOM + BOMB = MARRY", "Answer": "4221 + 9219 = 13440"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = TASTE", "Answer": "1339 + 9377 = 10716"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROLL = BOARD", "Answer": "4339 + 9355 = 13694"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOSS = RIVER", "Answer": "1449 + 9422 = 10871"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOSS = CARRY", "Answer": "1449 + 9433 = 10882"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSS = STATE", "Answer": "8669 + 9611 = 18280"}
{"Question": "TOOL + PORT = THREE", "Answer": "1225 + 9241 = 10466"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROPE = RAPID", "Answer": "9221 + 1248 = 10469"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAN = LUNCH", "Answer": "9221 + 1274 = 10495"}
{"Question": "TOOL + MOST = TERMS", "Answer": "1226 + 9271 = 10497"}
{"Question": "GOOD + SONG = GLASS", "Answer": "1228 + 9271 = 10499"}
{"Question": "MEET + DEAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "9335 + 1361 = 10696"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9331 + 1370 = 10701"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEAK = PRIDE", "Answer": "9441 + 1453 = 10894"}
{"Question": "SEED + TENT = TASTE", "Answer": "9443 + 1471 = 10914"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TONE = TIRED", "Answer": "9441 + 1482 = 10923"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROCK = RADIO", "Answer": "9441 + 1483 = 10924"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LONG = LATIN", "Answer": "9441 + 1487 = 10928"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAD = LOOSE", "Answer": "8551 + 1524 = 10075"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EDGE = ERROR", "Answer": "8559 + 1521 = 10080"}
{"Question": "FOOT + GOLF = FIFTH", "Answer": "1552 + 8571 = 10123"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEAR = TITLE", "Answer": "8551 + 1574 = 10125"}
{"Question": "BEER + RELY = RURAL", "Answer": "8551 + 1576 = 10127"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TENT = TITLE", "Answer": "8554 + 1591 = 10145"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LEFT = TOTAL", "Answer": "1557 + 8591 = 10148"}
{"Question": "GOOD + SONG = ODDS", "Answer": "1663 + 4671 = 6334"}
{"Question": "SOON + LOTS = START", "Answer": "1669 + 8601 = 10270"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOLK = FEWER", "Answer": "8661 + 1647 = 10308"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HEAT = TRUTH", "Answer": "1667 + 8651 = 10318"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MODE = MARRY", "Answer": "8661 + 1674 = 10335"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEAK = PHASE", "Answer": "8771 + 1756 = 10527"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "8771 + 1759 = 10530"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "6881 + 1837 = 8718"}
{"Question": "NEED + DEAR = EARN", "Answer": "6881 + 1875 = 8756"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROSE = ODDS", "Answer": "3662 + 2675 = 6337"}
{"Question": "NEED + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "2665 + 7602 = 10267"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ELSE = STEAL", "Answer": "7664 + 2612 = 10276"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOTS = TEST", "Answer": "3882 + 2864 = 6746"}
{"Question": "DEEP + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "3114 + 7103 = 10217"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOST = STILL", "Answer": "7223 + 3210 = 10433"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EDGE = SALAD", "Answer": "7441 + 3463 = 10904"}
{"Question": "MEET + DEAD = TRADE", "Answer": "7441 + 3493 = 10934"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MODE = ENEMY", "Answer": "6553 + 3581 = 10134"}
{"Question": "BEER + RELY = AWARE", "Answer": "6553 + 3582 = 10135"}
{"Question": "FEED + DENY = CYCLE", "Answer": "8553 + 3592 = 12145"}
{"Question": "BEER + READ = GRADE", "Answer": "9883 + 3875 = 13758"}
{"Question": "BEER + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "8224 + 4251 = 12475"}
{"Question": "GOOD + DOWN = YOUNG", "Answer": "9334 + 4325 = 13659"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAL = LEAST", "Answer": "9334 + 4361 = 13695"}
{"Question": "SOON + LOTS = ELSE", "Answer": "4552 + 1594 = 6146"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOAN = EVENT", "Answer": "7554 + 4583 = 12137"}
{"Question": "DEER + RELY = AWARD", "Answer": "7554 + 4593 = 12147"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "4662 + 7614 = 12276"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAD = ODDS", "Answer": "2774 + 4785 = 7559"}
{"Question": "BEER + REAL = FLAME", "Answer": "8774 + 4753 = 13527"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOVE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9774 + 4785 = 14559"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOAN = PLANT", "Answer": "9884 + 4875 = 14759"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOWN = ENTER", "Answer": "8225 + 5293 = 13518"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEWS = ASSET", "Answer": "9225 + 5204 = 14429"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOWN = INNER", "Answer": "9225 + 5264 = 14489"}
{"Question": "ROOT + POUR = STRIP", "Answer": "5224 + 9285 = 14509"}
{"Question": "DEER + REST = STAND", "Answer": "7335 + 5312 = 12647"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MODE = BOARD", "Answer": "8335 + 5349 = 13684"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEAR = FRONT", "Answer": "9335 + 5324 = 14659"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAL = CLASS", "Answer": "9335 + 5364 = 14699"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOAD = ADULT", "Answer": "7445 + 5412 = 12857"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAN = DANCE", "Answer": "7445 + 5428 = 12873"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MODE = FEWER", "Answer": "7445 + 5482 = 12927"}
{"Question": "PEER + READ = HAPPY", "Answer": "8445 + 5437 = 13882"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MOVE = NEVER", "Answer": "8445 + 5493 = 13938"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEAK = MAKER", "Answer": "4665 + 5602 = 10267"}
{"Question": "ROOM + YOUR = MARRY", "Answer": "5771 + 6785 = 12556"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "6775 + 5782 = 12557"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LEAD = APPLY", "Answer": "5774 + 8715 = 14489"}
{"Question": "PEER + TEST = STRIP", "Answer": "9774 + 5715 = 15489"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TONE = ONTO", "Answer": "2885 + 5873 = 8758"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MOVE = RIVER", "Answer": "4885 + 5876 = 10761"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEAR = STATE", "Answer": "9885 + 5873 = 15758"}
{"Question": "DEER + RELY = AHEAD", "Answer": "8995 + 5923 = 14918"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOWN = OWNER", "Answer": "8116 + 6142 = 14258"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TONE = OWNER", "Answer": "9116 + 6123 = 15239"}
{"Question": "MOON + FORM = ENTER", "Answer": "6223 + 7296 = 13519"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BOMB = LIMIT", "Answer": "7441 + 6496 = 13937"}
{"Question": "HEEL + YEAH = APPLY", "Answer": "6557 + 3516 = 10073"}
{"Question": "TOOL + COAT = ELECT", "Answer": "6550 + 3586 = 10136"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "7556 + 6510 = 14066"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PEAK = ASIDE", "Answer": "7556 + 6519 = 14075"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOLK = COLOR", "Answer": "8556 + 6502 = 15058"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEFT = FENCE", "Answer": "8556 + 6519 = 15075"}
{"Question": "DOOR + LOAD = WORLD", "Answer": "6550 + 8536 = 15086"}
{"Question": "DOOR + LOUD = TOTAL", "Answer": "6552 + 8596 = 15148"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TEND = ADAPT", "Answer": "6553 + 9586 = 16139"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEBT = TASTE", "Answer": "3776 + 6741 = 10517"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAN = UNCLE", "Answer": "5776 + 6792 = 12568"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TONE = INNER", "Answer": "8776 + 6752 = 15528"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "5886 + 6827 = 12713"}
{"Question": "DEER + REAL = BLADE", "Answer": "5886 + 6872 = 12758"}
{"Question": "BEER + REAL = CABLE", "Answer": "7886 + 6842 = 14728"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEFT = EARTH", "Answer": "3117 + 7146 = 10263"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEAD = EARTH", "Answer": "6117 + 7139 = 13256"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TOUR = COURT", "Answer": "7228 + 5247 = 12475"}
{"Question": "FEED + DEAL = BLADE", "Answer": "8227 + 7245 = 15472"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEFT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8227 + 7291 = 15518"}
{"Question": "DOOR + COLD = LOCAL", "Answer": "7334 + 6317 = 13651"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOVE = VOTER", "Answer": "6337 + 7315 = 13652"}
{"Question": "DEEP + HEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "7336 + 9317 = 16653"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "2557 + 7518 = 10075"}
{"Question": "POOR + SOUP = TRUST", "Answer": "7554 + 6507 = 14061"}
{"Question": "BEER + REST = STORM", "Answer": "8557 + 7516 = 16073"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MODE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8557 + 7563 = 16120"}
{"Question": "TEEN + BEST = STATE", "Answer": "7558 + 9517 = 17075"}
{"Question": "TEEN + REST = NEVER", "Answer": "7661 + 8607 = 16268"}
{"Question": "MEET + TEND = FENCE", "Answer": "8667 + 7639 = 16306"}
{"Question": "BEER + READ = SENSE", "Answer": "8667 + 7649 = 16316"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEAF = RIFLE", "Answer": "9228 + 8254 = 17482"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROPE = SPEED", "Answer": "4338 + 8326 = 12664"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ROCK = BOARD", "Answer": "5338 + 8347 = 13685"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TOWN = HONOR", "Answer": "5338 + 8397 = 13735"}
{"Question": "BEER + REST = STATE", "Answer": "7338 + 8315 = 15653"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LEAD = LOOSE", "Answer": "8557 + 1538 = 10095"}
{"Question": "BEER + READ = BIBLE", "Answer": "1558 + 8567 = 10125"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOLK = RURAL", "Answer": "1558 + 8579 = 10137"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOUD = ADAPT", "Answer": "3558 + 8572 = 12130"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "9558 + 8517 = 18075"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOSE = ELECT", "Answer": "9558 + 8571 = 18129"}
{"Question": "BEER + REAL = BADLY", "Answer": "1668 + 8607 = 10275"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LOUD = TRUST", "Answer": "1668 + 8623 = 10291"}
{"Question": "POOL + SOUP = SLEEP", "Answer": "8660 + 1678 = 10338"}
{"Question": "BEER + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "7668 + 8621 = 16289"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEAF = REFER", "Answer": "7668 + 8693 = 16361"}
{"Question": "PEER + REST = TROOP", "Answer": "9668 + 8671 = 18339"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOAD = CABLE", "Answer": "1778 + 8705 = 10483"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOAD = PEACE", "Answer": "1778 + 8752 = 10530"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MOVE = RIVER", "Answer": "1778 + 8753 = 10531"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEBT = SALES", "Answer": "1778 + 8793 = 10571"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LEAN = HONEY", "Answer": "1778 + 8795 = 10573"}
{"Question": "BEER + READ = TASTE", "Answer": "4778 + 8739 = 13517"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "4778 + 8753 = 13531"}
{"Question": "BEER + REAL = APPLE", "Answer": "5778 + 8719 = 14497"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TOUR = FRUIT", "Answer": "8771 + 9758 = 18529"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MODE = BREAD", "Answer": "1229 + 9234 = 10463"}
{"Question": "SEED + DEAL = STAFF", "Answer": "1229 + 9248 = 10477"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TOUR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1229 + 9264 = 10493"}
{"Question": "MOOD + POEM = PRIME", "Answer": "9227 + 1269 = 10496"}
{"Question": "COOL + LOST = CATCH", "Answer": "1229 + 9285 = 10514"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MODE = RIVER", "Answer": "1339 + 9382 = 10721"}
{"Question": "ROOF + HOUR = COUCH", "Answer": "9335 + 4379 = 13714"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MODE = LABEL", "Answer": "7339 + 9382 = 16721"}
{"Question": "POOL + LOVE = PRESS", "Answer": "1449 + 9428 = 10877"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FOLK = REFER", "Answer": "1449 + 9452 = 10901"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TOUR = THREE", "Answer": "9443 + 1479 = 10922"}
{"Question": "GOOD + LONG = LEGAL", "Answer": "9442 + 1489 = 10931"}
{"Question": "BEER + REST = BIRTH", "Answer": "1449 + 9483 = 10932"}
{"Question": "FEED + DESK = STATE", "Answer": "7449 + 9415 = 16864"}
{"Question": "PEER + READ = APPLE", "Answer": "2669 + 9617 = 12286"}
{"Question": "PEER + REAL = APPLY", "Answer": "2669 + 9618 = 12287"}
{"Question": "TEEN + NEAR = STATE", "Answer": "3779 + 9758 = 13537"}
{"Question": "MEET + TREE = THIRD", "Answer": "9221 + 1422 = 10643"}
{"Question": "MEET + TREE = ENTRY", "Answer": "7113 + 3211 = 10324"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = STATE", "Answer": "9225 + 5722 = 14947"}
{"Question": "MEET + TREE = STORM", "Answer": "9445 + 5844 = 15289"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KNEE = LESS", "Answer": "1556 + 6955 = 8511"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = MASS", "Answer": "1667 + 7466 = 9133"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = THREE", "Answer": "4667 + 7366 = 12033"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = CLASS", "Answer": "9667 + 7266 = 16933"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ELITE", "Answer": "5338 + 8133 = 13471"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "1448 + 8744 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = AFTER", "Answer": "1448 + 8944 = 10392"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = BLADE", "Answer": "6448 + 8244 = 14692"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ONION", "Answer": "4558 + 8655 = 13213"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ASSET", "Answer": "1668 + 8366 = 10034"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = AWARE", "Answer": "1668 + 8466 = 10134"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KNEE = SHELF", "Answer": "1668 + 8966 = 10634"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ORDER", "Answer": "5668 + 8366 = 14034"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = AGREE", "Answer": "1778 + 8577 = 10355"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KNEE = SHELL", "Answer": "1778 + 8977 = 10755"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KNEE = DRESS", "Answer": "5778 + 8977 = 14755"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YELL = ABOVE", "Answer": "1339 + 9233 = 10572"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KNEE = SHOOT", "Answer": "1339 + 9433 = 10772"}
{"Question": "WEEK + KNEE = NEWLY", "Answer": "4339 + 9133 = 13472"}
{"Question": "MEET + TREE = MONTH", "Answer": "1449 + 9244 = 10693"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEM = TOUCH", "Answer": "8331 + 1938 = 10269"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEM = MONTH", "Answer": "1448 + 8941 = 10389"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEM = ELITE", "Answer": "8113 + 3918 = 12031"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEM = HATE", "Answer": "3774 + 4873 = 8647"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEM = BIRTH", "Answer": "6887 + 7386 = 14273"}
{"Question": "POOR + DROP = PEACE", "Answer": "1339 + 8931 = 10270"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = ADAPT", "Answer": "8664 + 1461 = 10125"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = AVOID", "Answer": "8667 + 1761 = 10428"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = TIME", "Answer": "2664 + 1462 = 4126"}
{"Question": "POOR + DROP = KNOCK", "Answer": "2669 + 7962 = 10631"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = AIDE", "Answer": "2775 + 3572 = 6347"}
{"Question": "POOR + CROP = KNOCK", "Answer": "2889 + 7982 = 10871"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = ESSAY", "Answer": "6119 + 3913 = 10032"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = START", "Answer": "8449 + 3943 = 12392"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = BITE", "Answer": "3774 + 2473 = 6247"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = STATE", "Answer": "4662 + 8264 = 12926"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = QUITE", "Answer": "4662 + 9264 = 13926"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = BOMB", "Answer": "4772 + 1274 = 6046"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = ROAD", "Answer": "1226 + 5625 = 6851"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = CRIME", "Answer": "5227 + 9725 = 14952"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = EASE", "Answer": "5772 + 1275 = 7047"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = FADE", "Answer": "3115 + 6516 = 9631"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = APPLE", "Answer": "6448 + 5846 = 12294"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = EARN", "Answer": "1887 + 6786 = 8673"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = BOARD", "Answer": "3887 + 6786 = 10673"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = CARE", "Answer": "1225 + 7527 = 8752"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = URBAN", "Answer": "8335 + 7537 = 15872"}
{"Question": "POOR + DROP = BOARD", "Answer": "7449 + 6947 = 14396"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = RAISE", "Answer": "9881 + 7187 = 17068"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = ELITE", "Answer": "8113 + 4318 = 12431"}
{"Question": "POOR + CROP = TOPIC", "Answer": "8226 + 4628 = 12854"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = STILL", "Answer": "8227 + 9728 = 17955"}
{"Question": "TOOL + PLOT = SWEEP", "Answer": "8334 + 2438 = 10772"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = GRADE", "Answer": "7335 + 8538 = 15873"}
{"Question": "BEER + AREA = STATE", "Answer": "9335 + 8538 = 17873"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = ISSUE", "Answer": "8446 + 1648 = 10094"}
{"Question": "POOR + CROP = CATCH", "Answer": "8556 + 1658 = 10214"}
{"Question": "POOR + CROP = CLOCK", "Answer": "8559 + 1958 = 10517"}
{"Question": "POOR + DROP = AHEAD", "Answer": "8556 + 4658 = 13214"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = SENSE", "Answer": "8557 + 6758 = 15315"}
{"Question": "POOR + CROP = TOOTH", "Answer": "8559 + 6958 = 15517"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = IDEAL", "Answer": "8669 + 1968 = 10637"}
{"Question": "POOR + DROP = RAPID", "Answer": "8661 + 9168 = 17829"}
{"Question": "PEER + AREA = PIECE", "Answer": "1779 + 8978 = 10757"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "8772 + 5278 = 14050"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = IRAQI", "Answer": "9332 + 1239 = 10571"}
{"Question": "TOOL + PLOT = PARTY", "Answer": "9443 + 1349 = 10792"}
{"Question": "MEET + ITEM = TOOTH", "Answer": "9551 + 8159 = 17710"}
{"Question": "TOOL + PLOT = APPLE", "Answer": "9775 + 3579 = 13354"}
{"Question": "DEER + AREA = DRAMA", "Answer": "1880 + 9089 = 10969"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "1225 + 9421 = 10646"}
{"Question": "NEED + THEN = NIGHT", "Answer": "1228 + 9421 = 10649"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = ACTOR", "Answer": "9226 + 1721 = 10947"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SIDE = SPEND", "Answer": "8331 + 1932 = 10263"}
{"Question": "POOL + CROP = PIECE", "Answer": "1442 + 8941 = 10383"}
{"Question": "POOL + SHOP = PRESS", "Answer": "1447 + 8941 = 10388"}
{"Question": "NEED + DIET = DANCE", "Answer": "9441 + 1543 = 10984"}
{"Question": "MOOD + FROM = METER", "Answer": "1556 + 8751 = 10307"}
{"Question": "MEET + POEM = MOTOR", "Answer": "1556 + 9051 = 10607"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLOW = FEWER", "Answer": "9551 + 1258 = 10809"}
{"Question": "WEEK + AREA = ALLOW", "Answer": "8667 + 1361 = 10028"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POEM = POUND", "Answer": "9661 + 1068 = 10729"}
{"Question": "DEEP + USED = EASE", "Answer": "1776 + 5471 = 7247"}
{"Question": "WOOD + SHOW = ODDS", "Answer": "1774 + 5671 = 7445"}
{"Question": "NEED + DIET = INTO", "Answer": "6771 + 1874 = 8645"}
{"Question": "FEEL + AREA = APPLY", "Answer": "8774 + 1271 = 10045"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "1776 + 8471 = 10247"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POEM = PRIOR", "Answer": "8771 + 1579 = 10350"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POEM = PRESS", "Answer": "8771 + 1973 = 10744"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DROP = DRESS", "Answer": "9771 + 1073 = 10844"}
{"Question": "SEED + AREA = EASE", "Answer": "6887 + 1281 = 8168"}
{"Question": "NEED + OPEN = PHONE", "Answer": "2664 + 8162 = 10826"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "1775 + 2472 = 4247"}
{"Question": "DEER + USED = PURE", "Answer": "2886 + 4582 = 7468"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SHOT = HOST", "Answer": "2880 + 6982 = 9862"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = TEST", "Answer": "2887 + 6982 = 9869"}
{"Question": "MEET + AREA = RATE", "Answer": "1774 + 3573 = 5347"}
{"Question": "FEEL + AREA = RELAX", "Answer": "8223 + 4124 = 12347"}
{"Question": "HEEL + AREA = THAT", "Answer": "1772 + 4374 = 6146"}
{"Question": "NEED + THEN = FIFTH", "Answer": "4779 + 5374 = 10153"}
{"Question": "NEED + DIET = THIN", "Answer": "2115 + 5317 = 7432"}
{"Question": "POOL + SHOP = LOSS", "Answer": "5118 + 3015 = 8133"}
{"Question": "SEEM + AREA = MASS", "Answer": "3118 + 5415 = 8533"}
{"Question": "WEEK + CREW = FENCE", "Answer": "5338 + 7935 = 13273"}
{"Question": "POOL + STOP = ELECT", "Answer": "5442 + 6745 = 12187"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = DRESS", "Answer": "5443 + 8045 = 13488"}
{"Question": "FEED + DIET = STAFF", "Answer": "8445 + 5243 = 13688"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AREA = SHARE", "Answer": "4883 + 5685 = 10568"}
{"Question": "DEER + USED = START", "Answer": "5887 + 6185 = 12072"}
{"Question": "MEET + AREA = STARE", "Answer": "7883 + 5685 = 13568"}
{"Question": "NEED + OPEN = ERROR", "Answer": "6114 + 3916 = 10030"}
{"Question": "POOR + STOP = TREAT", "Answer": "6335 + 9136 = 15471"}
{"Question": "MOON + FROM = SENSE", "Answer": "6554 + 3856 = 10410"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "6559 + 7156 = 13715"}
{"Question": "FEEL + AREA = LEARN", "Answer": "9551 + 6056 = 15607"}
{"Question": "FEED + DIET = MEDIA", "Answer": "9556 + 6052 = 15608"}
{"Question": "NEED + AREA = LEARN", "Answer": "9553 + 6056 = 15609"}
{"Question": "NEED + AREA = EARN", "Answer": "1885 + 6786 = 8671"}
{"Question": "NEED + THEN = EARTH", "Answer": "7118 + 3517 = 10635"}
{"Question": "SEED + DIET = ODDS", "Answer": "2337 + 7435 = 9772"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLOW = NERVE", "Answer": "2447 + 7843 = 10290"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = GRANT", "Answer": "6449 + 7347 = 13796"}
{"Question": "SEED + DIET = THESE", "Answer": "6887 + 7981 = 14868"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = ENTRY", "Answer": "4112 + 8318 = 12430"}
{"Question": "POOL + CROP = CYCLE", "Answer": "8225 + 1928 = 10153"}
{"Question": "KEEP + POET = STAKE", "Answer": "7338 + 8635 = 15973"}
{"Question": "NEED + THEN = TOOTH", "Answer": "8556 + 1458 = 10014"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = TOOTH", "Answer": "1559 + 8458 = 10017"}
{"Question": "POOL + SHOP = SENSE", "Answer": "8552 + 1758 = 10310"}
{"Question": "COOK + KNOW = CROSS", "Answer": "1668 + 8965 = 10633"}
{"Question": "POOL + DROP = SALAD", "Answer": "8667 + 5068 = 13735"}
{"Question": "NEED + THEN = TREAT", "Answer": "8773 + 1978 = 10751"}
{"Question": "COOK + KNOW = CROWD", "Answer": "1778 + 8975 = 10753"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AREA = IRAQI", "Answer": "2773 + 8078 = 10851"}
{"Question": "DEEP + AREA = BRAND", "Answer": "2774 + 8078 = 10852"}
{"Question": "FEED + DIET = BIBLE", "Answer": "4778 + 8379 = 13157"}
{"Question": "FEED + CHEF = WHICH", "Answer": "8776 + 5478 = 14254"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = SHIRT", "Answer": "9225 + 1429 = 10654"}
{"Question": "WOOD + SLOW = SHALL", "Answer": "9226 + 1529 = 10755"}
{"Question": "WOOD + BLOW = BADLY", "Answer": "9227 + 1529 = 10756"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = THANK", "Answer": "1225 + 9729 = 10954"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEN = MATCH", "Answer": "1229 + 9728 = 10957"}
{"Question": "PEER + STEP = HEART", "Answer": "9225 + 3429 = 12654"}
{"Question": "WOOD + KNOW = KNOCK", "Answer": "9332 + 1039 = 10371"}
{"Question": "TEEN + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "1442 + 9049 = 10491"}
{"Question": "MEET + THEN = MOUTH", "Answer": "1449 + 9243 = 10692"}
{"Question": "MEET + AREA = TRUTH", "Answer": "3551 + 9259 = 12810"}
{"Question": "HEEL + AREA = COACH", "Answer": "7558 + 9359 = 16917"}
{"Question": "POOL + DROP = DRAMA", "Answer": "9668 + 1069 = 10737"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLOW = LOWER", "Answer": "7669 + 9168 = 16837"}
{"Question": "POOL + CROP = REPLY", "Answer": "9775 + 3179 = 12954"}
{"Question": "AREA + MERE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1921 + 8292 = 10213"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = RICH", "Answer": "1851 + 6585 = 8436"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEED = SHARP", "Answer": "8551 + 1775 = 10326"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEED = SAUCE", "Answer": "8661 + 1776 = 10437"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = SALAD", "Answer": "2842 + 9484 = 12326"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = COACH", "Answer": "2652 + 7565 = 10217"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = FAVOR", "Answer": "2862 + 9686 = 12548"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEED = ABUSE", "Answer": "6553 + 3885 = 10438"}
{"Question": "TALL + FLAT = CLOCK", "Answer": "5744 + 8475 = 14219"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEED = AWARE", "Answer": "7226 + 6882 = 14108"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = TREAT", "Answer": "6056 + 4505 = 10561"}
{"Question": "TENT + KNEE = NEWLY", "Answer": "7317 + 6133 = 13450"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEED = ADOPT", "Answer": "8557 + 7335 = 15892"}
{"Question": "AREA + MERE = CREAM", "Answer": "7067 + 3606 = 10673"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = REACT", "Answer": "7167 + 9616 = 16783"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = CRASH", "Answer": "8268 + 4626 = 12894"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = BREAD", "Answer": "8078 + 2707 = 10785"}
{"Question": "AREA + HERE = BRUSH", "Answer": "9249 + 3424 = 12673"}
{"Question": "NEED + DOOR = ONCE", "Answer": "3771 + 1556 = 5327"}
{"Question": "HURT + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "7832 + 2381 = 10213"}
{"Question": "TEST + USER = SURE", "Answer": "2682 + 5864 = 8546"}
{"Question": "HALF + FLAT = ELITE", "Answer": "9523 + 3258 = 12781"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEEK = DATA", "Answer": "3884 + 4772 = 8656"}
{"Question": "DIRT + TRIP = IRAQI", "Answer": "7125 + 5216 = 12341"}
{"Question": "CARD + DRAG = PAPER", "Answer": "6285 + 5823 = 12108"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POOL = AHEAD", "Answer": "8225 + 5993 = 14218"}
{"Question": "FROM + MORE = TREAT", "Answer": "9425 + 5246 = 14671"}
{"Question": "HALF + FLAT = CATCH", "Answer": "7385 + 5832 = 13217"}
{"Question": "BOOK + KEEP = COACH", "Answer": "7335 + 5884 = 13219"}
{"Question": "BOOK + KEEP = AWARE", "Answer": "8335 + 5772 = 14107"}
{"Question": "CARD + DRAG = EAGER", "Answer": "8475 + 5742 = 14217"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LOOK = COACH", "Answer": "8775 + 5443 = 14218"}
{"Question": "SOON + NEED = ODDS", "Answer": "1775 + 5886 = 7661"}
{"Question": "FLAT + TALE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9136 + 6315 = 15451"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POOR = ROUND", "Answer": "7886 + 6441 = 14327"}
{"Question": "DRAW + WARN = ROUND", "Answer": "3147 + 7416 = 10563"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEEK = DEATH", "Answer": "5117 + 7229 = 12346"}
{"Question": "AREA + TERM = ROUTE", "Answer": "7137 + 5316 = 12453"}
{"Question": "CROP + PORT = ROUTE", "Answer": "6137 + 7315 = 13452"}
{"Question": "KICK + ACID = IDEAL", "Answer": "7147 + 6413 = 13560"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEEN = ENTRY", "Answer": "8667 + 7115 = 15782"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEEK = DANCE", "Answer": "9117 + 7225 = 16342"}
{"Question": "SLIP + PILE = CLASS", "Answer": "6327 + 7239 = 13566"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FEEL = APPLE", "Answer": "8227 + 7336 = 15563"}
{"Question": "DEER + ROOF = WORLD", "Answer": "6447 + 7339 = 13786"}
{"Question": "KICK + ACID = SCENE", "Answer": "8328 + 4237 = 12565"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEEN = FORTH", "Answer": "7558 + 8226 = 15784"}
{"Question": "AREA + TERM = TREAT", "Answer": "9089 + 1802 = 10891"}
{"Question": "MEET + THAT = THEME", "Answer": "9221 + 1071 = 10292"}
{"Question": "EDGE + AIDE = ESSAY", "Answer": "1351 + 8731 = 10082"}
{"Question": "EDGE + RIDE = DEER", "Answer": "1471 + 2641 = 4112"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TEST = TASTE", "Answer": "9441 + 1271 = 10712"}
{"Question": "THAT + LAST = TITLE", "Answer": "1651 + 8531 = 10182"}
{"Question": "EDGE + FADE = EAGER", "Answer": "1561 + 9051 = 10612"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = TIRED", "Answer": "9551 + 1381 = 10932"}
{"Question": "MEET + THAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8771 + 1241 = 10012"}
{"Question": "MEET + THAT = TROOP", "Answer": "8771 + 1561 = 10332"}
{"Question": "GANG + DRAG = GUESS", "Answer": "1751 + 8671 = 10422"}
{"Question": "ELSE + RULE = USER", "Answer": "1831 + 2481 = 4312"}
{"Question": "ROOT + THAT = THREE", "Answer": "9881 + 1041 = 10922"}
{"Question": "DEAD + USED = STATE", "Answer": "2462 + 8142 = 10604"}
{"Question": "TENT + UNIT = ISSUE", "Answer": "2462 + 7612 = 10074"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = FORCE", "Answer": "9223 + 3683 = 12906"}
{"Question": "EDGE + RIDE = TIRED", "Answer": "3673 + 9263 = 12936"}
{"Question": "TENT + POET = ONTO", "Answer": "3853 + 2683 = 6536"}
{"Question": "EDGE + SIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "4174 + 8314 = 12488"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TENT = NOISE", "Answer": "7224 + 4814 = 12038"}
{"Question": "ROOT + THAT = HONOR", "Answer": "8224 + 4104 = 12328"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "4124 + 8234 = 12358"}
{"Question": "THAT + LAST = HOTEL", "Answer": "4134 + 8364 = 12498"}
{"Question": "ELSE + RULE = SUPER", "Answer": "4314 + 8234 = 12548"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = HONOR", "Answer": "8334 + 4704 = 13038"}
{"Question": "THAT + SALT = CLASS", "Answer": "4064 + 8624 = 12688"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TENT = ONTO", "Answer": "3884 + 4764 = 8648"}
{"Question": "EDGE + RIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "4874 + 5284 = 10158"}
{"Question": "DEAD + USED = ABUSE", "Answer": "4814 + 7984 = 12798"}
{"Question": "EDGE + CODE = TOOTH", "Answer": "4924 + 5094 = 10018"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KICK = ERROR", "Answer": "4115 + 5965 = 10080"}
{"Question": "TENT + POET = ERROR", "Answer": "5175 + 4915 = 10090"}
{"Question": "TENT + UNIT = ENTER", "Answer": "5135 + 8375 = 13510"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CARD = ORDER", "Answer": "5875 + 4705 = 10580"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DEAD = ERROR", "Answer": "4885 + 5195 = 10080"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TENT = ORDER", "Answer": "5116 + 6976 = 12092"}
{"Question": "TENT + DIET = NERVE", "Answer": "6216 + 5826 = 12042"}
{"Question": "BOOT + THAT = EARTH", "Answer": "4556 + 6206 = 10762"}
{"Question": "THAT + SALT = WHEEL", "Answer": "6356 + 7526 = 13882"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ABLE = START", "Answer": "6716 + 5876 = 12592"}
{"Question": "TENT + POET = ONION", "Answer": "6826 + 5186 = 12012"}
{"Question": "ELSE + HOLE = ORDER", "Answer": "6876 + 5186 = 12062"}
{"Question": "THAT + FACT = ACTOR", "Answer": "7617 + 3107 = 10724"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ROLE = SORRY", "Answer": "7317 + 5237 = 12554"}
{"Question": "TENT + UNIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7567 + 2607 = 10174"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "5667 + 7407 = 13074"}
{"Question": "MEET + THAT = DEATH", "Answer": "8667 + 7407 = 16074"}
{"Question": "EDGE + CODE = ONION", "Answer": "7827 + 6187 = 14014"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TENT = NERVE", "Answer": "6887 + 7417 = 14304"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MALE = ALTER", "Answer": "8258 + 4128 = 12386"}
{"Question": "DEAD + YARD = ESSAY", "Answer": "8128 + 6298 = 14426"}
{"Question": "EDGE + AIDE = ASSET", "Answer": "8348 + 1738 = 10086"}
{"Question": "GANG + DRAG = RANGE", "Answer": "8348 + 5138 = 13486"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TALE = ASSET", "Answer": "8348 + 6138 = 14486"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "8648 + 1428 = 10076"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = MOTOR", "Answer": "6448 + 8398 = 14846"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CARD = FENCE", "Answer": "8648 + 7428 = 16076"}
{"Question": "FOOT + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1558 + 8628 = 10186"}
{"Question": "THAT + WAIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8658 + 3528 = 12186"}
{"Question": "THAT + LAST = WHEEL", "Answer": "8458 + 6538 = 14996"}
{"Question": "THAT + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "8758 + 6528 = 15286"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TALE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8678 + 1468 = 10146"}
{"Question": "SEEK + KICK = SCALE", "Answer": "1668 + 8908 = 10576"}
{"Question": "EDGE + AIDE = AVOID", "Answer": "8628 + 1968 = 10596"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MALE = RURAL", "Answer": "8678 + 3468 = 12146"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FILE = USUAL", "Answer": "8628 + 3568 = 12196"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TALE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8738 + 1278 = 10016"}
{"Question": "TENT + UNIT = UPPER", "Answer": "8278 + 1748 = 10026"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8708 + 1378 = 10086"}
{"Question": "FOOT + THAT = FAITH", "Answer": "1778 + 8608 = 10386"}
{"Question": "THAT + CAST = COUCH", "Answer": "8678 + 1738 = 10416"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DEAD = FLAME", "Answer": "1778 + 8648 = 10426"}
{"Question": "TENT + DIET = FIFTH", "Answer": "8708 + 5478 = 14186"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = METER", "Answer": "8229 + 9749 = 17978"}
{"Question": "THAT + EAST = SEVEN", "Answer": "9739 + 5319 = 15058"}
{"Question": "THAT + EAST = SEIZE", "Answer": "9739 + 8319 = 18058"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HAND = HONEY", "Answer": "9249 + 1479 = 10728"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TENT = INNER", "Answer": "8449 + 9279 = 17728"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TENT = ENTER", "Answer": "4779 + 9139 = 13918"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PALE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9719 + 8279 = 17998"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FLEE = DRAFT", "Answer": "1271 + 9522 = 10793"}
{"Question": "ELSE + KILL = SEEK", "Answer": "1471 + 5644 = 7115"}
{"Question": "AREA + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "1541 + 9404 = 10945"}
{"Question": "MEET + TAKE = THEIR", "Answer": "8551 + 1975 = 10526"}
{"Question": "TELL + PLOT = TASTE", "Answer": "1766 + 8651 = 10417"}
{"Question": "DATA + GLAD = DRAFT", "Answer": "1676 + 8961 = 10637"}
{"Question": "TREE + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1277 + 8741 = 10018"}
{"Question": "DEER + ROPE = RAPID", "Answer": "8771 + 1527 = 10298"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ROLL = EAGER", "Answer": "1741 + 8577 = 10318"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PACE = ODDS", "Answer": "1332 + 2783 = 4115"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PACE = UPPER", "Answer": "9442 + 2804 = 12246"}
{"Question": "MEET + TRUE = BUYER", "Answer": "7662 + 2806 = 10468"}
{"Question": "MEET + TRUE = OTHER", "Answer": "9662 + 2806 = 12468"}
{"Question": "DEER + RISE = ODDS", "Answer": "1443 + 3674 = 5117"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MINE = BASIS", "Answer": "7443 + 3284 = 10727"}
{"Question": "TREE + BEAT = LATER", "Answer": "3855 + 6503 = 10358"}
{"Question": "AREA + GENE = CLEAN", "Answer": "3953 + 6585 = 10538"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOAD = ERROR", "Answer": "3747 + 6273 = 10020"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PILE = BASIS", "Answer": "6554 + 4385 = 10939"}
{"Question": "MEET + TONE = ONION", "Answer": "7884 + 4128 = 12012"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SAND = ASIAN", "Answer": "9884 + 4128 = 14012"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BALL = ASSET", "Answer": "5235 + 8122 = 13357"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEAD = TITLE", "Answer": "5313 + 4835 = 10148"}
{"Question": "PEER + RICE = TOPIC", "Answer": "8775 + 5027 = 13802"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ROLL = LOVER", "Answer": "6156 + 7311 = 13467"}
{"Question": "SELL + PLUS = CLOSE", "Answer": "6822 + 5246 = 12068"}
{"Question": "DEER + RICE = AWARD", "Answer": "8226 + 6942 = 15168"}
{"Question": "DATA + GLAD = CATCH", "Answer": "6383 + 7436 = 13819"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ROLL = OCCUR", "Answer": "6376 + 9133 = 15509"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POLE = COLOR", "Answer": "7446 + 6384 = 13830"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEND = NOSE", "Answer": "1776 + 6387 = 8163"}
{"Question": "MERE + THEM = BIRTH", "Answer": "6707 + 8376 = 15083"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MINE = DRAMA", "Answer": "3886 + 6578 = 10464"}
{"Question": "PULL + SLIP = ONION", "Answer": "6388 + 7826 = 14214"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LIKE = YIELD", "Answer": "3227 + 7052 = 10279"}
{"Question": "DATA + GLAD = STEEL", "Answer": "7626 + 5367 = 12993"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LIKE = FIFTH", "Answer": "5887 + 7308 = 13195"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LATE = CATCH", "Answer": "5887 + 7328 = 13215"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FREE = REFER", "Answer": "8398 + 5133 = 13531"}
{"Question": "KEEP + PURE = DRAMA", "Answer": "6448 + 8754 = 15202"}
{"Question": "YELL + PLAY = PAPER", "Answer": "8655 + 1508 = 10163"}
{"Question": "BEER + RICE = BASIC", "Answer": "1558 + 8935 = 10493"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEAD = LOOSE", "Answer": "8626 + 1468 = 10094"}
{"Question": "WELL + BLOW = BIBLE", "Answer": "8466 + 1698 = 10164"}
{"Question": "KNEE + DECK = NAKED", "Answer": "8166 + 4698 = 12864"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PALE = BLOOD", "Answer": "4668 + 8326 = 12994"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEND = OFFER", "Answer": "1778 + 8247 = 10025"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LINE = HONOR", "Answer": "1778 + 8427 = 10205"}
{"Question": "MEET + TRUE = MAKER", "Answer": "1778 + 8597 = 10375"}
{"Question": "BEER + RIDE = BADLY", "Answer": "1778 + 8647 = 10425"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MODE = SPEND", "Answer": "1778 + 8957 = 10735"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LIFE = FIFTH", "Answer": "5778 + 8417 = 14195"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEAD = LEVEL", "Answer": "9272 + 1029 = 10301"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TALL = TREAT", "Answer": "9249 + 1722 = 10971"}
{"Question": "SELL + PLUS = PAUSE", "Answer": "9233 + 1359 = 10592"}
{"Question": "TELL + FLAT = PLATE", "Answer": "9233 + 4359 = 13592"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LIFE = FIGHT", "Answer": "5339 + 9413 = 14752"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MALE = SALAD", "Answer": "1449 + 9054 = 10503"}
{"Question": "BEER + RISE = BASIC", "Answer": "1449 + 9274 = 10723"}
{"Question": "MEET + TYPE = MARRY", "Answer": "1449 + 9324 = 10773"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOAD = HELLO", "Answer": "9424 + 7349 = 16773"}
{"Question": "SEEM + MODE = SALAD", "Answer": "1559 + 9245 = 10804"}
{"Question": "MEET + TIRE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1559 + 9345 = 10904"}
{"Question": "AREA + GENE = GUARD", "Answer": "9359 + 1575 = 10934"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEND = HELLO", "Answer": "4559 + 9325 = 13884"}
{"Question": "ELSE + KILL = CHEEK", "Answer": "9629 + 5366 = 14995"}
{"Question": "TENT + FLEE = LATIN", "Answer": "9769 + 3177 = 12946"}
{"Question": "BEER + RACE = CARRY", "Answer": "3779 + 9217 = 12996"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BALL = AHEAD", "Answer": "9739 + 5177 = 14916"}
{"Question": "ELSE + POLL = SWEEP", "Answer": "9719 + 6277 = 15996"}
{"Question": "AREA + GENE = GRAIN", "Answer": "9089 + 1878 = 10967"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "5889 + 9708 = 15597"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LEFT = TITLE", "Answer": "1228 + 8961 = 10189"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LEFT = DATA", "Answer": "1552 + 2761 = 4313"}
{"Question": "WEEK + KNOW = WRONG", "Answer": "1558 + 8721 = 10279"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAR = DATA", "Answer": "3771 + 1643 = 5414"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LIST = TASTE", "Answer": "1778 + 8641 = 10419"}
{"Question": "SOON + NEWS = SENSE", "Answer": "1889 + 9021 = 10910"}
{"Question": "AREA + TENT = RARE", "Answer": "5875 + 2712 = 8587"}
{"Question": "DOOR + READ = AGREE", "Answer": "2887 + 7912 = 10799"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "3226 + 6913 = 10139"}
{"Question": "THEM + MEAT = HATE", "Answer": "3874 + 4763 = 8637"}
{"Question": "DOOR + READ = GRADE", "Answer": "9883 + 3209 = 13092"}
{"Question": "THAT + EASE = SALES", "Answer": "7827 + 4214 = 12041"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LEFT = AFTER", "Answer": "4558 + 8934 = 13492"}
{"Question": "DOOR + READ = GUIDE", "Answer": "4778 + 8264 = 13042"}
{"Question": "DOOR + READ = HEART", "Answer": "4778 + 8304 = 13082"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "8774 + 4638 = 13412"}
{"Question": "THUS + SUIT = ELITE", "Answer": "4687 + 7854 = 12541"}
{"Question": "THAT + EASE = LABEL", "Answer": "5825 + 6236 = 12061"}
{"Question": "TAIL + LIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "5837 + 7315 = 13152"}
{"Question": "THAT + EASE = PAPER", "Answer": "8748 + 5405 = 14153"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LIFT = FIELD", "Answer": "5668 + 8415 = 14083"}
{"Question": "GOOD + DRUG = RANGE", "Answer": "5887 + 7165 = 13052"}
{"Question": "THAT + EASE = PHOTO", "Answer": "5385 + 7867 = 13252"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAR = FAITH", "Answer": "6227 + 7846 = 14073"}
{"Question": "GOOD + DRAG = TOUGH", "Answer": "6558 + 8706 = 15264"}
{"Question": "DEER + ROAD = GRADE", "Answer": "9556 + 6839 = 16395"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAR = STATE", "Answer": "9558 + 8729 = 18287"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TAKE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8721 + 1297 = 10018"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STIR = RAISE", "Answer": "1225 + 9571 = 10796"}
{"Question": "POOR + WRAP = PEACE", "Answer": "1339 + 8921 = 10260"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = AWARD", "Answer": "8447 + 1731 = 10178"}
{"Question": "POOL + SLIP = PEACE", "Answer": "1449 + 8921 = 10370"}
{"Question": "BEER + GRAB = EARN", "Answer": "1557 + 3721 = 5278"}
{"Question": "POOR + AREA = ADAPT", "Answer": "8556 + 1631 = 10187"}
{"Question": "POOR + AREA = DEAD", "Answer": "7668 + 1851 = 9519"}
{"Question": "BEER + GRAB = BIBLE", "Answer": "1665 + 8531 = 10196"}
{"Question": "PEER + TRIP = PAINT", "Answer": "1667 + 8731 = 10398"}
{"Question": "WOOD + DATA = AWAY", "Answer": "3771 + 1585 = 5356"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FLAT = TITLE", "Answer": "1773 + 8361 = 10134"}
{"Question": "FEAR + RACE = REFER", "Answer": "9081 + 1820 = 10901"}
{"Question": "PEER + WRAP = APART", "Answer": "2556 + 9612 = 12168"}
{"Question": "PEER + WRAP = APPLE", "Answer": "2775 + 9512 = 12287"}
{"Question": "THUS + SUCH = ISSUE", "Answer": "9482 + 2804 = 12286"}
{"Question": "SEED + DATA = EAST", "Answer": "6992 + 2575 = 9567"}
{"Question": "DEAD + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "3143 + 9451 = 12594"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "1775 + 3583 = 5358"}
{"Question": "TENT + ONCE = MOON", "Answer": "3473 + 2754 = 6227"}
{"Question": "PEER + TRIP = BIBLE", "Answer": "3774 + 8423 = 12197"}
{"Question": "YEAR + RACE = SORRY", "Answer": "8573 + 3765 = 12338"}
{"Question": "POOL + SLIP = ODDS", "Answer": "3881 + 4123 = 8004"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CARE = ORDER", "Answer": "4954 + 8539 = 13493"}
{"Question": "NEED + DATA = STONE", "Answer": "9664 + 4232 = 13896"}
{"Question": "SEED + DATA = AIDS", "Answer": "2115 + 5737 = 7852"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "5915 + 4179 = 10094"}
{"Question": "FEED + DATA = SENSE", "Answer": "6225 + 5787 = 12012"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DATA = TODAY", "Answer": "7225 + 5313 = 12538"}
{"Question": "NEED + DATA = LATIN", "Answer": "9225 + 5464 = 14689"}
{"Question": "DEAD + RACE = FEWER", "Answer": "5235 + 7392 = 12627"}
{"Question": "ITEM + MEAT = TIME", "Answer": "3945 + 5409 = 9354"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = BREAD", "Answer": "7662 + 5295 = 12957"}
{"Question": "TEAR + RACE = EXTRA", "Answer": "8165 + 5691 = 13856"}
{"Question": "BEER + GRAB = TASTE", "Answer": "5772 + 8245 = 14017"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "5771 + 9145 = 14916"}
{"Question": "THAT + CASH = HELLO", "Answer": "5185 + 7821 = 13006"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BAKE = IDEA", "Answer": "6516 + 2135 = 8651"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ELSE = ASSET", "Answer": "5339 + 6926 = 12265"}
{"Question": "DEAD + RACE = EAGER", "Answer": "6136 + 7381 = 13517"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MERE = REFER", "Answer": "9336 + 6515 = 15851"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TAPE = PATCH", "Answer": "8246 + 6412 = 14658"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "6246 + 8472 = 14718"}
{"Question": "DEAR + RATE = TIRED", "Answer": "5976 + 6719 = 12695"}
{"Question": "CREW + WEAR = REACH", "Answer": "5127 + 7231 = 12358"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "7527 + 8215 = 15742"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CARE = EAGER", "Answer": "7137 + 6381 = 13518"}
{"Question": "YEAR + RATE = ENTRY", "Answer": "8137 + 7341 = 15478"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FATE = METER", "Answer": "7347 + 6483 = 13830"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STAR = YOURS", "Answer": "7449 + 6927 = 14376"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TAKE = EARTH", "Answer": "8157 + 7521 = 15678"}
{"Question": "HEAR + RACE = EARTH", "Answer": "8157 + 7591 = 15748"}
{"Question": "HEAD + DARE = TRUTH", "Answer": "9257 + 7562 = 16819"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = BOARD", "Answer": "4226 + 8638 = 12864"}
{"Question": "YEAR + RACE = MARRY", "Answer": "4628 + 8256 = 12884"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MERE = BIRTH", "Answer": "1338 + 8929 = 10267"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CAKE = CRACK", "Answer": "8938 + 1379 = 10317"}
{"Question": "ITEM + MEAT = ISSUE", "Answer": "1648 + 8426 = 10074"}
{"Question": "PEER + CROP = CYCLE", "Answer": "8446 + 1678 = 10124"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SAFE = OFFER", "Answer": "8248 + 9472 = 17720"}
{"Question": "SEED + DATA = STONE", "Answer": "1558 + 8707 = 10265"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MERE = BRIEF", "Answer": "1668 + 8707 = 10375"}
{"Question": "FEED + DATA = FIGHT", "Answer": "1668 + 8757 = 10425"}
{"Question": "COOL + ELSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "4662 + 8218 = 12880"}
{"Question": "FLAT + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1478 + 8704 = 10182"}
{"Question": "POOR + TRIP = THERE", "Answer": "8774 + 1468 = 10242"}
{"Question": "POOR + AREA = PIECE", "Answer": "1776 + 8648 = 10424"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = TREAT", "Answer": "4773 + 8308 = 13081"}
{"Question": "PEER + TRIP = IRISH", "Answer": "8774 + 5418 = 14192"}
{"Question": "STOP + POET = THESE", "Answer": "6178 + 8791 = 14969"}
{"Question": "MERE + FROM = REFER", "Answer": "9212 + 3109 = 12321"}
{"Question": "MOOD + DATA = METER", "Answer": "1229 + 9474 = 10703"}
{"Question": "POOR + WRAP = COACH", "Answer": "9225 + 3589 = 12814"}
{"Question": "ITEM + MEAT = RAISE", "Answer": "5329 + 9243 = 14572"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "5229 + 9464 = 14693"}
{"Question": "COOL + ELSE = ASSET", "Answer": "7224 + 9469 = 16693"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TAKE = CATCH", "Answer": "4539 + 9375 = 13914"}
{"Question": "MOOD + DATA = METAL", "Answer": "1449 + 9383 = 10832"}
{"Question": "POOL + SLIP = ISSUE", "Answer": "9448 + 2819 = 12267"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9249 + 3472 = 12721"}
{"Question": "DEAD + PAGE = EAGER", "Answer": "9149 + 5461 = 14610"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MALE = SALES", "Answer": "9249 + 5472 = 14721"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STIR = ELITE", "Answer": "9442 + 6279 = 15721"}
{"Question": "THAT + EACH = ELITE", "Answer": "9259 + 1532 = 10791"}
{"Question": "ITEM + MEAT = IRAQI", "Answer": "1259 + 9582 = 10841"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "4552 + 9239 = 13791"}
{"Question": "LEAF + FACE = REFER", "Answer": "3269 + 9652 = 12921"}
{"Question": "THEY + YEAH = STATE", "Answer": "4879 + 9768 = 14647"}
{"Question": "AREA + TELL = APART", "Answer": "1921 + 8277 = 10198"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MESS = METER", "Answer": "9221 + 1088 = 10309"}
{"Question": "MESS + ITEM = MUSIC", "Answer": "1277 + 9521 = 10798"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TELL = TIRED", "Answer": "9221 + 1755 = 10976"}
{"Question": "TALL + HEAT = TRUTH", "Answer": "1388 + 9231 = 10619"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TEST = TIRED", "Answer": "9332 + 1521 = 10853"}
{"Question": "TALL + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1477 + 8541 = 10018"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PULL = PROUD", "Answer": "9441 + 1288 = 10729"}
{"Question": "KNEE + RANK = NEAR", "Answer": "1522 + 3751 = 5273"}
{"Question": "AREA + WIRE = ALLOW", "Answer": "1571 + 8457 = 10028"}
{"Question": "MEET + TOSS = TITLE", "Answer": "8551 + 1644 = 10195"}
{"Question": "TEEN + PANT = TROOP", "Answer": "1557 + 8671 = 10228"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MISS = MUSIC", "Answer": "8551 + 1722 = 10273"}
{"Question": "TREE + DIRT = THEIR", "Answer": "1544 + 8951 = 10495"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TALL = TRUTH", "Answer": "9551 + 1266 = 10817"}
{"Question": "WALL + DRAW = WHERE", "Answer": "1577 + 9251 = 10828"}
{"Question": "FEEL + HALF = FIFTH", "Answer": "1667 + 8471 = 10138"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PASS = POUND", "Answer": "8661 + 1577 = 10238"}
{"Question": "TENT + OPEN = TASTE", "Answer": "1651 + 8765 = 10416"}
{"Question": "MEET + TALL = TASTE", "Answer": "9661 + 1055 = 10716"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TREE = TREND", "Answer": "9661 + 1077 = 10738"}
{"Question": "SEEM + BOMB = BASIS", "Answer": "9668 + 1281 = 10949"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = TONE", "Answer": "4776 + 1361 = 6137"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MESS = MARRY", "Answer": "8771 + 1455 = 10226"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TALL = THOSE", "Answer": "8771 + 1955 = 10726"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PASS = PIECE", "Answer": "8771 + 1966 = 10737"}
{"Question": "BEER + ROLL = ROUTE", "Answer": "9771 + 1066 = 10837"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SALT = ODDS", "Answer": "1885 + 6451 = 8336"}
{"Question": "MALL + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "1822 + 9081 = 10903"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SALT = TASTE", "Answer": "1883 + 9031 = 10914"}
{"Question": "MEET + TOSS = TOOTH", "Answer": "8991 + 1022 = 10013"}
{"Question": "TELL + POET = TROOP", "Answer": "1977 + 8691 = 10668"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LOSS = REFER", "Answer": "8002 + 2799 = 10801"}
{"Question": "AREA + BELL = START", "Answer": "2562 + 7688 = 10250"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TALL = AUTO", "Answer": "3772 + 2655 = 6427"}
{"Question": "USER + ROSE = YOURS", "Answer": "8752 + 2075 = 10827"}
{"Question": "WELL + VIEW = RIVER", "Answer": "2799 + 8072 = 10871"}
{"Question": "DEER + CARD = ASIDE", "Answer": "2775 + 8152 = 10927"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LOSS = SHOE", "Answer": "3882 + 2466 = 6348"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = NOISE", "Answer": "9886 + 2162 = 12048"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POLL = ERROR", "Answer": "6113 + 3977 = 10090"}
{"Question": "KNEE + LINK = IDEAL", "Answer": "3466 + 9143 = 12609"}
{"Question": "BEER + ROLL = START", "Answer": "6553 + 3877 = 10430"}
{"Question": "TENT + OPEN = PHOTO", "Answer": "3763 + 9176 = 12939"}
{"Question": "TENT + OPEN = NOTE", "Answer": "3853 + 1285 = 5138"}
{"Question": "BEER + ROLL = AWARE", "Answer": "6883 + 3255 = 10138"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TALL = PHOTO", "Answer": "6883 + 3955 = 10838"}
{"Question": "MEET + TALL = WASTE", "Answer": "7883 + 3055 = 10938"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GANG = EARTH", "Answer": "8116 + 4264 = 12380"}
{"Question": "AREA + BELL = COLOR", "Answer": "4054 + 8566 = 12620"}
{"Question": "FOOT + TELL = REFER", "Answer": "9554 + 4377 = 13931"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EASE = BREAD", "Answer": "5662 + 4824 = 10486"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = STONE", "Answer": "7662 + 4824 = 12486"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ALSO = TOOTH", "Answer": "4883 + 9534 = 14417"}
{"Question": "AREA + HIRE = REACH", "Answer": "5125 + 7412 = 12537"}
{"Question": "DEAD + WALL = ALLOW", "Answer": "5215 + 8133 = 13348"}
{"Question": "SEED + AIDS = DATA", "Answer": "5228 + 3085 = 8313"}
{"Question": "LOTS + SHOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "6215 + 5921 = 12136"}
{"Question": "LIST + THIS = FIFTY", "Answer": "6235 + 5923 = 12158"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "8224 + 5945 = 14169"}
{"Question": "MATH + HEAT = THEM", "Answer": "2375 + 5137 = 7512"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLEE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8445 + 5722 = 14167"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = UNION", "Answer": "7668 + 5385 = 13053"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MESS = AWARE", "Answer": "6775 + 5388 = 12163"}
{"Question": "WEEK + KISS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8775 + 5422 = 14197"}
{"Question": "KEEP + PULL = CLOCK", "Answer": "9775 + 5044 = 14819"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FROM = REFER", "Answer": "5765 + 9176 = 14941"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLEE = ELECT", "Answer": "7885 + 5311 = 13196"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ELSE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9886 + 5165 = 15051"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = ERROR", "Answer": "3114 + 6946 = 10060"}
{"Question": "FLEE + GOLF = LEGAL", "Answer": "6155 + 9816 = 15971"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TALL = ELITE", "Answer": "6136 + 9355 = 15491"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TELL = SALES", "Answer": "7446 + 6055 = 13501"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BALL = SALES", "Answer": "6046 + 8455 = 14501"}
{"Question": "TALL + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "6422 + 8146 = 14568"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FALL = SOLAR", "Answer": "8556 + 6722 = 15278"}
{"Question": "BOMB + WHOM = HELLO", "Answer": "6826 + 7182 = 14008"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KISS = SOLID", "Answer": "5227 + 7311 = 12538"}
{"Question": "SING + GAIN = BASIS", "Answer": "6297 + 7329 = 13626"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TALL = LATER", "Answer": "8227 + 7511 = 15738"}
{"Question": "LOOK + KNEE = HELLO", "Answer": "8227 + 7655 = 15882"}
{"Question": "DOOR + CARD = FORCE", "Answer": "7442 + 6827 = 14269"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LOSS = PRIOR", "Answer": "2557 + 7933 = 10490"}
{"Question": "AREA + BELL = CREAM", "Answer": "7057 + 3522 = 10579"}
{"Question": "AREA + TELL = LEAST", "Answer": "7257 + 8511 = 15768"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TALL = FORTH", "Answer": "8557 + 7322 = 15879"}
{"Question": "COOL + LESS = FENCE", "Answer": "5887 + 7366 = 13253"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ALSO = AWARD", "Answer": "8224 + 1948 = 10172"}
{"Question": "FOOT + TALL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1228 + 8955 = 10183"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HALL = EARTH", "Answer": "8128 + 4266 = 12394"}
{"Question": "GANG + KNEE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8628 + 5233 = 13861"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ELSE = BLOOD", "Answer": "7224 + 8548 = 15772"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EASE = OFFER", "Answer": "1334 + 8748 = 10082"}
{"Question": "AREA + MESS = CREAM", "Answer": "8038 + 2344 = 10382"}
{"Question": "MEET + ONTO = LEMON", "Answer": "5334 + 8248 = 13582"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EASE = ASSET", "Answer": "6334 + 8148 = 14482"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ALSO = AHEAD", "Answer": "8446 + 1768 = 10214"}
{"Question": "BEER + ROLL = SENSE", "Answer": "5448 + 8766 = 14214"}
{"Question": "AREA + CORE = TREAT", "Answer": "8438 + 5943 = 14381"}
{"Question": "ONTO + PANT = PRIOR", "Answer": "8528 + 1952 = 10480"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MESS = RIVER", "Answer": "1558 + 8933 = 10491"}
{"Question": "POOL + LESS = PHOTO", "Answer": "1558 + 8977 = 10535"}
{"Question": "AREA + BELL = CLEAR", "Answer": "8058 + 4522 = 12580"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TELL = METER", "Answer": "4558 + 8266 = 12824"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TALL = MOTOR", "Answer": "7558 + 8299 = 15857"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SELL = OCCUR", "Answer": "1668 + 8377 = 10045"}
{"Question": "MESS + POEM = PRIOR", "Answer": "8622 + 1968 = 10590"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "2668 + 8144 = 10812"}
{"Question": "MOON + GANG = SENSE", "Answer": "3664 + 8748 = 12412"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LESS = THREE", "Answer": "1778 + 8466 = 10244"}
{"Question": "AREA + SURE = SHELL", "Answer": "8748 + 1674 = 10422"}
{"Question": "DEER + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "9118 + 7689 = 16807"}
{"Question": "ONTO + PANT = ENTER", "Answer": "9289 + 3528 = 12817"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PULL = GUIDE", "Answer": "6229 + 9533 = 15762"}
{"Question": "BOOK + KILL = BASIC", "Answer": "1339 + 9288 = 10627"}
{"Question": "GANG + THAN = TIGHT", "Answer": "9329 + 1632 = 10961"}
{"Question": "BEER + ROLL = BASIS", "Answer": "1449 + 9288 = 10737"}
{"Question": "AREA + TELL = TREAT", "Answer": "9069 + 1622 = 10691"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TELL = ELITE", "Answer": "3669 + 9122 = 12791"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TALL = VOTER", "Answer": "7669 + 9288 = 16957"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MESS = REFER", "Answer": "1779 + 9022 = 10801"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ELSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "3771 + 9219 = 12990"}
{"Question": "MOON + TENT = ENTER", "Answer": "4773 + 9139 = 13912"}
{"Question": "SELF + FUEL = ISSUE", "Answer": "4789 + 9678 = 14467"}
{"Question": "DOOR + CARD = LOCAL", "Answer": "9772 + 8029 = 17801"}
{"Question": "SHOT + TOUR = TRUST", "Answer": "9521 + 1270 = 10791"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TAIL = TRIBE", "Answer": "9221 + 1573 = 10794"}
{"Question": "FOOD + SELF = FALSE", "Answer": "1224 + 9571 = 10795"}
{"Question": "MOOD + DEAL = DRAMA", "Answer": "9221 + 1576 = 10797"}
{"Question": "POOL + STEP = PRESS", "Answer": "1228 + 9571 = 10799"}
{"Question": "LOOK + AREA = APPLE", "Answer": "8334 + 1751 = 10085"}
{"Question": "MEET + FORM = MOTOR", "Answer": "1445 + 9061 = 10506"}
{"Question": "ROOF + EDGE = EAGER", "Answer": "9448 + 1271 = 10719"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9441 + 1287 = 10728"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TEND = TASTE", "Answer": "9441 + 1372 = 10813"}
{"Question": "ODDS + STAR = SMART", "Answer": "9441 + 1382 = 10823"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LAST = TITLE", "Answer": "1554 + 8631 = 10185"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MENU = MARRY", "Answer": "8551 + 1673 = 10224"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FUEL = FENCE", "Answer": "8551 + 1709 = 10260"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SNAP = STAND", "Answer": "8551 + 1724 = 10275"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TERM = THREE", "Answer": "8551 + 1726 = 10277"}
{"Question": "PEER + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "1553 + 8941 = 10494"}
{"Question": "REAL + LAWN = LOWER", "Answer": "8951 + 1547 = 10498"}
{"Question": "MEET + TASK = TASTE", "Answer": "9551 + 1064 = 10615"}
{"Question": "TOOL + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "1558 + 9061 = 10619"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PORT = POUND", "Answer": "9551 + 1078 = 10629"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RICE = RADIO", "Answer": "9551 + 1384 = 10935"}
{"Question": "LOOK + TENT = TITLE", "Answer": "8664 + 1521 = 10185"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PORT = PRIOR", "Answer": "8661 + 1709 = 10370"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POUR = POUND", "Answer": "9661 + 1078 = 10739"}
{"Question": "DEAD + VARY = EVER", "Answer": "1671 + 4798 = 6469"}
{"Question": "MOOD + ITEM = TIME", "Answer": "1773 + 6841 = 8614"}
{"Question": "EASE + BOAT = ERROR", "Answer": "1741 + 8279 = 10020"}
{"Question": "ODDS + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "1774 + 8251 = 10025"}
{"Question": "DEEP + POST = PRIOR", "Answer": "8771 + 1469 = 10240"}
{"Question": "BOOT + THUS = TRUTH", "Answer": "8771 + 1645 = 10416"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FIND = FENCE", "Answer": "8771 + 1649 = 10420"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MEAT = METER", "Answer": "9771 + 1038 = 10809"}
{"Question": "DOOR + SAND = ODDS", "Answer": "1885 + 6231 = 8116"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TANK = ONTO", "Answer": "6881 + 1437 = 8318"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SALT = TASTE", "Answer": "1887 + 9031 = 10918"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HOST = TOOTH", "Answer": "1997 + 8021 = 10018"}
{"Question": "HERO + OPEN = ERROR", "Answer": "7102 + 2918 = 10020"}
{"Question": "AREA + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "2712 + 8105 = 10817"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RANK = NERVE", "Answer": "7332 + 2918 = 10250"}
{"Question": "DOOR + REST = ODDS", "Answer": "1442 + 2675 = 4117"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PRAY = AWARE", "Answer": "7552 + 2613 = 10165"}
{"Question": "GANG + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "2532 + 8051 = 10583"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FACT = ACTOR", "Answer": "8552 + 2106 = 10658"}
{"Question": "YEAH + HAIR = THREE", "Answer": "9572 + 2783 = 12355"}
{"Question": "MENU + USER = NURSE", "Answer": "9712 + 2875 = 12587"}
{"Question": "KEEP + TASK = ASSET", "Answer": "2995 + 7102 = 10097"}
{"Question": "GOOD + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "7228 + 3503 = 10731"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TEAR = RATIO", "Answer": "8443 + 3921 = 12364"}
{"Question": "COOK + AREA = PEACE", "Answer": "6557 + 3803 = 10360"}
{"Question": "FEED + DRAW = AWARE", "Answer": "8553 + 3612 = 12165"}
{"Question": "FEED + DRAG = APART", "Answer": "8553 + 3614 = 12167"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TALE = STEAL", "Answer": "9883 + 3574 = 13457"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YOUR = LOCAL", "Answer": "8114 + 4267 = 12381"}
{"Question": "EASE + COAL = SALES", "Answer": "4214 + 8527 = 12741"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FINE = INNER", "Answer": "9224 + 4135 = 13359"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PRAY = AWARD", "Answer": "7554 + 4613 = 12167"}
{"Question": "ROOT + USER = STATE", "Answer": "4663 + 9174 = 13837"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MEAL = AREA", "Answer": "1774 + 4362 = 6136"}
{"Question": "ACID + DIET = PEACE", "Answer": "5874 + 4706 = 10580"}
{"Question": "COOL + LEAD = PEACE", "Answer": "8774 + 4309 = 13083"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LOAD = APPLE", "Answer": "4773 + 8614 = 13387"}
{"Question": "MOOD + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "9774 + 4130 = 13904"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DEAR = TRADE", "Answer": "4771 + 9524 = 14295"}
{"Question": "ROOM + DEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "4775 + 9814 = 14589"}
{"Question": "LEAF + FARM = OFFER", "Answer": "9584 + 4873 = 14457"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MARK = ORDER", "Answer": "6115 + 5927 = 12042"}
{"Question": "THAT + MALE = ALTER", "Answer": "5415 + 7123 = 12538"}
{"Question": "ROOF + EASE = OFFER", "Answer": "8113 + 5245 = 13358"}
{"Question": "ONTO + STEP = THOSE", "Answer": "5415 + 8172 = 13587"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CAST = TASTE", "Answer": "5625 + 7291 = 12916"}
{"Question": "MEAL + LADY = CYCLE", "Answer": "8925 + 5234 = 14159"}
{"Question": "PEER + SHOP = IRISH", "Answer": "5224 + 8965 = 14189"}
{"Question": "MEET + THUS = HOUSE", "Answer": "7335 + 5148 = 12483"}
{"Question": "THAT + MALE = SALES", "Answer": "5935 + 7326 = 13261"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MEAN = INNER", "Answer": "9335 + 5074 = 14409"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TIME = METER", "Answer": "9335 + 5214 = 14549"}
{"Question": "TEEN + COST = STATE", "Answer": "5338 + 9715 = 15053"}
{"Question": "ROOF + EASE = AREA", "Answer": "2443 + 5815 = 8258"}
{"Question": "ROOT + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "8445 + 5073 = 13518"}
{"Question": "PEER + RUSH = SHARP", "Answer": "8445 + 5213 = 13658"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LAND = ADULT", "Answer": "7665 + 5192 = 12857"}
{"Question": "COOL + LEFT = FENCE", "Answer": "8665 + 5419 = 14084"}
{"Question": "BEER + RAIL = CLIMB", "Answer": "9665 + 5074 = 14739"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TIRE = RATIO", "Answer": "4775 + 5812 = 10587"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FACE = EAGER", "Answer": "6775 + 5241 = 12016"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LADY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6775 + 5382 = 12157"}
{"Question": "TOOL + LIVE = EVENT", "Answer": "6775 + 5421 = 12196"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEST = STARE", "Answer": "5875 + 6712 = 12587"}
{"Question": "MEET + WHOM = TOOTH", "Answer": "5771 + 8645 = 14416"}
{"Question": "DEAD + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "5745 + 9172 = 14917"}
{"Question": "DEEP + PLAN = APPLE", "Answer": "9775 + 5812 = 15587"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SLIP = LEAVE", "Answer": "6885 + 5147 = 12032"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LOAD = TOOTH", "Answer": "8995 + 5423 = 14418"}
{"Question": "NEED + THIN = EIGHT", "Answer": "6118 + 4206 = 10324"}
{"Question": "BEER + RICH = EIGHT", "Answer": "8116 + 6423 = 14539"}
{"Question": "GANG + READ = ANGER", "Answer": "6146 + 8512 = 14658"}
{"Question": "FOOT + HALF = TOTAL", "Answer": "6221 + 5976 = 12197"}
{"Question": "TOOL + CAST = SALES", "Answer": "6225 + 7316 = 13541"}
{"Question": "SEED + DRAG = GRASS", "Answer": "7226 + 6351 = 13577"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SELF = CLOSE", "Answer": "7226 + 6539 = 13765"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CAST = STATE", "Answer": "6026 + 8214 = 14240"}
{"Question": "LEAF + FARM = REFER", "Answer": "8426 + 6215 = 14641"}
{"Question": "BEAT + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "9126 + 6235 = 15361"}
{"Question": "ROOT + YEAR = ENTRY", "Answer": "6223 + 9146 = 15369"}
{"Question": "GOOD + DARE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9226 + 6745 = 15971"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "5836 + 6329 = 12165"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RATE = TODAY", "Answer": "7336 + 6412 = 13748"}
{"Question": "ALLY + EDGE = GLASS", "Answer": "7339 + 6416 = 13755"}
{"Question": "ODDS + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "9336 + 6125 = 15461"}
{"Question": "LOOK + EASE = SALES", "Answer": "7445 + 6316 = 13761"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TAIL = LIGHT", "Answer": "6426 + 7841 = 14267"}
{"Question": "SELF + FLAG = GLASS", "Answer": "7946 + 6431 = 14377"}
{"Question": "GANG + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "6476 + 8142 = 14618"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LOAD = APPLY", "Answer": "6554 + 7916 = 14470"}
{"Question": "AREA + DESK = START", "Answer": "6976 + 3714 = 10690"}
{"Question": "HEEL + LAST = EARTH", "Answer": "5117 + 7268 = 12385"}
{"Question": "HEEL + WITH = EIGHT", "Answer": "7118 + 6357 = 13475"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MUCH = HUMOR", "Answer": "8227 + 7501 = 15728"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "8227 + 7531 = 15758"}
{"Question": "DEAD + POET = STATE", "Answer": "7327 + 8936 = 16263"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEST = STAGE", "Answer": "7437 + 9316 = 16753"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RISE = SPEED", "Answer": "3447 + 7216 = 10663"}
{"Question": "THAT + CARE = REACH", "Answer": "7047 + 6413 = 13460"}
{"Question": "TOOL + EAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "7443 + 6217 = 13660"}
{"Question": "NEED + THAN = DEATH", "Answer": "7441 + 6827 = 14268"}
{"Question": "NEED + DRUG = RANGE", "Answer": "6557 + 7128 = 13685"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TEAM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8557 + 7201 = 15758"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "7553 + 8617 = 16170"}
{"Question": "ALLY + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "7663 + 2547 = 10210"}
{"Question": "FOOT + HALF = TOOTH", "Answer": "7661 + 8957 = 16618"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HANG = EAGER", "Answer": "7167 + 9648 = 16815"}
{"Question": "DEAD + RAIL = EAGER", "Answer": "7167 + 9652 = 16819"}
{"Question": "DOOR + RATE = TREAT", "Answer": "9667 + 7814 = 17481"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FARM = ORDER", "Answer": "7987 + 2803 = 10790"}
{"Question": "DOOR + USED = START", "Answer": "7885 + 4167 = 12052"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DIET = TITLE", "Answer": "4867 + 7281 = 12148"}
{"Question": "BOOT + THEN = SENSE", "Answer": "4887 + 7625 = 12512"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YOUR = ONION", "Answer": "5887 + 7126 = 13013"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LUNG = UNION", "Answer": "5887 + 7136 = 13023"}
{"Question": "DEAD + POET = TASTE", "Answer": "7837 + 6081 = 13918"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "7487 + 9831 = 17318"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LACK = APPLE", "Answer": "5218 + 8164 = 13382"}
{"Question": "ITEM + MEAL = ELITE", "Answer": "5418 + 8123 = 13541"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FAIL = SALES", "Answer": "8028 + 4273 = 12301"}
{"Question": "THEN + NEAR = HEART", "Answer": "4128 + 8236 = 12364"}
{"Question": "UNIT + TIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "7528 + 8291 = 15819"}
{"Question": "FEEL + LINK = RIFLE", "Answer": "9228 + 8754 = 17982"}
{"Question": "TEST + IDEA = ISSUE", "Answer": "8308 + 1735 = 10043"}
{"Question": "URGE + EARN = UPPER", "Answer": "1348 + 8735 = 10083"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TRIP = RIGHT", "Answer": "8348 + 5137 = 13485"}
{"Question": "URGE + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "7348 + 8135 = 15483"}
{"Question": "TEEN + CAST = STONE", "Answer": "8335 + 9718 = 18053"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "1448 + 8705 = 10153"}
{"Question": "BEAR + RAIN = BIBLE", "Answer": "1748 + 8409 = 10157"}
{"Question": "COOL + LEAD = CYCLE", "Answer": "1448 + 8739 = 10187"}
{"Question": "POOL + SNAP = SALES", "Answer": "8443 + 1908 = 10351"}
{"Question": "KICK + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "8408 + 5749 = 14157"}
{"Question": "HAIR + RING = TIGHT", "Answer": "5948 + 8403 = 14351"}
{"Question": "HELP + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "9248 + 8471 = 17719"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MEAL = BADLY", "Answer": "1558 + 8706 = 10264"}
{"Question": "SEED + THUS = TRUST", "Answer": "8553 + 1728 = 10281"}
{"Question": "SEED + DROP = START", "Answer": "1558 + 8932 = 10490"}
{"Question": "SEED + DRUG = TRUST", "Answer": "2558 + 8063 = 10621"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MEAT = STATE", "Answer": "4558 + 8062 = 12620"}
{"Question": "AREA + BIRD = TREAT", "Answer": "8528 + 6753 = 15281"}
{"Question": "DEEP + ACID = FENCE", "Answer": "8557 + 6938 = 15495"}
{"Question": "ROOT + TWIN = NORTH", "Answer": "7558 + 8231 = 15789"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TEAR = FORTH", "Answer": "8551 + 7328 = 15879"}
{"Question": "AREA + BEST = STATE", "Answer": "8358 + 9517 = 17875"}
{"Question": "ROOM + MALE = RURAL", "Answer": "1668 + 8479 = 10147"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TAIL = TITLE", "Answer": "8568 + 1607 = 10175"}
{"Question": "MEET + PALM = PHOTO", "Answer": "8664 + 1578 = 10242"}
{"Question": "TEEN + PORT = PRIOR", "Answer": "8662 + 1708 = 10370"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SEAT = SALES", "Answer": "8663 + 1708 = 10371"}
{"Question": "FLAG + GAME = LEGAL", "Answer": "5168 + 8693 = 13861"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SEAT = OFFER", "Answer": "1778 + 8245 = 10023"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SURE = OCCUR", "Answer": "1778 + 8246 = 10024"}
{"Question": "CLUB + BELT = CYCLE", "Answer": "1798 + 8375 = 10173"}
{"Question": "FOOT + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1778 + 8405 = 10183"}
{"Question": "FOOT + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "1778 + 8406 = 10184"}
{"Question": "RAIL + LIFT = REFER", "Answer": "1478 + 8723 = 10201"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SAFE = ONION", "Answer": "1778 + 8632 = 10410"}
{"Question": "SOON + NEAR = START", "Answer": "1778 + 8642 = 10420"}
{"Question": "KEEP + PLOT = KNOCK", "Answer": "1778 + 8643 = 10421"}
{"Question": "PEER + THAT = PARTY", "Answer": "1776 + 8908 = 10684"}
{"Question": "SEEK + AIDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "8775 + 1938 = 10713"}
{"Question": "ONTO + STIR = UNION", "Answer": "8378 + 4705 = 13083"}
{"Question": "ALLY + YOUR = TOTAL", "Answer": "4778 + 8369 = 13147"}
{"Question": "TENT + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "8738 + 4675 = 13413"}
{"Question": "FOOD + DATE = REFER", "Answer": "4778 + 8653 = 13431"}
{"Question": "HEEL + WITH = TITLE", "Answer": "8779 + 5418 = 14197"}
{"Question": "BOOM + MENU = BLAME", "Answer": "1229 + 9364 = 10593"}
{"Question": "SELF + FLAT = STAFF", "Answer": "1529 + 9270 = 10799"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HEAD = COACH", "Answer": "9224 + 3589 = 12813"}
{"Question": "BOOT + THAN = COACH", "Answer": "3229 + 9586 = 12815"}
{"Question": "SHOP + POUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "7529 + 9286 = 16815"}
{"Question": "SOON + NEAR = SALES", "Answer": "1339 + 9402 = 10741"}
{"Question": "SHIP + PILE = SALES", "Answer": "1439 + 9382 = 10821"}
{"Question": "QUIT + TRUE = IRAQI", "Answer": "5319 + 9432 = 14751"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SLIP = GLASS", "Answer": "9319 + 5436 = 14755"}
{"Question": "COOL + LIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "5339 + 9482 = 14821"}
{"Question": "MOOD + TERM = THREE", "Answer": "9443 + 1279 = 10722"}
{"Question": "BEER + RISK = BASIS", "Answer": "1449 + 9278 = 10727"}
{"Question": "KEEP + LACK = LOCAL", "Answer": "9442 + 1389 = 10831"}
{"Question": "PEER + STOP = TRUST", "Answer": "9442 + 3189 = 12631"}
{"Question": "SEEM + LOTS = MOTOR", "Answer": "9441 + 3279 = 12720"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "7449 + 9368 = 16817"}
{"Question": "ROOF + FIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "1559 + 9062 = 10621"}
{"Question": "TOOL + EASE = TREAT", "Answer": "1552 + 9379 = 10931"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "3559 + 9062 = 12621"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "9159 + 3572 = 12731"}
{"Question": "POOR + REAL = APPLE", "Answer": "3669 + 9718 = 13387"}
{"Question": "ODDS + SELF = LOOSE", "Answer": "2779 + 9516 = 12295"}
{"Question": "POOR + ELSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "3774 + 9219 = 12993"}
{"Question": "BOOT + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "4779 + 9136 = 13915"}
{"Question": "BOOT + ELSE = STEEL", "Answer": "4773 + 9219 = 13992"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = ROOF", "Answer": "1337 + 1323 = 2660"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = ROOM", "Answer": "1338 + 1323 = 2661"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = BOOM", "Answer": "1447 + 1434 = 2881"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = THEM", "Answer": "1883 + 1898 = 3781"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = ALLY", "Answer": "2663 + 2676 = 5339"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = ITEM", "Answer": "3112 + 3101 = 6213"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = LOOK", "Answer": "4338 + 4323 = 8661"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = FULLY", "Answer": "5448 + 5434 = 10882"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = STATE", "Answer": "5440 + 5464 = 10904"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "6221 + 6242 = 12463"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = CROSS", "Answer": "6884 + 6838 = 13722"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = RELAX", "Answer": "7448 + 7414 = 14862"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = HELLO", "Answer": "7446 + 7434 = 14880"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = TIRED", "Answer": "8551 + 8505 = 17056"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = IRISH", "Answer": "8553 + 8575 = 17128"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8551 + 8595 = 17146"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8553 + 8595 = 17148"}
{"Question": "MEET + MERE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8774 + 8797 = 17571"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = BRUSH", "Answer": "9227 + 9282 = 18509"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERE = SHOOT", "Answer": "9662 + 9676 = 19338"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = SAFE", "Answer": "2660 + 2066 = 4726"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = DEAD", "Answer": "2669 + 2966 = 5635"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = LEAF", "Answer": "4559 + 4955 = 9514"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = LESS", "Answer": "4889 + 4988 = 9877"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = ELSE", "Answer": "4990 + 4099 = 9089"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = RIFLE", "Answer": "6550 + 6055 = 12605"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = ALBUM", "Answer": "6552 + 6255 = 12807"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6557 + 6755 = 13312"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = ONION", "Answer": "6558 + 6855 = 13413"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = APPLY", "Answer": "6775 + 6577 = 13352"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = KNIFE", "Answer": "6880 + 6088 = 12968"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = PRIOR", "Answer": "6885 + 6588 = 13473"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = DRESS", "Answer": "6889 + 6988 = 13877"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = CRAFT", "Answer": "7884 + 7488 = 15372"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = APPLE", "Answer": "8550 + 8055 = 16605"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = CLOCK", "Answer": "8557 + 8755 = 17312"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = NERVE", "Answer": "8660 + 8066 = 16726"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = CLASS", "Answer": "8667 + 8766 = 17433"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = AGENT", "Answer": "8669 + 8966 = 17635"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = NEWLY", "Answer": "8775 + 8577 = 17352"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLEE = ISSUE", "Answer": "9770 + 9077 = 18847"}
{"Question": "FEED + FREE = RIDE", "Answer": "1550 + 1255 = 2805"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KNEE = NINE", "Answer": "1660 + 1266 = 2926"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KNEE = PINK", "Answer": "1883 + 1788 = 3671"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = LEAF", "Answer": "1883 + 1988 = 3871"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = LEFT", "Answer": "2114 + 2011 = 4125"}
{"Question": "FEED + FREE = ROOF", "Answer": "2339 + 2433 = 4772"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = NINE", "Answer": "2770 + 2177 = 4947"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "4771 + 4977 = 9748"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = LEGAL", "Answer": "6229 + 6122 = 12351"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6223 + 6922 = 13145"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KNEE = ONION", "Answer": "6557 + 6255 = 12812"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = AHEAD", "Answer": "6557 + 6955 = 13512"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = GUESS", "Answer": "6778 + 6977 = 13755"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = CLASS", "Answer": "6889 + 6388 = 13277"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TREE = REACT", "Answer": "7443 + 7144 = 14587"}
{"Question": "FEED + FREE = READY", "Answer": "7449 + 7144 = 14593"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = HELLO", "Answer": "7449 + 7544 = 14993"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = RIFLE", "Answer": "7550 + 7155 = 14705"}
{"Question": "FEED + FREE = TROOP", "Answer": "7663 + 7566 = 15229"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TREE = RANGE", "Answer": "7880 + 7188 = 15068"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TREE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7884 + 7388 = 15272"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KNEE = PROOF", "Answer": "8551 + 8455 = 17006"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLEE = PROOF", "Answer": "8553 + 8455 = 17008"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = LEARN", "Answer": "8661 + 8266 = 16927"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FREE = CLASS", "Answer": "8667 + 8566 = 17233"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TREE = FENCE", "Answer": "8770 + 8277 = 17047"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TREE = START", "Answer": "9445 + 9844 = 19289"}
{"Question": "FEED + FREE = RIFLE", "Answer": "9770 + 9177 = 18947"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLOT = TRIP", "Answer": "3177 + 3716 = 6893"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = ACTOR", "Answer": "5233 + 5329 = 10562"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = RIGHT", "Answer": "5166 + 5619 = 10785"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLUS = LEAST", "Answer": "6711 + 6179 = 12890"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLAG = ELITE", "Answer": "6522 + 6259 = 12781"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLUS = SALAD", "Answer": "6944 + 6491 = 13435"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLOT = CATCH", "Answer": "6477 + 6742 = 13219"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLUS = SEVEN", "Answer": "6588 + 6851 = 13439"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = MATCH", "Answer": "6788 + 6871 = 13659"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLUS = SEIZE", "Answer": "7844 + 7481 = 15325"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = ADMIT", "Answer": "7844 + 7483 = 15327"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLAG = GLOVE", "Answer": "7855 + 7581 = 15436"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = LEAST", "Answer": "7855 + 7582 = 15437"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLOT = ALTER", "Answer": "7855 + 7584 = 15439"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = OCCUR", "Answer": "7866 + 7682 = 15548"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLAG = GHOST", "Answer": "7488 + 7841 = 15329"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = COLOR", "Answer": "8233 + 8329 = 16562"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLUS = SENSE", "Answer": "8566 + 8651 = 17217"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = CRAFT", "Answer": "8766 + 8672 = 17438"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLAG = BLIND", "Answer": "8677 + 8762 = 17439"}
{"Question": "TREE + TERM = STAIR", "Answer": "9866 + 9682 = 19548"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = LOOK", "Answer": "1633 + 1376 = 3009"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = SAFE", "Answer": "1055 + 1560 = 2615"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = ALLY", "Answer": "1277 + 1732 = 3009"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = LOSS", "Answer": "2855 + 2578 = 5433"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = ROLL", "Answer": "3744 + 3467 = 7211"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = EAST", "Answer": "3677 + 3746 = 7423"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = EASE", "Answer": "4088 + 4890 = 8978"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5011 + 5190 = 10201"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = COURT", "Answer": "5233 + 5392 = 10625"}
{"Question": "CELL + CLUE = EXACT", "Answer": "5166 + 5691 = 10857"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = DOUBT", "Answer": "5266 + 5692 = 10958"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = LAUGH", "Answer": "6711 + 6197 = 12908"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = BRAIN", "Answer": "6255 + 6582 = 12837"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = KNIFE", "Answer": "6077 + 6790 = 12867"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = IRISH", "Answer": "6377 + 6743 = 13120"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = TRUST", "Answer": "6477 + 6724 = 13201"}
{"Question": "CELL + CLUE = KNOCK", "Answer": "6477 + 6784 = 13261"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = FIFTH", "Answer": "6288 + 6872 = 13160"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = UNION", "Answer": "6588 + 6815 = 13403"}
{"Question": "CELL + CLUE = WHICH", "Answer": "6588 + 6875 = 13463"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = URBAN", "Answer": "6788 + 6817 = 13605"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = AGENT", "Answer": "6988 + 6819 = 13807"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = REACH", "Answer": "7144 + 7461 = 14605"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = TROOP", "Answer": "7544 + 7465 = 15009"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = PLATE", "Answer": "7088 + 7890 = 14978"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = PAPER", "Answer": "7288 + 7832 = 15120"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = RIVER", "Answer": "7388 + 7843 = 15231"}
{"Question": "CELL + CLUE = URBAN", "Answer": "7488 + 7814 = 15302"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = STUFF", "Answer": "7488 + 7834 = 15322"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "7588 + 7825 = 15413"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "7588 + 7845 = 15433"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = FEWER", "Answer": "7588 + 7865 = 15453"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = AGENT", "Answer": "7988 + 7819 = 15807"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAR = EXACT", "Answer": "8711 + 8197 = 16908"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8244 + 8492 = 16736"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = FIBER", "Answer": "8344 + 8493 = 16837"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = CROSS", "Answer": "8755 + 8567 = 17322"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = LEAVE", "Answer": "8066 + 8670 = 16736"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = CRACK", "Answer": "8766 + 8647 = 17413"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = FLOOR", "Answer": "8277 + 8732 = 17009"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLUE = ALTER", "Answer": "8277 + 8752 = 17029"}
{"Question": "FREE + FEAR = TASTE", "Answer": "9033 + 9380 = 18413"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "1522 + 1288 = 2810"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = DEAD", "Answer": "1344 + 1488 = 2832"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = LEAD", "Answer": "2144 + 2466 = 4610"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = LEAF", "Answer": "2344 + 2488 = 4832"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = GRAB", "Answer": "3447 + 3274 = 6721"}
{"Question": "SEED + SIDE = DATA", "Answer": "3447 + 3674 = 7121"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = BADLY", "Answer": "5448 + 5084 = 10532"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TONE = HOTEL", "Answer": "5449 + 5094 = 10543"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = MORAL", "Answer": "5448 + 5384 = 10832"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = AVOID", "Answer": "5778 + 5187 = 10965"}
{"Question": "SEED + SIDE = INDEX", "Answer": "5779 + 5197 = 10976"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HOLE = FORTH", "Answer": "5887 + 5078 = 10965"}
{"Question": "SEED + SIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "5889 + 5098 = 10987"}
{"Question": "TREE + TELL = REFER", "Answer": "6122 + 6299 = 12421"}
{"Question": "FEED + FADE = REFER", "Answer": "6229 + 6392 = 12621"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HOLE = ORDER", "Answer": "6339 + 6193 = 12532"}
{"Question": "PEER + PURE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6887 + 6278 = 13165"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = ALBUM", "Answer": "7144 + 7488 = 14632"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "7448 + 7284 = 14732"}
{"Question": "WEEK + WAKE = FEWER", "Answer": "7449 + 7294 = 14743"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HOLE = BELOW", "Answer": "7448 + 7384 = 14832"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7448 + 7684 = 15132"}
{"Question": "SEED + SIDE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7668 + 7586 = 15254"}
{"Question": "TREE + TELL = ORDER", "Answer": "7566 + 7699 = 15265"}
{"Question": "SEED + SIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7885 + 7258 = 15143"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILE = BASIS", "Answer": "7884 + 7348 = 15232"}
{"Question": "TREE + TELL = INNER", "Answer": "8233 + 8399 = 16632"}
{"Question": "FEED + FADE = PAPER", "Answer": "8339 + 8793 = 17132"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = ASSET", "Answer": "8449 + 8194 = 16643"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TONE = RATIO", "Answer": "8557 + 8275 = 16832"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = FINAL", "Answer": "8557 + 8375 = 16932"}
{"Question": "PEER + PURE = DRAMA", "Answer": "8557 + 8675 = 17232"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = TERMS", "Answer": "8667 + 8076 = 16743"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SAKE = MEDIA", "Answer": "8775 + 8257 = 17032"}
{"Question": "FALL + FLEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9144 + 9466 = 18610"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HOLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "9448 + 9384 = 18832"}
{"Question": "TREE + TELL = OCCUR", "Answer": "9255 + 9577 = 18832"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = TODAY", "Answer": "9557 + 9375 = 18932"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = BIRTH", "Answer": "9667 + 9076 = 18743"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARE = ALLOW", "Answer": "9667 + 9176 = 18843"}
{"Question": "SELL + SLOW = LOSS", "Answer": "1522 + 1289 = 2811"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHOE = ODDS", "Answer": "1447 + 1324 = 2771"}
{"Question": "BEER + BAKE = ARAB", "Answer": "2884 + 2568 = 5452"}
{"Question": "BEER + BAKE = AREA", "Answer": "3552 + 3705 = 7257"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAM = RARE", "Answer": "3755 + 3520 = 7275"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DARE = AREA", "Answer": "4118 + 4901 = 9019"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "5411 + 5103 = 10514"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FIRE = COLOR", "Answer": "5226 + 5382 = 10608"}
{"Question": "FEED + FINE = UNDER", "Answer": "5226 + 5402 = 10628"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = BUYER", "Answer": "5224 + 5602 = 10826"}
{"Question": "DATA + DRAG = ENTER", "Answer": "5292 + 5624 = 10916"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "5323 + 5031 = 10354"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = LEAST", "Answer": "5343 + 5031 = 10374"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "5332 + 5103 = 10435"}
{"Question": "FEED + FINE = INDEX", "Answer": "5334 + 5103 = 10437"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAM = MAKER", "Answer": "5433 + 5301 = 10734"}
{"Question": "SEED + SITE = VISIT", "Answer": "5442 + 5064 = 10506"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = STYLE", "Answer": "5606 + 5367 = 10973"}
{"Question": "NEED + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "5778 + 5197 = 10975"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SHOE = WORKS", "Answer": "5778 + 5207 = 10985"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HIDE = TIGHT", "Answer": "5883 + 5068 = 10951"}
{"Question": "FEED + FIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "5883 + 5098 = 10981"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLOW = LOWER", "Answer": "6311 + 6124 = 12435"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = ENTRY", "Answer": "6112 + 6541 = 12653"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "6122 + 6235 = 12357"}
{"Question": "DATA + DRAW = WATER", "Answer": "6252 + 6321 = 12573"}
{"Question": "NEED + NAME = SENSE", "Answer": "6220 + 6392 = 12612"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "6242 + 6729 = 12971"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLAN = SENSE", "Answer": "6533 + 6379 = 12912"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SITE = METER", "Answer": "6331 + 6703 = 13034"}
{"Question": "BEER + BONE = NERVE", "Answer": "6330 + 6713 = 13043"}
{"Question": "NEED + NOSE = DOZEN", "Answer": "6551 + 6205 = 12756"}
{"Question": "SEED + SAFE = FALSE", "Answer": "6550 + 6215 = 12765"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "6255 + 6583 = 12838"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FEAR = START", "Answer": "6755 + 6528 = 13283"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "6553 + 6805 = 13358"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FADE = YIELD", "Answer": "6552 + 6975 = 13527"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHOE = CROSS", "Answer": "6779 + 6087 = 12866"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHOE = COACH", "Answer": "6775 + 6237 = 13012"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TAPE = PAINT", "Answer": "6779 + 6317 = 13096"}
{"Question": "MEET + MINE = DRAMA", "Answer": "6775 + 6487 = 13262"}
{"Question": "PULL + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6488 + 6831 = 13319"}
{"Question": "BALL + BLUE = GUESS", "Answer": "6588 + 6834 = 13422"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = AGREE", "Answer": "7181 + 7019 = 14200"}
{"Question": "SELL + SLOW = WHOSE", "Answer": "7322 + 7251 = 14573"}
{"Question": "SEED + SAFE = BASIS", "Answer": "7225 + 7482 = 14707"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLAN = HAPPY", "Answer": "7522 + 7248 = 14770"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SAFE = TERMS", "Answer": "7443 + 7094 = 14537"}
{"Question": "MEET + MODE = LEMON", "Answer": "7445 + 7284 = 14729"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "7448 + 7294 = 14742"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLAN = SLEEP", "Answer": "7855 + 7592 = 15447"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = THREE", "Answer": "7818 + 7082 = 14900"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FEAR = LARGE", "Answer": "7188 + 7850 = 15038"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TUBE = BASIS", "Answer": "7884 + 7318 = 15202"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHOE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7886 + 7548 = 15434"}
{"Question": "BALL + BLUE = LABEL", "Answer": "8611 + 8190 = 16801"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "8116 + 8701 = 16817"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHOE = LOOSE", "Answer": "8220 + 8462 = 16682"}
{"Question": "BEER + BAKE = CARRY", "Answer": "8339 + 8653 = 16992"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TIME = INNER", "Answer": "8446 + 8194 = 16640"}
{"Question": "SEED + SITE = BASIS", "Answer": "8553 + 8275 = 16828"}
{"Question": "CELL + CLUB = BIBLE", "Answer": "8655 + 8501 = 17156"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAM = AWARE", "Answer": "8655 + 8510 = 17165"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEAM = APART", "Answer": "8655 + 8513 = 17168"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DARE = RURAL", "Answer": "8554 + 8615 = 17169"}
{"Question": "TREE + TEND = ORDER", "Answer": "8755 + 8502 = 17257"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TIME = LIMIT", "Answer": "8553 + 8725 = 17278"}
{"Question": "BEER + BITE = RATIO", "Answer": "8551 + 8945 = 17496"}
{"Question": "NEED + NAME = HUMAN", "Answer": "8553 + 8945 = 17498"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAR = START", "Answer": "8575 + 8952 = 17527"}
{"Question": "FEED + FIVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8665 + 8296 = 16961"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAR = STARE", "Answer": "8676 + 8963 = 17639"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FATE = ALTER", "Answer": "8776 + 8197 = 16973"}
{"Question": "SELL + SLOW = CLOSE", "Answer": "8377 + 8706 = 17083"}
{"Question": "BEER + BONE = SENSE", "Answer": "8770 + 8647 = 17417"}
{"Question": "MEET + MALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8774 + 8917 = 17691"}
{"Question": "SELL + SLOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "9711 + 9186 = 18897"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = LOOSE", "Answer": "9373 + 9431 = 18804"}
{"Question": "BELL + BLOW = OFFER", "Answer": "9533 + 9317 = 18850"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "9464 + 9140 = 18604"}
{"Question": "FILL + FLAG = BASIS", "Answer": "9244 + 9483 = 18727"}
{"Question": "NEED + NAME = INDEX", "Answer": "9442 + 9804 = 19246"}
{"Question": "SELL + SLIP = ONION", "Answer": "9055 + 9563 = 18618"}
{"Question": "POLL + PLAN = ERROR", "Answer": "9255 + 9573 = 18828"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TAPE = APPLE", "Answer": "9660 + 9186 = 18846"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRUE = OTHER", "Answer": "9662 + 9806 = 19468"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEAL = TRADE", "Answer": "9717 + 9073 = 18790"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = TIGHT", "Answer": "1447 + 9474 = 10921"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERE = HABIT", "Answer": "9448 + 1484 = 10932"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1557 + 8575 = 10132"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERE = BASIS", "Answer": "1667 + 8676 = 10343"}
{"Question": "DEER + HERE = DIRTY", "Answer": "1775 + 8757 = 10532"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = THICK", "Answer": "1776 + 8767 = 10543"}
{"Question": "DEER + HERE = TIRED", "Answer": "3449 + 7494 = 10943"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = ADAPT", "Answer": "3558 + 6585 = 10143"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERE = FORTH", "Answer": "4887 + 5878 = 10765"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERE = LABEL", "Answer": "5229 + 8292 = 13521"}
{"Question": "BEER + MERE = LEMON", "Answer": "5448 + 9484 = 14932"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = METER", "Answer": "7339 + 6393 = 13732"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GENE = ANGRY", "Answer": "6884 + 7848 = 14732"}
{"Question": "FEED + HERE = FORTH", "Answer": "1227 + 9242 = 10469"}
{"Question": "MEET + HERE = MONTH", "Answer": "1227 + 9252 = 10479"}
{"Question": "TEEN + MERE = MONTH", "Answer": "9224 + 1272 = 10496"}
{"Question": "HEEL + MERE = HONOR", "Answer": "1226 + 9282 = 10508"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HERE = TIGHT", "Answer": "1338 + 9353 = 10691"}
{"Question": "FEED + HERE = ROOF", "Answer": "1447 + 2434 = 3881"}
{"Question": "NEED + HERE = HONOR", "Answer": "9442 + 1464 = 10906"}
{"Question": "FEED + GENE = FIGHT", "Answer": "1443 + 9484 = 10927"}
{"Question": "DEEP + HERE = DRAFT", "Answer": "1669 + 8606 = 10275"}
{"Question": "BEER + GENE = BASIS", "Answer": "1667 + 8656 = 10323"}
{"Question": "KEEP + HERE = KNOCK", "Answer": "1665 + 8676 = 10341"}
{"Question": "MEET + HERE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1775 + 8727 = 10502"}
{"Question": "MEET + HERE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8775 + 1797 = 10572"}
{"Question": "FEED + GENE = FIBER", "Answer": "1776 + 8797 = 10573"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HERE = EARTH", "Answer": "3116 + 7121 = 10237"}
{"Question": "MEET + HERE = EARTH", "Answer": "6113 + 4121 = 10234"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HERE = REACT", "Answer": "5332 + 8313 = 13645"}
{"Question": "DEER + GENE = READY", "Answer": "5331 + 8323 = 13654"}
{"Question": "KEEP + HERE = CRACK", "Answer": "5669 + 8646 = 14315"}
{"Question": "DEEP + GENE = BLOOD", "Answer": "8662 + 5676 = 14338"}
{"Question": "FEED + GENE = REFER", "Answer": "7338 + 6393 = 13731"}
{"Question": "MEET + HERE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6771 + 8747 = 15518"}
{"Question": "BEER + TREE = DEBT", "Answer": "1559 + 4955 = 6514"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FLEE = LIFT", "Answer": "6558 + 1855 = 8413"}
{"Question": "TEEN + KNEE = TRUTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8755 = 10312"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FLEE = HONOR", "Answer": "1552 + 9255 = 10807"}
{"Question": "BEER + FREE = BOARD", "Answer": "1775 + 8577 = 10352"}
{"Question": "BEER + FREE = BADLY", "Answer": "1776 + 8677 = 10453"}
{"Question": "BEER + TREE = REST", "Answer": "2779 + 6977 = 9756"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FLEE = CATCH", "Answer": "3558 + 6855 = 10413"}
{"Question": "TEEN + KNEE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5668 + 7866 = 13534"}
{"Question": "BEER + TREE = METAL", "Answer": "6553 + 9355 = 15908"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FLEE = TIGHT", "Answer": "7883 + 6388 = 14271"}
{"Question": "BEER + FREE = CRAFT", "Answer": "6884 + 7488 = 14372"}
{"Question": "PEER + FREE = REPLY", "Answer": "7551 + 8155 = 15706"}
{"Question": "BEER + TREE = LEAST", "Answer": "7553 + 8355 = 15908"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "1226 + 8922 = 10148"}
{"Question": "TEEN + FREE = TREND", "Answer": "1224 + 9022 = 10246"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ROLL = ACTOR", "Answer": "1227 + 9422 = 10649"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CELL = CHASE", "Answer": "9225 + 1722 = 10947"}
{"Question": "TEEN + FREE = TREAT", "Answer": "1338 + 9033 = 10371"}
{"Question": "SEEM + KNEE = SMOKE", "Answer": "1440 + 8944 = 10384"}
{"Question": "SEED + FLEE = FLESH", "Answer": "9448 + 1044 = 10492"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TREE = TIGHT", "Answer": "9447 + 1244 = 10691"}
{"Question": "NEED + FLEE = FUNNY", "Answer": "9448 + 1544 = 10992"}
{"Question": "TEEN + FLEE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8455 = 10012"}
{"Question": "MEET + FLEE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1552 + 8655 = 10207"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FREE = HONOR", "Answer": "1552 + 8755 = 10307"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CELL = COLOR", "Answer": "8552 + 1955 = 10507"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CELL = COACH", "Answer": "9557 + 1355 = 10912"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BILL = AGREE", "Answer": "1667 + 8566 = 10233"}
{"Question": "DEEP + FLEE = DRESS", "Answer": "1667 + 8966 = 10633"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ROLL = AGREE", "Answer": "1667 + 9266 = 10933"}
{"Question": "FEEL + KNEE = FIELD", "Answer": "1775 + 8977 = 10752"}
{"Question": "DEEP + FLEE = DREAM", "Answer": "1776 + 8977 = 10753"}
{"Question": "ALLY + SELL = LOOSE", "Answer": "7118 + 2911 = 10029"}
{"Question": "FEED + TREE = ROOF", "Answer": "2448 + 3544 = 5992"}
{"Question": "ALLY + SELL = ELSE", "Answer": "2881 + 6988 = 9869"}
{"Question": "NEED + FREE = HONOR", "Answer": "3552 + 6755 = 10307"}
{"Question": "DEEP + FLEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "3558 + 6955 = 10513"}
{"Question": "DEEP + FLEE = PROOF", "Answer": "3771 + 8677 = 12448"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ROLL = ERROR", "Answer": "9776 + 3577 = 13353"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TREE = RIGHT", "Answer": "7886 + 4188 = 12074"}
{"Question": "FEED + TREE = DRAFT", "Answer": "8441 + 5344 = 13785"}
{"Question": "SEEM + TREE = LIMIT", "Answer": "8669 + 5266 = 13935"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FREE = IRISH", "Answer": "5669 + 8466 = 14135"}
{"Question": "DEEP + FREE = PROOF", "Answer": "7551 + 6455 = 14006"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FREE = PROOF", "Answer": "6552 + 7455 = 14007"}
{"Question": "ALLY + POLL = SLEEP", "Answer": "6553 + 8455 = 15008"}
{"Question": "GENE + KNEE = GREAT", "Answer": "1393 + 8933 = 10326"}
{"Question": "HERE + FREE = FLESH", "Answer": "8494 + 1944 = 10438"}
{"Question": "GENE + KNEE = NECK", "Answer": "6191 + 2911 = 9102"}
{"Question": "MERE + TREE = CATCH", "Answer": "7383 + 2833 = 10216"}
{"Question": "GENE + KNEE = SIGN", "Answer": "2484 + 6844 = 9328"}
{"Question": "HERE + FREE = RICH", "Answer": "4282 + 3822 = 8104"}
{"Question": "HERE + FREE = ROUGH", "Answer": "4717 + 6177 = 10894"}
{"Question": "MERE + TREE = DEATH", "Answer": "6535 + 9355 = 15890"}
{"Question": "HERE + FREE = IRISH", "Answer": "8464 + 7644 = 16108"}
{"Question": "HERE + TREE = METAL", "Answer": "7535 + 8355 = 15890"}
{"Question": "FEED + ODDS = FLAME", "Answer": "1224 + 9448 = 10672"}
{"Question": "TALL + FLAG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1344 + 9437 = 10781"}
{"Question": "LESS + USER = SURE", "Answer": "1755 + 3572 = 5327"}
{"Question": "HERE + CREW = CATCH", "Answer": "8565 + 1653 = 10218"}
{"Question": "FEED + ODDS = FALSE", "Answer": "1775 + 8552 = 10327"}
{"Question": "PULL + CLUE = CHEAP", "Answer": "8755 + 1573 = 10328"}
{"Question": "DATA + STAR = SMART", "Answer": "8595 + 1954 = 10549"}
{"Question": "LESS + USER = LARGE", "Answer": "1255 + 9527 = 10782"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ALLY = ADMIT", "Answer": "8776 + 1662 = 10438"}
{"Question": "HALL + FLAG = FIGHT", "Answer": "9266 + 1628 = 10894"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ALLY = COACH", "Answer": "7883 + 2334 = 10217"}
{"Question": "HERE + CREW = RICH", "Answer": "5484 + 2841 = 8325"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ALLY = CRASH", "Answer": "2335 + 8557 = 10892"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ALLY = YOUTH", "Answer": "7886 + 2661 = 10547"}
{"Question": "PULL + BLUE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9522 + 3257 = 12779"}
{"Question": "FULL + BLUE = OFFER", "Answer": "3844 + 9482 = 13326"}
{"Question": "TREE + HERO = MOTOR", "Answer": "3755 + 8572 = 12327"}
{"Question": "TREE + HERO = MONTH", "Answer": "3766 + 8672 = 12438"}
{"Question": "DATA + STAR = TIRED", "Answer": "3616 + 9167 = 12783"}
{"Question": "COOL + ALLY = MUSIC", "Answer": "4225 + 6559 = 10784"}
{"Question": "DATA + STAR = YOURS", "Answer": "6535 + 4359 = 10894"}
{"Question": "ROLL + PLOT = STRIP", "Answer": "4855 + 7582 = 12437"}
{"Question": "MESS + USER = CRIME", "Answer": "4866 + 7682 = 12548"}
{"Question": "COOL + ALLY = BOARD", "Answer": "4226 + 8667 = 12893"}
{"Question": "FREE + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8766 + 4671 = 13437"}
{"Question": "KILL + SLIP = CLOCK", "Answer": "7833 + 5384 = 13217"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ALLY = BLADE", "Answer": "8223 + 5339 = 13562"}
{"Question": "HERE + CREW = OCCUR", "Answer": "9686 + 5862 = 15548"}
{"Question": "NEED + ODDS = STONE", "Answer": "5887 + 6771 = 12658"}
{"Question": "MALL + GLAD = ADMIT", "Answer": "8177 + 5713 = 13890"}
{"Question": "DATA + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "5717 + 9174 = 14891"}
{"Question": "COOL + ALLY = PEACE", "Answer": "7224 + 6449 = 13673"}
{"Question": "DATA + STAR = RAPID", "Answer": "6575 + 8751 = 15326"}
{"Question": "POLL + SLOW = WORKS", "Answer": "6577 + 8751 = 15328"}
{"Question": "LESS + USED = APPLE", "Answer": "7244 + 9428 = 16672"}
{"Question": "COOL + ALLY = BLACK", "Answer": "8225 + 7559 = 15784"}
{"Question": "HALL + FLAT = CATCH", "Answer": "7655 + 8562 = 16217"}
{"Question": "HERE + CREW = TRUTH", "Answer": "8565 + 7653 = 16218"}
{"Question": "CALL + PLAN = KNOCK", "Answer": "9355 + 7536 = 16891"}
{"Question": "MERE + FLEE = MORAL", "Answer": "1262 + 9422 = 10684"}
{"Question": "HERE + FLEE = FORTH", "Answer": "8434 + 1944 = 10378"}
{"Question": "HERE + FLEE = FRONT", "Answer": "8606 + 1966 = 10572"}
{"Question": "HERE + FLEE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1797 + 8477 = 10274"}
{"Question": "GENE + FREE = ANGER", "Answer": "2404 + 7844 = 10248"}
{"Question": "GENE + FREE = OFFER", "Answer": "9404 + 2844 = 12248"}
{"Question": "GENE + TREE = ENTER", "Answer": "7101 + 3211 = 10312"}
{"Question": "GENE + TREE = METER", "Answer": "4303 + 9633 = 13936"}
{"Question": "HERE + FLEE = PROOF", "Answer": "7464 + 8544 = 16008"}
{"Question": "MOON + INTO = METER", "Answer": "1225 + 9582 = 10807"}
{"Question": "BEER + TRUE = BOARD", "Answer": "1442 + 9284 = 10726"}
{"Question": "SOON + INTO = SHIFT", "Answer": "1662 + 9286 = 10948"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ALSO = LOTS", "Answer": "6889 + 2978 = 9867"}
{"Question": "BEER + URGE = ARGUE", "Answer": "3880 + 7098 = 10978"}
{"Question": "BEER + TRUE = CRAFT", "Answer": "4662 + 8276 = 12938"}
{"Question": "POOL + ALSO = STRIP", "Answer": "4886 + 7618 = 12504"}
{"Question": "BEER + TRUE = HEART", "Answer": "8332 + 5293 = 13625"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BLUE = LUNCH", "Answer": "8771 + 5137 = 13908"}
{"Question": "TEEN + ONCE = PRIOR", "Answer": "5884 + 6478 = 12362"}
{"Question": "POOL + ALSO = SHARP", "Answer": "5887 + 6718 = 12605"}
{"Question": "TREE + HEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "6788 + 5827 = 12615"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ALSO = ELITE", "Answer": "5883 + 7368 = 13251"}
{"Question": "MOON + INTO = JOINT", "Answer": "6553 + 9385 = 15938"}
{"Question": "FREE + HEAR = BEACH", "Answer": "7355 + 8593 = 15948"}
{"Question": "MEET + BITE = ITEM", "Answer": "1229 + 5692 = 6921"}
{"Question": "BEER + CARE = ARAB", "Answer": "2448 + 1384 = 3832"}
{"Question": "BALL + FLEE = LEAF", "Answer": "3244 + 1477 = 4721"}
{"Question": "TALL + FLEE = TREAT", "Answer": "1244 + 9477 = 10721"}
{"Question": "BEER + SURE = SHRUG", "Answer": "9448 + 1384 = 10832"}
{"Question": "SEEK + BAKE = ARAB", "Answer": "1557 + 2375 = 3932"}
{"Question": "BEER + CARE = BIRTH", "Answer": "1558 + 9285 = 10843"}
{"Question": "BOOT + INTO = BEING", "Answer": "1557 + 9375 = 10932"}
{"Question": "DEEP + ROPE = RADIO", "Answer": "9558 + 1385 = 10943"}
{"Question": "HEEL + MALE = THAT", "Answer": "2668 + 1586 = 4254"}
{"Question": "GENE + THEN = TIGHT", "Answer": "9656 + 1265 = 10921"}
{"Question": "MEET + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "1779 + 4697 = 6476"}
{"Question": "DATA + BEAT = BIBLE", "Answer": "8767 + 1376 = 10143"}
{"Question": "BEER + FIRE = BASIC", "Answer": "1776 + 8467 = 10243"}
{"Question": "BOOT + INTO = ONION", "Answer": "8119 + 2091 = 10210"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TAPE = BROAD", "Answer": "2557 + 8375 = 10932"}
{"Question": "BEER + FIRE = CABIN", "Answer": "2668 + 7586 = 10254"}
{"Question": "HERE + USER = RUSH", "Answer": "3767 + 2476 = 6243"}
{"Question": "DEEP + ROPE = OFFER", "Answer": "2889 + 7198 = 10087"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TAPE = RAPID", "Answer": "3558 + 9285 = 12843"}
{"Question": "NEED + HIDE = AGAIN", "Answer": "3667 + 8476 = 12143"}
{"Question": "FREE + BELL = REFER", "Answer": "4122 + 8299 = 12421"}
{"Question": "FOOT + INTO = KNIFE", "Answer": "4558 + 6085 = 10643"}
{"Question": "MEET + NOTE = HONOR", "Answer": "4557 + 9375 = 13932"}
{"Question": "BOOT + AUTO = URBAN", "Answer": "8667 + 4176 = 12843"}
{"Question": "BEER + TIRE = HABIT", "Answer": "4778 + 5687 = 10465"}
{"Question": "BEER + CORE = PORCH", "Answer": "4778 + 6087 = 10865"}
{"Question": "ROOT + AUTO = EXTRA", "Answer": "5886 + 4768 = 10654"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LINE = FIFTH", "Answer": "4885 + 7258 = 12143"}
{"Question": "HEEL + PILE = FIFTH", "Answer": "4886 + 7268 = 12154"}
{"Question": "BOOT + INTO = UNION", "Answer": "5449 + 8394 = 13843"}
{"Question": "MERE + USER = SHRUG", "Answer": "7686 + 5168 = 12854"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ROLE = OTHER", "Answer": "8669 + 5196 = 13865"}
{"Question": "DEEP + ROPE = BOARD", "Answer": "5778 + 6287 = 12065"}
{"Question": "TREE + HELL = RIGHT", "Answer": "5188 + 6877 = 12065"}
{"Question": "FREE + LESS = COLOR", "Answer": "6244 + 7488 = 13732"}
{"Question": "BEER + MORE = LEMON", "Answer": "6557 + 9375 = 15932"}
{"Question": "BEER + DARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6558 + 9385 = 15943"}
{"Question": "BEER + CARE = URBAN", "Answer": "9557 + 8375 = 17932"}
{"Question": "FOOT + HERO = FIFTH", "Answer": "1226 + 8942 = 10168"}
{"Question": "FEED + TYPE = FIFTY", "Answer": "1227 + 8962 = 10189"}
{"Question": "POOL + HERO = PAPER", "Answer": "1225 + 8972 = 10197"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LAKE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1226 + 8972 = 10198"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SHOE = SHELF", "Answer": "9227 + 1052 = 10279"}
{"Question": "FREE + MEAL = FLAME", "Answer": "1522 + 9270 = 10792"}
{"Question": "LOOK + INTO = LATIN", "Answer": "1223 + 9572 = 10795"}
{"Question": "SELL + FLAG = STATE", "Answer": "1522 + 9283 = 10805"}
{"Question": "TREE + LEAD = LATER", "Answer": "9722 + 1205 = 10927"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TEND = THOSE", "Answer": "9225 + 1732 = 10957"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BITE = HABIT", "Answer": "1223 + 9752 = 10975"}
{"Question": "TELL + SLIP = TASTE", "Answer": "1533 + 9382 = 10915"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BOWL = AWARD", "Answer": "1449 + 8704 = 10153"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BONE = HONOR", "Answer": "1448 + 9054 = 10502"}
{"Question": "MEET + ROLE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1445 + 9064 = 10509"}
{"Question": "BEER + COME = BOARD", "Answer": "1442 + 9084 = 10526"}
{"Question": "BEER + HIDE = BIRTH", "Answer": "1445 + 9084 = 10529"}
{"Question": "COOK + HERO = CRIME", "Answer": "1448 + 9204 = 10652"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SEAT = SHALL", "Answer": "9244 + 1478 = 10722"}
{"Question": "MEET + CLUE = CATCH", "Answer": "9448 + 1364 = 10812"}
{"Question": "MEET + BLUE = MOUTH", "Answer": "1442 + 9384 = 10826"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GIRL = GRAIN", "Answer": "9448 + 1504 = 10952"}
{"Question": "BOSS + USER = SURE", "Answer": "1755 + 3594 = 5349"}
{"Question": "BEER + DATE = BLOOD", "Answer": "1553 + 8675 = 10228"}
{"Question": "LOOK + HERO = LABEL", "Answer": "1556 + 8935 = 10491"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CODE = FIELD", "Answer": "1552 + 8975 = 10527"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TRUE = TRUTH", "Answer": "9554 + 1065 = 10619"}
{"Question": "SEED + BLUE = SHALL", "Answer": "1557 + 9265 = 10822"}
{"Question": "TOSS + USER = THERE", "Answer": "1255 + 9583 = 10838"}
{"Question": "KEEP + SHOE = KNOCK", "Answer": "1556 + 9285 = 10841"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TYPE = FULLY", "Answer": "1558 + 9325 = 10883"}
{"Question": "BEER + AIDE = BOARD", "Answer": "1552 + 9375 = 10927"}
{"Question": "BEER + SIDE = BASIS", "Answer": "1554 + 9385 = 10939"}
{"Question": "KEEP + AIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8667 + 1506 = 10173"}
{"Question": "BEER + CLUE = BUILD", "Answer": "1669 + 8706 = 10375"}
{"Question": "TALL + BLUE = TREAT", "Answer": "1966 + 8625 = 10591"}
{"Question": "BEER + FACE = BASIC", "Answer": "1662 + 9086 = 10748"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SHOE = SOLAR", "Answer": "9668 + 1206 = 10874"}
{"Question": "BELL + ALSO = BIBLE", "Answer": "1377 + 8796 = 10173"}
{"Question": "FEEL + AIDE = FULLY", "Answer": "1772 + 8457 = 10229"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BOWL = AGREE", "Answer": "1776 + 8457 = 10233"}
{"Question": "BEER + FATE = FIRST", "Answer": "8772 + 1497 = 10269"}
{"Question": "BEER + CLUE = BASIS", "Answer": "1776 + 8547 = 10323"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SHOE = SOUTH", "Answer": "8779 + 1607 = 10386"}
{"Question": "SEED + BLUE = STUFF", "Answer": "1775 + 8647 = 10422"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SHOE = SALES", "Answer": "8774 + 1697 = 10471"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TAKE = FAULT", "Answer": "1772 + 9057 = 10829"}
{"Question": "TEEN + FILE = FINAL", "Answer": "9778 + 1057 = 10835"}
{"Question": "BEER + CASE = BASIC", "Answer": "1772 + 9087 = 10859"}
{"Question": "SOON + HERO = SERVE", "Answer": "1773 + 9087 = 10860"}
{"Question": "MEET + BONE = MONTH", "Answer": "1776 + 9087 = 10863"}
{"Question": "SOON + AUTO = STAND", "Answer": "1778 + 9207 = 10985"}
{"Question": "DEEP + GAME = ARMED", "Answer": "2775 + 8197 = 10972"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CLUB = ERROR", "Answer": "2477 + 9765 = 12242"}
{"Question": "DATA + YEAR = READY", "Answer": "7252 + 3021 = 10273"}
{"Question": "MEET + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "3225 + 7102 = 10327"}
{"Question": "MEET + SURE = TERMS", "Answer": "9221 + 3572 = 12793"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "3225 + 9702 = 12927"}
{"Question": "DEEP + MALE = SALAD", "Answer": "3449 + 7054 = 10503"}
{"Question": "DATA + REAL = ENTER", "Answer": "7464 + 3149 = 10613"}
{"Question": "BEER + SHOE = IRISH", "Answer": "8442 + 3694 = 12136"}
{"Question": "BOOT + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "3772 + 8917 = 12689"}
{"Question": "BOOM + ALSO = SMALL", "Answer": "3882 + 9018 = 12900"}
{"Question": "SELL + CLUB = ABUSE", "Answer": "9522 + 4273 = 13795"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "7336 + 4913 = 12249"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HERO = FORTH", "Answer": "4335 + 8923 = 13258"}
{"Question": "PEER + ONCE = TROOP", "Answer": "7552 + 4895 = 12447"}
{"Question": "YELL + PLAN = HAPPY", "Answer": "4355 + 8529 = 12884"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LEAD = HELLO", "Answer": "4668 + 9326 = 13994"}
{"Question": "FEED + TRUE = OFFER", "Answer": "4662 + 9806 = 14468"}
{"Question": "BEER + MINE = DRAMA", "Answer": "8773 + 4267 = 13040"}
{"Question": "FEEL + RATE = LATER", "Answer": "4771 + 8307 = 13078"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SAFE = FALSE", "Answer": "4770 + 8317 = 13087"}
{"Question": "DATA + BEAR = TRADE", "Answer": "9717 + 4073 = 13790"}
{"Question": "FEED + ABLE = BLADE", "Answer": "4770 + 9137 = 13907"}
{"Question": "SEED + TUBE = BASIS", "Answer": "4886 + 7518 = 12404"}
{"Question": "ODDS + HEAD = DEATH", "Answer": "5116 + 7231 = 12347"}
{"Question": "BEER + LAKE = EARLY", "Answer": "5113 + 7261 = 12374"}
{"Question": "FLEE + YEAH = EARLY", "Answer": "5311 + 7126 = 12437"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "5161 + 7312 = 12473"}
{"Question": "BEER + TONE = ENTRY", "Answer": "5113 + 7621 = 12734"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ALSO = START", "Answer": "5339 + 7413 = 12752"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BITE = TIGHT", "Answer": "5338 + 9413 = 14751"}
{"Question": "HERE + OPEN = TROOP", "Answer": "5424 + 7349 = 12773"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ONCE = COLOR", "Answer": "9442 + 5814 = 15256"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SHOE = PHOTO", "Answer": "5663 + 7296 = 12959"}
{"Question": "FLEE + HERO = PROOF", "Answer": "5366 + 7629 = 12995"}
{"Question": "FREE + HELP = PROOF", "Answer": "7366 + 5641 = 13007"}
{"Question": "DEEP + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "5771 + 8407 = 14178"}
{"Question": "HALL + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8677 + 5741 = 14418"}
{"Question": "ROOF + AUTO = THREE", "Answer": "5882 + 7618 = 13500"}
{"Question": "FOOD + HERO = REFER", "Answer": "6229 + 8412 = 14641"}
{"Question": "BEER + HOPE = PORCH", "Answer": "6227 + 9512 = 15739"}
{"Question": "FEED + RACE = ORDER", "Answer": "9442 + 6804 = 16246"}
{"Question": "WEEK + HOLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "7552 + 6945 = 14497"}
{"Question": "CELL + ALSO = SPACE", "Answer": "8977 + 6712 = 15689"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HERO = EARTH", "Answer": "9225 + 7132 = 16357"}
{"Question": "SOON + HERO = NURSE", "Answer": "7221 + 9352 = 16573"}
{"Question": "PEER + ABLE = DRAMA", "Answer": "7335 + 8493 = 15828"}
{"Question": "BEER + PACE = HAPPY", "Answer": "7339 + 8543 = 15882"}
{"Question": "DOOR + AUTO = START", "Answer": "8552 + 9375 = 17927"}
{"Question": "NEED + NEED = GENE", "Answer": "1005 + 1005 = 2010"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MOOD = BOMB", "Answer": "1006 + 1006 = 2012"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ODDS = DATA", "Answer": "1227 + 1227 = 2454"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ODDS = BOSS", "Answer": "1550 + 1550 = 3100"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = ROLL", "Answer": "1883 + 1883 = 3766"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = GRAB", "Answer": "2336 + 2336 = 4672"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SEEM = BOMB", "Answer": "2337 + 2337 = 4674"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HEEL = EACH", "Answer": "2446 + 2446 = 4892"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOOK = OKAY", "Answer": "2448 + 2448 = 4896"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ROOM = MERE", "Answer": "3116 + 3116 = 6232"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEET = BOMB", "Answer": "3118 + 3118 = 6236"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = RACE", "Answer": "3226 + 3226 = 6452"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = EASY", "Answer": "3660 + 3660 = 7320"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = MASS", "Answer": "3661 + 3661 = 7322"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOOR = OVER", "Answer": "3770 + 3770 = 7540"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = LESS", "Answer": "3772 + 3772 = 7544"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = FAIL", "Answer": "4226 + 4226 = 8452"}
{"Question": "FEED + FEED = DATA", "Answer": "4338 + 4338 = 8676"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = TRUE", "Answer": "4663 + 4663 = 9326"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROOF = OCCUR", "Answer": "6118 + 6118 = 12236"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = HEART", "Answer": "6225 + 6225 = 12450"}
{"Question": "COOK + COOK = TOPIC", "Answer": "6228 + 6228 = 12456"}
{"Question": "COOK + COOK = LUCKY", "Answer": "6337 + 6337 = 12674"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEED = BASIS", "Answer": "6338 + 6338 = 12676"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEEP = RAPID", "Answer": "6448 + 6448 = 12896"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TOOL = ELECT", "Answer": "6553 + 6553 = 13106"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = YOUNG", "Answer": "6771 + 6771 = 13542"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = CROSS", "Answer": "6772 + 6772 = 13544"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEER = BRAND", "Answer": "6773 + 6773 = 13546"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = TODAY", "Answer": "6880 + 6880 = 13760"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOOM = MAYBE", "Answer": "6881 + 6881 = 13762"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FOOT = STAFF", "Answer": "6883 + 6883 = 13766"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEEP = SPEND", "Answer": "6993 + 6993 = 13986"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = APPLE", "Answer": "7226 + 7226 = 14452"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOOD = JUDGE", "Answer": "7336 + 7336 = 14672"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = TERMS", "Answer": "7448 + 7448 = 14896"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "7551 + 7551 = 15102"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = CRAZY", "Answer": "7880 + 7880 = 15760"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOT = TABLE", "Answer": "7881 + 7881 = 15762"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = GRASS", "Answer": "7883 + 7883 = 15766"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HEEL = EARTH", "Answer": "8119 + 8119 = 16238"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = ARGUE", "Answer": "8226 + 8226 = 16452"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEEP = APPLY", "Answer": "8336 + 8336 = 16672"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROOF = INNER", "Answer": "8339 + 8339 = 16678"}
{"Question": "ODDS + ODDS = SHOOT", "Answer": "8441 + 8441 = 16882"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = URBAN", "Answer": "8446 + 8446 = 16892"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEEN = ADAPT", "Answer": "8554 + 8554 = 17108"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOT = COAST", "Answer": "8770 + 8770 = 17540"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = REACH", "Answer": "8771 + 8771 = 17542"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOOR = BOARD", "Answer": "8774 + 8774 = 17548"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = DELAY", "Answer": "8990 + 8990 = 17980"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEED = GUESS", "Answer": "8994 + 8994 = 17988"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOT = OTHER", "Answer": "9118 + 9118 = 18236"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = CRAFT", "Answer": "9228 + 9228 = 18456"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEER = DRAMA", "Answer": "9338 + 9338 = 18676"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEED = LOOSE", "Answer": "9447 + 9447 = 18894"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALLY = PANEL", "Answer": "9884 + 9884 = 19768"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SEED = MESS", "Answer": "1002 + 1009 = 2011"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SEED = KISS", "Answer": "3116 + 3117 = 6233"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FOOT = ORDER", "Answer": "5112 + 5118 = 10230"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOM = TERMS", "Answer": "6441 + 6449 = 12890"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEEP = RAPID", "Answer": "6771 + 6775 = 13546"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FEED = BLADE", "Answer": "6773 + 6774 = 13547"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROOT = START", "Answer": "6880 + 6883 = 13763"}
{"Question": "FEED + FEEL = DRESS", "Answer": "6991 + 6997 = 13988"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOOK = OFTEN", "Answer": "7112 + 7118 = 14230"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = APPLE", "Answer": "7224 + 7228 = 14452"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOOT = MONTH", "Answer": "7441 + 7449 = 14890"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = PRICE", "Answer": "7661 + 7665 = 15326"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = BREAD", "Answer": "7992 + 7995 = 15987"}
{"Question": "FEED + FEEL = ELITE", "Answer": "8115 + 8116 = 16231"}
{"Question": "COOL + COOK = LUCKY", "Answer": "8441 + 8449 = 16890"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = PAUSE", "Answer": "8661 + 8665 = 17326"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = PROUD", "Answer": "8661 + 8667 = 17328"}
{"Question": "FEED + FEEL = LEGAL", "Answer": "8770 + 8771 = 17541"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEEP = REPLY", "Answer": "8771 + 8775 = 17546"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FEED = LEAVE", "Answer": "8771 + 8776 = 17547"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROOT = VOTER", "Answer": "8773 + 8775 = 17548"}
{"Question": "POOL + POOR = WORLD", "Answer": "8774 + 8775 = 17549"}
{"Question": "COOL + COOK = KNOCK", "Answer": "8990 + 8991 = 17981"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROOF = OFTEN", "Answer": "9112 + 9118 = 18230"}
{"Question": "COOK + COOL = ELITE", "Answer": "9223 + 9228 = 18451"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEER = ARGUE", "Answer": "9335 + 9338 = 18673"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = EASE", "Answer": "1226 + 1266 = 2492"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = NONE", "Answer": "1994 + 1944 = 3938"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = ELSE", "Answer": "2337 + 2377 = 4714"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6221 + 6211 = 12432"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = BEACH", "Answer": "6223 + 6233 = 12456"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = FEWER", "Answer": "6229 + 6299 = 12528"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6441 + 6411 = 12852"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = FIFTH", "Answer": "6558 + 6588 = 13146"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = BASIS", "Answer": "6772 + 6722 = 13494"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = COLOR", "Answer": "6775 + 6755 = 13530"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = AGREE", "Answer": "6889 + 6899 = 13788"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = FLESH", "Answer": "6993 + 6933 = 13926"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = LOOSE", "Answer": "7221 + 7211 = 14432"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7224 + 7244 = 14468"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = LIMIT", "Answer": "7331 + 7311 = 14642"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = FENCE", "Answer": "7442 + 7422 = 14864"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = COACH", "Answer": "7446 + 7466 = 14912"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = COLOR", "Answer": "7449 + 7499 = 14948"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = CLEAN", "Answer": "8006 + 8066 = 16072"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = ALIVE", "Answer": "8226 + 8266 = 16492"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLL = ELECT", "Answer": "8557 + 8577 = 17134"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = CLASS", "Answer": "8667 + 8677 = 17344"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELL = BELOW", "Answer": "8775 + 8755 = 17530"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = ELSE", "Answer": "1224 + 1248 = 2472"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = TEEN", "Answer": "1332 + 1328 = 2660"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = DIET", "Answer": "1339 + 1392 = 2731"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = SEEM", "Answer": "1443 + 1438 = 2881"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = DEAD", "Answer": "1553 + 1530 = 3083"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = PIPE", "Answer": "1885 + 1853 = 3738"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TOSS = SALT", "Answer": "2338 + 2344 = 4682"}
{"Question": "MEET + MESS = TREE", "Answer": "2334 + 2399 = 4733"}
{"Question": "SOON + SONG = ODDS", "Answer": "2443 + 2439 = 4882"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = FLOW", "Answer": "3446 + 3499 = 6945"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = HEEL", "Answer": "4332 + 4328 = 8660"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = BEER", "Answer": "4556 + 4561 = 9117"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLL = THERE", "Answer": "5221 + 5233 = 10454"}
{"Question": "SEED + SELL = TASTE", "Answer": "5224 + 5288 = 10512"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SELL = MOUSE", "Answer": "5331 + 5322 = 10653"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = DRAMA", "Answer": "5441 + 5417 = 10858"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = TASTE", "Answer": "5446 + 5468 = 10914"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = OFFER", "Answer": "6112 + 6144 = 12256"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOSS = SORRY", "Answer": "6229 + 6211 = 12440"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = FENCE", "Answer": "6224 + 6248 = 12472"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = HONOR", "Answer": "6227 + 6299 = 12526"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLL = METER", "Answer": "6449 + 6477 = 12926"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = SPACE", "Answer": "6552 + 6523 = 13075"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = ELECT", "Answer": "6557 + 6571 = 13128"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = VIDEO", "Answer": "6775 + 6752 = 13527"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = HAPPY", "Answer": "6778 + 6781 = 13559"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOSS = SHALL", "Answer": "6889 + 6811 = 13700"}
{"Question": "POOR + PORT = TRUTH", "Answer": "6883 + 6831 = 13714"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = FEWER", "Answer": "6881 + 6855 = 13736"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = DANCE", "Answer": "6887 + 6871 = 13758"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TOSS = CLOCK", "Answer": "6993 + 6922 = 13915"}
{"Question": "SOON + SONG = GHOST", "Answer": "6997 + 6971 = 13968"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = PIECE", "Answer": "6998 + 6981 = 13979"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = OTHER", "Answer": "7114 + 7142 = 14256"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = ISSUE", "Answer": "7223 + 7239 = 14462"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = ALLOW", "Answer": "7224 + 7245 = 14469"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOSS = STATE", "Answer": "7334 + 7311 = 14645"}
{"Question": "SOON + SONG = LEGAL", "Answer": "7335 + 7356 = 14691"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = DOUBT", "Answer": "7443 + 7430 = 14873"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = SORRY", "Answer": "7443 + 7439 = 14882"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "7448 + 7499 = 14947"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = DEATH", "Answer": "7552 + 7521 = 15073"}
{"Question": "POOR + PORT = TOTAL", "Answer": "7558 + 7581 = 15139"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "7559 + 7588 = 15147"}
{"Question": "POOR + PORT = STRIP", "Answer": "7662 + 7625 = 15287"}
{"Question": "COOL + COLD = SALES", "Answer": "7663 + 7638 = 15301"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = LEMON", "Answer": "7889 + 7895 = 15784"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = FLESH", "Answer": "7995 + 7952 = 15947"}
{"Question": "MEET + MESS = THEME", "Answer": "7991 + 7988 = 15979"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLL = STORE", "Answer": "8006 + 8077 = 16083"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TELL = ELITE", "Answer": "8115 + 8166 = 16281"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BOSS = SHEET", "Answer": "8229 + 8211 = 16440"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOSS = SALAD", "Answer": "8449 + 8411 = 16860"}
{"Question": "BEER + BELL = CLIMB", "Answer": "8442 + 8466 = 16908"}
{"Question": "POOL + POLE = BELOW", "Answer": "8449 + 8496 = 16945"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TOSS = SALES", "Answer": "8550 + 8511 = 17061"}
{"Question": "POOR + PORT = METER", "Answer": "8552 + 8520 = 17072"}
{"Question": "COOL + COLD = DANCE", "Answer": "8553 + 8531 = 17084"}
{"Question": "COOL + COLD = FENCE", "Answer": "8553 + 8534 = 17087"}
{"Question": "COOL + COLD = ADAPT", "Answer": "8556 + 8567 = 17123"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MODE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8557 + 8579 = 17136"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ROLL = LIMIT", "Answer": "8662 + 8611 = 17273"}
{"Question": "SEED + SELL = FALSE", "Answer": "8664 + 8622 = 17286"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = SHALL", "Answer": "8665 + 8657 = 17322"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = STEEL", "Answer": "8667 + 8672 = 17339"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLL = ELITE", "Answer": "8664 + 8677 = 17341"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = HOTEL", "Answer": "8775 + 8751 = 17526"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLL = SOLAR", "Answer": "8773 + 8755 = 17528"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = LEVEL", "Answer": "8779 + 8792 = 17571"}
{"Question": "BEER + BELL = TREAT", "Answer": "9008 + 9033 = 18041"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOTH = CHEEK", "Answer": "9332 + 9328 = 18660"}
{"Question": "BEER + BELL = TRIBE", "Answer": "9338 + 9355 = 18693"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEND = STATE", "Answer": "9772 + 9725 = 19497"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = PHASE", "Answer": "9776 + 9761 = 19537"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLL = TRUTH", "Answer": "9881 + 9833 = 19714"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = SHAPE", "Answer": "9885 + 9853 = 19738"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HELP = PHOTO", "Answer": "9886 + 9861 = 19747"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = ONTO", "Answer": "1226 + 1236 = 2462"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = EASE", "Answer": "1226 + 1246 = 2472"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = EASE", "Answer": "1226 + 1286 = 2512"}
{"Question": "POOR + POUR = HERE", "Answer": "1338 + 1348 = 2686"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = AUTO", "Answer": "1447 + 1427 = 2874"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = EDGE", "Answer": "2337 + 2387 = 4724"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = ODDS", "Answer": "2448 + 2438 = 4886"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = TALL", "Answer": "2665 + 2635 = 5300"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = DATA", "Answer": "3227 + 3247 = 6474"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAR = FADE", "Answer": "3442 + 3492 = 6934"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = ABLE", "Answer": "3668 + 3678 = 7346"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = LACK", "Answer": "4118 + 4128 = 8246"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WORD = GROW", "Answer": "4552 + 4502 = 9054"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOCK = CALL", "Answer": "4552 + 4592 = 9144"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAT = LATER", "Answer": "5224 + 5204 = 10428"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WORD = FEWER", "Answer": "5224 + 5284 = 10508"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "5338 + 5348 = 10686"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = MAYBE", "Answer": "5446 + 5406 = 10852"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = MAYBE", "Answer": "5447 + 5407 = 10854"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = SORRY", "Answer": "5448 + 5438 = 10886"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WORD = OCCUR", "Answer": "6114 + 6184 = 12298"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = UNCLE", "Answer": "6339 + 6359 = 12698"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = ARGUE", "Answer": "6442 + 6412 = 12854"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "6447 + 6427 = 12874"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = EARTH", "Answer": "6559 + 6539 = 13098"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOCK = SKILL", "Answer": "6773 + 6793 = 13566"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = STEEL", "Answer": "6774 + 6784 = 13558"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WORD = ORDER", "Answer": "7112 + 7142 = 14254"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = DOUBT", "Answer": "7440 + 7430 = 14870"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "7441 + 7431 = 14872"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = REACH", "Answer": "7441 + 7491 = 14932"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = NERVE", "Answer": "7442 + 7412 = 14854"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = FENCE", "Answer": "7442 + 7492 = 14934"}
{"Question": "POOR + POUR = SORRY", "Answer": "7448 + 7438 = 14886"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = MODEL", "Answer": "7449 + 7489 = 14938"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "7665 + 7615 = 15280"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "7665 + 7635 = 15300"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAR = GUIDE", "Answer": "7668 + 7608 = 15276"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BOAT = TABLE", "Answer": "7881 + 7851 = 15732"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = BLOCK", "Answer": "8006 + 8076 = 16082"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "8112 + 8162 = 16274"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = SALAD", "Answer": "8220 + 8240 = 16460"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "8224 + 8204 = 16428"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = TRIBE", "Answer": "8226 + 8256 = 16482"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WORD = ALLOW", "Answer": "8334 + 8304 = 16638"}
{"Question": "WEEK + WEAK = ALLOW", "Answer": "8339 + 8319 = 16658"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAT = LIMIT", "Answer": "8440 + 8420 = 16860"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = START", "Answer": "8443 + 8493 = 16936"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = LIMIT", "Answer": "8556 + 8516 = 17072"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = SLICE", "Answer": "8557 + 8527 = 17084"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOLD = ADAPT", "Answer": "8557 + 8567 = 17124"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = HAPPY", "Answer": "8662 + 8672 = 17334"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = ALONE", "Answer": "9008 + 9018 = 18026"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = DRESS", "Answer": "9008 + 9058 = 18066"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "9221 + 9281 = 18502"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = ORDER", "Answer": "9224 + 9204 = 18428"}
{"Question": "COOL + COAL = PEACE", "Answer": "9334 + 9364 = 18698"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = ONION", "Answer": "9334 + 9384 = 18718"}
{"Question": "POOR + POUR = DRAMA", "Answer": "9338 + 9308 = 18646"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "9442 + 9452 = 18894"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAR = ABOVE", "Answer": "9663 + 9613 = 19276"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEND = ASIDE", "Answer": "9884 + 9864 = 19748"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROPE = PEER", "Answer": "1335 + 1326 = 2661"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERO = ROLL", "Answer": "1558 + 1530 = 3088"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MOST = ODDS", "Answer": "2448 + 2435 = 4883"}
{"Question": "NEED + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "3771 + 3752 = 7523"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAN = NAME", "Answer": "4113 + 4128 = 8241"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "5227 + 5281 = 10508"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROAD = FAVOR", "Answer": "5331 + 5304 = 10635"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOTS = SHALL", "Answer": "5334 + 5321 = 10655"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "5339 + 5316 = 10655"}
{"Question": "COOL + CODE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5441 + 5460 = 10901"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MOVE = VIDEO", "Answer": "5448 + 5416 = 10864"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLE = OFFER", "Answer": "6112 + 6134 = 12246"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERO = ERROR", "Answer": "6118 + 6124 = 12242"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ROLE = OFFER", "Answer": "6119 + 6157 = 12276"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOWN = WORRY", "Answer": "6224 + 6219 = 12443"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ROAD = MARRY", "Answer": "6331 + 6329 = 12660"}
{"Question": "COOL + COME = SMELL", "Answer": "6558 + 6530 = 13088"}
{"Question": "COOL + COME = LEMON", "Answer": "6551 + 6503 = 13054"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FORM = DRAMA", "Answer": "6551 + 6539 = 13090"}
{"Question": "POOL + POSE = ELECT", "Answer": "6553 + 6571 = 13124"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAN = TITLE", "Answer": "6551 + 6574 = 13125"}
{"Question": "BEER + BELT = RURAL", "Answer": "6551 + 6598 = 13149"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DENY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6552 + 6593 = 13145"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOTH = THEME", "Answer": "6557 + 6513 = 13070"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BORN = ENEMY", "Answer": "6554 + 6593 = 13147"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MORE = DREAM", "Answer": "6771 + 6735 = 13506"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLE = ENTER", "Answer": "6775 + 6741 = 13516"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FOUR = DRAFT", "Answer": "6771 + 6793 = 13564"}
{"Question": "NEED + NEWS = TASTE", "Answer": "6772 + 6745 = 13517"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6778 + 6753 = 13531"}
{"Question": "COOL + COPE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6773 + 6785 = 13558"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAN = TRIBE", "Answer": "6773 + 6794 = 13567"}
{"Question": "ROOM + ROSE = SMELL", "Answer": "6883 + 6817 = 13700"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAR = PRESS", "Answer": "6991 + 6953 = 13944"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7002 + 7018 = 14020"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAN = ENTER", "Answer": "7112 + 7104 = 14216"}
{"Question": "BEER + BELT = ELITE", "Answer": "7115 + 7146 = 14261"}
{"Question": "COOK + CORE = ORDER", "Answer": "7118 + 7146 = 14264"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BONE = INNER", "Answer": "7223 + 7246 = 14469"}
{"Question": "COOL + CODE = ALLOW", "Answer": "7224 + 7205 = 14429"}
{"Question": "SOON + SORT = ENTER", "Answer": "7224 + 7295 = 14519"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOAT = MAYBE", "Answer": "7331 + 7348 = 14679"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FEAR = RIFLE", "Answer": "7332 + 7391 = 14723"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAT = WRITE", "Answer": "7334 + 7359 = 14693"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "7449 + 7431 = 14880"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HEAD = DEATH", "Answer": "7446 + 7491 = 14937"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOWN = WOUND", "Answer": "7442 + 7415 = 14857"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALSO = BLOOD", "Answer": "7442 + 7438 = 14880"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOWN = WORLD", "Answer": "7448 + 7419 = 14867"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FOLK = TOTAL", "Answer": "7551 + 7598 = 15149"}
{"Question": "COOK + COPE = PIECE", "Answer": "7660 + 7612 = 15272"}
{"Question": "COOK + COPE = PEACE", "Answer": "7660 + 7615 = 15275"}
{"Question": "POOR + POET = STRIP", "Answer": "7662 + 7635 = 15297"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOTH = MIGHT", "Answer": "7881 + 7809 = 15690"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROSE = TERMS", "Answer": "7881 + 7865 = 15746"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HERO = ROUGH", "Answer": "7882 + 7815 = 15697"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "7883 + 7895 = 15778"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GOAL = ALONG", "Answer": "7992 + 7915 = 15907"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAR = TREND", "Answer": "7992 + 7945 = 15937"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FORM = ORDER", "Answer": "8112 + 8164 = 16276"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "8112 + 8167 = 16279"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAL = ELITE", "Answer": "8115 + 8136 = 16251"}
{"Question": "MOON + MOVE = NEVER", "Answer": "8221 + 8246 = 16467"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLE = FIBER", "Answer": "8221 + 8257 = 16478"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROSE = STEEL", "Answer": "8226 + 8214 = 16440"}
{"Question": "FEED + FEAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "8331 + 8376 = 16707"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOWL = CLIMB", "Answer": "8332 + 8396 = 16728"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "8336 + 8317 = 16653"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FOUR = REFER", "Answer": "8440 + 8421 = 16861"}
{"Question": "DEER + DEAL = RAPID", "Answer": "8441 + 8467 = 16908"}
{"Question": "POOL + POSE = SHELL", "Answer": "8556 + 8510 = 17066"}
{"Question": "POOR + POSE = SERVE", "Answer": "8550 + 8517 = 17067"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAL = PRIDE", "Answer": "8551 + 8534 = 17085"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BONE = ENEMY", "Answer": "8552 + 8571 = 17123"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TONE = ELECT", "Answer": "8557 + 8591 = 17148"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DOWN = AWARD", "Answer": "8552 + 8576 = 17128"}
{"Question": "SOON + SOUP = ADAPT", "Answer": "8552 + 8594 = 17146"}
{"Question": "POOR + POLE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8554 + 8517 = 17071"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BOAT = MARRY", "Answer": "8661 + 8674 = 17335"}
{"Question": "COOK + COPE = SPEED", "Answer": "8662 + 8673 = 17335"}
{"Question": "POOR + POLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "8665 + 8673 = 17338"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BONE = MONEY", "Answer": "8771 + 8752 = 17523"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FEAR = LEAVE", "Answer": "8771 + 8756 = 17527"}
{"Question": "ROOT + ROLE = VOTER", "Answer": "8775 + 8763 = 17538"}
{"Question": "SEED + SELF = REFER", "Answer": "8776 + 8795 = 17571"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ALSO = LOCAL", "Answer": "9113 + 9178 = 18291"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEAT = RATIO", "Answer": "9221 + 9285 = 18506"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LOVE = SHELL", "Answer": "9225 + 9274 = 18499"}
{"Question": "POOR + POEM = DRAMA", "Answer": "9228 + 9236 = 18464"}
{"Question": "MEET + MEAL = TASTE", "Answer": "9331 + 9382 = 18713"}
{"Question": "BEER + BEST = STARE", "Answer": "9335 + 9318 = 18653"}
{"Question": "NEED + NEAR = DANCE", "Answer": "9441 + 9483 = 18924"}
{"Question": "COOK + CORE = INNER", "Answer": "9445 + 9427 = 18872"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "9448 + 9416 = 18864"}
{"Question": "SEED + SEAT = ASIDE", "Answer": "9557 + 9518 = 19075"}
{"Question": "ROOF + ROLE = FRESH", "Answer": "9771 + 9735 = 19506"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HEAD = SHADE", "Answer": "9883 + 9875 = 19758"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TEAR = START", "Answer": "9884 + 9875 = 19759"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = ONTO", "Answer": "1227 + 1725 = 2952"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = EVEN", "Answer": "2771 + 2170 = 4941"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = THERE", "Answer": "5662 + 5267 = 10929"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = RATIO", "Answer": "6335 + 6538 = 12873"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = COAST", "Answer": "6337 + 6732 = 13069"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = BOARD", "Answer": "6337 + 6739 = 13076"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = PRICE", "Answer": "6552 + 6251 = 12803"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = SENSE", "Answer": "6554 + 6459 = 13013"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = PHOTO", "Answer": "6779 + 6978 = 13757"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = PRIDE", "Answer": "6883 + 6381 = 13264"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = LEVEL", "Answer": "7228 + 7823 = 15051"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = STAFF", "Answer": "7332 + 7234 = 14566"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = START", "Answer": "7449 + 7946 = 15395"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = SPEND", "Answer": "7553 + 7354 = 14907"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "7559 + 7951 = 15510"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = GRASS", "Answer": "7665 + 7568 = 15233"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = AVOID", "Answer": "7669 + 7968 = 15637"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = PRESS", "Answer": "7885 + 7581 = 15466"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = WHOSE", "Answer": "7889 + 7981 = 15870"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = CRACK", "Answer": "8557 + 8759 = 17316"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = WHEEL", "Answer": "8665 + 8560 = 17225"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLOT = HOTEL", "Answer": "8772 + 8270 = 17042"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = ORDER", "Answer": "9118 + 9810 = 18928"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DROP = ADAPT", "Answer": "9338 + 9837 = 19175"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = BASIS", "Answer": "9553 + 9356 = 18909"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNOW = TASTE", "Answer": "9553 + 9357 = 18910"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = THEM", "Answer": "2935 + 2359 = 5294"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = KNEE", "Answer": "3764 + 3647 = 7411"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = KISS", "Answer": "4985 + 4859 = 9844"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = VISIT", "Answer": "5409 + 5094 = 10503"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = SALAD", "Answer": "5809 + 5098 = 10907"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = ASSET", "Answer": "6019 + 6190 = 12209"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOWL = ONION", "Answer": "6319 + 6193 = 12512"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6918 + 6189 = 13107"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = RAPID", "Answer": "6521 + 6215 = 12736"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = LABEL", "Answer": "6724 + 6247 = 12971"}
{"Question": "WEAK + WAKE = FEWER", "Answer": "6238 + 6382 = 12620"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = ERROR", "Answer": "6845 + 6458 = 13303"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6253 + 6532 = 12785"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOWL = NEWLY", "Answer": "6752 + 6527 = 13279"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = FIGHT", "Answer": "6079 + 6790 = 12869"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = ELITE", "Answer": "6972 + 6729 = 13701"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = DRAMA", "Answer": "6978 + 6789 = 13767"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOWL = SLEEP", "Answer": "6384 + 6843 = 13227"}
{"Question": "SKIN + SINK = BASIS", "Answer": "6789 + 6897 = 13686"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = ENEMY", "Answer": "6197 + 6971 = 13168"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = COACH", "Answer": "7928 + 7289 = 15217"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = SALES", "Answer": "7348 + 7483 = 14831"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "7064 + 7640 = 14704"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = CLOCK", "Answer": "7365 + 7653 = 15018"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = LEVEL", "Answer": "7586 + 7865 = 15451"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = TREND", "Answer": "7295 + 7952 = 15247"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = METAL", "Answer": "8629 + 8296 = 16925"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = METER", "Answer": "8752 + 8527 = 17279"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOWL = ELITE", "Answer": "8754 + 8547 = 17301"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = UNDER", "Answer": "8073 + 8730 = 16803"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = MATCH", "Answer": "8573 + 8735 = 17308"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOWL = TOOTH", "Answer": "8973 + 8739 = 17712"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MALE = ALLOW", "Answer": "9618 + 9186 = 18804"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HATE = ERROR", "Answer": "9167 + 9671 = 18838"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARE = INNER", "Answer": "9073 + 9730 = 18803"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DATE = TALE", "Answer": "1970 + 1739 = 3709"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BAKE = AREA", "Answer": "2549 + 2405 = 4954"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SKIN = KISS", "Answer": "4229 + 4915 = 9144"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DRAG = EDGE", "Answer": "4558 + 4861 = 9419"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = SALAD", "Answer": "5708 + 5097 = 10805"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "5113 + 5304 = 10417"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "5327 + 5203 = 10530"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DRAG = HELLO", "Answer": "5224 + 5438 = 10662"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FACE = REFER", "Answer": "5041 + 5460 = 10501"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAT = WATER", "Answer": "5442 + 5206 = 10648"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "5176 + 5791 = 10967"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MALE = ALTER", "Answer": "6314 + 6123 = 12437"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DATE = ARMED", "Answer": "6412 + 6134 = 12546"}
{"Question": "MOON + MERE = OWNER", "Answer": "6118 + 6757 = 12875"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TAKE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6917 + 6189 = 13106"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = READY", "Answer": "6221 + 6139 = 12360"}
{"Question": "BELT + BLUE = ELITE", "Answer": "6120 + 6281 = 12401"}
{"Question": "READ + RACE = EAGER", "Answer": "6125 + 6291 = 12416"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = EAGER", "Answer": "6128 + 6291 = 12419"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DATA = TODAY", "Answer": "6229 + 6414 = 12643"}
{"Question": "REAL + RACE = LATER", "Answer": "6521 + 6235 = 12756"}
{"Question": "DEER + DROP = HELLO", "Answer": "6225 + 6549 = 12774"}
{"Question": "LEAN + LAKE = PANEL", "Answer": "6729 + 6247 = 12976"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HAVE = FIFTH", "Answer": "6927 + 6249 = 13176"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SKIN = KNIFE", "Answer": "6331 + 6142 = 12473"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = GRAVE", "Answer": "6332 + 6251 = 12583"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DATA = RADIO", "Answer": "6331 + 6272 = 12603"}
{"Question": "TERM + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "6231 + 6392 = 12623"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLAN = SENSE", "Answer": "6334 + 6478 = 12812"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TALE = LARGE", "Answer": "6730 + 6317 = 13047"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DATE = METER", "Answer": "6248 + 6472 = 12720"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6249 + 6472 = 12721"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNAP = HAPPY", "Answer": "6443 + 6327 = 12770"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GENE = INDEX", "Answer": "6442 + 6838 = 13280"}
{"Question": "STAR + SALT = LOOSE", "Answer": "6948 + 6419 = 13367"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DATA = PAINT", "Answer": "6551 + 6232 = 12783"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DATA = SALAD", "Answer": "6554 + 6272 = 12826"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = GRASS", "Answer": "6552 + 6281 = 12833"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAT = PLATE", "Answer": "6552 + 6283 = 12835"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNAP = PLANE", "Answer": "6557 + 6721 = 13278"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HAVE = TIGHT", "Answer": "6071 + 6790 = 12861"}
{"Question": "COOL + CLUE = FENCE", "Answer": "6770 + 6092 = 12862"}
{"Question": "COOL + CLUE = PIECE", "Answer": "6770 + 6098 = 12868"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TAPE = EMPTY", "Answer": "6172 + 6791 = 12963"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TALE = RELAX", "Answer": "6371 + 6703 = 13074"}
{"Question": "COOL + CLUE = ELECT", "Answer": "6773 + 6391 = 13164"}
{"Question": "MOON + MERE = INNER", "Answer": "6773 + 6585 = 13358"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DATA = PAPER", "Answer": "6881 + 6303 = 13184"}
{"Question": "SHIP + SIGH = THESE", "Answer": "6389 + 6873 = 13262"}
{"Question": "STEP + SEAT = APPLE", "Answer": "6583 + 6815 = 13398"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAT = CATCH", "Answer": "6885 + 6534 = 13419"}
{"Question": "COOL + CLUB = PIECE", "Answer": "6885 + 6579 = 13464"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = UNDER", "Answer": "6782 + 6897 = 13679"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = LOVER", "Answer": "6981 + 6809 = 13790"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DRAG = AVOID", "Answer": "6889 + 6917 = 13806"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "7512 + 7145 = 14657"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SAME = METER", "Answer": "7426 + 7214 = 14640"}
{"Question": "POOL + PLAN = HAPPY", "Answer": "7225 + 7548 = 14773"}
{"Question": "REAL + RACE = COLOR", "Answer": "7235 + 7312 = 14547"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "7238 + 7312 = 14550"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "7439 + 7324 = 14763"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HAVE = EARTH", "Answer": "7146 + 7421 = 14567"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TAKE = EARTH", "Answer": "7145 + 7431 = 14576"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DRUG = ROUND", "Answer": "7441 + 7156 = 14597"}
{"Question": "PEAK + PAGE = EAGER", "Answer": "7149 + 7461 = 14610"}
{"Question": "DEER + DATA = TERMS", "Answer": "7446 + 7212 = 14658"}
{"Question": "PEAK + PACE = CARRY", "Answer": "7248 + 7412 = 14660"}
{"Question": "NEAR + NAME = PANEL", "Answer": "7243 + 7482 = 14725"}
{"Question": "STEP + SEAT = PEACE", "Answer": "7341 + 7483 = 14824"}
{"Question": "COOL + CLUB = WOULD", "Answer": "7443 + 7389 = 14832"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DATA = TREAT", "Answer": "7445 + 7616 = 15061"}
{"Question": "DEER + DROP = POUND", "Answer": "7446 + 7651 = 15097"}
{"Question": "DEER + DATA = TRIBE", "Answer": "7445 + 7919 = 15364"}
{"Question": "DEER + DATA = BROAD", "Answer": "7554 + 7383 = 14937"}
{"Question": "DEER + DROP = PRIDE", "Answer": "7554 + 7421 = 14975"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DARE = PAPER", "Answer": "7654 + 7506 = 15160"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BAKE = NAKED", "Answer": "7851 + 7538 = 15389"}
{"Question": "MEAN + MALE = PANEL", "Answer": "7954 + 7539 = 15493"}
{"Question": "MOON + MERE = ENTER", "Answer": "7664 + 7151 = 14815"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BASE = SORRY", "Answer": "7268 + 7612 = 14880"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GENE = SEVEN", "Answer": "7664 + 7595 = 15259"}
{"Question": "SOON + SNAP = APPLE", "Answer": "7669 + 7915 = 15584"}
{"Question": "SPOT + SOUP = TRUST", "Answer": "7081 + 7890 = 14971"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HATE = IRISH", "Answer": "7285 + 7862 = 15147"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = ARGUE", "Answer": "7885 + 7513 = 15398"}
{"Question": "PEER + PRAY = DRAMA", "Answer": "7885 + 7549 = 15434"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DATE = TREND", "Answer": "7295 + 7912 = 15207"}
{"Question": "NEAR + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "7295 + 7932 = 15227"}
{"Question": "DEER + DATA = BRAND", "Answer": "7995 + 7242 = 15237"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAG = ERROR", "Answer": "8114 + 8492 = 16606"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DATE = TIRED", "Answer": "8325 + 8213 = 16538"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAG = RANGE", "Answer": "8223 + 8369 = 16592"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TAKE = METER", "Answer": "8621 + 8246 = 16867"}
{"Question": "PEAK + PAGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8625 + 8296 = 16921"}
{"Question": "MOON + MERE = SENSE", "Answer": "8220 + 8797 = 17017"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = AGAIN", "Answer": "8229 + 8917 = 17146"}
{"Question": "SEEK + SKIN = NOISE", "Answer": "8332 + 8251 = 16583"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = TASTE", "Answer": "8553 + 8362 = 16915"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = AWARD", "Answer": "8556 + 8612 = 17168"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAG = APART", "Answer": "8556 + 8613 = 17169"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MERE = REFER", "Answer": "8554 + 8717 = 17271"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MERE = UNDER", "Answer": "8554 + 8939 = 17493"}
{"Question": "REAL + RACE = EARLY", "Answer": "8163 + 8671 = 16834"}
{"Question": "BELT + BLUE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8561 + 8635 = 17196"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRAW = GRASS", "Answer": "8667 + 8732 = 17399"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DATE = ORDER", "Answer": "8076 + 8730 = 16806"}
{"Question": "READ + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "8375 + 8763 = 17138"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DATA = SORRY", "Answer": "8772 + 8454 = 17226"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HAVE = CATCH", "Answer": "8573 + 8745 = 17318"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BASE = TASTE", "Answer": "8670 + 8746 = 17416"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8672 + 8746 = 17418"}
{"Question": "MEAN + MALE = LABEL", "Answer": "8972 + 8719 = 17691"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9332 + 9281 = 18613"}
{"Question": "READ + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "9143 + 9451 = 18594"}
{"Question": "DEER + DROP = SPORT", "Answer": "9442 + 9278 = 18720"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GENE = INNER", "Answer": "9447 + 9383 = 18830"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "9554 + 9383 = 18937"}
{"Question": "PEER + PRAY = APART", "Answer": "9556 + 9612 = 19168"}
{"Question": "DEER + DRUG = JUDGE", "Answer": "9662 + 9284 = 18946"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FLAT = OFTEN", "Answer": "9884 + 9402 = 19286"}
{"Question": "READ + RACE = ORDER", "Answer": "9584 + 9875 = 19459"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = LESS", "Answer": "1883 + 1983 = 3866"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = HATE", "Answer": "3668 + 3768 = 7436"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = PHOTO", "Answer": "5779 + 5079 = 10858"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = HEART", "Answer": "6228 + 6128 = 12356"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = RURAL", "Answer": "6770 + 6370 = 13140"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = CLASS", "Answer": "6772 + 6072 = 12844"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = STAFF", "Answer": "6883 + 6083 = 12966"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = HONOR", "Answer": "7223 + 7123 = 14346"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = IRISH", "Answer": "7334 + 7834 = 15168"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = FIFTY", "Answer": "7336 + 7836 = 15172"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = CROSS", "Answer": "7883 + 7083 = 14966"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = LIMIT", "Answer": "8334 + 8234 = 16568"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEN = CIVIL", "Answer": "8335 + 8935 = 17270"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FUEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "9221 + 9621 = 18842"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = ONTO", "Answer": "2445 + 2149 = 4594"}
{"Question": "SOON + STOP = ONTO", "Answer": "3772 + 3475 = 7247"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GROW = WRONG", "Answer": "5334 + 5031 = 10365"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "5336 + 5037 = 10373"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ABLE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6118 + 6913 = 13031"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOE = HONEY", "Answer": "6223 + 6124 = 12347"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = THESE", "Answer": "6334 + 6231 = 12565"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ABLE = CLEAN", "Answer": "6335 + 6932 = 13267"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DIET = TOOTH", "Answer": "6559 + 6751 = 13310"}
{"Question": "FEED + FUEL = VALUE", "Answer": "6775 + 6472 = 13247"}
{"Question": "COOK + CROP = KNOCK", "Answer": "6881 + 6980 = 13861"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THEM = ENEMY", "Answer": "7114 + 7012 = 14126"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7225 + 7921 = 15146"}
{"Question": "SEED + STEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "7225 + 7924 = 15149"}
{"Question": "COOL + CROP = LOCAL", "Answer": "7441 + 7340 = 14781"}
{"Question": "SEEM + STEP = TERMS", "Answer": "7449 + 7148 = 14597"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = TRUTH", "Answer": "7559 + 7051 = 14610"}
{"Question": "COOK + CROP = TOPIC", "Answer": "7553 + 7854 = 15407"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DIET = SPEND", "Answer": "7885 + 7982 = 15867"}
{"Question": "PEER + POEM = TROOP", "Answer": "7995 + 7892 = 15887"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DIET = STATE", "Answer": "8336 + 8937 = 17273"}
{"Question": "SEED + STEP = ADOPT", "Answer": "8447 + 8649 = 17096"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = TASTE", "Answer": "8559 + 8251 = 16810"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BLOW = MODEL", "Answer": "8661 + 8069 = 16730"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BLOW = TOTAL", "Answer": "8771 + 8372 = 17143"}
{"Question": "SEED + STEP = DEPTH", "Answer": "8771 + 8472 = 17243"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHOT = ENTER", "Answer": "9558 + 9056 = 18614"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = ODDS", "Answer": "1225 + 1655 = 2880"}
{"Question": "CALL + COAL = ALSO", "Answer": "1277 + 1427 = 2704"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = LEFT", "Answer": "1288 + 1528 = 2816"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = BOMB", "Answer": "2117 + 2077 = 4194"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FALL = LIFE", "Answer": "2884 + 2044 = 4928"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HILL = THAT", "Answer": "3228 + 3088 = 6316"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FULL = BLUE", "Answer": "3447 + 3277 = 6724"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = LESS", "Answer": "3677 + 3067 = 6744"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = ALSO", "Answer": "4221 + 4911 = 9132"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = NONE", "Answer": "4225 + 4055 = 8280"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = COOL", "Answer": "4266 + 4726 = 8992"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALL = FLAT", "Answer": "4552 + 4722 = 9274"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "5337 + 5177 = 10514"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALL = RATIO", "Answer": "5447 + 5077 = 10524"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = RADIO", "Answer": "5884 + 5044 = 10928"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "6133 + 6913 = 13046"}
{"Question": "FREE + FIRE = ERROR", "Answer": "6211 + 6021 = 12232"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALL = ELECT", "Answer": "6223 + 6933 = 13156"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = EARTH", "Answer": "6255 + 6125 = 12380"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = SOLVE", "Answer": "6227 + 6477 = 12704"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = ELECT", "Answer": "6311 + 6831 = 13142"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = TOOTH", "Answer": "6337 + 6977 = 13314"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALL = ALTER", "Answer": "6552 + 6122 = 12674"}
{"Question": "POOL + PULL = SLEEP", "Answer": "6773 + 6233 = 13006"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HALL = FLESH", "Answer": "6773 + 6933 = 13706"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FALL = PAPER", "Answer": "6779 + 6399 = 13178"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = ELECT", "Answer": "6993 + 6133 = 13126"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7144 + 7314 = 14458"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FALL = LARGE", "Answer": "7221 + 7411 = 14632"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = BLOCK", "Answer": "7334 + 7044 = 14378"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = LARGE", "Answer": "7411 + 7241 = 14652"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = LOVER", "Answer": "7441 + 7511 = 14952"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HALL = FENCE", "Answer": "7442 + 7522 = 14964"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = FENCE", "Answer": "7552 + 7422 = 14974"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = AGREE", "Answer": "7556 + 7266 = 14822"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FULL = ISSUE", "Answer": "7663 + 7933 = 15596"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = ALTER", "Answer": "7664 + 7044 = 14708"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = IDEAL", "Answer": "7688 + 7168 = 14856"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7688 + 7568 = 15256"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = ELECT", "Answer": "8066 + 8106 = 16172"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = SLEEP", "Answer": "8006 + 8766 = 16772"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FALL = ALIVE", "Answer": "8226 + 8166 = 16392"}
{"Question": "TREE + TIRE = LIMIT", "Answer": "8344 + 8734 = 17078"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = HAPPY", "Answer": "8335 + 8655 = 16990"}
{"Question": "POOL + PULL = CLOCK", "Answer": "8337 + 8977 = 17314"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILL = ISSUE", "Answer": "8447 + 8177 = 16624"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "8511 + 8351 = 16862"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = SALAD", "Answer": "8552 + 8722 = 17274"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALL = ASSET", "Answer": "8554 + 8144 = 16698"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILL = LIMIT", "Answer": "8661 + 8711 = 17372"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILL = AWARE", "Answer": "8663 + 8533 = 17196"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FALL = PROOF", "Answer": "8664 + 8344 = 17008"}
{"Question": "FREE + FIRE = DRESS", "Answer": "8677 + 8067 = 16744"}
{"Question": "COOL + CALL = SORRY", "Answer": "8773 + 8233 = 17006"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = PAPER", "Answer": "8755 + 8375 = 17130"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = ELECT", "Answer": "9008 + 9188 = 18196"}
{"Question": "COOL + CELL = OFFER", "Answer": "9115 + 9755 = 18870"}
{"Question": "CALL + COAL = ERROR", "Answer": "9244 + 9624 = 18868"}
{"Question": "MALL + MEAL = STATE", "Answer": "9255 + 9025 = 18280"}
{"Question": "POOL + PULL = HAPPY", "Answer": "9335 + 9655 = 18990"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = CATCH", "Answer": "9337 + 9577 = 18914"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = STATE", "Answer": "9554 + 9844 = 19398"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TELL = VOTER", "Answer": "9882 + 9022 = 18904"}
{"Question": "SOON + SAND = ODDS", "Answer": "1224 + 1547 = 2771"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MASS = ODDS", "Answer": "1330 + 1677 = 3007"}
{"Question": "CARE + CREW = WEAR", "Answer": "1752 + 1523 = 3275"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIRT = INTO", "Answer": "3665 + 3751 = 7416"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILM = REFER", "Answer": "5009 + 5492 = 10501"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5009 + 5896 = 10905"}
{"Question": "HALL + HEAT = DEATH", "Answer": "5266 + 5029 = 10295"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DARE = SPEED", "Answer": "5226 + 5769 = 10995"}
{"Question": "YEAR + YARD = READY", "Answer": "5031 + 5314 = 10345"}
{"Question": "POOL + PALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "5331 + 5410 = 10741"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KILL = PIECE", "Answer": "5441 + 5033 = 10474"}
{"Question": "POOL + PALE = SALES", "Answer": "5667 + 5074 = 10741"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = EAGER", "Answer": "5774 + 5041 = 10815"}
{"Question": "TOUR + TURN = NORTH", "Answer": "5078 + 5781 = 10859"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = ACTOR", "Answer": "5779 + 5196 = 10975"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HALF = FAITH", "Answer": "5884 + 5041 = 10925"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HALF = SALES", "Answer": "5889 + 5092 = 10981"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WELL = BELOW", "Answer": "5886 + 5099 = 10985"}
{"Question": "SELL + STEP = ELECT", "Answer": "6122 + 6018 = 12140"}
{"Question": "PEER + PART = EARTH", "Answer": "6113 + 6234 = 12347"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WELL = LOWER", "Answer": "6229 + 6411 = 12640"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FATE = LATER", "Answer": "6123 + 6235 = 12358"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "6255 + 6123 = 12378"}
{"Question": "MASS + MEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "6255 + 6328 = 12583"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FREE = ROUTE", "Answer": "6220 + 6188 = 12408"}
{"Question": "TALL + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "6288 + 6325 = 12613"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARK = EAGER", "Answer": "6129 + 6290 = 12419"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BITE = TOTAL", "Answer": "6331 + 6819 = 13150"}
{"Question": "TALL + TEAM = ELITE", "Answer": "6322 + 6139 = 12461"}
{"Question": "SELL + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "6322 + 6531 = 12853"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BELL = ROUTE", "Answer": "6335 + 6722 = 13057"}
{"Question": "BEER + BORN = NERVE", "Answer": "6332 + 6921 = 13253"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FREE = DRAMA", "Answer": "6331 + 6244 = 12575"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BITE = METER", "Answer": "6338 + 6482 = 12820"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DARE = RADIO", "Answer": "6441 + 6213 = 12654"}
{"Question": "TREE + TURN = EVENT", "Answer": "6411 + 6745 = 13156"}
{"Question": "SELL + STEP = LOOSE", "Answer": "6511 + 6854 = 13365"}
{"Question": "CARE + CREW = SWEAR", "Answer": "6752 + 6523 = 13275"}
{"Question": "HOUR + HURT = ERROR", "Answer": "6853 + 6530 = 13383"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOSS = SORRY", "Answer": "6779 + 6211 = 12990"}
{"Question": "DEER + DIRT = STATE", "Answer": "6775 + 6052 = 12827"}
{"Question": "PLAN + PANT = TROOP", "Answer": "6475 + 6751 = 13226"}
{"Question": "POOL + PASS = HELLO", "Answer": "6772 + 6455 = 13227"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIRT = PHOTO", "Answer": "6775 + 6952 = 13727"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIRT = RATIO", "Answer": "6881 + 6917 = 13798"}
{"Question": "SHIT + SITE = HELLO", "Answer": "6182 + 6823 = 13005"}
{"Question": "MEET + MATH = HAPPY", "Answer": "6884 + 6341 = 13225"}
{"Question": "WALL + WRAP = FEWER", "Answer": "6855 + 6782 = 13637"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LAKE = SHELL", "Answer": "6887 + 6079 = 12966"}
{"Question": "SPIN + SING = PRESS", "Answer": "6187 + 6879 = 13066"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MALL = DRAMA", "Answer": "6991 + 6877 = 13868"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FILM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7133 + 7415 = 14548"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARK = ARMED", "Answer": "7514 + 7143 = 14657"}
{"Question": "LEAD + LADY = APPLE", "Answer": "7315 + 7158 = 14473"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7188 + 7012 = 14200"}
{"Question": "BALL + BOAT = AGREE", "Answer": "7188 + 7312 = 14500"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TALL = ENTER", "Answer": "7114 + 7599 = 14713"}
{"Question": "SELL + STEP = APART", "Answer": "7244 + 7925 = 15169"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = ENTRY", "Answer": "7225 + 7351 = 14576"}
{"Question": "MOON + MINE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7225 + 7951 = 15176"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FARM = REFER", "Answer": "7431 + 7310 = 14741"}
{"Question": "MEET + MATH = TITLE", "Answer": "7331 + 7812 = 15143"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALE = ASSET", "Answer": "7332 + 7125 = 14457"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = METER", "Answer": "7332 + 7925 = 15257"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KISS = ISSUE", "Answer": "7339 + 7144 = 14483"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KIND = AGAIN", "Answer": "7344 + 7839 = 15183"}
{"Question": "FREE + FARM = SMELL", "Answer": "7366 + 7234 = 14600"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LESS = SORRY", "Answer": "7449 + 7211 = 14660"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LESS = SOLVE", "Answer": "7442 + 7311 = 14753"}
{"Question": "THIN + TINY = NIGHT", "Answer": "7541 + 7416 = 14957"}
{"Question": "HALL + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7422 + 7145 = 14567"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "7422 + 7146 = 14568"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAN = SALES", "Answer": "7455 + 7046 = 14501"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "7145 + 7452 = 14597"}
{"Question": "MOON + MANY = WOMAN", "Answer": "7448 + 7280 = 14728"}
{"Question": "CELL + CREW = REFER", "Answer": "7499 + 7142 = 14641"}
{"Question": "THIN + TINY = FIFTH", "Answer": "7652 + 7524 = 15176"}
{"Question": "BEER + BALL = RELAX", "Answer": "7551 + 7833 = 15384"}
{"Question": "MAIN + MIND = ADMIT", "Answer": "7159 + 7594 = 14753"}
{"Question": "DEER + DIRT = BIBLE", "Answer": "7662 + 7524 = 15186"}
{"Question": "MOON + MIND = RADIO", "Answer": "7662 + 7824 = 15486"}
{"Question": "TALL + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "7655 + 7064 = 14719"}
{"Question": "MOON + MESS = ENTER", "Answer": "7664 + 7155 = 14819"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FADE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7883 + 7130 = 15013"}
{"Question": "RAIN + RING = EAGER", "Answer": "7583 + 7834 = 15417"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LAKE = RURAL", "Answer": "7884 + 7243 = 15127"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FREE = PRESS", "Answer": "7889 + 7544 = 15433"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TALL = ALONE", "Answer": "7883 + 7155 = 15038"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DARE = BREAD", "Answer": "7885 + 7352 = 15237"}
{"Question": "PEER + PARK = TROOP", "Answer": "7885 + 7452 = 15337"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TREE = HELLO", "Answer": "7883 + 7455 = 15338"}
{"Question": "WEEK + WILL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7882 + 7655 = 15537"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FARM = DRAMA", "Answer": "7985 + 7853 = 15838"}
{"Question": "TALL + TEAM = ELECT", "Answer": "7955 + 7192 = 15147"}
{"Question": "POUR + PURE = TROOP", "Answer": "7495 + 7952 = 15447"}
{"Question": "MOON + MESS = ENEMY", "Answer": "8006 + 8177 = 16183"}
{"Question": "ACID + AIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8316 + 8164 = 16480"}
{"Question": "WALL + WEAK = ALLOW", "Answer": "8166 + 8512 = 16678"}
{"Question": "FREE + FARM = ESSAY", "Answer": "8211 + 8429 = 16640"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "8221 + 8613 = 16834"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TREE = ELECT", "Answer": "8227 + 8911 = 17138"}
{"Question": "TREE + TURN = HONOR", "Answer": "8233 + 8729 = 16962"}
{"Question": "TALL + THAN = EVENT", "Answer": "8233 + 8925 = 17158"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LESS = HELLO", "Answer": "8227 + 8655 = 16882"}
{"Question": "PEER + PARK = HAPPY", "Answer": "8225 + 8659 = 16884"}
{"Question": "YEAR + YARD = DIRTY", "Answer": "8527 + 8271 = 16798"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAR = RELAX", "Answer": "8299 + 8621 = 16920"}
{"Question": "BEER + BORN = NURSE", "Answer": "8332 + 8921 = 17253"}
{"Question": "BEER + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "8334 + 8740 = 17074"}
{"Question": "SHIT + SITE = CHEST", "Answer": "8735 + 8350 = 17085"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = PAPER", "Answer": "8442 + 8726 = 17168"}
{"Question": "FREE + FARM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8433 + 8641 = 17074"}
{"Question": "WALL + WRAP = COLOR", "Answer": "8433 + 8946 = 17379"}
{"Question": "WEEK + WALL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8442 + 8166 = 16608"}
{"Question": "DEER + DARK = BLOOD", "Answer": "8446 + 8562 = 17008"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DARK = NAKED", "Answer": "8446 + 8762 = 17208"}
{"Question": "HOUR + HURT = TRUTH", "Answer": "8947 + 8471 = 17418"}
{"Question": "TALL + TEAM = LIMIT", "Answer": "8511 + 8257 = 16768"}
{"Question": "POOL + PALM = ENEMY", "Answer": "8553 + 8639 = 17192"}
{"Question": "WALL + WHAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8533 + 8759 = 17292"}
{"Question": "MOON + MINE = ENTER", "Answer": "8556 + 8361 = 16917"}
{"Question": "SOON + SELL = LOOSE", "Answer": "8669 + 8011 = 16680"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BELL = LEVEL", "Answer": "8660 + 8711 = 17371"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FILM = LIMIT", "Answer": "8661 + 8713 = 17374"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LIKE = FIELD", "Answer": "8662 + 8723 = 17385"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8664 + 8749 = 17413"}
{"Question": "PEER + PART = TASTE", "Answer": "8665 + 8751 = 17416"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HARD = ORDER", "Answer": "8367 + 8670 = 17037"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "8667 + 8471 = 17138"}
{"Question": "WILL + WAIT = ELITE", "Answer": "8677 + 8964 = 17641"}
{"Question": "MEET + MATH = THEME", "Answer": "8771 + 8016 = 16787"}
{"Question": "PEER + PASS = SORRY", "Answer": "8779 + 8211 = 16990"}
{"Question": "BALL + BOAT = SALES", "Answer": "8722 + 8479 = 17201"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARK = NAKED", "Answer": "8972 + 8726 = 17698"}
{"Question": "BALL + BOAT = TASTE", "Answer": "8744 + 8271 = 17015"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "8744 + 8571 = 17315"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIRT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8774 + 8941 = 17715"}
{"Question": "FEED + FALL = ASIDE", "Answer": "8772 + 8155 = 16927"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LAKE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8776 + 8362 = 17138"}
{"Question": "POOR + PASS = WORRY", "Answer": "8773 + 8566 = 17339"}
{"Question": "PEER + PORT = TROOP", "Answer": "8997 + 8671 = 17668"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "9144 + 9016 = 18160"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RATE = OFFER", "Answer": "9114 + 9745 = 18859"}
{"Question": "MEET + MYTH = ENEMY", "Answer": "9117 + 9073 = 18190"}
{"Question": "BEER + BURN = UNCLE", "Answer": "9224 + 9148 = 18372"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BAKE = HELLO", "Answer": "9224 + 9548 = 18772"}
{"Question": "BEER + BALL = TRIBE", "Answer": "9338 + 9455 = 18793"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LAKE = HELLO", "Answer": "9335 + 9658 = 18993"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIRT = RADIO", "Answer": "9441 + 9513 = 18954"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FADE = REFER", "Answer": "9443 + 9538 = 18981"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BELL = SALES", "Answer": "9446 + 9055 = 18501"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BELL = ELITE", "Answer": "9443 + 9188 = 18631"}
{"Question": "BALL + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "9522 + 9058 = 18580"}
{"Question": "MEET + MALL = THEME", "Answer": "9551 + 9044 = 18595"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DARK = AGREE", "Answer": "9557 + 9176 = 18733"}
{"Question": "CROP + COPE = UPPER", "Answer": "9258 + 9584 = 18842"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARK = ORDER", "Answer": "9358 + 9580 = 18938"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DARK = ERROR", "Answer": "9168 + 9680 = 18848"}
{"Question": "BEER + BURN = ISSUE", "Answer": "9773 + 9034 = 18807"}
{"Question": "TALL + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "9755 + 9172 = 18927"}
{"Question": "HAIR + HIRE = CHECK", "Answer": "9583 + 9834 = 19417"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LAKE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9884 + 9342 = 19226"}
{"Question": "BEER + BALL = ABOVE", "Answer": "9882 + 9166 = 19048"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEER = RIDE", "Answer": "1553 + 1663 = 3216"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEER = ONCE", "Answer": "3774 + 3884 = 7658"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FEED = ODDS", "Answer": "3776 + 3886 = 7662"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEER = BOARD", "Answer": "6228 + 6558 = 12786"}
{"Question": "FROM + FORM = DRESS", "Answer": "6259 + 6529 = 12788"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEER = FORCE", "Answer": "7554 + 7884 = 15438"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = APPLE", "Answer": "7663 + 7883 = 15546"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = AHEAD", "Answer": "8224 + 8994 = 17218"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = GRADE", "Answer": "8226 + 8556 = 16782"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = COULD", "Answer": "8554 + 8774 = 17328"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = WORLD", "Answer": "8664 + 8774 = 17438"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = CROSS", "Answer": "9008 + 9558 = 18566"}
{"Question": "DEER + DOOR = STATE", "Answer": "9226 + 9556 = 18782"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FEEL = LIFE", "Answer": "3551 + 3887 = 7438"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TOOL = ELITE", "Answer": "6119 + 6442 = 12561"}
{"Question": "PLAN + PALE = LABEL", "Answer": "6127 + 6214 = 12341"}
{"Question": "DRAG + DARE = GREEN", "Answer": "6251 + 6527 = 12778"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOOK = REACH", "Answer": "6221 + 6559 = 12780"}
{"Question": "DARE + DRAG = LABEL", "Answer": "6258 + 6523 = 12781"}
{"Question": "CROP + CORE = TREAT", "Answer": "6254 + 6527 = 12781"}
{"Question": "SITE + STIR = FIRST", "Answer": "6238 + 6325 = 12563"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEEP = WORLD", "Answer": "6227 + 6559 = 12786"}
{"Question": "WARM + WRAP = METER", "Answer": "6581 + 6857 = 13438"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DOOR = PRESS", "Answer": "6551 + 6993 = 13544"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TURN = INNER", "Answer": "6572 + 6753 = 13325"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TOOL = ELECT", "Answer": "7112 + 7995 = 15107"}
{"Question": "CORE + CROP = OFFER", "Answer": "7135 + 7318 = 14453"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOOM = CRIME", "Answer": "7334 + 7559 = 14893"}
{"Question": "SEED + SOON = DANCE", "Answer": "7441 + 7883 = 15324"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DOOR = BREAD", "Answer": "7442 + 7995 = 15437"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEEP = ROUND", "Answer": "7551 + 7886 = 15437"}
{"Question": "DARK + DRAG = EAGER", "Answer": "7564 + 7652 = 15216"}
{"Question": "DARE + DRAG = ASSET", "Answer": "8157 + 8513 = 16670"}
{"Question": "PALE + PLAN = ANGER", "Answer": "8124 + 8216 = 16340"}
{"Question": "WARN + WRAP = ANGER", "Answer": "8136 + 8317 = 16453"}
{"Question": "POOL + PEER = REPLY", "Answer": "8229 + 8661 = 16890"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEEP = GRADE", "Answer": "8226 + 8559 = 16785"}
{"Question": "WRAP + WARM = PAPER", "Answer": "8371 + 8732 = 17103"}
{"Question": "MEET + MOOD = TASTE", "Answer": "8551 + 8664 = 17215"}
{"Question": "POOL + PEER = LEAVE", "Answer": "8551 + 8776 = 17327"}
{"Question": "MOON + MEET = FENCE", "Answer": "8553 + 8774 = 17327"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DOOR = FORCE", "Answer": "8662 + 8774 = 17436"}
{"Question": "STIR + SITE = TREAT", "Answer": "9128 + 9213 = 18341"}
{"Question": "PLAN + PALE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9163 + 9618 = 18781"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOOT = EARTH", "Answer": "9116 + 9557 = 18673"}
{"Question": "DARE + DRAW = FEWER", "Answer": "9258 + 9527 = 18785"}
{"Question": "STOP + SOUP = TEST", "Answer": "2417 + 2107 = 4524"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SALT = ELSE", "Answer": "2437 + 2387 = 4824"}
{"Question": "LEAN + LAWN = WALL", "Answer": "2971 + 2751 = 5722"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FLAT = TALL", "Answer": "3446 + 3276 = 6722"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BELT = FLEE", "Answer": "4553 + 4613 = 9166"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ARMY = MALL", "Answer": "4668 + 4798 = 9466"}
{"Question": "PLOT + POST = LOTS", "Answer": "4973 + 4763 = 9736"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = ORDER", "Answer": "5110 + 5430 = 10540"}
{"Question": "THEM + TERM = EARTH", "Answer": "5216 + 5136 = 10352"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THIN = SHINE", "Answer": "5663 + 5073 = 10736"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "5771 + 5081 = 10852"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REST = OTHER", "Answer": "6113 + 6983 = 13096"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THIN = EIGHT", "Answer": "6118 + 6428 = 12546"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FAIR = EAGER", "Answer": "6120 + 6290 = 12410"}
{"Question": "REAL + RAIL = EAGER", "Answer": "6123 + 6293 = 12416"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HAND = EAGER", "Answer": "6125 + 6285 = 12410"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BELT = HOTEL", "Answer": "6225 + 6305 = 12530"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "6228 + 6358 = 12586"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REST = MOTOR", "Answer": "6228 + 6598 = 12826"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HARD = EAGER", "Answer": "6129 + 6289 = 12418"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FAST = STILL", "Answer": "6432 + 6312 = 12744"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = SORRY", "Answer": "6332 + 6892 = 13224"}
{"Question": "WOOD + WILD = MODEL", "Answer": "6332 + 6942 = 13274"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ARMY = FLOOR", "Answer": "6334 + 6894 = 13228"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HARD = PAPER", "Answer": "6837 + 6347 = 13184"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FAIL = ALIVE", "Answer": "6442 + 6152 = 12594"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FLAT = STAFF", "Answer": "6443 + 6823 = 13266"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEST = ASSET", "Answer": "6550 + 6830 = 13380"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SALT = LOOSE", "Answer": "6854 + 6514 = 13368"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BANK = URBAN", "Answer": "6557 + 6047 = 12604"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LAND = TOTAL", "Answer": "6378 + 6798 = 13176"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FIND = RADIO", "Answer": "6884 + 6574 = 13458"}
{"Question": "LEAN + LAWN = ANGLE", "Answer": "7814 + 7164 = 14978"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HARD = DRAMA", "Answer": "7021 + 7241 = 14262"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DROP = PRICE", "Answer": "7221 + 7431 = 14652"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DROP = PRIDE", "Answer": "7221 + 7451 = 14672"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DROP = PROVE", "Answer": "7221 + 7461 = 14682"}
{"Question": "GOOD + GLAD = ADAPT", "Answer": "7225 + 7915 = 15140"}
{"Question": "FEED + FIND = AGAIN", "Answer": "7228 + 7968 = 15196"}
{"Question": "LEAD + LAND = DELAY", "Answer": "7431 + 7301 = 14732"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "7331 + 7421 = 14752"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7331 + 7481 = 14812"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TUBE = ORDER", "Answer": "7432 + 7392 = 14824"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = START", "Answer": "7332 + 7592 = 14924"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "7334 + 7814 = 15148"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "7338 + 7518 = 14856"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FAIL = APPLY", "Answer": "7339 + 7159 = 14498"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "7839 + 7359 = 15198"}
{"Question": "MOON + MAIN = WOMAN", "Answer": "7440 + 7280 = 14720"}
{"Question": "THEM + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "7341 + 7401 = 14742"}
{"Question": "LEAD + LAND = DAILY", "Answer": "7541 + 7431 = 14972"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = HELLO", "Answer": "7442 + 7562 = 15004"}
{"Question": "SOON + SPIN = POUND", "Answer": "7448 + 7138 = 14586"}
{"Question": "PLOT + PORT = LOVER", "Answer": "7149 + 7489 = 14638"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BELT = LEAVE", "Answer": "7552 + 7412 = 14964"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = FENCE", "Answer": "7552 + 7432 = 14984"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = ROUTE", "Answer": "7553 + 7683 = 15236"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEST = SOLVE", "Answer": "7554 + 7814 = 15368"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ARMY = CLEAR", "Answer": "7554 + 7824 = 15378"}
{"Question": "PEER + PAIR = CARRY", "Answer": "7559 + 7439 = 14998"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SORT = FORTH", "Answer": "7859 + 7539 = 15398"}
{"Question": "PEER + PAIR = RURAL", "Answer": "7661 + 7481 = 15142"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "7968 + 7618 = 15586"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "7669 + 7249 = 14918"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SORT = THREE", "Answer": "7581 + 7841 = 15422"}
{"Question": "MOON + MEAN = ENEMY", "Answer": "8006 + 8176 = 16182"}
{"Question": "WEAK + WALK = ALLOW", "Answer": "8514 + 8164 = 16678"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FAIR = ARISE", "Answer": "8216 + 8136 = 16352"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "8521 + 8291 = 16812"}
{"Question": "MOON + MAIN = SENSE", "Answer": "8223 + 8093 = 16316"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LUCK = FULLY", "Answer": "8227 + 8657 = 16884"}
{"Question": "REAL + RAIL = INNER", "Answer": "8429 + 8219 = 16648"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SOME = THESE", "Answer": "8730 + 8350 = 17080"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = STAGE", "Answer": "8336 + 8256 = 16592"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DROP = UPPER", "Answer": "8336 + 8296 = 16632"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REST = METER", "Answer": "8339 + 8629 = 16968"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HARD = ERROR", "Answer": "8143 + 8463 = 16606"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HAIR = FIFTH", "Answer": "8649 + 8479 = 17128"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REST = THREE", "Answer": "8551 + 8271 = 16822"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SOFT = THESE", "Answer": "8751 + 8531 = 17282"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FACT = CYCLE", "Answer": "8652 + 8512 = 17164"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TRUE = ASSET", "Answer": "8054 + 8594 = 16648"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FAIR = RAISE", "Answer": "8261 + 8691 = 16952"}
{"Question": "PEER + POUR = RURAL", "Answer": "8661 + 8471 = 17132"}
{"Question": "SEED + SAND = FENCE", "Answer": "8663 + 8293 = 16956"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8663 + 8473 = 17136"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "8667 + 8407 = 17074"}
{"Question": "COAT + CAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8671 + 8741 = 17412"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FAST = CATCH", "Answer": "8573 + 8743 = 17316"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SOUP = COUCH", "Answer": "8673 + 8743 = 17416"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THIN = CATCH", "Answer": "8775 + 8035 = 16810"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "8976 + 8716 = 17692"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEST = STEEL", "Answer": "9008 + 9218 = 18226"}
{"Question": "BOOT + BEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9331 + 9281 = 18612"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HAND = ORDER", "Answer": "9034 + 9374 = 18408"}
{"Question": "FEED + FUND = ONION", "Answer": "9334 + 9284 = 18618"}
{"Question": "MEAN + MAIN = INNER", "Answer": "9538 + 9318 = 18856"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TUBE = METER", "Answer": "9638 + 9348 = 18986"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TWIN = WHITE", "Answer": "9442 + 9152 = 18594"}
{"Question": "MEET + MUST = ISSUE", "Answer": "9447 + 9387 = 18834"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TAIL = VITAL", "Answer": "9550 + 9380 = 18930"}
{"Question": "SHUT + SUIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "9251 + 9561 = 18812"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FLAT = AWFUL", "Answer": "9552 + 9412 = 18964"}
{"Question": "THEM + TERM = DRAMA", "Answer": "9053 + 9583 = 18636"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HARD = THREE", "Answer": "9854 + 9534 = 19388"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FAST = ASSET", "Answer": "9660 + 9180 = 18840"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TUBE = ENTER", "Answer": "9261 + 9651 = 18912"}
{"Question": "THEM + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "9361 + 9621 = 18982"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FAIL = APPLE", "Answer": "9663 + 9173 = 18836"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HAIR = THREE", "Answer": "9864 + 9624 = 19488"}
{"Question": "PLOT + POET = DEPTH", "Answer": "9265 + 9685 = 18950"}
{"Question": "SEED + SAND = ASIDE", "Answer": "9884 + 9164 = 19048"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SALT = WASTE", "Answer": "9085 + 9865 = 18950"}
{"Question": "SEED + SAND = ASIAN", "Answer": "9886 + 9126 = 19012"}
{"Question": "ODDS + OPEN = POSE", "Answer": "2663 + 2574 = 5237"}
{"Question": "SEED + STAR = DATA", "Answer": "3446 + 3059 = 6505"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FARM = RIFLE", "Answer": "5224 + 5318 = 10542"}
{"Question": "ROOM + REST = METER", "Answer": "5331 + 5074 = 10405"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SOFT = FLESH", "Answer": "5639 + 5317 = 10956"}
{"Question": "TERM + TRIP = METER", "Answer": "5041 + 5463 = 10504"}
{"Question": "SEED + SALT = TASTE", "Answer": "5443 + 5071 = 10514"}
{"Question": "SEED + SKIN = DRINK", "Answer": "5441 + 5382 = 10823"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SOUL = MOUSE", "Answer": "5771 + 5086 = 10857"}
{"Question": "SEED + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "5774 + 5028 = 10802"}
{"Question": "ODDS + OPEN = SPEND", "Answer": "5881 + 5097 = 10978"}
{"Question": "CROP + CODE = ORDER", "Answer": "6217 + 6135 = 12352"}
{"Question": "PEER + PLUS = RURAL", "Answer": "6221 + 6938 = 13159"}
{"Question": "COOL + CITE = ELECT", "Answer": "6223 + 6941 = 13164"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BONE = LOWER", "Answer": "6123 + 6247 = 12370"}
{"Question": "TOOL + THUS = HOUSE", "Answer": "6224 + 6135 = 12359"}
{"Question": "ROOM + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "6331 + 6705 = 13036"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "6335 + 6921 = 13256"}
{"Question": "ROOT + RACE = METER", "Answer": "6334 + 6092 = 12426"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REAL = ELITE", "Answer": "6339 + 6152 = 12491"}
{"Question": "FOOD + FIVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6339 + 6482 = 12821"}
{"Question": "ROOF + RATE = METER", "Answer": "6334 + 6592 = 12926"}
{"Question": "LOOK + LINE = NOVEL", "Answer": "6332 + 6714 = 13046"}
{"Question": "SEED + STAR = HEART", "Answer": "6334 + 6925 = 13259"}
{"Question": "SEEM + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "6441 + 6287 = 12728"}
{"Question": "DIET + DEAR = TRADE", "Answer": "6841 + 6423 = 13264"}
{"Question": "SHIP + SITE = THESE", "Answer": "6250 + 6517 = 12767"}
{"Question": "FEED + FIRM = DRAMA", "Answer": "6551 + 6327 = 12878"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FAIR = TRIAL", "Answer": "6551 + 6723 = 13274"}
{"Question": "KEEP + KNOW = PHONE", "Answer": "6551 + 6724 = 13275"}
{"Question": "COAL + CARE = ERROR", "Answer": "6852 + 6531 = 13383"}
{"Question": "WAIT + WILD = ELITE", "Answer": "6058 + 6523 = 12581"}
{"Question": "PLOT + POSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6259 + 6517 = 12776"}
{"Question": "ROOM + RING = MINOR", "Answer": "6771 + 6305 = 13076"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BOTH = WHEEL", "Answer": "6471 + 6753 = 13224"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BIRD = RADIO", "Answer": "6772 + 6815 = 13587"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FIVE = VIDEO", "Answer": "6778 + 6319 = 13097"}
{"Question": "FEED + FLAT = TITLE", "Answer": "6887 + 6241 = 13128"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "6385 + 6801 = 13186"}
{"Question": "POOR + PLUS = SLEEP", "Answer": "6885 + 6341 = 13226"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DATE = TREAT", "Answer": "6882 + 6019 = 12901"}
{"Question": "GRAB + GAIN = INNER", "Answer": "6582 + 6813 = 13395"}
{"Question": "CARE + CROP = UPPER", "Answer": "6485 + 6873 = 13358"}
{"Question": "COOK + CARE = OFFER", "Answer": "7118 + 7302 = 14420"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "7112 + 7485 = 14597"}
{"Question": "ROOM + READ = MARRY", "Answer": "7221 + 7549 = 14770"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "7228 + 7591 = 14819"}
{"Question": "BOOK + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "7225 + 7691 = 14916"}
{"Question": "MOOD + MINE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7223 + 7951 = 15174"}
{"Question": "ROOT + REAL = TITLE", "Answer": "7221 + 7968 = 15189"}
{"Question": "SALT + SLOW = TOTAL", "Answer": "7831 + 7352 = 15183"}
{"Question": "BOOM + BITE = METER", "Answer": "7331 + 7925 = 15256"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DARK = APPLE", "Answer": "7334 + 7129 = 14463"}
{"Question": "FEEL + FIRM = RIFLE", "Answer": "7335 + 7418 = 14753"}
{"Question": "COOL + CAKE = LOCAL", "Answer": "7441 + 7280 = 14721"}
{"Question": "DRAW + DATE = WATER", "Answer": "7341 + 7482 = 14823"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FAIR = TRIAL", "Answer": "7641 + 7405 = 15046"}
{"Question": "COAL + CASH = SALES", "Answer": "7549 + 7412 = 14961"}
{"Question": "GLAD + GAME = SMELL", "Answer": "7946 + 7453 = 15399"}
{"Question": "GRAB + GAME = LABEL", "Answer": "7246 + 7405 = 14651"}
{"Question": "SEED + STIR = ARISE", "Answer": "7449 + 7825 = 15274"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DESK = SORRY", "Answer": "7446 + 7219 = 14665"}
{"Question": "DARE + DROP = ORDER", "Answer": "7346 + 7418 = 14764"}
{"Question": "PRAY + PALE = LAYER", "Answer": "7549 + 7416 = 14965"}
{"Question": "MEET + MUCH = THEME", "Answer": "7551 + 7024 = 14575"}
{"Question": "FEED + FAIR = DRIVE", "Answer": "7551 + 7284 = 14835"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOAT = TRIBE", "Answer": "7554 + 7321 = 14875"}
{"Question": "TEEN + THIS = SENSE", "Answer": "7554 + 7861 = 15415"}
{"Question": "SOON + SEAT = NOISE", "Answer": "7551 + 7928 = 15479"}
{"Question": "SOON + SHIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "7558 + 7961 = 15519"}
{"Question": "SHUT + SURE = TRUTH", "Answer": "7961 + 7658 = 15619"}
{"Question": "TURN + TRIP = ENTER", "Answer": "7064 + 7652 = 14716"}
{"Question": "TEEN + TRIP = APART", "Answer": "7662 + 7485 = 15147"}
{"Question": "COOK + CARE = PAPER", "Answer": "7663 + 7529 = 15192"}
{"Question": "PLOT + POSE = STEEL", "Answer": "7264 + 7618 = 14882"}
{"Question": "POOR + PAGE = AGREE", "Answer": "7880 + 7153 = 15033"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOAT = RATIO", "Answer": "7881 + 7049 = 14930"}
{"Question": "CROP + COAL = PEACE", "Answer": "7081 + 7893 = 14974"}
{"Question": "THAN + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "7286 + 7851 = 15137"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FUEL = TITLE", "Answer": "7881 + 7309 = 15190"}
{"Question": "BLOW + BONE = WHEEL", "Answer": "7381 + 7842 = 15223"}
{"Question": "COOL + CARE = LATER", "Answer": "7881 + 7509 = 15390"}
{"Question": "PEER + PANT = STRIP", "Answer": "7882 + 7365 = 15247"}
{"Question": "CHIP + CITE = SHEET", "Answer": "7582 + 7864 = 15446"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AIDS = USUAL", "Answer": "7883 + 7295 = 15178"}
{"Question": "DEEP + DARK = RAPID", "Answer": "7883 + 7514 = 15397"}
{"Question": "COOL + CITY = ELECT", "Answer": "7885 + 7294 = 15179"}
{"Question": "BEER + BOND = NORTH", "Answer": "7884 + 7519 = 15403"}
{"Question": "LEAD + LAST = STEEL", "Answer": "7092 + 7915 = 15007"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TEAM = ELECT", "Answer": "7995 + 7142 = 15137"}
{"Question": "FEED + FOUR = PROOF", "Answer": "7992 + 7345 = 15337"}
{"Question": "TOOL + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "8112 + 8634 = 16746"}
{"Question": "URGE + UGLY = GREEN", "Answer": "8617 + 8153 = 16770"}
{"Question": "MEET + MAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "8115 + 8236 = 16351"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HARD = TRADE", "Answer": "8021 + 8269 = 16290"}
{"Question": "SOUP + SURE = PRESS", "Answer": "8521 + 8267 = 16788"}
{"Question": "THAN + TAKE = ENTER", "Answer": "8526 + 8291 = 16817"}
{"Question": "ROOM + RACE = MARRY", "Answer": "8221 + 8659 = 16880"}
{"Question": "HEEL + HANG = ANGLE", "Answer": "8229 + 8163 = 16392"}
{"Question": "MOON + MEAL = ALONE", "Answer": "8224 + 8016 = 16240"}
{"Question": "PILE + PLUS = USUAL", "Answer": "8925 + 8217 = 17142"}
{"Question": "FOOT + FIRE = METER", "Answer": "8227 + 8536 = 16763"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HALF = REFER", "Answer": "8731 + 8340 = 17071"}
{"Question": "DIET + DEAL = TITLE", "Answer": "8731 + 8392 = 17123"}
{"Question": "ROOF + RUSH = SHRUG", "Answer": "8334 + 8516 = 16850"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "8135 + 8346 = 16481"}
{"Question": "FLAG + FACE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8135 + 8396 = 16531"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DIET = RADIO", "Answer": "8551 + 8274 = 16825"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HARD = TRUTH", "Answer": "8351 + 8567 = 16918"}
{"Question": "SEED + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "8553 + 8941 = 17494"}
{"Question": "ROOF + RATE = AFTER", "Answer": "8556 + 8172 = 16728"}
{"Question": "WEEK + WRAP = APART", "Answer": "8552 + 8617 = 17169"}
{"Question": "FLAG + FATE = STEEL", "Answer": "8654 + 8572 = 17226"}
{"Question": "SEED + STOP = ADAPT", "Answer": "8557 + 8639 = 17196"}
{"Question": "WAIT + WIRE = TREAT", "Answer": "8361 + 8670 = 17031"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MAIL = TITLE", "Answer": "8461 + 8673 = 17134"}
{"Question": "MEET + MAIN = TITLE", "Answer": "8661 + 8475 = 17136"}
{"Question": "ALLY + AUTO = TOTAL", "Answer": "8669 + 8517 = 17186"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MASK = TASTE", "Answer": "8671 + 8745 = 17416"}
{"Question": "PLAN + PAGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8175 + 8796 = 16971"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MASK = SALES", "Answer": "8976 + 8715 = 17691"}
{"Question": "SEED + SNAP = ASIDE", "Answer": "9335 + 9718 = 19053"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "9442 + 9371 = 18813"}
{"Question": "SEED + SHIT = TASTE", "Answer": "9554 + 9361 = 18915"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "9153 + 9578 = 18731"}
{"Question": "DOOR + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "9556 + 9317 = 18873"}
{"Question": "SEED + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "9663 + 9128 = 18791"}
{"Question": "ROOF + RATE = TREAT", "Answer": "9667 + 9814 = 19481"}
{"Question": "TRIP + TIME = METER", "Answer": "9365 + 9618 = 18983"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HAIR = THREE", "Answer": "9572 + 9783 = 19355"}
{"Question": "ROOF + RATE = GREAT", "Answer": "9883 + 9574 = 19457"}
{"Question": "FEEL + HEEL = FULLY", "Answer": "1224 + 9224 = 10448"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = RIDE", "Answer": "1226 + 5226 = 6452"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = BLAME", "Answer": "1226 + 9226 = 10452"}
{"Question": "FOOD + GOOD = FENCE", "Answer": "1335 + 9335 = 10670"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = BIRTH", "Answer": "1336 + 9336 = 10672"}
{"Question": "BOOM + ROOM = MERE", "Answer": "1338 + 7338 = 8676"}
{"Question": "POOL + COOL = PEACE", "Answer": "1445 + 9445 = 10890"}
{"Question": "BOOK + COOK = BEACH", "Answer": "1446 + 9446 = 10892"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = BLADE", "Answer": "1447 + 9447 = 10894"}
{"Question": "FEEL + HEEL = FALSE", "Answer": "1663 + 8663 = 10326"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = BLIND", "Answer": "1664 + 8664 = 10328"}
{"Question": "COOK + BOOK = CLASS", "Answer": "1772 + 8772 = 10544"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = BOARD", "Answer": "1774 + 8774 = 10548"}
{"Question": "FEED + SEED = EASE", "Answer": "1884 + 6884 = 8768"}
{"Question": "GOOD + FOOD = OUGHT", "Answer": "2117 + 8117 = 10234"}
{"Question": "DEER + PEER = RAPID", "Answer": "2881 + 7881 = 10762"}
{"Question": "BOOK + COOK = FENCE", "Answer": "3446 + 9446 = 12892"}
{"Question": "ROOT + BOOT = FORTH", "Answer": "4225 + 8225 = 12450"}
{"Question": "POOL + COOL = TOPIC", "Answer": "4229 + 8229 = 12458"}
{"Question": "DOOR + POOR = BOARD", "Answer": "4337 + 9337 = 13674"}
{"Question": "TOOL + POOL = ELECT", "Answer": "4552 + 7552 = 12104"}
{"Question": "DEEP + KEEP = SPEND", "Answer": "4992 + 7992 = 12984"}
{"Question": "SEED + FEED = LOOSE", "Answer": "5226 + 9226 = 14452"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = CROWD", "Answer": "5664 + 8664 = 14328"}
{"Question": "WOOD + GOOD = FEWER", "Answer": "5773 + 8773 = 14546"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = RADIO", "Answer": "5881 + 7881 = 13762"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEER = MEDIA", "Answer": "6445 + 8445 = 14890"}
{"Question": "PEER + BEER = APPLE", "Answer": "7884 + 9884 = 17768"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SEED = FALSE", "Answer": "1448 + 9446 = 10894"}
{"Question": "WOOD + ROOF = FEWER", "Answer": "3667 + 8661 = 12328"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEEP = CROWD", "Answer": "3772 + 8776 = 12548"}
{"Question": "FOOD + SOON = DRESS", "Answer": "3881 + 6885 = 10766"}
{"Question": "PEER + FEED = REPLY", "Answer": "4221 + 8229 = 12450"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BOOM = LIMIT", "Answer": "4661 + 7663 = 12324"}
{"Question": "COOK + ROOF = FENCE", "Answer": "4772 + 8771 = 13543"}
{"Question": "MEET + BEER = DRAMA", "Answer": "4772 + 8773 = 13545"}
{"Question": "DEER + FEEL = READY", "Answer": "5221 + 7229 = 12450"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEEP = TRIBE", "Answer": "5223 + 8229 = 13452"}
{"Question": "DOOR + LOOK = WORLD", "Answer": "5448 + 9447 = 14895"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DOOR = TRADE", "Answer": "5881 + 6882 = 12763"}
{"Question": "DEER + WEEK = CROWD", "Answer": "5882 + 6883 = 12765"}
{"Question": "BEER + SEED = CROSS", "Answer": "5882 + 6884 = 12766"}
{"Question": "NEED + BEER = URBAN", "Answer": "5882 + 7883 = 13765"}
{"Question": "ROOF + COOK = FORCE", "Answer": "6331 + 7339 = 13670"}
{"Question": "MOON + ROOT = NORTH", "Answer": "6441 + 8449 = 14890"}
{"Question": "BOOK + ROOT = FORTH", "Answer": "6443 + 8449 = 14892"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LOOK = TOTAL", "Answer": "6551 + 8557 = 15108"}
{"Question": "COOL + ROLL = RELAX", "Answer": "9224 + 1244 = 10468"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CELL = FORCE", "Answer": "1226 + 9266 = 10492"}
{"Question": "COOL + POLL = CATCH", "Answer": "1228 + 9288 = 10516"}
{"Question": "COOL + POLL = PEACE", "Answer": "9335 + 1355 = 10690"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ROLL = RATIO", "Answer": "9447 + 1477 = 10924"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CELL = FOCUS", "Answer": "1448 + 9488 = 10936"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BELL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8577 = 10134"}
{"Question": "TOOL + POLL = THREE", "Answer": "1667 + 8677 = 10344"}
{"Question": "POOL + ROLL = PIECE", "Answer": "1772 + 8722 = 10494"}
{"Question": "HEEL + CELL = CATCH", "Answer": "8774 + 1744 = 10518"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CELL = CHECK", "Answer": "8992 + 1922 = 10914"}
{"Question": "COOL + POLL = CROWD", "Answer": "1993 + 8933 = 10926"}
{"Question": "FEEL + HELL = FRESH", "Answer": "1994 + 8944 = 10938"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TELL = LIFT", "Answer": "2338 + 6388 = 8726"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ROLL = LATER", "Answer": "8441 + 2411 = 10852"}
{"Question": "TOOL + POLL = ONTO", "Answer": "2884 + 5844 = 8728"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TELL = ENTER", "Answer": "7119 + 3199 = 10318"}
{"Question": "HEEL + CELL = FENCE", "Answer": "3226 + 9266 = 12492"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "3558 + 6588 = 10146"}
{"Question": "FEEL + WELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7662 + 4622 = 12284"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BELL = FLESH", "Answer": "8994 + 5944 = 14938"}
{"Question": "POOL + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "6449 + 8499 = 14948"}
{"Question": "HEEL + CELL = BEACH", "Answer": "6553 + 8533 = 15086"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TELL = CATCH", "Answer": "6883 + 7833 = 14716"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CELL = PLACE", "Answer": "7226 + 9266 = 16492"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TELL = CRAFT", "Answer": "7334 + 8344 = 15678"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ROLL = START", "Answer": "8554 + 9544 = 18098"}
{"Question": "DOOR + SORT = SERVE", "Answer": "9224 + 1246 = 10470"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BELT = FALSE", "Answer": "1224 + 9248 = 10472"}
{"Question": "COOL + POLE = CHEAP", "Answer": "1225 + 9254 = 10479"}
{"Question": "TOOL + HOLD = TIGHT", "Answer": "1226 + 9265 = 10491"}
{"Question": "DEEP + SELL = ODDS", "Answer": "6339 + 1322 = 7661"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SELF = HORSE", "Answer": "1335 + 9358 = 10693"}
{"Question": "DEEP + SELL = SALAD", "Answer": "9332 + 1377 = 10709"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LESS = TASTE", "Answer": "1336 + 9377 = 10713"}
{"Question": "SOON + POLL = SCENE", "Answer": "1446 + 9422 = 10868"}
{"Question": "BOOT + NOTE = TEEN", "Answer": "2443 + 1438 = 3881"}
{"Question": "BEER + TERM = ROOT", "Answer": "1443 + 2439 = 3882"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ROLL = REFER", "Answer": "9446 + 1455 = 10901"}
{"Question": "TOOL + COLD = CATCH", "Answer": "9446 + 1467 = 10913"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SEND = TASTE", "Answer": "1446 + 9468 = 10914"}
{"Question": "ROOT + VOTE = RIVER", "Answer": "1448 + 9483 = 10931"}
{"Question": "FEEL + RELY = FORCE", "Answer": "1448 + 9486 = 10934"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERO = BIBLE", "Answer": "1556 + 8569 = 10125"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BELT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8572 = 10129"}
{"Question": "FEED + SELL = FALSE", "Answer": "1664 + 8622 = 10286"}
{"Question": "HEEL + SELF = SALAD", "Answer": "8663 + 1639 = 10302"}
{"Question": "MEET + BELL = MOTOR", "Answer": "1663 + 8644 = 10307"}
{"Question": "BEER + TERM = BLOOD", "Answer": "1667 + 8672 = 10339"}
{"Question": "LOOK + JOKE = LABEL", "Answer": "1667 + 8674 = 10341"}
{"Question": "TEEN + BEND = THREE", "Answer": "1669 + 8697 = 10366"}
{"Question": "SOON + POLL = SALES", "Answer": "1776 + 8755 = 10531"}
{"Question": "TOOL + HOLE = TREAT", "Answer": "1776 + 8765 = 10541"}
{"Question": "KEEP + CELL = CHECK", "Answer": "8996 + 1922 = 10918"}
{"Question": "POOR + SORT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1995 + 8954 = 10949"}
{"Question": "NEED + YELL = FUNNY", "Answer": "8449 + 2433 = 10882"}
{"Question": "HEEL + BELT = FIFTH", "Answer": "2558 + 7584 = 10142"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SEND = LEAST", "Answer": "3226 + 9267 = 12493"}
{"Question": "TOOL + HOLD = CATCH", "Answer": "9446 + 3467 = 12913"}
{"Question": "COOK + JOKE = ELECT", "Answer": "3558 + 6581 = 10139"}
{"Question": "MEET + SELL = TASTE", "Answer": "8661 + 3655 = 12316"}
{"Question": "ROOF + SOFT = OFFER", "Answer": "8112 + 4126 = 12238"}
{"Question": "WOOD + ROLL = LOWER", "Answer": "4227 + 8211 = 12438"}
{"Question": "ROOF + BOSS = SORRY", "Answer": "4229 + 8211 = 12440"}
{"Question": "TOOL + HOLE = ALTER", "Answer": "4223 + 9235 = 13458"}
{"Question": "NEED + CELL = FENCE", "Answer": "4227 + 8255 = 12482"}
{"Question": "ROOF + SOFT = MOTOR", "Answer": "4229 + 8295 = 12524"}
{"Question": "MOON + TONE = ELECT", "Answer": "4557 + 8571 = 13128"}
{"Question": "POOL + COLD = ADAPT", "Answer": "4558 + 7582 = 12140"}
{"Question": "BEER + HERO = TOOTH", "Answer": "4665 + 8653 = 13318"}
{"Question": "COOL + FOLK = REFER", "Answer": "4772 + 5729 = 10501"}
{"Question": "PEER + LESS = APPLE", "Answer": "4775 + 9722 = 14497"}
{"Question": "ROOM + TOSS = METER", "Answer": "4771 + 5733 = 10504"}
{"Question": "BOOT + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "9112 + 5123 = 14235"}
{"Question": "TOOL + ROLE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5229 + 7298 = 12527"}
{"Question": "DOOR + BORN = ROUND", "Answer": "5331 + 8314 = 13645"}
{"Question": "DEEP + CELL = PEACE", "Answer": "8331 + 5322 = 13653"}
{"Question": "ROOF + SOFT = COLOR", "Answer": "5339 + 8396 = 13735"}
{"Question": "FEEL + HELP = PROOF", "Answer": "8667 + 5671 = 14338"}
{"Question": "POOL + ROLE = UPPER", "Answer": "5776 + 9763 = 15539"}
{"Question": "MOON + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "5883 + 7831 = 13714"}
{"Question": "ROOT + NOTE = OTHER", "Answer": "7113 + 6134 = 13247"}
{"Question": "ROOF + SOFT = FORTH", "Answer": "6331 + 7314 = 13645"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FLEE = CLASS", "Answer": "7334 + 6388 = 13722"}
{"Question": "BEER + VERY = LEVEL", "Answer": "6339 + 7392 = 13731"}
{"Question": "ROOT + BOTH = MOTOR", "Answer": "6449 + 8497 = 14946"}
{"Question": "ROOF + BOSS = START", "Answer": "6553 + 7511 = 14064"}
{"Question": "BEER + MESS = TERMS", "Answer": "6550 + 8533 = 15083"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "6551 + 8577 = 15128"}
{"Question": "LOOK + JOKE = TOTAL", "Answer": "6557 + 8579 = 15136"}
{"Question": "HEEL + RELY = TOOTH", "Answer": "6774 + 8742 = 15516"}
{"Question": "DOOR + MORE = ARMED", "Answer": "6884 + 7842 = 14726"}
{"Question": "ROOT + LOTS = OTHER", "Answer": "8115 + 7153 = 15268"}
{"Question": "NEED + CELL = DANCE", "Answer": "8441 + 7433 = 15874"}
{"Question": "BOOM + HOME = COACH", "Answer": "8665 + 7652 = 16317"}
{"Question": "TEEN + MENU = QUITE", "Answer": "8225 + 9257 = 17482"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BOSS = ELITE", "Answer": "8337 + 9344 = 17681"}
{"Question": "GOOD + LOAD = GRASS", "Answer": "1223 + 9243 = 10466"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TOUR = THREE", "Answer": "9224 + 1264 = 10488"}
{"Question": "FOOD + COLD = FENCE", "Answer": "1225 + 9265 = 10490"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAR = BLAME", "Answer": "1226 + 9246 = 10472"}
{"Question": "SEED + BEND = STATE", "Answer": "1226 + 9276 = 10502"}
{"Question": "FEED + TEND = TASTE", "Answer": "9226 + 1286 = 10512"}
{"Question": "BOOM + FORM = BLAME", "Answer": "1228 + 9258 = 10486"}
{"Question": "COOK + FOLK = CLASS", "Answer": "1337 + 9307 = 10644"}
{"Question": "MEET + BEAT = MOTOR", "Answer": "1337 + 9367 = 10704"}
{"Question": "SOON + BORN = SCENE", "Answer": "1338 + 9348 = 10686"}
{"Question": "FEED + SEND = FALSE", "Answer": "1442 + 9452 = 10894"}
{"Question": "FEEL + REAL = RIFLE", "Answer": "9442 + 1482 = 10924"}
{"Question": "FOOD + WORD = FEWER", "Answer": "1443 + 9463 = 10906"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SOIL = TASTE", "Answer": "1443 + 9473 = 10916"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HOST = HELLO", "Answer": "9447 + 1437 = 10884"}
{"Question": "FEED + READ = FORCE", "Answer": "1447 + 9487 = 10934"}
{"Question": "FEEL + DEAL = FULLY", "Answer": "1448 + 9438 = 10886"}
{"Question": "COOL + BOWL = CYCLE", "Answer": "1552 + 8572 = 10124"}
{"Question": "FOOT + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "1554 + 8594 = 10148"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAR = BLADE", "Answer": "1663 + 8623 = 10286"}
{"Question": "ROOT + COST = RATIO", "Answer": "1663 + 8693 = 10356"}
{"Question": "FOOD + ROAD = FAVOR", "Answer": "1664 + 8604 = 10268"}
{"Question": "SEED + LEAD = SHALL", "Answer": "1664 + 8624 = 10288"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAR = BLOOD", "Answer": "1664 + 8674 = 10338"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SOFT = SENSE", "Answer": "8665 + 1645 = 10310"}
{"Question": "POOL + BOWL = PRIOR", "Answer": "1665 + 8695 = 10360"}
{"Question": "COOL + GOAL = CABLE", "Answer": "1667 + 8607 = 10274"}
{"Question": "BEER + YEAR = BADLY", "Answer": "1669 + 8609 = 10278"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "1669 + 8629 = 10298"}
{"Question": "BEER + FEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "1772 + 8752 = 10524"}
{"Question": "BOOM + POEM = BLAME", "Answer": "1773 + 8763 = 10536"}
{"Question": "BEER + HEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1774 + 8724 = 10498"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SORT = BRUSH", "Answer": "1776 + 8706 = 10482"}
{"Question": "BOOT + COAT = CLOCK", "Answer": "8993 + 1923 = 10916"}
{"Question": "FEEL + DEAL = FIELD", "Answer": "1994 + 8954 = 10948"}
{"Question": "FEED + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "8113 + 2103 = 10216"}
{"Question": "BEER + TEAR = ENTRY", "Answer": "8117 + 2157 = 10274"}
{"Question": "DEER + NEAR = ROUND", "Answer": "2331 + 8351 = 10682"}
{"Question": "SOON + DOWN = ODDS", "Answer": "2661 + 3671 = 6332"}
{"Question": "PEER + BEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "2663 + 9613 = 12276"}
{"Question": "BOOK + LOCK = CABLE", "Answer": "2664 + 7614 = 10278"}
{"Question": "SEED + LEAD = ELSE", "Answer": "2668 + 3658 = 6326"}
{"Question": "SEEM + TEAM = WASTE", "Answer": "2668 + 7608 = 10276"}
{"Question": "BEER + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "5886 + 2876 = 8762"}
{"Question": "BEER + TEAR = RATE", "Answer": "2889 + 6879 = 9768"}
{"Question": "SEED + BEND = DRESS", "Answer": "2991 + 7931 = 10922"}
{"Question": "ROOT + COST = START", "Answer": "3220 + 7210 = 10430"}
{"Question": "MEET + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "9112 + 4102 = 13214"}
{"Question": "FEED + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "4113 + 6103 = 10216"}
{"Question": "MEET + REST = THREE", "Answer": "9221 + 4201 = 13422"}
{"Question": "NEED + HEAD = DANCE", "Answer": "4221 + 9231 = 13452"}
{"Question": "ROOT + COST = SORRY", "Answer": "4225 + 8215 = 12440"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HOST = FORTH", "Answer": "4229 + 8269 = 12498"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "4331 + 9361 = 13692"}
{"Question": "FOOT + COST = STAFF", "Answer": "4332 + 8312 = 12644"}
{"Question": "BOOT + POST = STOP", "Answer": "5337 + 4397 = 9734"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BOWL = ELECT", "Answer": "4552 + 7582 = 12134"}
{"Question": "COOL + BOWL = ELECT", "Answer": "4553 + 8593 = 13146"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SOIL = PILOT", "Answer": "4662 + 5602 = 10264"}
{"Question": "FEED + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "4663 + 7613 = 12276"}
{"Question": "FEED + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "4668 + 7608 = 12276"}
{"Question": "ROOM + POEM = TERMS", "Answer": "4778 + 5708 = 10486"}
{"Question": "MEET + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "5114 + 8134 = 13248"}
{"Question": "MEET + BEST = TERMS", "Answer": "5331 + 8321 = 13652"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HOST = SOUTH", "Answer": "5334 + 8314 = 13648"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HOUR = COUCH", "Answer": "5339 + 8379 = 13718"}
{"Question": "FEED + READ = CARRY", "Answer": "5446 + 8436 = 13882"}
{"Question": "BEER + TEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "5448 + 7428 = 12876"}
{"Question": "MOON + BORN = DRAMA", "Answer": "7449 + 5429 = 12878"}
{"Question": "BEER + FEAR = PROOF", "Answer": "5664 + 8674 = 14338"}
{"Question": "SEEM + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "9331 + 6321 = 15652"}
{"Question": "MEET + BELT = LEMON", "Answer": "6339 + 7319 = 13658"}
{"Question": "MEET + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "6441 + 8421 = 14862"}
{"Question": "MEET + REST = SERVE", "Answer": "6442 + 8412 = 14854"}
{"Question": "ROOT + LOST = SOLAR", "Answer": "6443 + 8413 = 14856"}
{"Question": "DEER + BEAR = ASIDE", "Answer": "6447 + 9417 = 15864"}
{"Question": "BEER + YEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "7448 + 6438 = 13886"}
{"Question": "BEER + YEAR = SORRY", "Answer": "9448 + 6438 = 15886"}
{"Question": "BOOT + COAT = TOUCH", "Answer": "6551 + 8531 = 15082"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HOST = FORTH", "Answer": "6559 + 8539 = 15098"}
{"Question": "SEED + BEAR = START", "Answer": "1223 + 9247 = 10470"}
{"Question": "MOOD + PORT = METER", "Answer": "1223 + 9285 = 10508"}
{"Question": "PEER + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "1225 + 9204 = 10429"}
{"Question": "FEEL + NEWS = FALSE", "Answer": "1224 + 9258 = 10482"}
{"Question": "GOOD + SOME = GUESS", "Answer": "1225 + 9274 = 10499"}
{"Question": "FOOD + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "1334 + 9356 = 10690"}
{"Question": "SOON + CODE = SPEND", "Answer": "1338 + 9346 = 10684"}
{"Question": "BEER + TEAM = BIRTH", "Answer": "1336 + 9358 = 10694"}
{"Question": "WEEK + REST = WORKS", "Answer": "1442 + 9486 = 10928"}
{"Question": "SOON + COPE = SPEND", "Answer": "1445 + 9408 = 10853"}
{"Question": "BOOT + FOUR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1447 + 9428 = 10875"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "1553 + 8572 = 10125"}
{"Question": "FOOT + HOLD = FIFTH", "Answer": "1552 + 8576 = 10128"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BLUE = ASSET", "Answer": "1557 + 8539 = 10096"}
{"Question": "COOL + JOKE = CHECK", "Answer": "1662 + 8653 = 10315"}
{"Question": "SOON + BOAT = SENSE", "Answer": "1663 + 8647 = 10310"}
{"Question": "FEEL + YEAH = FULLY", "Answer": "1663 + 8675 = 10338"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TERM = DRAMA", "Answer": "1665 + 8607 = 10272"}
{"Question": "SEED + BELT = SLIDE", "Answer": "1667 + 8609 = 10276"}
{"Question": "PEER + TEAM = PARTY", "Answer": "1774 + 8709 = 10483"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SEND = SALES", "Answer": "8775 + 1796 = 10571"}
{"Question": "TOOL + NOSE = OFTEN", "Answer": "2113 + 8145 = 10258"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "2881 + 7806 = 10687"}
{"Question": "DOOR + LOSE = SPEED", "Answer": "3229 + 7214 = 10443"}
{"Question": "ROOM + TONE = METER", "Answer": "3441 + 9482 = 12923"}
{"Question": "MEET + LEAD = TITLE", "Answer": "6551 + 3584 = 10135"}
{"Question": "FEEL + DESK = SALAD", "Answer": "3887 + 6819 = 10706"}
{"Question": "ROOF + HOST = FORTH", "Answer": "4221 + 8257 = 12478"}
{"Question": "WOOD + ROLE = LOWER", "Answer": "4225 + 8213 = 12438"}
{"Question": "COOL + BONE = ELECT", "Answer": "4552 + 7591 = 12143"}
{"Question": "COOL + BODY = ELECT", "Answer": "4552 + 7596 = 12148"}
{"Question": "COOL + BOTH = ELECT", "Answer": "4553 + 8596 = 13149"}
{"Question": "COOL + WORD = ALLOW", "Answer": "4662 + 7605 = 12267"}
{"Question": "COOL + VOTE = LEVEL", "Answer": "4771 + 5730 = 10501"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LOVE = STEAL", "Answer": "4773 + 8795 = 13568"}
{"Question": "FEED + HEAT = DEATH", "Answer": "5221 + 7246 = 12467"}
{"Question": "DOOR + BOWL = WORLD", "Answer": "7224 + 5213 = 12437"}
{"Question": "LOOK + NOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "5339 + 7316 = 12655"}
{"Question": "BOOM + ROAD = MARRY", "Answer": "5441 + 8439 = 13880"}
{"Question": "MOOD + ROSE = TERMS", "Answer": "5447 + 8403 = 13850"}
{"Question": "PEER + BEAT = TROOP", "Answer": "5664 + 8671 = 14335"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LEAF = APPLE", "Answer": "5774 + 8713 = 14487"}
{"Question": "FEED + BEAR = DRAFT", "Answer": "5881 + 6872 = 12753"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "5884 + 7831 = 13715"}
{"Question": "FEED + TEAR = CRAFT", "Answer": "5884 + 6872 = 12756"}
{"Question": "DOOR + MOVE = ARMED", "Answer": "5883 + 7842 = 13725"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BEND = CABLE", "Answer": "5882 + 7846 = 13728"}
{"Question": "DEEP + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "6113 + 8145 = 14258"}
{"Question": "ROOT + COME = METER", "Answer": "7224 + 6213 = 13437"}
{"Question": "BEER + DEAL = GRADE", "Answer": "6223 + 7249 = 13472"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LOAD = TABLE", "Answer": "6331 + 8349 = 14680"}
{"Question": "ROOM + BOTH = MOTOR", "Answer": "8551 + 6507 = 15058"}
{"Question": "FEEL + VERY = LEAVE", "Answer": "6551 + 8534 = 15085"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LOCK = TOTAL", "Answer": "6551 + 8597 = 15148"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LEAD = ADULT", "Answer": "7553 + 6514 = 14067"}
{"Question": "KEEP + TEND = ADAPT", "Answer": "6553 + 7584 = 14137"}
{"Question": "DOOR + BOWL = WOULD", "Answer": "6559 + 8517 = 15076"}
{"Question": "ROOF + TOWN = ENTER", "Answer": "6882 + 7834 = 14716"}
{"Question": "SEED + MEAL = LOOSE", "Answer": "7332 + 9341 = 16673"}
{"Question": "BOOK + NOSE = SEVEN", "Answer": "7552 + 8516 = 16068"}
{"Question": "DOOR + GROW = GUARD", "Answer": "9224 + 1425 = 10649"}
{"Question": "SEED + IDEA = SHADE", "Answer": "1225 + 9527 = 10752"}
{"Question": "BEER + CREW = BIBLE", "Answer": "1229 + 8923 = 10152"}
{"Question": "DEEP + OPEN = DANCE", "Answer": "1335 + 9538 = 10873"}
{"Question": "SEED + IDEA = SHALL", "Answer": "1442 + 9246 = 10688"}
{"Question": "COOL + FLOW = FENCE", "Answer": "9442 + 1248 = 10690"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SLOW = TRUST", "Answer": "1443 + 9348 = 10791"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FLOW = FIFTH", "Answer": "8447 + 1742 = 10189"}
{"Question": "FEED + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "1449 + 3945 = 5394"}
{"Question": "BOOT + STOP = SENSE", "Answer": "8556 + 1654 = 10210"}
{"Question": "MOON + KNOW = BOMB", "Answer": "1559 + 4957 = 6516"}
{"Question": "SEED + IDEA = SLIDE", "Answer": "1662 + 9264 = 10926"}
{"Question": "BEER + CREW = BASIS", "Answer": "1665 + 8567 = 10232"}
{"Question": "POOL + BLOW = PHOTO", "Answer": "1669 + 8967 = 10636"}
{"Question": "FEED + IDEA = ISSUE", "Answer": "8772 + 1275 = 10047"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STOP = SUPER", "Answer": "8775 + 1573 = 10348"}
{"Question": "FEED + IDEA = NINE", "Answer": "1885 + 4583 = 6468"}
{"Question": "FEED + IDEA = ELITE", "Answer": "2117 + 8714 = 10831"}
{"Question": "FEED + IDEA = ONION", "Answer": "7556 + 2654 = 10210"}
{"Question": "MEET + STEP = TEST", "Answer": "2889 + 6980 = 9869"}
{"Question": "NEED + IDEA = RANGE", "Answer": "3775 + 8572 = 12347"}
{"Question": "NEED + IDEA = AGAIN", "Answer": "3882 + 6281 = 10163"}
{"Question": "MEET + STEP = TERMS", "Answer": "4221 + 8127 = 12348"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BLOW = ELECT", "Answer": "7882 + 4285 = 12167"}
{"Question": "DOOR + IRON = ROUND", "Answer": "5221 + 7124 = 12345"}
{"Question": "BEER + CREW = TRIBE", "Answer": "5224 + 9428 = 14652"}
{"Question": "NEED + IDEA = LEARN", "Answer": "5336 + 8639 = 13975"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STOP = PAPER", "Answer": "5664 + 7461 = 13125"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STOP = WORRY", "Answer": "7334 + 6438 = 13772"}
{"Question": "BEER + CREW = TWICE", "Answer": "6339 + 7934 = 14273"}
{"Question": "BOOT + STOP = TASTE", "Answer": "6551 + 7159 = 13710"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STOP = OTHER", "Answer": "8115 + 7513 = 15628"}
{"Question": "NEED + IDEA = PLANE", "Answer": "7335 + 9538 = 16873"}
{"Question": "SEED + IDEA = ARISE", "Answer": "8443 + 7341 = 15784"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = HUMOR", "Answer": "1626 + 9206 = 10832"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1626 + 9276 = 10902"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRUE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8636 + 1376 = 10012"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRUE = MOUNT", "Answer": "1939 + 8329 = 10268"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8646 + 1406 = 10052"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = HONEY", "Answer": "1252 + 9572 = 10824"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1353 + 9583 = 10936"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8454 + 1564 = 10018"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = HUMAN", "Answer": "1757 + 8507 = 10264"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRUE = MOUTH", "Answer": "1757 + 8527 = 10284"}
{"Question": "HERE + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8363 + 1673 = 10036"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONCE = OFFER", "Answer": "8272 + 1752 = 10024"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRUE = SHOOT", "Answer": "8636 + 2356 = 10992"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "6121 + 4291 = 10412"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "5242 + 7482 = 12724"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONCE = ANGER", "Answer": "6232 + 7392 = 13624"}
{"Question": "HERE + URGE = TRUTH", "Answer": "6343 + 8473 = 14816"}
{"Question": "HERE + URGE = BRUSH", "Answer": "6353 + 9573 = 15926"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONCE = ENJOY", "Answer": "7151 + 8531 = 15682"}
{"Question": "COOL + FLEE = CHECK", "Answer": "1225 + 9588 = 10813"}
{"Question": "MEAL + TALE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1627 + 9276 = 10903"}
{"Question": "POOR + HERE = HAPPY", "Answer": "9226 + 1767 = 10993"}
{"Question": "POOL + FLEE = PRESS", "Answer": "1334 + 9488 = 10822"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FLEE = TREAT", "Answer": "1339 + 8922 = 10261"}
{"Question": "TEAR + DARE = DIRTY", "Answer": "8943 + 1439 = 10382"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TREE = THIRD", "Answer": "9552 + 1277 = 10829"}
{"Question": "SKIN + LINK = SALES", "Answer": "1358 + 9583 = 10941"}
{"Question": "SOON + KNEE = SPEND", "Answer": "1557 + 8722 = 10279"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DATA = REFER", "Answer": "1554 + 8747 = 10301"}
{"Question": "BEAR + CARE = ARAB", "Answer": "1269 + 5692 = 6961"}
{"Question": "SHOT + BOTH = BASIS", "Answer": "9267 + 1672 = 10939"}
{"Question": "SOON + GENE = SALES", "Answer": "1662 + 8929 = 10591"}
{"Question": "TEAM + GAME = TOOTH", "Answer": "1274 + 8742 = 10016"}
{"Question": "COOL + FLEE = CARRY", "Answer": "1774 + 8455 = 10229"}
{"Question": "IDEA + HEAD = IMAGE", "Answer": "1572 + 8725 = 10297"}
{"Question": "MEAT + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1573 + 8735 = 10308"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "1886 + 4655 = 6541"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HERE = VIDEO", "Answer": "2885 + 7353 = 10238"}
{"Question": "PEAK + BAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "3724 + 9247 = 12971"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TREE = HEART", "Answer": "3446 + 8622 = 12068"}
{"Question": "STAR + PART = THESE", "Answer": "3167 + 9671 = 12838"}
{"Question": "THUS + RUSH = ENTER", "Answer": "9628 + 4286 = 13914"}
{"Question": "POOR + TREE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8229 + 4955 = 13184"}
{"Question": "BEAT + RATE = EAGER", "Answer": "4138 + 9381 = 13519"}
{"Question": "IDEA + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "4671 + 8716 = 13387"}
{"Question": "SOON + KNEE = DRESS", "Answer": "4778 + 5866 = 10644"}
{"Question": "TEAM + GAME = METER", "Answer": "5321 + 8213 = 13534"}
{"Question": "REAL + TALE = ENTER", "Answer": "9138 + 5381 = 14519"}
{"Question": "SOON + KNEE = BASIS", "Answer": "9662 + 5277 = 14939"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DATA = SPEED", "Answer": "8773 + 5232 = 14005"}
{"Question": "KNOW + TOWN = SWEET", "Answer": "6384 + 7843 = 14227"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DATA = LABEL", "Answer": "7226 + 8565 = 15791"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HERE = TRUTH", "Answer": "8665 + 7252 = 15917"}
{"Question": "YEAR + CARE = HAPPY", "Answer": "7364 + 8643 = 16007"}
{"Question": "BEAT + FATE = REFER", "Answer": "8724 + 9247 = 17971"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DATA = CARRY", "Answer": "9226 + 8767 = 17993"}
{"Question": "DOOR + MERE = ARMED", "Answer": "9557 + 8272 = 17829"}
{"Question": "BEAT + GATE = EAGER", "Answer": "8174 + 9741 = 17915"}
{"Question": "TOOL + PLUS = TRUST", "Answer": "1223 + 9358 = 10581"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SNAP = TRUST", "Answer": "1223 + 9368 = 10591"}
{"Question": "DEER + GRAB = DANCE", "Answer": "1224 + 9408 = 10632"}
{"Question": "LOOK + SKIN = STILL", "Answer": "9225 + 1574 = 10799"}
{"Question": "MEAL + RATE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1524 + 9285 = 10809"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONLY = ORDER", "Answer": "9626 + 1234 = 10860"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TYPE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1334 + 9478 = 10812"}
{"Question": "MERE + TRIP = MOTOR", "Answer": "1535 + 9368 = 10903"}
{"Question": "LEAD + CARE = COLOR", "Answer": "9532 + 1375 = 10907"}
{"Question": "ITEM + BEST = ISSUE", "Answer": "1736 + 8307 = 10043"}
{"Question": "STEP + LEFT = LOOSE", "Answer": "8736 + 1347 = 10083"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRAG = BLAME", "Answer": "1339 + 8924 = 10263"}
{"Question": "LADY + IDEA = DEAL", "Answer": "1249 + 3472 = 4721"}
{"Question": "HEAT + LAKE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1247 + 9482 = 10729"}
{"Question": "NEAR + HAVE = EVEN", "Answer": "2349 + 1483 = 3832"}
{"Question": "BEND + ONCE = ORDER", "Answer": "9258 + 1562 = 10820"}
{"Question": "HEEL + PLUS = HOUSE", "Answer": "1552 + 9283 = 10835"}
{"Question": "HERO + TRUE = ROOT", "Answer": "4358 + 1523 = 5881"}
{"Question": "SNAP + EARN = SCENE", "Answer": "1356 + 9583 = 10939"}
{"Question": "FOOT + STIR = FIFTH", "Answer": "1556 + 8607 = 10163"}
{"Question": "HERE + PRAY = PAPER", "Answer": "8656 + 1509 = 10165"}
{"Question": "FEEL + PLOT = FORTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8706 = 10263"}
{"Question": "GOOD + IDEA = GRADE", "Answer": "1559 + 8934 = 10493"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TYPE = AFTER", "Answer": "1662 + 9273 = 10935"}
{"Question": "GENE + UNIT = GIVEN", "Answer": "1767 + 8609 = 10376"}
{"Question": "STAR + PANT = SENSE", "Answer": "1763 + 8647 = 10410"}
{"Question": "DEER + ARMY = AWARD", "Answer": "8773 + 1365 = 10138"}
{"Question": "FLAG + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1479 + 8704 = 10183"}
{"Question": "POOR + CREW = PEACE", "Answer": "1776 + 8604 = 10380"}
{"Question": "BOOK + SKIN = SENSE", "Answer": "8776 + 1634 = 10410"}
{"Question": "COOK + SKIN = SINCE", "Answer": "8779 + 1906 = 10685"}
{"Question": "FEEL + PLAN = APPLE", "Answer": "9557 + 2718 = 12275"}
{"Question": "SEEK + OKAY = LOOSE", "Answer": "9557 + 2738 = 12295"}
{"Question": "GRAB + HAIR = TIGHT", "Answer": "7526 + 3205 = 10731"}
{"Question": "SNAP + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "8921 + 3209 = 12130"}
{"Question": "LOUD + AUTO = RURAL", "Answer": "3924 + 8259 = 12183"}
{"Question": "SOON + MERE = TERMS", "Answer": "9557 + 3282 = 12839"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "3556 + 8612 = 12168"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SNAP = WASTE", "Answer": "6558 + 3807 = 10365"}
{"Question": "POOL + BLUE = UPPER", "Answer": "3667 + 9718 = 13385"}
{"Question": "IDEA + SEND = TASTE", "Answer": "8572 + 3745 = 12317"}
{"Question": "ALLY + GENE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9118 + 4373 = 13491"}
{"Question": "READ + GAME = EAGER", "Answer": "8127 + 4291 = 12418"}
{"Question": "LEAN + TAPE = PANEL", "Answer": "8325 + 4213 = 12538"}
{"Question": "TOOL + HERE = VOTER", "Answer": "8227 + 4636 = 12863"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRAG = GRADE", "Answer": "4332 + 8251 = 12583"}
{"Question": "BEER + GRAY = MAYBE", "Answer": "4335 + 6508 = 10843"}
{"Question": "YEAH + RACE = MARRY", "Answer": "4638 + 9356 = 13994"}
{"Question": "ROOM + DATA = MOTOR", "Answer": "8331 + 4707 = 13038"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRAG = AWARD", "Answer": "4556 + 8612 = 13168"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRAG = GUARD", "Answer": "4557 + 8721 = 13278"}
{"Question": "BEAN + TAKE = ENTER", "Answer": "4162 + 8651 = 12813"}
{"Question": "OKAY + RANK = HONOR", "Answer": "4782 + 9867 = 14649"}
{"Question": "TEAM + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "5314 + 7123 = 12437"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SLIP = ELITE", "Answer": "9224 + 5467 = 14691"}
{"Question": "HEAT + BAKE = CATCH", "Answer": "5629 + 7286 = 12915"}
{"Question": "HERE + TRIP = IRISH", "Answer": "6929 + 5217 = 12146"}
{"Question": "HEAT + CARE = EARTH", "Answer": "8137 + 5341 = 13478"}
{"Question": "HEAT + CAKE = MATCH", "Answer": "5639 + 8346 = 13985"}
{"Question": "BEER + DRUG = GUARD", "Answer": "5337 + 8741 = 14078"}
{"Question": "TERM + URGE = METER", "Answer": "8341 + 5493 = 13834"}
{"Question": "BOOT + STAR = GRASS", "Answer": "8662 + 5293 = 13955"}
{"Question": "HERO + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5264 + 9682 = 14946"}
{"Question": "DATA + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "7383 + 5869 = 13252"}
{"Question": "HEEL + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "5884 + 7431 = 13315"}
{"Question": "DEAL + CARE = ARMED", "Answer": "6412 + 7134 = 13546"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TYPE = LEAST", "Answer": "6114 + 7493 = 13607"}
{"Question": "ROOF + GENE = OFFER", "Answer": "9115 + 6434 = 15549"}
{"Question": "HEAD + TAPE = DEPTH", "Answer": "6521 + 9275 = 15796"}
{"Question": "HEAT + GAME = MATCH", "Answer": "7235 + 6312 = 13547"}
{"Question": "ROOT + STEP = HORSE", "Answer": "7334 + 6428 = 13762"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SLOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "6441 + 9153 = 15594"}
{"Question": "HEAT + RACE = OTHER", "Answer": "8254 + 6572 = 14826"}
{"Question": "YEAR + TAPE = PARTY", "Answer": "9257 + 6512 = 15769"}
{"Question": "BEER + CROP = PRICE", "Answer": "6554 + 8431 = 14985"}
{"Question": "DOOR + GRAB = BOARD", "Answer": "8557 + 6721 = 15278"}
{"Question": "IRON + YOUR = FUNNY", "Answer": "8472 + 6754 = 15226"}
{"Question": "HEEL + DATA = CATCH", "Answer": "6882 + 7434 = 14316"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ALSO = COUCH", "Answer": "8223 + 7395 = 15618"}
{"Question": "GENE + ONLY = LEGAL", "Answer": "7525 + 8216 = 15741"}
{"Question": "ALLY + HERE = REACH", "Answer": "8332 + 7515 = 15847"}
{"Question": "ITEM + DEBT = MEDIA", "Answer": "7351 + 8523 = 15874"}
{"Question": "TOOL + CLUE = ELECT", "Answer": "7556 + 8631 = 16187"}
{"Question": "STEP + LEFT = APPLE", "Answer": "8527 + 9265 = 17792"}
{"Question": "LOOK + GENE = HELLO", "Answer": "9225 + 8767 = 17992"}
{"Question": "ROOT + PLOT = RATIO", "Answer": "1226 + 9426 = 10652"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = SHIFT", "Answer": "1338 + 9638 = 10976"}
{"Question": "PEER + OVER = PRIOR", "Answer": "1440 + 8940 = 10380"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = RURAL", "Answer": "8442 + 1742 = 10184"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = APART", "Answer": "1443 + 8743 = 10186"}
{"Question": "SOON + IRON = START", "Answer": "1445 + 8945 = 10390"}
{"Question": "SEEM + THEM = THESE", "Answer": "9447 + 1047 = 10494"}
{"Question": "MEET + DIET = DRAMA", "Answer": "9448 + 1248 = 10696"}
{"Question": "MOON + IRON = METER", "Answer": "1553 + 8653 = 10206"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ONLY = ASIAN", "Answer": "1556 + 9256 = 10812"}
{"Question": "TEEN + WHEN = TOOTH", "Answer": "1557 + 8457 = 10014"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SHOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1662 + 8462 = 10124"}
{"Question": "SOON + IRON = STONE", "Answer": "1662 + 8962 = 10624"}
{"Question": "MEET + POET = MONTH", "Answer": "1662 + 9062 = 10724"}
{"Question": "PEER + OVER = PIECE", "Answer": "1663 + 8963 = 10626"}
{"Question": "PEER + USER = PAUSE", "Answer": "1663 + 9263 = 10926"}
{"Question": "HEEL + FUEL = FRESH", "Answer": "8664 + 1964 = 10628"}
{"Question": "ODDS + AIDS = ORDER", "Answer": "1665 + 8965 = 10630"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = START", "Answer": "1665 + 9065 = 10730"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ONLY = AGAIN", "Answer": "1667 + 8467 = 10134"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ONLY = LOSS", "Answer": "5772 + 1372 = 7144"}
{"Question": "ALLY + HOLY = AGREE", "Answer": "1772 + 8572 = 10344"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = SHELL", "Answer": "1772 + 8972 = 10744"}
{"Question": "ALLY + UGLY = AGREE", "Answer": "1772 + 9072 = 10844"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = SHOOT", "Answer": "1773 + 8673 = 10446"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = AFTER", "Answer": "1779 + 8579 = 10358"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = FREE", "Answer": "1883 + 5683 = 7566"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = STILL", "Answer": "1883 + 9083 = 10966"}
{"Question": "BEER + OVER = ERROR", "Answer": "7110 + 2910 = 10020"}
{"Question": "DEER + USER = ROUND", "Answer": "2331 + 8531 = 10862"}
{"Question": "TEEN + OPEN = PORT", "Answer": "6338 + 2938 = 9276"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SHOT = WHOSE", "Answer": "2443 + 8043 = 10486"}
{"Question": "SOON + UPON = ISSUE", "Answer": "2445 + 9845 = 12290"}
{"Question": "DEEP + STEP = PRESS", "Answer": "7661 + 2961 = 10622"}
{"Question": "ALLY + UGLY = LUNG", "Answer": "2778 + 4678 = 7456"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SHOT = HOST", "Answer": "2880 + 6980 = 9860"}
{"Question": "MEET + DIET = TREND", "Answer": "7881 + 2981 = 10862"}
{"Question": "MEET + POET = TROOP", "Answer": "7991 + 2891 = 10882"}
{"Question": "TEEN + OPEN = ERROR", "Answer": "6115 + 3915 = 10030"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = EXIST", "Answer": "3118 + 7618 = 10736"}
{"Question": "ROOT + SHOT = THREE", "Answer": "7661 + 3061 = 10722"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SPOT = PASS", "Answer": "3772 + 4872 = 8644"}
{"Question": "TEEN + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "4112 + 6012 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TEEN + OPEN = EVENT", "Answer": "4112 + 9012 = 13124"}
{"Question": "MEET + DIET = THEME", "Answer": "4221 + 9021 = 13242"}
{"Question": "SEEM + POEM = MOUSE", "Answer": "4221 + 9321 = 13542"}
{"Question": "ODDS + AIDS = SALAD", "Answer": "9221 + 4821 = 14042"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SHOT = THOSE", "Answer": "4331 + 6031 = 10362"}
{"Question": "FEED + USED = STUFF", "Answer": "4772 + 9172 = 13944"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = THREE", "Answer": "4883 + 5683 = 10566"}
{"Question": "ALLY + RELY = PEACE", "Answer": "6227 + 8427 = 14654"}
{"Question": "SOON + IRON = NOISE", "Answer": "6331 + 7431 = 13762"}
{"Question": "DEER + USER = PROUD", "Answer": "8334 + 6234 = 14568"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ITEM = TERMS", "Answer": "8449 + 6149 = 14598"}
{"Question": "BEER + USER = STUFF", "Answer": "6772 + 9172 = 15944"}
{"Question": "FOOT + PLOT = STAFF", "Answer": "6883 + 7083 = 13966"}
{"Question": "DEER + OVER = BLOOD", "Answer": "8339 + 7439 = 15778"}
{"Question": "ALLY + HOLY = CLASS", "Answer": "8772 + 9072 = 17844"}
{"Question": "ALLY + UGLY = GLASS", "Answer": "9772 + 8172 = 17944"}
{"Question": "ROOT + SHOT = FORTH", "Answer": "8775 + 9075 = 17850"}
{"Question": "FOOT + SHOE = FIFTH", "Answer": "1224 + 8925 = 10149"}
{"Question": "FEEL + DIET = FIELD", "Answer": "1224 + 9025 = 10249"}
{"Question": "BEER + DIET = BOARD", "Answer": "1224 + 9625 = 10849"}
{"Question": "COOL + SHOE = SALES", "Answer": "9226 + 1425 = 10651"}
{"Question": "TEEN + IDEA = THANK", "Answer": "1225 + 9628 = 10853"}
{"Question": "ODDS + RIDE = OFFER", "Answer": "1332 + 8736 = 10068"}
{"Question": "FOOD + IRON = FENCE", "Answer": "1332 + 9538 = 10870"}
{"Question": "GOOD + SHOE = GUESS", "Answer": "1445 + 8943 = 10388"}
{"Question": "FEEL + STEP = FALSE", "Answer": "1446 + 9248 = 10694"}
{"Question": "COOK + SHOT = CATCH", "Answer": "1554 + 9258 = 10812"}
{"Question": "ODDS + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9557 + 1258 = 10815"}
{"Question": "TOOL + WHOM = THEME", "Answer": "1665 + 9062 = 10727"}
{"Question": "SEED + OVER = START", "Answer": "1667 + 8563 = 10230"}
{"Question": "ODDS + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "1667 + 8963 = 10630"}
{"Question": "FEEL + USED = FALSE", "Answer": "1772 + 8475 = 10247"}
{"Question": "BEER + ITEM = TIME", "Answer": "1773 + 6874 = 8647"}
{"Question": "DEER + THEM = THIRD", "Answer": "9774 + 1075 = 10849"}
{"Question": "TEEN + IDEA = TREAT", "Answer": "1776 + 8975 = 10751"}
{"Question": "BEER + DIET = BIRTH", "Answer": "1778 + 9075 = 10853"}
{"Question": "DEEP + THEM = EMPTY", "Answer": "9118 + 3712 = 12830"}
{"Question": "DOOR + UPON = POUND", "Answer": "9225 + 3124 = 12349"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ITEM = ELITE", "Answer": "8112 + 4319 = 12431"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FROM = METER", "Answer": "9226 + 5721 = 14947"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "9223 + 5724 = 14947"}
{"Question": "TEEN + CHEF = FENCE", "Answer": "5443 + 8941 = 14384"}
{"Question": "DOOR + SHOE = BREAD", "Answer": "5442 + 6943 = 12385"}
{"Question": "MEET + USED = STUFF", "Answer": "7442 + 5146 = 12588"}
{"Question": "DEEP + OVER = PROOF", "Answer": "5881 + 6782 = 12663"}
{"Question": "ALLY + ROLE = ERROR", "Answer": "9884 + 5681 = 15565"}
{"Question": "MEET + USER = STORM", "Answer": "9225 + 6124 = 15349"}
{"Question": "DEEP + ITEM = MEDIA", "Answer": "7338 + 6431 = 13769"}
{"Question": "PEER + IDEA = RAPID", "Answer": "8331 + 6534 = 14865"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BELT = PLATE", "Answer": "6443 + 8249 = 14692"}
{"Question": "DEEP + OVER = PROVE", "Answer": "8551 + 6054 = 14605"}
{"Question": "BEER + STEP = TERMS", "Answer": "6557 + 9152 = 15709"}
{"Question": "DOOR + SHOE = AHEAD", "Answer": "7558 + 6359 = 13917"}
{"Question": "TEEN + IDEA = STATE", "Answer": "6885 + 9483 = 16368"}
{"Question": "KEEP + IDEA = RAPID", "Answer": "7443 + 8946 = 16389"}
{"Question": "DEER + OPEN = PROUD", "Answer": "9556 + 7153 = 16709"}
{"Question": "TOOL + IRON = ENTER", "Answer": "9556 + 8357 = 17913"}
{"Question": "FLEE + TALE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8266 + 1926 = 10192"}
{"Question": "SELL + FUEL = FALSE", "Answer": "9266 + 1426 = 10692"}
{"Question": "COOL + KILL = LOCK", "Answer": "1228 + 6988 = 8216"}
{"Question": "FLEE + ABLE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9288 + 1528 = 10816"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SELL = TASTE", "Answer": "1228 + 9688 = 10916"}
{"Question": "FEEL + POLL = PRIOR", "Answer": "8335 + 1955 = 10290"}
{"Question": "COOL + FALL = FENCE", "Answer": "9335 + 1455 = 10790"}
{"Question": "COOL + TELL = CATCH", "Answer": "1337 + 9577 = 10914"}
{"Question": "POOL + BELL = PAPER", "Answer": "1443 + 8733 = 10176"}
{"Question": "POOL + BALL = PHOTO", "Answer": "1447 + 8977 = 10424"}
{"Question": "TREE + FIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "1477 + 9247 = 10724"}
{"Question": "FALL + REAL = FORCE", "Answer": "1522 + 9452 = 10974"}
{"Question": "POOL + CALL = PIECE", "Answer": "1554 + 9344 = 10898"}
{"Question": "TOOL + BELL = THREE", "Answer": "1556 + 9266 = 10822"}
{"Question": "COOL + BILL = CABIN", "Answer": "1557 + 9377 = 10934"}
{"Question": "POOL + BILL = PIECE", "Answer": "1558 + 9088 = 10646"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TALL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1662 + 8522 = 10184"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BILL = FALSE", "Answer": "1663 + 8733 = 10396"}
{"Question": "FLEE + MALE = FINAL", "Answer": "1633 + 8963 = 10596"}
{"Question": "FILL + RAIL = FEWER", "Answer": "1644 + 8564 = 10208"}
{"Question": "CALL + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "1644 + 8764 = 10408"}
{"Question": "FEEL + CALL = COLOR", "Answer": "8773 + 1533 = 10306"}
{"Question": "COOL + SELL = STATE", "Answer": "8773 + 1633 = 10406"}
{"Question": "ODDS + KISS = SOON", "Answer": "1774 + 2344 = 4118"}
{"Question": "ODDS + KISS = DOOR", "Answer": "1774 + 5344 = 7118"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TALL = TOOTH", "Answer": "8774 + 1244 = 10018"}
{"Question": "COOL + HELL = CATCH", "Answer": "1774 + 8544 = 10318"}
{"Question": "TALL + MEAL = METER", "Answer": "9822 + 1082 = 10904"}
{"Question": "COOL + TALL = CATCH", "Answer": "1883 + 9033 = 10916"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ROLL = FORCE", "Answer": "1884 + 9044 = 10928"}
{"Question": "MALL + REAL = ARMY", "Answer": "6877 + 1287 = 8164"}
{"Question": "TALL + COAL = TOOTH", "Answer": "1922 + 8092 = 10014"}
{"Question": "COOL + BELL = CHEEK", "Answer": "1993 + 8233 = 10226"}
{"Question": "POOL + BELL = PIECE", "Answer": "1993 + 8633 = 10626"}
{"Question": "FEEL + POLL = PROOF", "Answer": "8994 + 1344 = 10338"}
{"Question": "BILL + SOIL = ODDS", "Answer": "5166 + 2716 = 7882"}
{"Question": "FREE + DARE = AHEAD", "Answer": "8466 + 2146 = 10612"}
{"Question": "TREE + CARE = ELECT", "Answer": "2611 + 7561 = 10172"}
{"Question": "SELL + FUEL = ISSUE", "Answer": "2688 + 9568 = 12256"}
{"Question": "BILL + RAIL = ARAB", "Answer": "2711 + 5871 = 8582"}
{"Question": "WALL + REAL = LOWER", "Answer": "7811 + 2981 = 10792"}
{"Question": "ODDS + KISS = FOOD", "Answer": "2884 + 6344 = 9228"}
{"Question": "FREE + CORE = ROOF", "Answer": "2911 + 6091 = 9002"}
{"Question": "SELL + FUEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "3211 + 6821 = 10032"}
{"Question": "HILL + JAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "8244 + 3924 = 12168"}
{"Question": "COOL + SELL = ODDS", "Answer": "3882 + 4122 = 8004"}
{"Question": "BALL + MEAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "8122 + 4712 = 12834"}
{"Question": "TALL + REAL = ENTER", "Answer": "4288 + 6128 = 10416"}
{"Question": "BALL + REAL = EAGER", "Answer": "9377 + 4137 = 13514"}
{"Question": "TOOL + CALL = ELECT", "Answer": "4552 + 7622 = 12174"}
{"Question": "COOL + MALL = ALBUM", "Answer": "8552 + 4122 = 12674"}
{"Question": "WALL + REAL = FEWER", "Answer": "9577 + 4357 = 13934"}
{"Question": "BALL + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "5822 + 4382 = 10204"}
{"Question": "TREE + CORE = REACT", "Answer": "8144 + 5914 = 14058"}
{"Question": "HILL + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "6233 + 5923 = 12156"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LESS = ERROR", "Answer": "5332 + 9122 = 14454"}
{"Question": "KISS + THIS = FIFTH", "Answer": "5344 + 7834 = 13178"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TALL = FLOAT", "Answer": "5334 + 8744 = 14078"}
{"Question": "FLEE + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "7633 + 5963 = 13596"}
{"Question": "COOL + PULL = SLEEP", "Answer": "5664 + 8344 = 14008"}
{"Question": "ODDS + MESS = HELLO", "Answer": "6773 + 5233 = 12006"}
{"Question": "POOL + KILL = CLOCK", "Answer": "5774 + 8944 = 14718"}
{"Question": "POOL + TELL = ELECT", "Answer": "5994 + 8144 = 14138"}
{"Question": "HEEL + ROLL = FLOOR", "Answer": "5994 + 8344 = 14338"}
{"Question": "BALL + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "7133 + 6413 = 13546"}
{"Question": "TALL + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "6144 + 8514 = 14658"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SALE = BASIS", "Answer": "8233 + 6423 = 14656"}
{"Question": "COOL + WELL = LOWER", "Answer": "6331 + 7411 = 13742"}
{"Question": "FLEE + ABLE = CLASS", "Answer": "6455 + 8345 = 14800"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ROLL = COLOR", "Answer": "7448 + 6388 = 13836"}
{"Question": "FREE + DARE = BREAD", "Answer": "6544 + 8954 = 15498"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BALL = PROOF", "Answer": "6773 + 8233 = 15006"}
{"Question": "COOL + YELL = DELAY", "Answer": "8773 + 6533 = 15306"}
{"Question": "KNEE + LINE = HELLO", "Answer": "7255 + 8625 = 15880"}
{"Question": "FEEL + ROLL = SORRY", "Answer": "7335 + 9655 = 16990"}
{"Question": "COOL + WALL = LOWER", "Answer": "7551 + 8311 = 15862"}
{"Question": "COOL + HILL = FIFTH", "Answer": "7554 + 8644 = 16198"}
{"Question": "COOL + YELL = SORRY", "Answer": "7664 + 8344 = 16008"}
{"Question": "TOOL + MALE = TREAT", "Answer": "1223 + 9638 = 10861"}
{"Question": "TEEN + LONG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1225 + 9456 = 10681"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SITE = BASIS", "Answer": "1225 + 9754 = 10979"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1226 + 9365 = 10591"}
{"Question": "BEER + TURN = BIRTH", "Answer": "1226 + 9467 = 10693"}
{"Question": "BEER + PART = BIRTH", "Answer": "1332 + 8925 = 10257"}
{"Question": "SEED + LADY = LOOSE", "Answer": "8334 + 1749 = 10083"}
{"Question": "LEAN + SAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "1735 + 8352 = 10087"}
{"Question": "WEEK + TOSS = WASTE", "Answer": "1338 + 9255 = 10593"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BASE = BLOOD", "Answer": "9335 + 1658 = 10993"}
{"Question": "TOOL + SELF = THREE", "Answer": "1338 + 9284 = 10622"}
{"Question": "STAR + VARY = SERVE", "Answer": "1943 + 8437 = 10380"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "1445 + 9056 = 10501"}
{"Question": "ROOT + MALL = METER", "Answer": "8442 + 1766 = 10208"}
{"Question": "LOOK + CAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "1448 + 9083 = 10531"}
{"Question": "MOOD + AIDS = MEDIA", "Answer": "1552 + 8726 = 10278"}
{"Question": "HALL + TEAR = HEART", "Answer": "1522 + 9057 = 10579"}
{"Question": "BALL + STAR = START", "Answer": "9522 + 1058 = 10580"}
{"Question": "DEER + CORN = DANCE", "Answer": "1553 + 8732 = 10285"}
{"Question": "BEER + CARD = ARAB", "Answer": "7554 + 1943 = 9497"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HAND = TOOTH", "Answer": "1556 + 8462 = 10018"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TASK = TASTE", "Answer": "9556 + 1062 = 10618"}
{"Question": "GOOD + LADY = LEGAL", "Answer": "9557 + 1374 = 10931"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TURN = THREE", "Answer": "9558 + 1286 = 10844"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ARMY = AWARE", "Answer": "8667 + 1479 = 10146"}
{"Question": "TELL + IDEA = TREAT", "Answer": "1677 + 8964 = 10641"}
{"Question": "PEER + YARD = PARTY", "Answer": "1667 + 9072 = 10739"}
{"Question": "COOL + SALE = SALES", "Answer": "9667 + 1074 = 10741"}
{"Question": "MOON + PANT = METER", "Answer": "1773 + 8432 = 10205"}
{"Question": "ODDS + REST = OFFER", "Answer": "1775 + 8253 = 10028"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "8772 + 1355 = 10127"}
{"Question": "BEER + FIRM = BLAME", "Answer": "1775 + 8652 = 10427"}
{"Question": "POOL + BELT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1775 + 8952 = 10727"}
{"Question": "MEET + LOTS = MOUSE", "Answer": "1775 + 9052 = 10827"}
{"Question": "BEER + CARD = BASIC", "Answer": "1775 + 9054 = 10829"}
{"Question": "COOL + SALT = SALES", "Answer": "9778 + 1083 = 10861"}
{"Question": "BEER + DIRT = BIRTH", "Answer": "1778 + 9086 = 10864"}
{"Question": "TEEN + SAND = TASTE", "Answer": "1883 + 9035 = 10918"}
{"Question": "FEED + LADY = FALSE", "Answer": "1886 + 9062 = 10948"}
{"Question": "LOOK + BAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "1886 + 9065 = 10951"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TOSS = TOOTH", "Answer": "8996 + 1022 = 10018"}
{"Question": "MEET + LOTS = LOOSE", "Answer": "8995 + 1054 = 10049"}
{"Question": "DEER + FARM = BLOOD", "Answer": "2335 + 8657 = 10992"}
{"Question": "BALL + ROAD = ERROR", "Answer": "9688 + 2564 = 12252"}
{"Question": "DOOR + SURE = ODDS", "Answer": "2884 + 5341 = 8225"}
{"Question": "DOOR + YELL = SORRY", "Answer": "9228 + 3655 = 12883"}
{"Question": "ROOT + WELL = TOWER", "Answer": "9221 + 3088 = 12309"}
{"Question": "TOOL + RULE = ALTER", "Answer": "3442 + 8926 = 12368"}
{"Question": "CALL + HEAR = REACH", "Answer": "7522 + 3051 = 10573"}
{"Question": "IDEA + MEAL = CLAIM", "Answer": "3067 + 9672 = 12739"}
{"Question": "PEER + LOSS = APPLE", "Answer": "3775 + 9622 = 13397"}
{"Question": "FIVE + OVER = PROOF", "Answer": "8576 + 3762 = 12338"}
{"Question": "LESS + ITEM = VISIT", "Answer": "9766 + 3872 = 13638"}
{"Question": "SEEM + JUMP = ISSUE", "Answer": "3886 + 9462 = 13348"}
{"Question": "HALL + BOAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "3922 + 6091 = 10013"}
{"Question": "TELL + IDEA = ELITE", "Answer": "4122 + 8719 = 12841"}
{"Question": "ALLY + MESS = LEGAL", "Answer": "8115 + 4266 = 12381"}
{"Question": "ROOF + YELL = SORRY", "Answer": "8229 + 4655 = 12884"}
{"Question": "LESS + IDEA = ASIDE", "Answer": "4322 + 8531 = 12853"}
{"Question": "DOOR + FIRE = TIRED", "Answer": "4335 + 8259 = 12594"}
{"Question": "BALL + YEAH = HAPPY", "Answer": "4377 + 8631 = 13008"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ARMY = GRASS", "Answer": "4558 + 9386 = 13944"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LEFT = METER", "Answer": "4665 + 8259 = 12924"}
{"Question": "BALL + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "4755 + 9172 = 13927"}
{"Question": "BOSS + FROM = REFER", "Answer": "4755 + 9176 = 13931"}
{"Question": "ALLY + FREE = TREAT", "Answer": "6773 + 4088 = 10861"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TELL = ASSET", "Answer": "4882 + 7355 = 12237"}
{"Question": "CLUB + TUBE = ELECT", "Answer": "4286 + 7861 = 12147"}
{"Question": "DEEP + LOSS = APPLE", "Answer": "7882 + 4366 = 12248"}
{"Question": "TELL + USED = STATE", "Answer": "4866 + 9182 = 14048"}
{"Question": "IDEA + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9786 + 4862 = 14648"}
{"Question": "FLAT + RATE = ALTER", "Answer": "5213 + 7134 = 12347"}
{"Question": "TOOL + MILK = LIMIT", "Answer": "8221 + 5317 = 13538"}
{"Question": "DOOR + GIRL = WORLD", "Answer": "5226 + 7469 = 12695"}
{"Question": "BALL + HEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "5288 + 7629 = 12917"}
{"Question": "REAL + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "8431 + 5317 = 13748"}
{"Question": "USER + VERY = SERVE", "Answer": "5134 + 8349 = 13483"}
{"Question": "ODDS + REST = STORE", "Answer": "7441 + 5312 = 12753"}
{"Question": "HILL + QUIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8422 + 5746 = 14168"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HURT = TOOTH", "Answer": "5447 + 8971 = 14418"}
{"Question": "BOAT + DATE = LABEL", "Answer": "5048 + 9483 = 14531"}
{"Question": "SELL + IDEA = RAISE", "Answer": "8622 + 5964 = 14586"}
{"Question": "BALL + OKAY = CLOCK", "Answer": "5644 + 9268 = 14912"}
{"Question": "ROOM + CAMP = PAPER", "Answer": "8667 + 5471 = 14138"}
{"Question": "ODDS + RISK = ERROR", "Answer": "9772 + 5823 = 15595"}
{"Question": "MEET + INTO = NOISE", "Answer": "5773 + 9134 = 14907"}
{"Question": "LESS + DIET = TITLE", "Answer": "5877 + 6281 = 12158"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LIFE = OFFER", "Answer": "7113 + 6234 = 13347"}
{"Question": "BEER + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "7114 + 6342 = 13456"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HELL = OTHER", "Answer": "7113 + 6544 = 13657"}
{"Question": "HERO + DROP = ORDER", "Answer": "6431 + 7312 = 13743"}
{"Question": "IDEA + BEAR = ARISE", "Answer": "6241 + 7413 = 13654"}
{"Question": "ODDS + BALL = LABOR", "Answer": "6449 + 7311 = 13760"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LAST = SALAD", "Answer": "6441 + 9513 = 15954"}
{"Question": "FULL + TRUE = REFER", "Answer": "6488 + 7143 = 13631"}
{"Question": "BOOT + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "6553 + 7834 = 14387"}
{"Question": "BELL + IDEA = ALIVE", "Answer": "6544 + 8351 = 14895"}
{"Question": "FILL + SPIN = PROOF", "Answer": "7822 + 6185 = 14007"}
{"Question": "USER + HERO = TOOTH", "Answer": "6583 + 7834 = 14417"}
{"Question": "ODDS + LAST = USUAL", "Answer": "6884 + 7243 = 14127"}
{"Question": "POOL + ABLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6884 + 7342 = 14226"}
{"Question": "ACID + RIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "9584 + 6842 = 16426"}
{"Question": "BEER + YARD = HAPPY", "Answer": "6885 + 7452 = 14337"}
{"Question": "BELL + OPEN = ALONE", "Answer": "6855 + 9083 = 15938"}
{"Question": "DATE + ITEM = MEDIA", "Answer": "8625 + 7251 = 15876"}
{"Question": "TREE + FORM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8322 + 7531 = 15853"}
{"Question": "DOOR + EARN = ARMED", "Answer": "7335 + 8152 = 15487"}
{"Question": "TALL + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7522 + 8156 = 15678"}
{"Question": "ROOF + CELL = FORCE", "Answer": "8551 + 7322 = 15873"}
{"Question": "ROOM + CAMP = PORCH", "Answer": "7553 + 8231 = 15784"}
{"Question": "TEEN + HILL = FIFTH", "Answer": "8554 + 7633 = 16187"}
{"Question": "BOAT + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "7056 + 8562 = 15618"}
{"Question": "STAR + EARN = TASTE", "Answer": "7156 + 8562 = 15718"}
{"Question": "IDEA + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "8065 + 7651 = 15716"}
{"Question": "DOOR + EARN = SENSE", "Answer": "9883 + 7534 = 17417"}
{"Question": "SELL + IDEA = FALSE", "Answer": "8255 + 9327 = 17582"}
{"Question": "WOOD + RIDE = FEWER", "Answer": "8552 + 9327 = 17879"}
{"Question": "BEER + TURN = FRONT", "Answer": "8557 + 9072 = 17629"}
{"Question": "PANT + INTO = UNION", "Answer": "9075 + 8752 = 17827"}
{"Question": "COOL + FEEL = CHECK", "Answer": "1993 + 8223 = 10216"}
{"Question": "GRAY + VARY = EVER", "Answer": "1256 + 7526 = 8782"}
{"Question": "BEER + DOOR = BLAME", "Answer": "1226 + 9556 = 10782"}
{"Question": "BORN + IRON = RING", "Answer": "1752 + 3572 = 5324"}
{"Question": "SURE + TRUE = REST", "Answer": "1562 + 4652 = 6214"}
{"Question": "BLUE + RULE = USER", "Answer": "1583 + 6853 = 8436"}
{"Question": "TOOL + FEEL = TASTE", "Answer": "1553 + 8663 = 10216"}
{"Question": "FEEL + COOL = ONCE", "Answer": "1884 + 5774 = 7658"}
{"Question": "MEET + ROOT = TRUE", "Answer": "2447 + 5117 = 7564"}
{"Question": "SEED + FOOD = DRESS", "Answer": "2331 + 7991 = 10322"}
{"Question": "TRUE + SURE = USER", "Answer": "2673 + 4763 = 7436"}
{"Question": "HEEL + TOOL = EIGHT", "Answer": "4118 + 6228 = 10346"}
{"Question": "HEEL + COOL = FENCE", "Answer": "4226 + 8556 = 12782"}
{"Question": "GOOD + NEED = YOUNG", "Answer": "4337 + 9557 = 13894"}
{"Question": "BEER + DOOR = MAYBE", "Answer": "4663 + 7883 = 12546"}
{"Question": "TRUE + PURE = METER", "Answer": "4673 + 8763 = 13436"}
{"Question": "PURE + TRUE = SUPER", "Answer": "5326 + 8236 = 13562"}
{"Question": "BLUE + RULE = LEARN", "Answer": "6175 + 9715 = 15890"}
{"Question": "DEER + POOR = BOARD", "Answer": "6228 + 9558 = 15786"}
{"Question": "SEEM + ROOM = TERMS", "Answer": "6338 + 7448 = 13786"}
{"Question": "ROOM + SEEM = HORSE", "Answer": "7556 + 8226 = 15782"}
{"Question": "POOL + HEEL = COACH", "Answer": "7664 + 8554 = 16218"}
{"Question": "LOOK + SEEK = APPLE", "Answer": "8556 + 9226 = 17782"}
{"Question": "SURE + DRUG = USED", "Answer": "2831 + 5384 = 8215"}
{"Question": "SEED + BOOT = TASTE", "Answer": "2554 + 7661 = 10215"}
{"Question": "SEED + ROOM = TERMS", "Answer": "4225 + 8669 = 12894"}
{"Question": "COOK + NEED = DANCE", "Answer": "4667 + 5881 = 10548"}
{"Question": "DOOR + ALLY = ROUND", "Answer": "6441 + 7885 = 14326"}
{"Question": "ROOF + MEET = TERMS", "Answer": "7229 + 8551 = 15780"}
{"Question": "GRAB + EARN = LABEL", "Answer": "7268 + 9623 = 16891"}
{"Question": "OKAY + BAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "7352 + 8539 = 15891"}
{"Question": "ROOT + SEAT = START", "Answer": "9220 + 1570 = 10790"}
{"Question": "TUBE + ABLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1923 + 8263 = 10186"}
{"Question": "TEEN + CORN = ONCE", "Answer": "1226 + 3406 = 4632"}
{"Question": "BEER + FAIR = BIBLE", "Answer": "1226 + 8906 = 10132"}
{"Question": "SEED + ACID = SINCE", "Answer": "1226 + 9306 = 10532"}
{"Question": "BOOT + HURT = HELLO", "Answer": "9226 + 1546 = 10772"}
{"Question": "COOL + FUEL = CYCLE", "Answer": "1227 + 8947 = 10174"}
{"Question": "BEER + STAR = BASIC", "Answer": "1228 + 9708 = 10936"}
{"Question": "FOOD + CARD = FENCE", "Answer": "1335 + 8945 = 10280"}
{"Question": "ALLY + BUSY = ASSET", "Answer": "1336 + 8706 = 10042"}
{"Question": "SOON + THEN = SCENE", "Answer": "1336 + 8926 = 10262"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LEAF = RIFLE", "Answer": "1337 + 9457 = 10794"}
{"Question": "TOOL + REAL = THREE", "Answer": "1338 + 9628 = 10966"}
{"Question": "USER + YEAR = YOURS", "Answer": "9638 + 1348 = 10986"}
{"Question": "TEEN + PLAN = TITLE", "Answer": "1442 + 8732 = 10174"}
{"Question": "SEED + GLAD = SLIDE", "Answer": "1442 + 9082 = 10524"}
{"Question": "SEED + ACID = SLIDE", "Answer": "1442 + 9382 = 10824"}
{"Question": "COOL + DEAL = CYCLE", "Answer": "1443 + 8693 = 10136"}
{"Question": "SOON + BEAN = SENSE", "Answer": "1445 + 9065 = 10510"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TINY = AGAIN", "Answer": "1446 + 8726 = 10172"}
{"Question": "ALLY + VERY = AGREE", "Answer": "1446 + 9276 = 10722"}
{"Question": "CARE + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8647 + 1427 = 10074"}
{"Question": "FEED + CARD = FORCE", "Answer": "1447 + 8937 = 10384"}
{"Question": "BEER + STAR = STATE", "Answer": "9447 + 1057 = 10504"}
{"Question": "PEER + STAR = PLATE", "Answer": "1447 + 9387 = 10834"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CITY = ADAPT", "Answer": "1552 + 8642 = 10194"}
{"Question": "BOOK + RISK = BASIS", "Answer": "1552 + 8942 = 10494"}
{"Question": "ODDS + THIS = THESE", "Answer": "9553 + 1083 = 10636"}
{"Question": "FEED + LAND = FINAL", "Answer": "1554 + 8724 = 10278"}
{"Question": "SHOE + LOVE = SMELL", "Answer": "1954 + 8534 = 10488"}
{"Question": "BOOK + LACK = BASIC", "Answer": "1554 + 9084 = 10638"}
{"Question": "BOOK + SICK = BASIC", "Answer": "1554 + 9384 = 10938"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SHIT = BIRTH", "Answer": "1556 + 9206 = 10762"}
{"Question": "POOL + DEAL = PAPER", "Answer": "1557 + 8607 = 10164"}
{"Question": "HEAT + SALT = HOTEL", "Answer": "1258 + 9568 = 10826"}
{"Question": "SHOE + COME = SMELL", "Answer": "1358 + 9508 = 10866"}
{"Question": "POOL + REAL = PAPER", "Answer": "1559 + 8609 = 10168"}
{"Question": "BEER + HOUR = BUNCH", "Answer": "1559 + 8709 = 10268"}
{"Question": "SEED + LOAD = SHALL", "Answer": "1559 + 8729 = 10288"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SOIL = FALSE", "Answer": "1663 + 8723 = 10386"}
{"Question": "BOOT + PANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8663 + 1973 = 10636"}
{"Question": "BEER + STAR = STARE", "Answer": "9663 + 1073 = 10736"}
{"Question": "ROOT + EAST = ENTER", "Answer": "8664 + 1754 = 10418"}
{"Question": "WEEK + RISK = WORKS", "Answer": "1664 + 9284 = 10948"}
{"Question": "ODDS + THIS = ONION", "Answer": "1665 + 8745 = 10410"}
{"Question": "BEER + STIR = START", "Answer": "9665 + 1085 = 10750"}
{"Question": "BELT + FLAT = BIBLE", "Answer": "1467 + 8697 = 10164"}
{"Question": "FOOT + QUIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1667 + 8507 = 10174"}
{"Question": "DEEP + TRIP = DRIVE", "Answer": "1668 + 9078 = 10746"}
{"Question": "BOOK + DARK = BREAD", "Answer": "1669 + 8709 = 10378"}
{"Question": "BOOM + ITEM = TIME", "Answer": "1773 + 2463 = 4236"}
{"Question": "TEEN + PLAN = PANEL", "Answer": "8773 + 1603 = 10376"}
{"Question": "SOON + WHEN = STONE", "Answer": "1773 + 8963 = 10736"}
{"Question": "ROOT + MUST = METER", "Answer": "8774 + 1634 = 10408"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "8774 + 1694 = 10468"}
{"Question": "BOAT + EAST = ERROR", "Answer": "8275 + 1745 = 10020"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "1776 + 8406 = 10182"}
{"Question": "MEET + DIRT = DRAMA", "Answer": "8776 + 1506 = 10282"}
{"Question": "MEET + COAT = MATCH", "Answer": "1776 + 8906 = 10682"}
{"Question": "BOOT + DIRT = BIRTH", "Answer": "1776 + 9086 = 10862"}
{"Question": "BOOT + CAST = CATCH", "Answer": "9778 + 1038 = 10816"}
{"Question": "MOOD + HEAD = MEDIA", "Answer": "1778 + 9068 = 10846"}
{"Question": "FOOT + WEST = FEWER", "Answer": "1883 + 9023 = 10906"}
{"Question": "MORE + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1084 + 9824 = 10908"}
{"Question": "SEEK + TALK = TASTE", "Answer": "9884 + 1034 = 10918"}
{"Question": "TEEN + BORN = TOOTH", "Answer": "1993 + 8023 = 10016"}
{"Question": "CARE + TRUE = ELECT", "Answer": "7831 + 2341 = 10172"}
{"Question": "ROOT + EAST = THREE", "Answer": "8331 + 2491 = 10822"}
{"Question": "SOON + EARN = NURSE", "Answer": "7441 + 2931 = 10372"}
{"Question": "ROOT + DEBT = TIRED", "Answer": "8441 + 2391 = 10832"}
{"Question": "BEER + FAIR = ARAB", "Answer": "6443 + 2953 = 9396"}
{"Question": "BOOT + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8551 + 2061 = 10612"}
{"Question": "DEEP + CROP = PROUD", "Answer": "2661 + 8071 = 10732"}
{"Question": "ABLE + CLUE = RURAL", "Answer": "7568 + 2608 = 10176"}
{"Question": "ROOM + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "2771 + 8031 = 10802"}
{"Question": "DOOR + STAR = ODDS", "Answer": "5881 + 2671 = 8552"}
{"Question": "ROLE + BLUE = ERROR", "Answer": "2381 + 9851 = 12232"}
{"Question": "MEET + SHIT = THESE", "Answer": "3221 + 7051 = 10272"}
{"Question": "ALLY + THEY = METAL", "Answer": "3226 + 7506 = 10732"}
{"Question": "SHOT + POET = THOSE", "Answer": "7051 + 3521 = 10572"}
{"Question": "BELT + FLAT = TABLE", "Answer": "7251 + 3501 = 10752"}
{"Question": "DOOR + GEAR = ARGUE", "Answer": "3552 + 9412 = 12964"}
{"Question": "POOL + DEAL = APPLY", "Answer": "3557 + 9817 = 13374"}
{"Question": "CARE + URGE = OCCUR", "Answer": "3768 + 9628 = 13396"}
{"Question": "COOL + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "3881 + 7091 = 10972"}
{"Question": "MOON + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "3885 + 9025 = 12910"}
{"Question": "ROOT + HEAT = OTHER", "Answer": "4112 + 8762 = 12874"}
{"Question": "ROOT + EAST = VOTER", "Answer": "4332 + 8952 = 13284"}
{"Question": "READ + BAND = EAGER", "Answer": "4132 + 9382 = 13514"}
{"Question": "HIRE + URGE = TRUTH", "Answer": "4532 + 9382 = 13914"}
{"Question": "ROOT + BEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "6338 + 4518 = 10856"}
{"Question": "DEEP + CAMP = MEDIA", "Answer": "9338 + 4618 = 13956"}
{"Question": "FEAR + HAIR = BRIEF", "Answer": "4852 + 7532 = 12384"}
{"Question": "POOR + YEAR = HAPPY", "Answer": "8557 + 4327 = 12884"}
{"Question": "STAR + HAIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7562 + 4612 = 12174"}
{"Question": "PLAY + EASY = SLEEP", "Answer": "4267 + 8617 = 12884"}
{"Question": "FEEL + GIRL = RIFLE", "Answer": "9668 + 4318 = 13986"}
{"Question": "SHOE + NOTE = THESE", "Answer": "8370 + 4710 = 13080"}
{"Question": "SEED + GLAD = CLASS", "Answer": "8779 + 4309 = 13088"}
{"Question": "TOOL + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "7882 + 4912 = 12794"}
{"Question": "MOON + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "7883 + 4263 = 12146"}
{"Question": "BOOK + WALK = ALLOW", "Answer": "5992 + 4102 = 10094"}
{"Question": "LEAN + GAIN = ANGLE", "Answer": "7412 + 5162 = 12574"}
{"Question": "BEER + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "5114 + 8364 = 13478"}
{"Question": "LOOK + MASK = SOLAR", "Answer": "5224 + 7314 = 12538"}
{"Question": "COOL + TAIL = ELECT", "Answer": "5224 + 8934 = 14158"}
{"Question": "ABLE + CLUE = ELECT", "Answer": "5831 + 7341 = 13172"}
{"Question": "THIN + SIGN = FIFTH", "Answer": "5834 + 7324 = 13158"}
{"Question": "TEAR + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "5134 + 8324 = 13458"}
{"Question": "BEER + STAR = TERMS", "Answer": "5334 + 8164 = 13498"}
{"Question": "UPON + DOWN = WOUND", "Answer": "5234 + 8314 = 13548"}
{"Question": "DARE + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "5042 + 9482 = 14524"}
{"Question": "TEEN + GAIN = ANGLE", "Answer": "5663 + 8143 = 13806"}
{"Question": "BEER + FAIR = TRIBE", "Answer": "5663 + 8293 = 13956"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "5773 + 9163 = 14936"}
{"Question": "BOOT + SHIT = THESE", "Answer": "5881 + 7391 = 13272"}
{"Question": "RELY + PLAY = LAYER", "Answer": "6718 + 9158 = 15876"}
{"Question": "HEAT + PART = EARTH", "Answer": "6138 + 7348 = 13486"}
{"Question": "MEET + COAT = TEACH", "Answer": "6441 + 7931 = 14372"}
{"Question": "USER + NEAR = SENSE", "Answer": "8142 + 6472 = 14614"}
{"Question": "FLAT + EAST = LATER", "Answer": "6145 + 8435 = 14580"}
{"Question": "COOL + FUEL = ELECT", "Answer": "6445 + 8715 = 15160"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LEAF = EAGER", "Answer": "6773 + 8143 = 14916"}
{"Question": "LOAN + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "7128 + 9268 = 16396"}
{"Question": "BOOM + TERM = METER", "Answer": "7331 + 8521 = 15852"}
{"Question": "BOOT + REST = SERVE", "Answer": "7338 + 9618 = 16956"}
{"Question": "BEAT + LAST = TABLE", "Answer": "7251 + 8531 = 15782"}
{"Question": "ROOF + CHEF = FORCE", "Answer": "8551 + 7321 = 15872"}
{"Question": "UPON + DOWN = POUND", "Answer": "7154 + 8594 = 15748"}
{"Question": "TRUE + HUGE = METER", "Answer": "7256 + 9506 = 16762"}
{"Question": "FLAT + EAST = STEEL", "Answer": "9256 + 7516 = 16772"}
{"Question": "BEER + STAR = TASTE", "Answer": "7663 + 8153 = 15816"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HAIR = TOOTH", "Answer": "7664 + 8954 = 16618"}
{"Question": "ALLY + TINY = VITAL", "Answer": "8226 + 9756 = 17982"}
{"Question": "SOON + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "1226 + 9305 = 10531"}
{"Question": "SLIP + TIME = SMELL", "Answer": "1328 + 9205 = 10533"}
{"Question": "DOOR + TIME = TIRED", "Answer": "9556 + 1083 = 10639"}
{"Question": "SEED + FOLK = SLIDE", "Answer": "1556 + 8709 = 10265"}
{"Question": "BEER + AIDS = BOARD", "Answer": "1663 + 9274 = 10937"}
{"Question": "MEET + RAIL = MOTOR", "Answer": "1772 + 8436 = 10208"}
{"Question": "FEEL + YARD = FULLY", "Answer": "1772 + 8456 = 10228"}
{"Question": "BEER + HOST = BIRTH", "Answer": "1772 + 8496 = 10268"}
{"Question": "BEER + GLAD = BLADE", "Answer": "1772 + 9085 = 10857"}
{"Question": "BEER + TAIL = BIRTH", "Answer": "1773 + 8609 = 10382"}
{"Question": "COOL + SAFE = SALES", "Answer": "9778 + 1053 = 10831"}
{"Question": "ALLY + CODE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1779 + 8634 = 10413"}
{"Question": "STIR + VIEW = SERVE", "Answer": "1976 + 8704 = 10680"}
{"Question": "DOOR + HEAT = DEATH", "Answer": "1774 + 9085 = 10859"}
{"Question": "ROOF + GIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "1775 + 9086 = 10861"}
{"Question": "SNAP + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "3921 + 8257 = 12178"}
{"Question": "SEEM + FOUR = MOUSE", "Answer": "3551 + 9284 = 12835"}
{"Question": "TOOL + EARN = ALTER", "Answer": "9772 + 3164 = 12936"}
{"Question": "DOOR + YEAH = READY", "Answer": "7881 + 3092 = 10973"}
{"Question": "FOOD + TEAR = DRAFT", "Answer": "9221 + 4573 = 13794"}
{"Question": "COOL + THEM = ELECT", "Answer": "4332 + 7815 = 12147"}
{"Question": "FEEL + TRIP = RIFLE", "Answer": "4336 + 8127 = 12463"}
{"Question": "ODDS + EARN = SENSE", "Answer": "9551 + 4763 = 14314"}
{"Question": "ODDS + WHAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "4557 + 9861 = 14418"}
{"Question": "RATE + STOP = PAPER", "Answer": "4283 + 7851 = 12134"}
{"Question": "ROOF + HEAT = OTHER", "Answer": "5112 + 8763 = 13875"}
{"Question": "LOOK + CAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5224 + 6971 = 12195"}
{"Question": "BOOM + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "5223 + 9146 = 14369"}
{"Question": "BOOK + MALE = LABEL", "Answer": "5227 + 8314 = 13541"}
{"Question": "FEEL + SHOP = LOOSE", "Answer": "5441 + 6823 = 12264"}
{"Question": "BORN + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "8043 + 5471 = 13514"}
{"Question": "HAIR + GIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "5749 + 8416 = 14165"}
{"Question": "IDEA + REST = STARE", "Answer": "5673 + 8714 = 14387"}
{"Question": "HEEL + GIFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "5776 + 8419 = 14195"}
{"Question": "CARD + IRON = RADIO", "Answer": "6415 + 8172 = 14587"}
{"Question": "DRAG + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "6712 + 8145 = 14857"}
{"Question": "OVER + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "6213 + 8145 = 14358"}
{"Question": "MEET + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "6113 + 8425 = 14538"}
{"Question": "ODDS + NEXT = STONE", "Answer": "6221 + 7453 = 13674"}
{"Question": "BOOM + DARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "6221 + 7483 = 13704"}
{"Question": "LOTS + ITEM = SMILE", "Answer": "6521 + 7243 = 13764"}
{"Question": "BOOT + CREW = TWICE", "Answer": "6221 + 7854 = 14075"}
{"Question": "POOL + CITE = ELECT", "Answer": "6224 + 7951 = 14175"}
{"Question": "BEAT + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "6132 + 7395 = 13527"}
{"Question": "FLAT + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "7134 + 6328 = 13462"}
{"Question": "TEEN + VARY = NERVE", "Answer": "7441 + 6823 = 14264"}
{"Question": "ODDS + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9441 + 6827 = 16268"}
{"Question": "ROOT + FIVE = VOTER", "Answer": "7442 + 6815 = 14257"}
{"Question": "TEAM + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "6143 + 8425 = 14568"}
{"Question": "WOOD + RATE = TOWER", "Answer": "6443 + 8215 = 14658"}
{"Question": "ROOF + SUCH = FOCUS", "Answer": "6551 + 8947 = 15498"}
{"Question": "STAR + EACH = THESE", "Answer": "8152 + 6534 = 14686"}
{"Question": "STAR + EACH = THERE", "Answer": "6154 + 7593 = 13747"}
{"Question": "IDEA + REST = STAIR", "Answer": "6853 + 7514 = 14367"}
{"Question": "ROLE + GLAD = EAGER", "Answer": "6071 + 8745 = 14816"}
{"Question": "DOOR + LIFE = FIELD", "Answer": "6774 + 8512 = 15286"}
{"Question": "ROOF + LINE = ENTER", "Answer": "6885 + 7031 = 13916"}
{"Question": "ROOM + LIFE = OFFER", "Answer": "8112 + 7456 = 15568"}
{"Question": "BOOM + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "7221 + 8635 = 15856"}
{"Question": "ROOF + THIS = FIRST", "Answer": "7221 + 9568 = 16789"}
{"Question": "ROOM + SITE = TERMS", "Answer": "7223 + 9516 = 16739"}
{"Question": "MOON + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "8335 + 7192 = 15527"}
{"Question": "FEEL + BACK = CABLE", "Answer": "7335 + 9618 = 16953"}
{"Question": "ALLY + SING = GLASS", "Answer": "8556 + 7321 = 15877"}
{"Question": "TOOL + RACE = ALTER", "Answer": "7556 + 9183 = 16739"}
{"Question": "LOOK + MENU = FULLY", "Answer": "8223 + 9657 = 17880"}
{"Question": "DOOR + EACH = AHEAD", "Answer": "9662 + 8157 = 17819"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BALL", "Answer": "1561 + 1561 = 3122"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BOMB = MEET", "Answer": "1831 + 1831 = 3662"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = CARD", "Answer": "2632 + 2632 = 5264"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BAKE", "Answer": "2642 + 2642 = 5284"}
{"Question": "TENT + TENT = DATA", "Answer": "2712 + 2712 = 5424"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BELL", "Answer": "2872 + 2872 = 5744"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = DRAG", "Answer": "2962 + 2962 = 5924"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = BAKE", "Answer": "3623 + 3623 = 7246"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = TOWN", "Answer": "3673 + 3673 = 7346"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ELSE = BELL", "Answer": "3683 + 3683 = 7366"}
{"Question": "EASE + EASE = ALSO", "Answer": "3703 + 3703 = 7406"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = ROOF", "Answer": "3723 + 3723 = 7446"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = GENE", "Answer": "3843 + 3843 = 7686"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = TRUE", "Answer": "3963 + 3963 = 7926"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BEAN", "Answer": "4624 + 4624 = 9248"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = STAR", "Answer": "4824 + 4824 = 9648"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BEAR", "Answer": "4874 + 4874 = 9748"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = ERROR", "Answer": "5015 + 5015 = 10030"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "6246 + 6246 = 12492"}
{"Question": "TENT + TENT = SENSE", "Answer": "6256 + 6256 = 12512"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = ORDER", "Answer": "6296 + 6296 = 12592"}
{"Question": "KICK + KICK = AGAIN", "Answer": "6576 + 6576 = 13152"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BOMB = ADAPT", "Answer": "6586 + 6586 = 13172"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = LATER", "Answer": "6736 + 6736 = 13472"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BLADE", "Answer": "6826 + 6826 = 13652"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BEACH", "Answer": "6836 + 6836 = 13672"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = ERROR", "Answer": "7237 + 7237 = 14474"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = START", "Answer": "7367 + 7367 = 14734"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BROAD", "Answer": "7537 + 7537 = 15074"}
{"Question": "EDGE + EDGE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7567 + 7567 = 15134"}
{"Question": "EASE + EASE = PAPER", "Answer": "7587 + 7587 = 15174"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BOMB = LIMIT", "Answer": "7627 + 7627 = 15254"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = CATCH", "Answer": "7657 + 7657 = 15314"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = TODAY", "Answer": "7897 + 7897 = 15794"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = MORAL", "Answer": "7987 + 7987 = 15974"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = ADAPT", "Answer": "8568 + 8568 = 17136"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HIGH = AGAIN", "Answer": "8578 + 8578 = 17156"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = ABOVE", "Answer": "8618 + 8618 = 17236"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = THEIR", "Answer": "8628 + 8628 = 17256"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = COLOR", "Answer": "8638 + 8638 = 17276"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = HUMOR", "Answer": "8648 + 8648 = 17296"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAD = CABLE", "Answer": "8678 + 8678 = 17356"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BUYER", "Answer": "8698 + 8698 = 17396"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = TRUTH", "Answer": "8708 + 8708 = 17416"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BRICK", "Answer": "8728 + 8728 = 17456"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = FRESH", "Answer": "8748 + 8748 = 17496"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BRIEF", "Answer": "8798 + 8798 = 17596"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = EXACT", "Answer": "8918 + 8918 = 17836"}
{"Question": "TENT + TENT = MOTOR", "Answer": "8938 + 8938 = 17876"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = BOARD", "Answer": "8948 + 8948 = 17896"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = FORCE", "Answer": "8968 + 8968 = 17936"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = TERMS", "Answer": "8978 + 8978 = 17956"}
{"Question": "EDGE + EDGE = BEGIN", "Answer": "9629 + 9629 = 19258"}
{"Question": "AREA + AREA = CABLE", "Answer": "9689 + 9689 = 19378"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "9749 + 9749 = 19498"}
{"Question": "ONTO + ONTO = COUNT", "Answer": "9789 + 9789 = 19578"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEST = STAGE", "Answer": "9819 + 9819 = 19638"}
{"Question": "TENT + TENT = STATE", "Answer": "9849 + 9849 = 19698"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = HATE", "Answer": "1251 + 1259 = 2510"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = AREA", "Answer": "1631 + 1632 = 3263"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = RARE", "Answer": "2372 + 2371 = 4743"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = EVEN", "Answer": "2472 + 2475 = 4947"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = TEEN", "Answer": "2612 + 2615 = 5227"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = RIDE", "Answer": "2712 + 2715 = 5427"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = BABY", "Answer": "2972 + 2978 = 5950"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = MALE", "Answer": "3243 + 3249 = 6492"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = STEP", "Answer": "3463 + 3469 = 6932"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = GANG", "Answer": "3623 + 3624 = 7247"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = DEAD", "Answer": "3683 + 3684 = 7367"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = ELSE", "Answer": "3713 + 3714 = 7427"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = EASE", "Answer": "3753 + 3754 = 7507"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = SAFE", "Answer": "3973 + 3970 = 7943"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = AREA", "Answer": "4894 + 4895 = 9789"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "4894 + 4897 = 9791"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "5145 + 5149 = 10294"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = ELITE", "Answer": "5175 + 5176 = 10351"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "5215 + 5210 = 10425"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = ESSAY", "Answer": "6106 + 6103 = 12209"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = APPLE", "Answer": "6146 + 6140 = 12286"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = SALAD", "Answer": "6216 + 6213 = 12429"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = BELOW", "Answer": "6236 + 6234 = 12470"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = HEART", "Answer": "6246 + 6249 = 12495"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = BEGIN", "Answer": "6296 + 6293 = 12589"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "6736 + 6735 = 13471"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = NORTH", "Answer": "6786 + 6781 = 13567"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = KNOCK", "Answer": "6936 + 6935 = 13871"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "7067 + 7063 = 14130"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = FIFTH", "Answer": "7087 + 7083 = 14170"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = ISSUE", "Answer": "7247 + 7240 = 14487"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7317 + 7316 = 14633"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = LEVEL", "Answer": "7527 + 7524 = 15051"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = LABEL", "Answer": "7537 + 7534 = 15071"}
{"Question": "EASE + EASY = VISIT", "Answer": "7627 + 7623 = 15250"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = STATE", "Answer": "7627 + 7629 = 15256"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = ORDER", "Answer": "7637 + 7638 = 15275"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = PAINT", "Answer": "7657 + 7650 = 15307"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = ONION", "Answer": "7657 + 7658 = 15315"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = ORDER", "Answer": "7947 + 7948 = 15895"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = THERE", "Answer": "7967 + 7962 = 15929"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = SCALE", "Answer": "8378 + 8375 = 16753"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = START", "Answer": "8628 + 8629 = 17257"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = UNION", "Answer": "8678 + 8679 = 17357"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = SENSE", "Answer": "8708 + 8709 = 17417"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = SHEET", "Answer": "8728 + 8720 = 17448"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = SEVEN", "Answer": "8738 + 8735 = 17473"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "8748 + 8741 = 17489"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = LEGAL", "Answer": "8798 + 8793 = 17591"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = RELAX", "Answer": "8798 + 8795 = 17593"}
{"Question": "EASE + EASY = TREAT", "Answer": "8948 + 8943 = 17891"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = FAULT", "Answer": "9289 + 9287 = 18576"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = ALTER", "Answer": "9319 + 9318 = 18637"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = TRUTH", "Answer": "9359 + 9351 = 18710"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "9389 + 9387 = 18776"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "9419 + 9418 = 18837"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEND = ASSET", "Answer": "9429 + 9420 = 18849"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEAL = BADLY", "Answer": "9489 + 9487 = 18976"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = METAL", "Answer": "9789 + 9785 = 19574"}
{"Question": "EASE + EAST = METER", "Answer": "9849 + 9846 = 19695"}
{"Question": "THAT + THAN = STAFF", "Answer": "9879 + 9876 = 19755"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEST = STEP", "Answer": "2612 + 2652 = 5264"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEST = SITE", "Answer": "4854 + 4894 = 9748"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEXT = SENSE", "Answer": "6216 + 6296 = 12512"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEXT = ASIAN", "Answer": "6726 + 6786 = 13512"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEST = LATIN", "Answer": "6826 + 6846 = 13672"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = HONOR", "Answer": "6856 + 6876 = 13732"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = SENSE", "Answer": "7417 + 7497 = 14914"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = MONTH", "Answer": "7807 + 7867 = 15674"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = DOZEN", "Answer": "7837 + 7847 = 15684"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = DANCE", "Answer": "8608 + 8628 = 17236"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = SINCE", "Answer": "8618 + 8628 = 17246"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEXT = NOISE", "Answer": "8618 + 8638 = 17256"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = WASTE", "Answer": "8628 + 8658 = 17286"}
{"Question": "TEXT + TENT = SEVEN", "Answer": "8708 + 8768 = 17476"}
{"Question": "TEST + TENT = STATE", "Answer": "9819 + 9879 = 19698"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = LEAN", "Answer": "1031 + 1022 = 2053"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = LATE", "Answer": "1391 + 1322 = 2713"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = NINE", "Answer": "1531 + 1503 = 3034"}
{"Question": "TEST + TELL = LOTS", "Answer": "2672 + 2655 = 5327"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = LESS", "Answer": "3923 + 3977 = 7900"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = KNEE", "Answer": "4874 + 4837 = 9711"}
{"Question": "KICK + KILL = CLIMB", "Answer": "6016 + 6022 = 12038"}
{"Question": "TEXT + TELL = RELAX", "Answer": "6206 + 6244 = 12450"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = LATIN", "Answer": "6376 + 6311 = 12687"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = IRISH", "Answer": "6586 + 6518 = 13104"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HILL = ELITE", "Answer": "7037 + 7044 = 14081"}
{"Question": "TEST + TELL = SOLVE", "Answer": "7317 + 7366 = 14683"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = CARRY", "Answer": "7427 + 7462 = 14889"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HILL = EIGHT", "Answer": "7507 + 7566 = 15073"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = FENCE", "Answer": "7507 + 7588 = 15095"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = ORDER", "Answer": "7687 + 7608 = 15295"}
{"Question": "TEST + TELL = ONION", "Answer": "7627 + 7688 = 15315"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = UNION", "Answer": "7657 + 7688 = 15345"}
{"Question": "KICK + KISS = SCENE", "Answer": "7957 + 7911 = 15868"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HILL = ONION", "Answer": "7927 + 7988 = 15915"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = FINAL", "Answer": "8258 + 8265 = 16523"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HILL = CLASS", "Answer": "8278 + 8266 = 16544"}
{"Question": "KICK + KISS = BASIC", "Answer": "8358 + 8377 = 16735"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = LATER", "Answer": "8438 + 8411 = 16849"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HILL = TIGHT", "Answer": "8748 + 8733 = 17481"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = RANGE", "Answer": "8748 + 8734 = 17482"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BOSS = MOTOR", "Answer": "8718 + 8755 = 17473"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = HELLO", "Answer": "8798 + 8755 = 17553"}
{"Question": "TEST + TELL = SENSE", "Answer": "8718 + 8799 = 17517"}
{"Question": "KICK + KISS = ASIAN", "Answer": "8938 + 8977 = 17915"}
{"Question": "TENT + TELL = CLEAN", "Answer": "8958 + 8977 = 17935"}
{"Question": "KICK + KILL = COLOR", "Answer": "9319 + 9366 = 18685"}
{"Question": "GANG + GAIN = ESSAY", "Answer": "9439 + 9403 = 18842"}
{"Question": "TEST + TELL = STATE", "Answer": "9619 + 9677 = 19296"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = RATE", "Answer": "1341 + 1372 = 2713"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEAM = MASS", "Answer": "1541 + 1503 = 3044"}
{"Question": "EASE + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "3783 + 3754 = 7537"}
{"Question": "AREA + ARMY = MERE", "Answer": "4014 + 4087 = 8101"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = AREA", "Answer": "4784 + 4795 = 9579"}
{"Question": "THAT + THIN = FAITH", "Answer": "5205 + 5247 = 10452"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "5315 + 5368 = 10683"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = ANGRY", "Answer": "6426 + 6413 = 12839"}
{"Question": "THAT + THIS = ASIAN", "Answer": "6516 + 6503 = 13019"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEM = LEAVE", "Answer": "6506 + 6537 = 13043"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "6596 + 6503 = 13099"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEBT = AWARE", "Answer": "6516 + 6589 = 13105"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEBT = AGAIN", "Answer": "6516 + 6592 = 13108"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DECK = NAKED", "Answer": "6536 + 6520 = 13056"}
{"Question": "EASE + EACH = CHIEF", "Answer": "6756 + 6713 = 13469"}
{"Question": "THAT + THUS = SOUTH", "Answer": "6726 + 6741 = 13467"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEBT = TASTE", "Answer": "6736 + 6781 = 13517"}
{"Question": "EASE + EACH = CHEAP", "Answer": "6876 + 6813 = 13689"}
{"Question": "THAT + THUS = COUCH", "Answer": "6846 + 6872 = 13718"}
{"Question": "EASE + EACH = START", "Answer": "6916 + 6987 = 13903"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEM = HEART", "Answer": "7127 + 7140 = 14267"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7137 + 7142 = 14279"}
{"Question": "EASE + EACH = ISSUE", "Answer": "7247 + 7250 = 14497"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HIRE = REFER", "Answer": "7327 + 7314 = 14641"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "7327 + 7364 = 14691"}
{"Question": "AREA + ARMY = TREAT", "Answer": "7507 + 7564 = 15071"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DENY = NAKED", "Answer": "7657 + 7610 = 15267"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DESK = ASIDE", "Answer": "7617 + 7659 = 15276"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HIRE = EAGER", "Answer": "7637 + 7681 = 15318"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BOND = MINOR", "Answer": "7817 + 7863 = 15680"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HIRE = OTHER", "Answer": "7837 + 7892 = 15729"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEM = MATCH", "Answer": "7857 + 7891 = 15748"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEN = FENCE", "Answer": "7907 + 7958 = 15865"}
{"Question": "EASE + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "8138 + 8146 = 16284"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "8208 + 8214 = 16422"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEBT = LABEL", "Answer": "8268 + 8253 = 16521"}
{"Question": "TENT + TERM = OFFER", "Answer": "8308 + 8324 = 16632"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DEBT = STATE", "Answer": "8508 + 8567 = 17075"}
{"Question": "EASE + EACH = SALES", "Answer": "8718 + 8763 = 17481"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAM = DEATH", "Answer": "8738 + 8742 = 17480"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DESK = STATE", "Answer": "9369 + 9314 = 18683"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEM = CATCH", "Answer": "9489 + 9425 = 18914"}
{"Question": "TENT + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9589 + 9506 = 19095"}
{"Question": "TEST + TEND = STATE", "Answer": "9519 + 9576 = 19095"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9829 + 9856 = 19685"}
{"Question": "THAT + THIS = STATE", "Answer": "9869 + 9821 = 19690"}
{"Question": "THAT + THEM = STATE", "Answer": "9869 + 9823 = 19692"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EASE = BELL", "Answer": "1261 + 1861 = 3122"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = SELL", "Answer": "4594 + 4894 = 9488"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = BASIS", "Answer": "6326 + 6926 = 13252"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = FIELD", "Answer": "6746 + 6946 = 13692"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = AFTER", "Answer": "7137 + 7937 = 15074"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = ASIAN", "Answer": "7157 + 7857 = 15014"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EASE = PANEL", "Answer": "7487 + 7587 = 15074"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = PAPER", "Answer": "7537 + 7637 = 15174"}
{"Question": "EASE + ELSE = MAKER", "Answer": "7587 + 7687 = 15274"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = OPEN", "Answer": "1891 + 1398 = 3289"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = TEEN", "Answer": "2982 + 2686 = 5668"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = NEXT", "Answer": "3073 + 3970 = 7043"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = AREA", "Answer": "3723 + 3424 = 7147"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = ENTRY", "Answer": "6126 + 6521 = 12647"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = LEMON", "Answer": "6396 + 6893 = 13289"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = LABEL", "Answer": "6276 + 6575 = 12851"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6186 + 6989 = 13175"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = DRAMA", "Answer": "6586 + 6989 = 13575"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = BLOOD", "Answer": "6986 + 6789 = 13775"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = NOVEL", "Answer": "7217 + 7412 = 14629"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = MONTH", "Answer": "7387 + 7483 = 14870"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = LEGAL", "Answer": "7467 + 7064 = 14531"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = GIVEN", "Answer": "7527 + 7325 = 14852"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = ANGRY", "Answer": "7147 + 7646 = 14793"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = ONION", "Answer": "7857 + 7158 = 15015"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = COLOR", "Answer": "7927 + 7529 = 15456"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7987 + 7689 = 15676"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = HONOR", "Answer": "8638 + 8736 = 17374"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = AGAIN", "Answer": "8648 + 8546 = 17194"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = BENCH", "Answer": "8678 + 8076 = 16754"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = FEWER", "Answer": "8738 + 8937 = 17675"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = HELLO", "Answer": "8768 + 8567 = 17335"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = ORDER", "Answer": "8948 + 8149 = 17097"}
{"Question": "TENT + TONE = INNER", "Answer": "9789 + 9087 = 18876"}
{"Question": "GANG + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "9189 + 9787 = 18976"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = NINE", "Answer": "1761 + 1066 = 2827"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = ROUTE", "Answer": "5275 + 5077 = 10352"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = OFTEN", "Answer": "5425 + 5122 = 10547"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = SEVEN", "Answer": "6216 + 6311 = 12527"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = FENCE", "Answer": "6376 + 6877 = 13253"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = MOTOR", "Answer": "7327 + 7422 = 14749"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOSS = ENTER", "Answer": "9159 + 9755 = 18914"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAR = RARE", "Answer": "2072 + 2674 = 4746"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = HATE", "Answer": "2512 + 2614 = 5126"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EAST = SELL", "Answer": "3473 + 3871 = 7344"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAR = HERE", "Answer": "4984 + 4187 = 9171"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAR = AREA", "Answer": "4694 + 4895 = 9589"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EAST = LABEL", "Answer": "5175 + 5076 = 10251"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EAST = CLEAN", "Answer": "5075 + 5473 = 10548"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = PLATE", "Answer": "5275 + 5479 = 10754"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAW = AWARE", "Answer": "6916 + 6213 = 13129"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = SHALL", "Answer": "6276 + 6479 = 12755"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HUGE = EIGHT", "Answer": "6286 + 6581 = 12867"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = LEAVE", "Answer": "6326 + 6927 = 13253"}
{"Question": "ELSE + EAST = USUAL", "Answer": "6436 + 6738 = 13174"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = PAPER", "Answer": "6436 + 6739 = 13175"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = START", "Answer": "6546 + 6947 = 13493"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = HEART", "Answer": "7167 + 7460 = 14627"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = ARMED", "Answer": "7217 + 7410 = 14627"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAR = WRITE", "Answer": "7837 + 7235 = 15072"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = APART", "Answer": "7817 + 7319 = 15136"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = TRADE", "Answer": "7387 + 7486 = 14873"}
{"Question": "TENT + TINY = LIMIT", "Answer": "7527 + 7420 = 14947"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = FIFTH", "Answer": "7687 + 7489 = 15176"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = LEVEL", "Answer": "7527 + 7824 = 15351"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HUGE = TIGHT", "Answer": "7537 + 7834 = 15371"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = IRAQI", "Answer": "8078 + 8673 = 16751"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = AWARE", "Answer": "8918 + 8214 = 17132"}
{"Question": "TENT + TANK = SENSE", "Answer": "8708 + 8309 = 17017"}
{"Question": "TENT + TANK = NAKED", "Answer": "8318 + 8619 = 16937"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = JUDGE", "Answer": "8378 + 8475 = 16853"}
{"Question": "TENT + TINY = BIBLE", "Answer": "8428 + 8726 = 17154"}
{"Question": "TENT + TANK = SEVEN", "Answer": "8738 + 8935 = 17673"}
{"Question": "TEST + TASK = ASSET", "Answer": "9689 + 9180 = 18869"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = APPLE", "Answer": "9219 + 9617 = 18836"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRAG = ASSET", "Answer": "9319 + 9517 = 18836"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAR = STARE", "Answer": "9829 + 9425 = 19254"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = STAGE", "Answer": "9839 + 9536 = 19375"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9849 + 9647 = 19496"}
{"Question": "THAT + TENT = EACH", "Answer": "3643 + 3783 = 7426"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAT = HATE", "Answer": "3693 + 3743 = 7436"}
{"Question": "EASE + EDGE = ASIAN", "Answer": "6136 + 6876 = 13012"}
{"Question": "THAT + TENT = NORTH", "Answer": "6246 + 6816 = 13062"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEST = SHALL", "Answer": "6306 + 6716 = 13022"}
{"Question": "THAT + TENT = NEVER", "Answer": "8358 + 8718 = 17076"}
{"Question": "THAT + TEST = WASTE", "Answer": "8478 + 8608 = 17086"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAT = WASTE", "Answer": "8608 + 8978 = 17586"}
{"Question": "TEST + THAT = SHADE", "Answer": "8618 + 8738 = 17356"}
{"Question": "EDGE + EASE = SALAD", "Answer": "8658 + 8718 = 17376"}
{"Question": "THAT + TENT = DEATH", "Answer": "8638 + 8748 = 17386"}
{"Question": "TENT + TIME = MEET", "Answer": "1071 + 1930 = 3001"}
{"Question": "TENT + TIME = ITEM", "Answer": "1791 + 1387 = 3178"}
{"Question": "TEST + TONE = ONTO", "Answer": "3423 + 3714 = 7137"}
{"Question": "TEST + TONE = SOON", "Answer": "3973 + 3029 = 7002"}
{"Question": "TENT + TYPE = EMPTY", "Answer": "5175 + 5681 = 10856"}
{"Question": "TEST + TIME = BASIS", "Answer": "5385 + 5463 = 10848"}
{"Question": "TEST + TALE = SALAD", "Answer": "5715 + 5087 = 10802"}
{"Question": "TEST + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "6026 + 6180 = 12206"}
{"Question": "TENT + TIRE = METER", "Answer": "6246 + 6382 = 12628"}
{"Question": "TEST + TAKE = SALES", "Answer": "6516 + 6235 = 12751"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HERE = TIGHT", "Answer": "6286 + 6575 = 12861"}
{"Question": "TEST + TAKE = SKILL", "Answer": "6916 + 6839 = 13755"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OPEN = STONE", "Answer": "6936 + 6759 = 13695"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HERE = EIGHT", "Answer": "7457 + 7121 = 14578"}
{"Question": "TEST + TIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "7137 + 7581 = 14718"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALE = LEVEL", "Answer": "7427 + 7514 = 14941"}
{"Question": "TEST + TRUE = SUPER", "Answer": "7617 + 7346 = 14963"}
{"Question": "TENT + TAPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7647 + 7516 = 15163"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OPEN = PHONE", "Answer": "7627 + 7136 = 14763"}
{"Question": "TENT + TIRE = ORDER", "Answer": "7827 + 7658 = 15485"}
{"Question": "TENT + TUBE = UNION", "Answer": "7857 + 7168 = 15025"}
{"Question": "TENT + TIRE = FIBER", "Answer": "7927 + 7569 = 15496"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HERE = EAGER", "Answer": "8028 + 8191 = 16219"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OVEN = EVENT", "Answer": "8428 + 8714 = 17142"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "8708 + 8167 = 16875"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OPEN = SCOPE", "Answer": "8748 + 8057 = 16805"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OPEN = TROOP", "Answer": "9519 + 9475 = 18994"}
{"Question": "TENT + TOSS = SOON", "Answer": "1031 + 1522 = 2553"}
{"Question": "AREA + ABLE = REAL", "Answer": "2452 + 2075 = 4527"}
{"Question": "THAT + TREE = HELL", "Answer": "2412 + 2388 = 4800"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = HALL", "Answer": "3483 + 3728 = 7211"}
{"Question": "TEXT + TALL = RELAX", "Answer": "5095 + 5344 = 10439"}
{"Question": "THAT + TOSS = COACH", "Answer": "5235 + 5077 = 10312"}
{"Question": "TEST + TALL = SLEEP", "Answer": "6316 + 6022 = 12338"}
{"Question": "TEST + TALL = SOLAR", "Answer": "6716 + 6088 = 12804"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BALL = ALBUM", "Answer": "6486 + 6122 = 12608"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "6126 + 6492 = 12618"}
{"Question": "TENT + TOSS = ONION", "Answer": "6836 + 6177 = 13013"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BALL = ORDER", "Answer": "6146 + 6877 = 13023"}
{"Question": "TENT + TWIN = WHICH", "Answer": "6976 + 6107 = 13083"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = DEATH", "Answer": "6286 + 6478 = 12764"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = LEAVE", "Answer": "6376 + 6827 = 13203"}
{"Question": "TEST + THUS = SOUTH", "Answer": "6816 + 6751 = 13567"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "6936 + 6813 = 13749"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALL = AGREE", "Answer": "7067 + 7133 = 14200"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HELL = EIGHT", "Answer": "7457 + 7122 = 14579"}
{"Question": "TEST + THUS = HOUSE", "Answer": "7927 + 7102 = 15029"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = EARTH", "Answer": "7127 + 7952 = 15079"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALL = ENTER", "Answer": "7147 + 7566 = 14713"}
{"Question": "TEXT + TALL = EXTRA", "Answer": "7147 + 7588 = 14735"}
{"Question": "THAT + TELL = LATER", "Answer": "7247 + 7511 = 14758"}
{"Question": "AREA + ABLE = CLEAR", "Answer": "7927 + 7352 = 15279"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = FAITH", "Answer": "7427 + 7952 = 15379"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BELL = SENSE", "Answer": "7427 + 7588 = 15015"}
{"Question": "TENT + TURN = NURSE", "Answer": "7817 + 7531 = 15348"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALL = NERVE", "Answer": "7517 + 7688 = 15205"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALL = SENSE", "Answer": "7527 + 7688 = 15215"}
{"Question": "THAT + TELL = SALES", "Answer": "8268 + 8033 = 16301"}
{"Question": "TEST + TALL = ISSUE", "Answer": "8568 + 8077 = 16645"}
{"Question": "TENT + TWIN = WHITE", "Answer": "8248 + 8134 = 16382"}
{"Question": "AREA + ABLE = BREAD", "Answer": "8678 + 8107 = 16785"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "8548 + 8264 = 16812"}
{"Question": "TENT + THIN = SHINE", "Answer": "8248 + 8694 = 16942"}
{"Question": "TENT + THAN = AWARE", "Answer": "8248 + 8914 = 17162"}
{"Question": "TENT + TURN = PAPER", "Answer": "8958 + 8235 = 17193"}
{"Question": "THAT + TREE = DEPTH", "Answer": "8508 + 8977 = 17485"}
{"Question": "TENT + TALL = SALES", "Answer": "8628 + 8733 = 17361"}
{"Question": "AREA + AIDE = DREAM", "Answer": "8768 + 8916 = 17684"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HATE = EIGHT", "Answer": "5095 + 5861 = 10956"}
{"Question": "THAT + TERM = EARTH", "Answer": "5305 + 5148 = 10453"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DIRT = RADIO", "Answer": "5305 + 5219 = 10524"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HEAD = GRADE", "Answer": "5315 + 5479 = 10794"}
{"Question": "TEST + TURN = ENTER", "Answer": "6136 + 6482 = 12618"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BURN = ORDER", "Answer": "6146 + 6937 = 13083"}
{"Question": "AREA + ACID = TREAT", "Answer": "6276 + 6485 = 12761"}
{"Question": "AREA + ACID = ERROR", "Answer": "6316 + 6987 = 13303"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DOWN = AWARE", "Answer": "6416 + 6738 = 13154"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DROP = AWARE", "Answer": "6416 + 6758 = 13174"}
{"Question": "TEST + TOWN = AWARE", "Answer": "6456 + 6738 = 13194"}
{"Question": "TENT + TOUR = UNION", "Answer": "6936 + 6517 = 13453"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DIRT = GRADE", "Answer": "6526 + 6739 = 13265"}
{"Question": "TENT + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "7107 + 7564 = 14671"}
{"Question": "TEST + TAIL = ASSET", "Answer": "7247 + 7180 = 14427"}
{"Question": "TENT + TRIP = ENTER", "Answer": "7147 + 7568 = 14715"}
{"Question": "TENT + TAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "7307 + 7856 = 15163"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7347 + 7619 = 14966"}
{"Question": "BOMB + BEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "7847 + 7316 = 15163"}
{"Question": "ONTO + OKAY = THANK", "Answer": "7417 + 7932 = 15349"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DIRT = TRADE", "Answer": "7827 + 7451 = 15278"}
{"Question": "HIGH + HEAR = GRAIN", "Answer": "7617 + 7845 = 15462"}
{"Question": "TENT + TRIP = INNER", "Answer": "7657 + 7912 = 15569"}
{"Question": "DEAD + DRUG = GUIDE", "Answer": "7827 + 7651 = 15478"}
{"Question": "EDGE + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "8238 + 8146 = 16384"}
{"Question": "THAT + TYPE = HEAVY", "Answer": "8158 + 8436 = 16594"}
{"Question": "TEXT + THIS = EXIST", "Answer": "8168 + 8240 = 16408"}
{"Question": "TEST + TAIL = SALES", "Answer": "8618 + 8743 = 17361"}
{"Question": "AREA + AUTO = TREAT", "Answer": "8768 + 8913 = 17681"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = UNIT", "Answer": "1021 + 4021 = 5042"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = OFTEN", "Answer": "1241 + 9241 = 10482"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEST = THREE", "Answer": "1261 + 9261 = 10522"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = GIVEN", "Answer": "1321 + 9321 = 10642"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = DRAFT", "Answer": "1371 + 9371 = 10742"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = TIRED", "Answer": "1471 + 9471 = 10942"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = OCCUR", "Answer": "1531 + 8531 = 10062"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = ELECT", "Answer": "1571 + 8571 = 10142"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = ELECT", "Answer": "1591 + 8591 = 10182"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "1621 + 8621 = 10242"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = GREEN", "Answer": "1721 + 8721 = 10442"}
{"Question": "KICK + PICK = CHIP", "Answer": "1841 + 2841 = 4682"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = BELL", "Answer": "1961 + 2961 = 4922"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = DRESS", "Answer": "1961 + 8961 = 10922"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = EXACT", "Answer": "1971 + 8971 = 10942"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = BALL", "Answer": "2372 + 4372 = 6744"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = CLASS", "Answer": "2372 + 8372 = 10744"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = SEVEN", "Answer": "2452 + 8452 = 10904"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = SHEET", "Answer": "2612 + 7612 = 10224"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = DEAD", "Answer": "2632 + 1632 = 4264"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = AREA", "Answer": "2842 + 1842 = 4684"}
{"Question": "THAT + WHAT = STAFF", "Answer": "2872 + 9872 = 12744"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = STAR", "Answer": "3193 + 6193 = 9386"}
{"Question": "THAT + WHAT = SHELL", "Answer": "3283 + 9283 = 12566"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = ELSE", "Answer": "3643 + 2643 = 6286"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = JOIN", "Answer": "3673 + 4673 = 8346"}
{"Question": "THAT + WHAT = HERE", "Answer": "3813 + 4813 = 8626"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SIGH = BASIS", "Answer": "3843 + 6843 = 10686"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = EARN", "Answer": "3873 + 4873 = 8746"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = SHELL", "Answer": "3983 + 6983 = 10966"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = PAPER", "Answer": "4054 + 8054 = 12108"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = BEACH", "Answer": "4254 + 8254 = 12508"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = LAUGH", "Answer": "4274 + 8274 = 12548"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "4614 + 5614 = 10228"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = AREA", "Answer": "4684 + 3684 = 8368"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = TENT", "Answer": "4714 + 3714 = 8428"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEST = EASE", "Answer": "4804 + 3804 = 8608"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = AREA", "Answer": "4824 + 3824 = 8648"}
{"Question": "TEXT + NEXT = STATE", "Answer": "4824 + 9824 = 14648"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = FADE", "Answer": "4874 + 1874 = 6748"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "4874 + 5874 = 10748"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = THREE", "Answer": "4894 + 7894 = 12788"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = SCENE", "Answer": "4904 + 7904 = 12808"}
{"Question": "TEXT + NEXT = GENE", "Answer": "5015 + 3015 = 8030"}
{"Question": "TEXT + NEXT = SCENE", "Answer": "5035 + 7035 = 12070"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "5085 + 7085 = 12170"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = ASSET", "Answer": "5125 + 7125 = 12250"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = EARLY", "Answer": "5145 + 9145 = 14290"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = NONE", "Answer": "5785 + 1785 = 7570"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "6216 + 8216 = 14432"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = TEEN", "Answer": "6276 + 1276 = 7552"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = HELLO", "Answer": "6386 + 7386 = 13772"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = APPLY", "Answer": "6516 + 3516 = 10032"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = START", "Answer": "6746 + 5746 = 12492"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = START", "Answer": "6876 + 5876 = 12752"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = ARAB", "Answer": "6946 + 2946 = 9892"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = EARTH", "Answer": "7187 + 3187 = 10374"}
{"Question": "THAT + WHAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "7237 + 5237 = 12474"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = BASIS", "Answer": "7247 + 5247 = 12494"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = SEED", "Answer": "7387 + 1387 = 8774"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = ANGLE", "Answer": "7417 + 3417 = 10834"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = FALSE", "Answer": "7467 + 9467 = 16934"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = UNION", "Answer": "7547 + 6547 = 14094"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = SEIZE", "Answer": "7827 + 6827 = 14654"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = COACH", "Answer": "7957 + 4957 = 12914"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = EQUAL", "Answer": "8198 + 6198 = 14396"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = HEART", "Answer": "8378 + 5378 = 13756"}
{"Question": "GANG + HANG = CATCH", "Answer": "8458 + 6458 = 14916"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = WHICH", "Answer": "8538 + 7538 = 16076"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = RURAL", "Answer": "8598 + 1598 = 10196"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "8618 + 3618 = 12236"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEST = SEIZE", "Answer": "8618 + 7618 = 16236"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "8628 + 7628 = 16256"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = FENCE", "Answer": "8648 + 7648 = 16296"}
{"Question": "TEXT + NEXT = STONE", "Answer": "8648 + 9648 = 18296"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = RAISE", "Answer": "8698 + 1698 = 10396"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = HORSE", "Answer": "8698 + 3698 = 12396"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAD = HUMAN", "Answer": "8798 + 1798 = 10596"}
{"Question": "TEST + REST = MOTOR", "Answer": "8928 + 6928 = 15856"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = BREAD", "Answer": "8948 + 1948 = 10896"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAD = MODEL", "Answer": "8948 + 6948 = 15896"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = COACH", "Answer": "8958 + 1958 = 10916"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SIGH = SWING", "Answer": "8968 + 1968 = 10936"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = BLACK", "Answer": "8978 + 1978 = 10956"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = BLOOD", "Answer": "9279 + 1279 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = THING", "Answer": "9319 + 6319 = 15638"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = AFTER", "Answer": "9319 + 8319 = 17638"}
{"Question": "EASE + BASE = BRIEF", "Answer": "9349 + 1349 = 10698"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = CLOCK", "Answer": "9359 + 1359 = 10718"}
{"Question": "DEAD + READ = INNER", "Answer": "9369 + 8369 = 17738"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASE = CHECK", "Answer": "9459 + 1459 = 10918"}
{"Question": "ONTO + INTO = LIMIT", "Answer": "9689 + 7689 = 17378"}
{"Question": "TEXT + NEXT = INNER", "Answer": "9739 + 4739 = 14478"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "1454 + 9451 = 10905"}
{"Question": "TENT + GENE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1571 + 8575 = 10146"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = COLOR", "Answer": "2353 + 8352 = 10705"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = AFTER", "Answer": "3474 + 9473 = 12947"}
{"Question": "TENT + GENE = SEVEN", "Answer": "4264 + 8262 = 12526"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = REST", "Answer": "4989 + 3984 = 8973"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = ORDER", "Answer": "7525 + 4527 = 12052"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = IRISH", "Answer": "7565 + 8567 = 16132"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7868 + 5867 = 13735"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = PROOF", "Answer": "8272 + 9278 = 17550"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = REFER", "Answer": "8313 + 5318 = 13631"}
{"Question": "TENT + GENE = GRAND", "Answer": "8698 + 1696 = 10394"}
{"Question": "TENT + GENE = GLASS", "Answer": "8728 + 1727 = 10455"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = ASSET", "Answer": "8737 + 5738 = 14475"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = GREAT", "Answer": "8969 + 7968 = 16937"}
{"Question": "MERE + TERM = THEIR", "Answer": "8979 + 1978 = 10957"}
{"Question": "TENT + GENE = EAGER", "Answer": "9159 + 3151 = 12310"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "1088 + 9081 = 10169"}
{"Question": "FALL + HALF = FEWER", "Answer": "1355 + 9351 = 10706"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = ADAPT", "Answer": "1561 + 8566 = 10127"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = ADAPT", "Answer": "1571 + 8577 = 10148"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = ALSO", "Answer": "1622 + 4621 = 6243"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = TRULY", "Answer": "1641 + 8644 = 10285"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = TROOP", "Answer": "1721 + 8722 = 10443"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = REST", "Answer": "1741 + 5744 = 7485"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = EXACT", "Answer": "1961 + 8966 = 10927"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = RIVER", "Answer": "2192 + 8199 = 10391"}
{"Question": "EASE + PASS = SUPER", "Answer": "2412 + 8411 = 10823"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = ESSAY", "Answer": "2512 + 7511 = 10023"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = SHEET", "Answer": "2612 + 7611 = 10223"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = SITE", "Answer": "2862 + 3866 = 6728"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "2866 + 9862 = 12728"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = FEWER", "Answer": "3266 + 9263 = 12529"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = ASIDE", "Answer": "3523 + 8522 = 12045"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = COAST", "Answer": "3653 + 8655 = 12308"}
{"Question": "KISS + RISK = AREA", "Answer": "3766 + 5763 = 9529"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = ASSET", "Answer": "4124 + 8122 = 12246"}
{"Question": "KISS + RISK = INNER", "Answer": "4155 + 9154 = 13309"}
{"Question": "TOSS + POST = SLEEP", "Answer": "4611 + 5614 = 10225"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = BEAR", "Answer": "4624 + 3622 = 8246"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = INNER", "Answer": "4633 + 7634 = 12267"}
{"Question": "EASE + PASS = SNAP", "Answer": "5365 + 1366 = 6731"}
{"Question": "TEST + MESS = LEVEL", "Answer": "5365 + 8366 = 13731"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = BREAD", "Answer": "5375 + 8377 = 13752"}
{"Question": "KILL + MILK = CLAIM", "Answer": "5422 + 7425 = 12847"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = FREE", "Answer": "6156 + 2155 = 8311"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = FLEE", "Answer": "6156 + 3155 = 9311"}
{"Question": "EASE + PASS = HAPPY", "Answer": "6386 + 7388 = 13774"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = BALL", "Answer": "6456 + 1455 = 7911"}
{"Question": "MALL + PALM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6811 + 5816 = 12627"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = ORDER", "Answer": "6946 + 3944 = 10890"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = BELL", "Answer": "6956 + 1955 = 8911"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = PAPER", "Answer": "7087 + 3088 = 10175"}
{"Question": "TOSS + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "7088 + 5087 = 12175"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = ARMED", "Answer": "7187 + 3188 = 10375"}
{"Question": "KILL + MILK = CLASS", "Answer": "7266 + 9267 = 16533"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = CRACK", "Answer": "7357 + 6355 = 13712"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = SEED", "Answer": "7387 + 1388 = 8775"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = LOOSE", "Answer": "7511 + 2517 = 10028"}
{"Question": "KISS + RISK = SORRY", "Answer": "7611 + 2617 = 10228"}
{"Question": "FALL + HALF = COUCH", "Answer": "7655 + 2657 = 10312"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = ONION", "Answer": "7657 + 4655 = 12312"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = CATCH", "Answer": "7657 + 9655 = 17312"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = ORDER", "Answer": "7697 + 8699 = 16396"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = SCALE", "Answer": "7817 + 2811 = 10628"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = SOLVE", "Answer": "7817 + 6811 = 14628"}
{"Question": "TOSS + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "7855 + 2857 = 10712"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = BALL", "Answer": "7867 + 1866 = 9733"}
{"Question": "FALL + HALF = CLASS", "Answer": "7966 + 8967 = 16933"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = ELITE", "Answer": "8133 + 5138 = 13271"}
{"Question": "KILL + MILK = LIMIT", "Answer": "8211 + 4218 = 12429"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = ISSUE", "Answer": "8248 + 6244 = 14492"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "8411 + 6418 = 14829"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = FAITH", "Answer": "8548 + 9544 = 18092"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8568 + 1566 = 10134"}
{"Question": "TOSS + COST = SORRY", "Answer": "8611 + 7618 = 16229"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LOST = STEEL", "Answer": "8611 + 9618 = 18229"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELT = STAFF", "Answer": "8677 + 9678 = 18355"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = SHELF", "Answer": "8699 + 1698 = 10397"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = BRIEF", "Answer": "8698 + 7699 = 16397"}
{"Question": "EASE + PASS = PRIOR", "Answer": "8728 + 1722 = 10450"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = LABEL", "Answer": "8738 + 1733 = 10471"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = FIBER", "Answer": "8798 + 1799 = 10597"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = VOTER", "Answer": "8798 + 5799 = 14597"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = LATER", "Answer": "8948 + 1944 = 10892"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = START", "Answer": "8948 + 3944 = 12892"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = HEART", "Answer": "8948 + 5944 = 14892"}
{"Question": "TOSS + COST = CLOCK", "Answer": "8955 + 1958 = 10913"}
{"Question": "KISS + RISK = ASIAN", "Answer": "8955 + 6958 = 15913"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = FIRST", "Answer": "8968 + 1966 = 10934"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = GRASS", "Answer": "8977 + 5978 = 14955"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASS = ADMIT", "Answer": "9179 + 3177 = 12356"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = LEARN", "Answer": "9211 + 3219 = 12430"}
{"Question": "TEST + LESS = LARGE", "Answer": "9239 + 1233 = 10472"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = GREAT", "Answer": "9249 + 3244 = 12493"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = FULLY", "Answer": "9279 + 1277 = 10556"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELT = PLATE", "Answer": "9344 + 5349 = 14693"}
{"Question": "TOSS + COST = CHECK", "Answer": "9355 + 1359 = 10714"}
{"Question": "FALL + HALF = CATCH", "Answer": "9355 + 4359 = 13714"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = TOOTH", "Answer": "9359 + 8355 = 17714"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = THIRD", "Answer": "9369 + 1366 = 10735"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = COLOR", "Answer": "9377 + 6379 = 15756"}
{"Question": "AREA + TREE = CRAFT", "Answer": "9469 + 5466 = 14935"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = GRASS", "Answer": "9489 + 5488 = 14977"}
{"Question": "AREA + FREE = STAFF", "Answer": "9489 + 7488 = 16977"}
{"Question": "YELL + RELY = ORDER", "Answer": "9733 + 2739 = 12472"}
{"Question": "TALL + SALT = ESSAY", "Answer": "9733 + 4739 = 14472"}
{"Question": "SHIT + THIS = SENSE", "Answer": "1359 + 9351 = 10710"}
{"Question": "SHIT + THIS = SEIZE", "Answer": "1379 + 9371 = 10750"}
{"Question": "DEAR + READ = EARN", "Answer": "1624 + 4621 = 6245"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAD = DRAFT", "Answer": "1628 + 8621 = 10249"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAD = DOZEN", "Answer": "1638 + 8631 = 10269"}
{"Question": "MEAT + TEAM = MONTH", "Answer": "1648 + 8641 = 10289"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "1658 + 8651 = 10309"}
{"Question": "SHIT + THIS = SLEEP", "Answer": "1728 + 8721 = 10449"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = APPLY", "Answer": "2517 + 7512 = 10029"}
{"Question": "THIS + SHIT = DATA", "Answer": "2814 + 4812 = 7626"}
{"Question": "READ + DEAR = ANGRY", "Answer": "2817 + 7812 = 10629"}
{"Question": "READ + DEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "2879 + 9872 = 12751"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "2917 + 7912 = 10829"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = FULLY", "Answer": "4725 + 5724 = 10449"}
{"Question": "MEAT + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "5627 + 7625 = 13252"}
{"Question": "TEAM + MEAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "5678 + 8675 = 14353"}
{"Question": "THIS + SHIT = ELITE", "Answer": "5876 + 6875 = 12751"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "6819 + 9816 = 16635"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = CLASS", "Answer": "6879 + 9876 = 16755"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = BLAME", "Answer": "7629 + 9627 = 17256"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = NEWLY", "Answer": "7638 + 8637 = 16275"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DEAL = BLADE", "Answer": "8749 + 9748 = 18497"}
{"Question": "TEAM + MEAN = MOUNT", "Answer": "9341 + 1348 = 10689"}
{"Question": "DEAD + YEAR = DIRTY", "Answer": "1431 + 9438 = 10869"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = APPLY", "Answer": "1521 + 8526 = 10047"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = APPLE", "Answer": "1531 + 8532 = 10063"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAF = LOOSE", "Answer": "8531 + 1534 = 10065"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = ERROR", "Answer": "1531 + 8539 = 10070"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = ERROR", "Answer": "1541 + 8549 = 10090"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = EVENT", "Answer": "8561 + 1562 = 10123"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEND = TITLE", "Answer": "1561 + 8564 = 10125"}
{"Question": "EASE + TASK = ELECT", "Answer": "1561 + 8567 = 10128"}
{"Question": "COAL + LOAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "8621 + 1629 = 10250"}
{"Question": "THIS + SHIP = SENSE", "Answer": "8651 + 1659 = 10310"}
{"Question": "SOUL + LOUD = ODDS", "Answer": "5721 + 1724 = 7445"}
{"Question": "AIDS + SIDE = SHEET", "Answer": "8721 + 1724 = 10445"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SIGN = HAPPY", "Answer": "1721 + 8725 = 10446"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MEAL = DRAMA", "Answer": "1741 + 8743 = 10484"}
{"Question": "EASE + TASK = EXACT", "Answer": "1961 + 8967 = 10928"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = DRESS", "Answer": "1971 + 8973 = 10944"}
{"Question": "CLUB + BLUE = LABEL", "Answer": "8142 + 2149 = 10291"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAF = APPLE", "Answer": "7512 + 2513 = 10025"}
{"Question": "EASE + PAST = STEP", "Answer": "2562 + 3561 = 6123"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAF = SALAD", "Answer": "7602 + 2605 = 10207"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = SLEEP", "Answer": "2612 + 7613 = 10225"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = STEEL", "Answer": "2612 + 7614 = 10226"}
{"Question": "EASE + PAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "2612 + 7615 = 10227"}
{"Question": "GANG + BAND = EDGE", "Answer": "2712 + 3714 = 6426"}
{"Question": "RACE + EACH = AREA", "Answer": "4712 + 2715 = 7427"}
{"Question": "TENT + DENY = STYLE", "Answer": "2782 + 9785 = 12567"}
{"Question": "WARM + MARK = FEWER", "Answer": "7852 + 2853 = 10705"}
{"Question": "LINK + KING = AGAIN", "Answer": "9053 + 3052 = 12105"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = SELL", "Answer": "3153 + 2158 = 5311"}
{"Question": "BEAT + TEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "9173 + 3174 = 12347"}
{"Question": "FLAG + GLAD = LEGAL", "Answer": "7193 + 3198 = 10391"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = ASIDE", "Answer": "3213 + 7219 = 10432"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = SALES", "Answer": "3213 + 9218 = 12431"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "3243 + 6249 = 9492"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAF = PANEL", "Answer": "3423 + 9426 = 12849"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GRAB = LABEL", "Answer": "9423 + 3428 = 12851"}
{"Question": "HURT + TURN = OCCUR", "Answer": "6523 + 3529 = 10052"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "3593 + 8592 = 12185"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = AGREE", "Answer": "9124 + 4120 = 13244"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = DRIVE", "Answer": "4324 + 9328 = 13652"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAF = REFER", "Answer": "4364 + 9367 = 13731"}
{"Question": "DEAD + YEAH = READY", "Answer": "4374 + 9375 = 13749"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "4534 + 8531 = 13065"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "8674 + 4673 = 13347"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GEAR = EDGE", "Answer": "4714 + 2713 = 7427"}
{"Question": "TENT + DENY = ORDER", "Answer": "4784 + 5786 = 10570"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = DEAD", "Answer": "4874 + 1872 = 6746"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REAL = START", "Answer": "4874 + 5876 = 10750"}
{"Question": "EASE + LAST = TALL", "Answer": "5015 + 3018 = 8033"}
{"Question": "SEAT + TEAR = DRESS", "Answer": "8045 + 5043 = 13088"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "5215 + 8213 = 13428"}
{"Question": "EAST + TASK = LABEL", "Answer": "7235 + 5236 = 12471"}
{"Question": "EASE + LAST = TELL", "Answer": "5265 + 3268 = 8533"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MEAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "5315 + 9314 = 14629"}
{"Question": "FAIR + RAIL = SALES", "Answer": "8345 + 5346 = 13691"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = MAYBE", "Answer": "5345 + 9348 = 14693"}
{"Question": "SHOW + WHOM = THEME", "Answer": "8365 + 5362 = 13727"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = TREAT", "Answer": "5375 + 8376 = 13751"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FEAR = BRIEF", "Answer": "5475 + 8473 = 13948"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAR = CRASH", "Answer": "5495 + 7492 = 12987"}
{"Question": "BEAR + REAL = SALAD", "Answer": "4605 + 5602 = 10207"}
{"Question": "EASE + TASK = SHOOT", "Answer": "5615 + 8613 = 14228"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "5635 + 7632 = 13267"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = FENCE", "Answer": "5635 + 7638 = 13273"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MEAL = LOOSE", "Answer": "5695 + 7691 = 13386"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = LOOK", "Answer": "5725 + 1724 = 7449"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = LOCAL", "Answer": "5735 + 4736 = 10471"}
{"Question": "WRAP + PRAY = UPPER", "Answer": "9785 + 5782 = 15567"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = METER", "Answer": "5805 + 4803 = 10608"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = START", "Answer": "5815 + 6817 = 12632"}
{"Question": "DARE + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "6825 + 5827 = 12652"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAF = BADLY", "Answer": "6825 + 5829 = 12654"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GEAR = ARGUE", "Answer": "5915 + 8914 = 14829"}
{"Question": "DEAD + PEAK = HAPPY", "Answer": "5945 + 8942 = 14887"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REAL = PAPER", "Answer": "6056 + 9053 = 15109"}
{"Question": "BEAT + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7136 + 6132 = 13268"}
{"Question": "ELSE + ALSO = LOCAL", "Answer": "6146 + 9145 = 15291"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "6156 + 9153 = 15309"}
{"Question": "CLUB + BLUE = LEVEL", "Answer": "9176 + 6175 = 15351"}
{"Question": "TEAR + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "4216 + 6210 = 10426"}
{"Question": "SOUP + POUR = TRUST", "Answer": "9246 + 6245 = 15491"}
{"Question": "YEAR + REAL = ALLY", "Answer": "1276 + 6275 = 7551"}
{"Question": "SALT + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "7316 + 6312 = 13628"}
{"Question": "LAST + TASK = SALES", "Answer": "8416 + 6415 = 14831"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "6496 + 8491 = 14987"}
{"Question": "YARD + DARE = CARRY", "Answer": "8506 + 6502 = 15008"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAF = APPLE", "Answer": "6516 + 3519 = 10035"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "6746 + 5742 = 12488"}
{"Question": "TEAM + MEAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "7826 + 6821 = 14647"}
{"Question": "DEAD + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "6876 + 1875 = 8751"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "6946 + 7945 = 14891"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7137 + 6132 = 13269"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAR = PRIDE", "Answer": "7237 + 8235 = 15472"}
{"Question": "YARD + DARE = ESSAY", "Answer": "8267 + 7261 = 15528"}
{"Question": "YEAR + REAL = APPLY", "Answer": "9317 + 7312 = 16629"}
{"Question": "GANG + RANK = EAGER", "Answer": "7357 + 6359 = 13716"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TEAM = MATCH", "Answer": "8357 + 7351 = 15708"}
{"Question": "EASE + MASK = SEEM", "Answer": "7387 + 1384 = 8771"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LEAF = HELLO", "Answer": "6387 + 7385 = 13772"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GRAB = BREAD", "Answer": "8607 + 7601 = 16208"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAR = REACH", "Answer": "7627 + 8621 = 16248"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = LEAVE", "Answer": "7627 + 8629 = 16256"}
{"Question": "REAL + LEAF = FEWER", "Answer": "8637 + 7631 = 16268"}
{"Question": "SHIT + THIN = PHOTO", "Answer": "8637 + 7635 = 16272"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "7657 + 8651 = 16308"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = TENT", "Answer": "1867 + 7862 = 9729"}
{"Question": "BOMB + COME = SMELL", "Answer": "7927 + 4928 = 12855"}
{"Question": "DARE + EARN = BRAND", "Answer": "5038 + 8037 = 13075"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GRAB = PAPER", "Answer": "9078 + 8072 = 17150"}
{"Question": "EAST + TASK = ASSET", "Answer": "4128 + 8120 = 12248"}
{"Question": "AIDS + SIDE = IRAQI", "Answer": "2148 + 8143 = 10291"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAT = MATCH", "Answer": "8328 + 4326 = 12654"}
{"Question": "YEAR + REAL = DELAY", "Answer": "5398 + 8397 = 13795"}
{"Question": "BEAT + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "6428 + 8421 = 14849"}
{"Question": "FACE + EACH = SHELL", "Answer": "9428 + 8427 = 17855"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = KNOCK", "Answer": "5478 + 8473 = 13951"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEND = SEVEN", "Answer": "8528 + 6524 = 15052"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAF = LOOSE", "Answer": "8548 + 1547 = 10095"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = BIBLE", "Answer": "8568 + 1567 = 10135"}
{"Question": "MEAN + NEAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "5628 + 8624 = 14252"}
{"Question": "SALT + TALK = SENSE", "Answer": "1658 + 8652 = 10310"}
{"Question": "LINK + KING = LEGAL", "Answer": "1678 + 8673 = 10351"}
{"Question": "EASE + PAST = PHOTO", "Answer": "8678 + 1675 = 10353"}
{"Question": "GANG + SAND = SCENE", "Answer": "8698 + 1695 = 10393"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = SHOCK", "Answer": "8718 + 3712 = 12430"}
{"Question": "FORM + MORE = REFER", "Answer": "4718 + 8713 = 13431"}
{"Question": "FAIR + RAIL = FLOOR", "Answer": "1728 + 8720 = 10448"}
{"Question": "REAL + LEAF = FLOOR", "Answer": "9728 + 8721 = 18449"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HEAT = HOTEL", "Answer": "8738 + 1734 = 10472"}
{"Question": "GANG + HAND = HUMAN", "Answer": "8738 + 1735 = 10473"}
{"Question": "BIRD + DIRT = STAIR", "Answer": "6738 + 8735 = 15473"}
{"Question": "SHIT + THIN = SEIZE", "Answer": "1748 + 8742 = 10490"}
{"Question": "BEAR + READ = BLADE", "Answer": "1748 + 8749 = 10497"}
{"Question": "GANG + SAND = SENSE", "Answer": "8758 + 1752 = 10510"}
{"Question": "BOMB + SOME = SALES", "Answer": "8768 + 1763 = 10531"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LEAF = LOCAL", "Answer": "8798 + 1793 = 10591"}
{"Question": "HEAT + TEAM = HUMAN", "Answer": "1798 + 8795 = 10593"}
{"Question": "EASE + TASK = TREAT", "Answer": "8948 + 1943 = 10891"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = CLEAR", "Answer": "1948 + 8946 = 10894"}
{"Question": "DARE + EARN = BREAD", "Answer": "5948 + 8947 = 14895"}
{"Question": "LINK + KIND = ONION", "Answer": "6958 + 8957 = 15915"}
{"Question": "BOMB + COME = CROSS", "Answer": "8968 + 1965 = 10933"}
{"Question": "TEND + DENY = TREAT", "Answer": "1978 + 8973 = 10951"}
{"Question": "GANG + BAND = BLADE", "Answer": "8978 + 1975 = 10953"}
{"Question": "EASE + LAST = SHALL", "Answer": "9019 + 3014 = 12033"}
{"Question": "KICK + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "9179 + 4175 = 13354"}
{"Question": "FLAG + GLAD = LEVEL", "Answer": "6179 + 9172 = 15351"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MEAL = ARMED", "Answer": "9219 + 4210 = 13429"}
{"Question": "HURT + TURN = INNER", "Answer": "5239 + 9234 = 14473"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = CLEAR", "Answer": "9249 + 1243 = 10492"}
{"Question": "FARM + MARK = FLOOR", "Answer": "1279 + 9278 = 10557"}
{"Question": "KICK + RICE = OFFER", "Answer": "9289 + 6287 = 15576"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "9319 + 7318 = 16637"}
{"Question": "EAST + TASK = ELITE", "Answer": "1349 + 9342 = 10691"}
{"Question": "CARE + EARN = COVER", "Answer": "1349 + 9345 = 10694"}
{"Question": "EASE + VAST = VOTER", "Answer": "9349 + 1346 = 10695"}
{"Question": "PANT + TANK = PHOTO", "Answer": "1349 + 9347 = 10696"}
{"Question": "EASE + CASH = COVER", "Answer": "9349 + 1348 = 10697"}
{"Question": "TEND + DENY = TASTE", "Answer": "1359 + 9354 = 10713"}
{"Question": "BOMB + COME = CHECK", "Answer": "9359 + 1357 = 10716"}
{"Question": "GANG + PANT = TASTE", "Answer": "9359 + 4351 = 13710"}
{"Question": "BIRD + DIRT = TRUTH", "Answer": "6359 + 9351 = 15710"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "9359 + 8351 = 17710"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REAL = RIVER", "Answer": "9369 + 1362 = 10731"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = COURT", "Answer": "9369 + 1365 = 10734"}
{"Question": "CARD + DARE = CLEAR", "Answer": "1369 + 9367 = 10736"}
{"Question": "TEAM + MEAL = LATER", "Answer": "7369 + 9361 = 16730"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEAN = BLAME", "Answer": "9379 + 1374 = 10753"}
{"Question": "DEAD + NEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "9379 + 4375 = 13754"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MEAL = BLAME", "Answer": "9379 + 5374 = 14753"}
{"Question": "VARY + YARD = LEVEL", "Answer": "8439 + 9432 = 17871"}
{"Question": "AREA + CREW = TRACE", "Answer": "9479 + 5478 = 14957"}
{"Question": "HAIR + RAIL = EARTH", "Answer": "5489 + 9486 = 14975"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TEAM = STATE", "Answer": "9629 + 5627 = 15256"}
{"Question": "REAL + LEAD = ORDER", "Answer": "4789 + 9785 = 14574"}
{"Question": "EASE + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "1251 + 9241 = 10492"}
{"Question": "TEST + BELT = TASTE", "Answer": "1251 + 9261 = 10512"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEND = DOZEN", "Answer": "1751 + 8721 = 10472"}
{"Question": "TEST + LEFT = SELL", "Answer": "1941 + 2981 = 4922"}
{"Question": "EASE + CAKE = KICK", "Answer": "2672 + 1642 = 4314"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAT = ENTRY", "Answer": "3123 + 9183 = 12306"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BLUE = STEAL", "Answer": "3613 + 8693 = 12306"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "3613 + 9623 = 13236"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHIT = CATCH", "Answer": "3623 + 8693 = 12316"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BLUE = SELL", "Answer": "3693 + 5673 = 9366"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATE = STAND", "Answer": "4014 + 8024 = 12038"}
{"Question": "EASE + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "4094 + 8014 = 12108"}
{"Question": "EASE + NAME = ASIAN", "Answer": "4124 + 8194 = 12318"}
{"Question": "EASE + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "4264 + 8254 = 12518"}
{"Question": "EASE + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "4714 + 8734 = 13448"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEAT = SCALE", "Answer": "4814 + 5864 = 10678"}
{"Question": "TEST + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "4814 + 9834 = 14648"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SEND = TASTE", "Answer": "4824 + 7894 = 12718"}
{"Question": "TENT + SEAT = EASE", "Answer": "4864 + 3874 = 8738"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEFT = FLEE", "Answer": "5035 + 1065 = 6100"}
{"Question": "TENT + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "6256 + 4206 = 10462"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BLUE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6316 + 7346 = 13662"}
{"Question": "EASE + HAVE = SEVEN", "Answer": "6716 + 9746 = 16462"}
{"Question": "EASE + BAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "6836 + 7826 = 14662"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATE = ASSET", "Answer": "7127 + 5147 = 12274"}
{"Question": "EASE + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "7357 + 6317 = 13674"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEND = TASTE", "Answer": "7427 + 5487 = 12914"}
{"Question": "EASE + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "7827 + 6847 = 14674"}
{"Question": "EASE + FATE = STAFF", "Answer": "8018 + 6048 = 14066"}
{"Question": "EASE + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "8178 + 2108 = 10286"}
{"Question": "EASE + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "8138 + 6148 = 14286"}
{"Question": "KICK + MILK = LIMIT", "Answer": "8208 + 4218 = 12426"}
{"Question": "EASE + DARE = SALAD", "Answer": "8518 + 6538 = 15056"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHOT = SOUTH", "Answer": "8678 + 1608 = 10286"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEND = FENCE", "Answer": "8608 + 7628 = 16236"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEFT = FENCE", "Answer": "8628 + 7618 = 16246"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAT = NERVE", "Answer": "8618 + 7638 = 16256"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEAT = SENSE", "Answer": "8618 + 7698 = 16316"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEND = BLAME", "Answer": "8628 + 1648 = 10276"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BEND = BLADE", "Answer": "8628 + 1658 = 10286"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "8658 + 9628 = 18286"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHIT = COACH", "Answer": "8638 + 5678 = 14316"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHIT = SALAD", "Answer": "8708 + 1798 = 10506"}
{"Question": "EASE + HATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8798 + 6718 = 15516"}
{"Question": "EASE + RATE = OTHER", "Answer": "8728 + 6758 = 15486"}
{"Question": "EASE + CARE = COLOR", "Answer": "8738 + 1768 = 10506"}
{"Question": "EASE + CAKE = CROSS", "Answer": "8768 + 1798 = 10566"}
{"Question": "EASE + LAKE = SHELL", "Answer": "8918 + 6948 = 15866"}
{"Question": "EASE + CAKE = CRACK", "Answer": "8948 + 1968 = 10916"}
{"Question": "TENT + SEAT = SHALL", "Answer": "9239 + 1249 = 10488"}
{"Question": "EASE + TAPE = TROOP", "Answer": "9269 + 1289 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BLUE = BUILD", "Answer": "9329 + 1309 = 10638"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "9409 + 5489 = 14898"}
{"Question": "EASE + CAKE = CHECK", "Answer": "9429 + 1489 = 10918"}
{"Question": "TENT + HEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "9439 + 8479 = 17918"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATA = ENTER", "Answer": "1261 + 9252 = 10513"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATA = SEAT", "Answer": "1591 + 7565 = 9156"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATA = ELECT", "Answer": "1571 + 8565 = 10136"}
{"Question": "GANG + DATA = GREAT", "Answer": "1691 + 8676 = 10367"}
{"Question": "GANG + DATA = ANGER", "Answer": "3123 + 9181 = 12304"}
{"Question": "TEST + HERE = ENTER", "Answer": "3173 + 9141 = 12314"}
{"Question": "DATA + HARD = TRUTH", "Answer": "3414 + 7403 = 10817"}
{"Question": "HERE + YEAH = CARRY", "Answer": "3484 + 7403 = 10887"}
{"Question": "MERE + TEAM = ADAPT", "Answer": "3595 + 8513 = 12108"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATA = STEEL", "Answer": "4214 + 9232 = 13446"}
{"Question": "DATA + CARD = ELECT", "Answer": "4595 + 7584 = 12179"}
{"Question": "EASE + DATA = TREAT", "Answer": "4754 + 8717 = 13471"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = REACH", "Answer": "5365 + 8313 = 13678"}
{"Question": "DATA + HAND = CATCH", "Answer": "5373 + 8345 = 13718"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = BEACH", "Answer": "5375 + 8393 = 13768"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "5415 + 8434 = 13849"}
{"Question": "HERE + YEAH = DRAMA", "Answer": "5434 + 8495 = 13929"}
{"Question": "TEST + GENE = ASIAN", "Answer": "6236 + 7282 = 13518"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "6246 + 8272 = 14518"}
{"Question": "DATA + YARD = TODAY", "Answer": "6313 + 9326 = 15639"}
{"Question": "TENT + HERE = NORTH", "Answer": "6716 + 3747 = 10463"}
{"Question": "DATA + CARD = ORDER", "Answer": "6808 + 7846 = 14654"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = ORDER", "Answer": "6836 + 7848 = 14684"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = APART", "Answer": "7517 + 6585 = 14102"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7517 + 9585 = 17102"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = IRISH", "Answer": "8578 + 3525 = 12103"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = GRAIN", "Answer": "8628 + 1646 = 10274"}
{"Question": "TENT + MERE = MARRY", "Answer": "8698 + 1636 = 10334"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HERE = HONOR", "Answer": "8658 + 1646 = 10304"}
{"Question": "TEST + GENE = GLASS", "Answer": "8648 + 1696 = 10344"}
{"Question": "MERE + TEAM = AFTER", "Answer": "8757 + 4718 = 13475"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = EAGER", "Answer": "9129 + 3181 = 12310"}
{"Question": "TENT + HERE = HONOR", "Answer": "9379 + 1323 = 10702"}
{"Question": "DATA + CARD = EAGER", "Answer": "9383 + 4329 = 13712"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GENE = GLASS", "Answer": "9379 + 1343 = 10722"}
{"Question": "TENT + MERE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9469 + 1434 = 10903"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELL = DRAMA", "Answer": "1241 + 9233 = 10474"}
{"Question": "POLL + SOUP = PAUSE", "Answer": "1255 + 9241 = 10496"}
{"Question": "GANG + BALL = GREEN", "Answer": "1281 + 9277 = 10558"}
{"Question": "TALL + PANT = TROOP", "Answer": "1288 + 9271 = 10559"}
{"Question": "LOTS + SOFT = SHELF", "Answer": "9341 + 1354 = 10695"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1371 + 9347 = 10718"}
{"Question": "HILL + RICH = HONOR", "Answer": "1388 + 9321 = 10709"}
{"Question": "TENT + SELL = TASTE", "Answer": "1481 + 9433 = 10914"}
{"Question": "EASE + TALL = ENTER", "Answer": "1451 + 9466 = 10917"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = ADAPT", "Answer": "1531 + 8593 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAN = TITLE", "Answer": "1541 + 8594 = 10135"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POEM = BIBLE", "Answer": "1561 + 8576 = 10137"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = APART", "Answer": "1561 + 8596 = 10157"}
{"Question": "HALL + MATH = THAT", "Answer": "1577 + 6581 = 8158"}
{"Question": "SELL + NEWS = SALAD", "Answer": "1633 + 8671 = 10304"}
{"Question": "HIGH + RING = HONOR", "Answer": "1671 + 8637 = 10308"}
{"Question": "LESS + DEAL = SALE", "Answer": "1766 + 4751 = 6517"}
{"Question": "TEST + BELL = TASTE", "Answer": "1751 + 8766 = 10517"}
{"Question": "SELL + NEWS = ELSE", "Answer": "1877 + 6841 = 8718"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = BLOCK", "Answer": "1951 + 8975 = 10926"}
{"Question": "GANG + BALL = GRAIN", "Answer": "1971 + 8966 = 10937"}
{"Question": "TALL + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "2155 + 8132 = 10287"}
{"Question": "MESS + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "2355 + 8372 = 10727"}
{"Question": "RATE + EAST = AREA", "Answer": "3642 + 2684 = 6326"}
{"Question": "DEAD + YELL = BADLY", "Answer": "2602 + 7655 = 10257"}
{"Question": "LOSS + COAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "2655 + 9612 = 12267"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = REACH", "Answer": "3123 + 9182 = 12305"}
{"Question": "DEAD + YELL = EARLY", "Answer": "3103 + 7144 = 10247"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAN = EXTRA", "Answer": "3163 + 7196 = 10359"}
{"Question": "TELL + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "3166 + 9153 = 12319"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PLUS = SELL", "Answer": "3183 + 5128 = 8311"}
{"Question": "LESS + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "3522 + 6513 = 10035"}
{"Question": "TEST + BELL = STATE", "Answer": "3513 + 9522 = 13035"}
{"Question": "TOSS + POET = QUOTE", "Answer": "3955 + 6983 = 10938"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELL = SALES", "Answer": "3903 + 6988 = 10891"}
{"Question": "TALL + PANT = LATIN", "Answer": "4211 + 8254 = 12465"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = TREAT", "Answer": "4374 + 9367 = 13741"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = EAGER", "Answer": "4514 + 9501 = 14015"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POEM = SENSE", "Answer": "4684 + 7628 = 12312"}
{"Question": "KISS + LINK = SKIN", "Answer": "4766 + 1704 = 6470"}
{"Question": "LOSS + BOWL = ALLOW", "Answer": "4766 + 9704 = 14470"}
{"Question": "GANG + EARN = KNEE", "Answer": "4874 + 1837 = 6711"}
{"Question": "HIGH + BILL = LIGHT", "Answer": "5245 + 7211 = 12456"}
{"Question": "TALL + PAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "5233 + 8215 = 13448"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TOSS = ASSET", "Answer": "5235 + 9244 = 14479"}
{"Question": "TALL + FACT = CATCH", "Answer": "5299 + 7215 = 12514"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOSS = MOTOR", "Answer": "5315 + 8322 = 13637"}
{"Question": "LOSS + GOAL = COACH", "Answer": "5344 + 8375 = 13719"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TELL = LAST", "Answer": "5375 + 1366 = 6741"}
{"Question": "TALL + EAST = SALES", "Answer": "5366 + 8315 = 13681"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TELL = LATER", "Answer": "5435 + 8411 = 13846"}
{"Question": "HALL + EACH = CLOSE", "Answer": "5422 + 7415 = 12837"}
{"Question": "RATE + EAST = OTHER", "Answer": "7425 + 5432 = 12857"}
{"Question": "GANG + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "5425 + 9472 = 14897"}
{"Question": "VERY + YEAR = LEVEL", "Answer": "9465 + 5476 = 14941"}
{"Question": "ONTO + KNEE = STEEL", "Answer": "5605 + 4622 = 10227"}
{"Question": "HILL + RICH = COLOR", "Answer": "5622 + 7615 = 13237"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CELL = PLACE", "Answer": "5745 + 6722 = 12467"}
{"Question": "GANG + EARN = TREAT", "Answer": "5765 + 4706 = 10471"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = BUYER", "Answer": "5835 + 4803 = 10638"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELL = STATE", "Answer": "5875 + 4833 = 10708"}
{"Question": "TELL + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "5833 + 6825 = 12658"}
{"Question": "LESS + DEAL = ORDER", "Answer": "5877 + 6805 = 12682"}
{"Question": "GANG + LAWN = SENSE", "Answer": "5875 + 6837 = 12712"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TELL = ELITE", "Answer": "6136 + 9155 = 15291"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PLUS = SLEEP", "Answer": "6316 + 7351 = 13667"}
{"Question": "YELL + VERY = NEVER", "Answer": "6388 + 7346 = 13734"}
{"Question": "ONTO + KNEE = ENEMY", "Answer": "6596 + 8511 = 15107"}
{"Question": "MESS + TEAM = LEAST", "Answer": "6522 + 8506 = 15028"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = ERROR", "Answer": "6546 + 3504 = 10050"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TELL = CATCH", "Answer": "6726 + 5788 = 12514"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PLUS = WHEEL", "Answer": "6826 + 3842 = 10668"}
{"Question": "MESS + TERM = ENTER", "Answer": "7122 + 3197 = 10319"}
{"Question": "GANG + MASS = ASIAN", "Answer": "7197 + 5122 = 12319"}
{"Question": "RATE + EAST = AFTER", "Answer": "9127 + 7152 = 16279"}
{"Question": "HALL + EACH = LOOSE", "Answer": "7211 + 8297 = 15508"}
{"Question": "HALL + EACH = SALES", "Answer": "7244 + 5207 = 12451"}
{"Question": "HALL + CASH = SALES", "Answer": "7244 + 5217 = 12461"}
{"Question": "GANG + TALL = LATIN", "Answer": "7387 + 6311 = 13698"}
{"Question": "TELL + HEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "7388 + 5327 = 12715"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TELL = LEAST", "Answer": "7627 + 8611 = 16238"}
{"Question": "TEST + NEWS = SEVEN", "Answer": "7617 + 8651 = 16268"}
{"Question": "GANG + WARN = ENTER", "Answer": "7627 + 4692 = 12319"}
{"Question": "TEST + BELL = SENSE", "Answer": "7617 + 8699 = 16316"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "7817 + 6801 = 14618"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = PRIOR", "Answer": "7857 + 4825 = 12682"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BOAT = WASTE", "Answer": "7866 + 2807 = 10673"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = REFER", "Answer": "7947 + 8914 = 16861"}
{"Question": "MALL + FARM = DRAMA", "Answer": "8022 + 7058 = 15080"}
{"Question": "LESS + REAL = EARLY", "Answer": "8177 + 2108 = 10285"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8238 + 5243 = 13481"}
{"Question": "VIEW + WIDE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5238 + 8293 = 13531"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "8358 + 7315 = 15673"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = GUEST", "Answer": "8368 + 4326 = 12694"}
{"Question": "TELL + BEAT = LATER", "Answer": "8411 + 5438 = 13849"}
{"Question": "POEM + MOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5438 + 8493 = 13931"}
{"Question": "GANG + EARN = ERROR", "Answer": "8528 + 1502 = 10030"}
{"Question": "TALL + EAST = ESSAY", "Answer": "8544 + 1508 = 10052"}
{"Question": "GANG + LAWN = LOOSE", "Answer": "8568 + 1526 = 10094"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8598 + 1577 = 10175"}
{"Question": "TENT + BELL = NERVE", "Answer": "8518 + 6577 = 15095"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "8578 + 9507 = 18085"}
{"Question": "TELL + REST = STARE", "Answer": "8577 + 9518 = 18095"}
{"Question": "SORT + TOUR = SERVE", "Answer": "1628 + 8642 = 10270"}
{"Question": "GANG + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "8628 + 3602 = 12230"}
{"Question": "TENT + MESS = MONTH", "Answer": "8628 + 1655 = 10283"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TOSS = THESE", "Answer": "8698 + 1655 = 10353"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CELL = COACH", "Answer": "8638 + 1677 = 10315"}
{"Question": "MASS + FARM = FLOOR", "Answer": "8677 + 1658 = 10335"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HELL = COACH", "Answer": "8638 + 5677 = 14315"}
{"Question": "HALL + MATH = SHEET", "Answer": "8677 + 9658 = 18335"}
{"Question": "GANG + WARN = WORRY", "Answer": "8698 + 1639 = 10337"}
{"Question": "EASE + CALL = CROSS", "Answer": "8678 + 1699 = 10377"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POEM = PEACE", "Answer": "8728 + 1702 = 10430"}
{"Question": "GANG + LAWN = LEVEL", "Answer": "8738 + 1763 = 10501"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TOSS = TRUST", "Answer": "8798 + 1733 = 10531"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8738 + 4793 = 13531"}
{"Question": "KICK + MISS = MUSIC", "Answer": "8728 + 1744 = 10472"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = ONION", "Answer": "8748 + 3764 = 12512"}
{"Question": "EASE + FALL = FULLY", "Answer": "8798 + 1755 = 10553"}
{"Question": "DATE + EAST = ORDER", "Answer": "4758 + 8725 = 13483"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOSS = LABEL", "Answer": "8928 + 1933 = 10861"}
{"Question": "GANG + LAWN = LEGAL", "Answer": "8938 + 1953 = 10891"}
{"Question": "EASE + TALL = SHEET", "Answer": "8918 + 4966 = 13884"}
{"Question": "AREA + URGE = START", "Answer": "8968 + 5926 = 14894"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POEM = PHONE", "Answer": "8978 + 1957 = 10935"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = MOTOR", "Answer": "9219 + 3201 = 12420"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEAN = SCALE", "Answer": "9239 + 8243 = 17482"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELL = TASTE", "Answer": "9279 + 8233 = 17512"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = FULLY", "Answer": "9289 + 1268 = 10557"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "9329 + 1302 = 10631"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAN = LEVEL", "Answer": "9329 + 4302 = 13631"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POEM = PIANO", "Answer": "9349 + 1324 = 10673"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FORM = FEWER", "Answer": "9359 + 1345 = 10704"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOSS = LEMON", "Answer": "9379 + 1355 = 10734"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TOSS = LIMIT", "Answer": "9379 + 5366 = 14745"}
{"Question": "TENT + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "9379 + 6357 = 15736"}
{"Question": "HIGH + BILL = BASIS", "Answer": "9349 + 1388 = 10737"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRUE = CRAFT", "Answer": "9469 + 5436 = 14905"}
{"Question": "TELL + REST = METER", "Answer": "9466 + 5479 = 14945"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SELL = ASSET", "Answer": "9619 + 2644 = 12263"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ROLL = ERROR", "Answer": "9809 + 6877 = 16686"}
{"Question": "TALE + EAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "1598 + 8561 = 10159"}
{"Question": "TAPE + EAST = STEP", "Answer": "1587 + 7591 = 9178"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TENT = DOZEN", "Answer": "1671 + 8698 = 10369"}
{"Question": "EACH + HATE = ENTER", "Answer": "1768 + 8751 = 10519"}
{"Question": "LAST + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "2589 + 9502 = 12091"}
{"Question": "HAVE + EACH = COVER", "Answer": "2867 + 7812 = 10679"}
{"Question": "HATE + EACH = TREAT", "Answer": "3918 + 8973 = 12891"}
{"Question": "NAME + EARN = TREAT", "Answer": "3968 + 8923 = 12891"}
{"Question": "TERM + MEAT = PARTY", "Answer": "4508 + 8534 = 13042"}
{"Question": "EAST + TAPE = SLEEP", "Answer": "4718 + 8724 = 13442"}
{"Question": "LONG + GOAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "4759 + 9714 = 14473"}
{"Question": "TAKE + EAST = CHECK", "Answer": "4795 + 5724 = 10519"}
{"Question": "LOTS + SOIL = FIRST", "Answer": "5638 + 8645 = 14283"}
{"Question": "EASE + GANG = INNER", "Answer": "5705 + 8748 = 14453"}
{"Question": "LOTS + SOUL = TRUST", "Answer": "5716 + 6745 = 12461"}
{"Question": "TENT + DEAD = CATCH", "Answer": "5765 + 8748 = 14513"}
{"Question": "TEAR + REST = STORE", "Answer": "6579 + 9516 = 16095"}
{"Question": "SLIP + PLUS = USUAL", "Answer": "6589 + 9516 = 16105"}
{"Question": "NAME + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "6538 + 8546 = 15084"}
{"Question": "NAME + EARN = MINOR", "Answer": "6817 + 7836 = 14653"}
{"Question": "LOTS + SOIL = PILOT", "Answer": "6837 + 7846 = 14683"}
{"Question": "TEST + DEAD = WASTE", "Answer": "7507 + 8568 = 16075"}
{"Question": "TEST + DEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "7567 + 8518 = 16085"}
{"Question": "EASE + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "1251 + 9240 = 10491"}
{"Question": "DEAD + MENU = DRAMA", "Answer": "1241 + 9253 = 10494"}
{"Question": "SONG + GOAL = GRASS", "Answer": "9251 + 1248 = 10499"}
{"Question": "CREW + WRAP = WHERE", "Answer": "9251 + 1274 = 10525"}
{"Question": "TENT + DESK = TASTE", "Answer": "1341 + 9372 = 10713"}
{"Question": "BOWL + LOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8671 + 1630 = 10301"}
{"Question": "HIGH + BIND = HONOR", "Answer": "1671 + 8634 = 10305"}
{"Question": "AIDS + SING = SENSE", "Answer": "8671 + 1639 = 10310"}
{"Question": "EASE + PART = ENTER", "Answer": "1671 + 8643 = 10314"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEAR = STARE", "Answer": "2712 + 9745 = 12457"}
{"Question": "REST + TEAM = SMART", "Answer": "7812 + 2860 = 10672"}
{"Question": "AREA + CROP = READY", "Answer": "3123 + 9184 = 12307"}
{"Question": "GANG + CARD = ANGER", "Answer": "3123 + 9185 = 12308"}
{"Question": "AREA + TRIP = REACT", "Answer": "3123 + 9186 = 12309"}
{"Question": "TENT + DEAL = ENTER", "Answer": "3123 + 9187 = 12310"}
{"Question": "FADE + EACH = AHEAD", "Answer": "9153 + 3162 = 12315"}
{"Question": "TENT + BEAR = EXTRA", "Answer": "3173 + 9185 = 12358"}
{"Question": "DIRT + TIME = ENTER", "Answer": "8643 + 3671 = 12314"}
{"Question": "EASE + DARK = ORDER", "Answer": "3823 + 6807 = 10630"}
{"Question": "DATE + EARN = TREAT", "Answer": "6214 + 4207 = 10421"}
{"Question": "EASE + LAWN = SWEAR", "Answer": "4214 + 6209 = 10423"}
{"Question": "EASE + PALM = SLEEP", "Answer": "4214 + 9235 = 13449"}
{"Question": "AREA + DRUG = GRADE", "Answer": "4254 + 8231 = 12485"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "4294 + 8251 = 12545"}
{"Question": "CARD + DATE = ORDER", "Answer": "8734 + 4759 = 13493"}
{"Question": "TENT + HERO = NORTH", "Answer": "5215 + 8243 = 13458"}
{"Question": "RATE + EACH = THEIR", "Answer": "8215 + 5293 = 13508"}
{"Question": "TEST + HERO = SOUTH", "Answer": "5315 + 7342 = 12657"}
{"Question": "ELSE + FLAT = STAFF", "Answer": "5315 + 7362 = 12677"}
{"Question": "GANG + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "5365 + 9374 = 14739"}
{"Question": "TEAR + RELY = ALTER", "Answer": "8415 + 5430 = 13845"}
{"Question": "GANG + MATH = ENTER", "Answer": "5425 + 7493 = 12918"}
{"Question": "BOMB + HOUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "5425 + 8493 = 13918"}
{"Question": "GANG + RATE = METER", "Answer": "5435 + 7492 = 12927"}
{"Question": "LEFT + TEAM = SMALL", "Answer": "7485 + 5492 = 12977"}
{"Question": "BIND + DIET = ENTER", "Answer": "4605 + 5612 = 10217"}
{"Question": "BOMB + HOLE = SMELL", "Answer": "5605 + 4672 = 10277"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TIRE = GREAT", "Answer": "5615 + 7632 = 13247"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SITE = GUEST", "Answer": "5615 + 8672 = 14287"}
{"Question": "DEAD + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "5635 + 4671 = 10306"}
{"Question": "SHOW + WHAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "7635 + 5681 = 13316"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELT = TASTE", "Answer": "5645 + 8671 = 14316"}
{"Question": "TEST + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "5715 + 9742 = 15457"}
{"Question": "DIRT + TINY = ENTER", "Answer": "6795 + 5724 = 12519"}
{"Question": "DUST + TURN = ENTER", "Answer": "8725 + 5794 = 14519"}
{"Question": "CREW + WRAP = EAGER", "Answer": "4815 + 5803 = 10618"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REST = STARE", "Answer": "5865 + 7813 = 13678"}
{"Question": "GANG + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "5845 + 6827 = 12672"}
{"Question": "LOAN + NOSE = SALES", "Answer": "8945 + 5916 = 14861"}
{"Question": "LIST + TINY = ASIAN", "Answer": "8945 + 5972 = 14917"}
{"Question": "EAST + TAIL = BIBLE", "Answer": "9086 + 6053 = 15139"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELT = LABEL", "Answer": "6206 + 4215 = 10421"}
{"Question": "NEWS + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "9316 + 6357 = 15673"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOTS = STEEL", "Answer": "6456 + 7431 = 13887"}
{"Question": "HOUR + ROCK = COUCH", "Answer": "8506 + 6512 = 15018"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELT = AWARE", "Answer": "6516 + 7589 = 14105"}
{"Question": "GAME + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "8576 + 6510 = 15086"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "6596 + 8512 = 15108"}
{"Question": "BOTH + HOLD = TOTAL", "Answer": "8516 + 6593 = 15109"}
{"Question": "GANG + CARE = PAPER", "Answer": "6546 + 8593 = 15139"}
{"Question": "GANG + FADE = ORDER", "Answer": "6786 + 3754 = 10540"}
{"Question": "DIRT + TIME = MOTOR", "Answer": "5806 + 6814 = 12620"}
{"Question": "RAIN + NAME = INNER", "Answer": "9816 + 6823 = 16639"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POET = EMPTY", "Answer": "6956 + 8917 = 15873"}
{"Question": "AREA + FROM = REFER", "Answer": "7107 + 3194 = 10301"}
{"Question": "EAST + TAIL = SALES", "Answer": "5217 + 7234 = 12451"}
{"Question": "TALE + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "6317 + 7358 = 13675"}
{"Question": "COAL + LOSE = ASSET", "Answer": "9317 + 7368 = 16685"}
{"Question": "BEAT + TERM = METER", "Answer": "6357 + 7381 = 13738"}
{"Question": "DEAD + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "7427 + 5418 = 12845"}
{"Question": "BOAT + TOWN = ALLOW", "Answer": "2517 + 7536 = 10053"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SNAP = APART", "Answer": "7597 + 4512 = 12109"}
{"Question": "DEBT + TERM = ORDER", "Answer": "2657 + 7603 = 10260"}
{"Question": "GANG + BACK = ONION", "Answer": "7627 + 4685 = 12312"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TIME = EIGHT", "Answer": "7627 + 8651 = 16278"}
{"Question": "FAIL + LAST = STILL", "Answer": "2867 + 7810 = 10677"}
{"Question": "NEWS + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "4897 + 7821 = 12718"}
{"Question": "BAND + DARE = UNDER", "Answer": "5837 + 7892 = 13729"}
{"Question": "BOMB + CORE = PRIOR", "Answer": "7967 + 4925 = 12892"}
{"Question": "TALE + EARN = ALTER", "Answer": "2108 + 8179 = 10287"}
{"Question": "TENT + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "8298 + 4251 = 12549"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8268 + 7251 = 15519"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TIME = MIGHT", "Answer": "8368 + 5317 = 13685"}
{"Question": "HALF + FACT = CATCH", "Answer": "5398 + 8317 = 13715"}
{"Question": "GANG + EAST = ESSAY", "Answer": "8548 + 1509 = 10057"}
{"Question": "THAT + CHEF = PEACE", "Answer": "8508 + 3524 = 12032"}
{"Question": "HIGH + BITE = FIGHT", "Answer": "8508 + 6579 = 15087"}
{"Question": "THAT + CHEF = CABLE", "Answer": "8608 + 1635 = 10243"}
{"Question": "BOMB + SOUL = SMILE", "Answer": "8608 + 1645 = 10253"}
{"Question": "AIDS + SITE = ADMIT", "Answer": "1608 + 8657 = 10265"}
{"Question": "THAT + WHEN = WASTE", "Answer": "8608 + 1679 = 10287"}
{"Question": "GANG + VARY = NERVE", "Answer": "8618 + 4625 = 13243"}
{"Question": "GIRL + LIFT = REFER", "Answer": "5618 + 8623 = 14241"}
{"Question": "THUS + SHIP = TRUST", "Answer": "1628 + 8653 = 10281"}
{"Question": "DIRT + TIME = ARMED", "Answer": "5648 + 8627 = 14275"}
{"Question": "GANG + SALT = SENSE", "Answer": "8638 + 1672 = 10310"}
{"Question": "AREA + CROP = CHECK", "Answer": "8638 + 1674 = 10312"}
{"Question": "THAT + SHOE = SALES", "Answer": "8708 + 1723 = 10431"}
{"Question": "BOMB + CORE = CREAM", "Answer": "8728 + 1704 = 10432"}
{"Question": "DEAD + HELP = HAPPY", "Answer": "8708 + 1734 = 10442"}
{"Question": "GIRL + LINK = GREEN", "Answer": "1708 + 8735 = 10443"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SNAP = START", "Answer": "8708 + 1742 = 10450"}
{"Question": "BOMB + SOIL = SMILE", "Answer": "8708 + 1745 = 10453"}
{"Question": "AREA + FROM = FENCE", "Answer": "8708 + 1752 = 10460"}
{"Question": "BOMB + PORT = PRIOR", "Answer": "8768 + 1702 = 10470"}
{"Question": "MIND + DIET = METER", "Answer": "1798 + 8705 = 10503"}
{"Question": "HATE + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "1768 + 8735 = 10503"}
{"Question": "BOMB + POSE = PRESS", "Answer": "8798 + 1735 = 10533"}
{"Question": "RING + GIFT = REFER", "Answer": "1748 + 8753 = 10501"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LOTS = LIMIT", "Answer": "8758 + 1746 = 10504"}
{"Question": "SELF + FEAR = START", "Answer": "1768 + 8752 = 10520"}
{"Question": "GANG + CAKE = CRACK", "Answer": "8978 + 1935 = 10913"}
{"Question": "SOIL + LOCK = SKILL", "Answer": "1249 + 9250 = 10499"}
{"Question": "GANG + CAKE = CLEAN", "Answer": "9249 + 1275 = 10524"}
{"Question": "BOMB + NOSE = ASIAN", "Answer": "9249 + 7268 = 16517"}
{"Question": "EASE + RANK = INNER", "Answer": "9329 + 7368 = 16697"}
{"Question": "SOUP + POLE = SALES", "Answer": "1349 + 9372 = 10721"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BELT = BLADE", "Answer": "9489 + 1405 = 10894"}
{"Question": "DEAD + REST = AFTER", "Answer": "9419 + 7428 = 16847"}
{"Question": "GANG + EACH = CHEAP", "Answer": "9429 + 8417 = 17846"}
{"Question": "EASE + NOSE = SOON", "Answer": "1031 + 2631 = 3662"}
{"Question": "THAT + BEAT = THREE", "Answer": "1061 + 9261 = 10322"}
{"Question": "EASE + RISE = EARLY", "Answer": "1071 + 9871 = 10942"}
{"Question": "TENT + PANT = TITLE", "Answer": "1231 + 8931 = 10162"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BASE = EQUAL", "Answer": "1231 + 9631 = 10862"}
{"Question": "TEST + LAST = TITLE", "Answer": "1241 + 8941 = 10182"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BASE = SELL", "Answer": "1261 + 4861 = 6122"}
{"Question": "TENT + PANT = THEME", "Answer": "1271 + 8971 = 10242"}
{"Question": "ONTO + AUTO = OFTEN", "Answer": "1281 + 9581 = 10862"}
{"Question": "TEST + POST = STOP", "Answer": "1341 + 2841 = 4182"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = AWARE", "Answer": "1421 + 8721 = 10142"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = ASIDE", "Answer": "1521 + 9421 = 10942"}
{"Question": "TEST + COST = TROOP", "Answer": "1971 + 8471 = 10442"}
{"Question": "EDGE + URGE = DRESS", "Answer": "2172 + 8072 = 10244"}
{"Question": "THAT + FLAT = SHELL", "Answer": "2072 + 8472 = 10544"}
{"Question": "GANG + KING = AGREE", "Answer": "2172 + 9872 = 12044"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ROAD = AREA", "Answer": "2842 + 1342 = 4184"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BASE = STEEL", "Answer": "2412 + 7812 = 10224"}
{"Question": "TEST + COST = STATE", "Answer": "2412 + 9612 = 12024"}
{"Question": "EDGE + PAGE = DEEP", "Answer": "2712 + 4512 = 7224"}
{"Question": "ONTO + AUTO = GANG", "Answer": "2632 + 1532 = 4164"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = GRADE", "Answer": "3063 + 7263 = 10326"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = RANGE", "Answer": "3163 + 9863 = 13026"}
{"Question": "THAT + SEAT = EASE", "Answer": "3513 + 2613 = 6126"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GLAD = EDGE", "Answer": "3613 + 2713 = 6326"}
{"Question": "THAT + BOAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "4024 + 6824 = 10848"}
{"Question": "EDGE + PAGE = ADAPT", "Answer": "4034 + 6134 = 10168"}
{"Question": "THAT + FLAT = SHALL", "Answer": "4094 + 6894 = 10988"}
{"Question": "EDGE + HUGE = DRESS", "Answer": "4194 + 6294 = 10488"}
{"Question": "GANG + SING = BASIS", "Answer": "4234 + 8634 = 12868"}
{"Question": "KICK + DECK = BIBLE", "Answer": "4254 + 7854 = 12108"}
{"Question": "EASE + RISE = AREA", "Answer": "4824 + 3524 = 8348"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LOAD = APPLE", "Answer": "6216 + 3816 = 10032"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GLAD = STATE", "Answer": "6276 + 9476 = 15752"}
{"Question": "THAT + BEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "7437 + 6137 = 13574"}
{"Question": "EASE + LOSE = ORDER", "Answer": "7937 + 6137 = 14074"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LOAD = ONION", "Answer": "7857 + 6157 = 14014"}
{"Question": "TEST + LIST = ISSUE", "Answer": "7467 + 9167 = 16634"}
{"Question": "EASE + RISE = PAPER", "Answer": "7237 + 4937 = 12174"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LOAD = TOTAL", "Answer": "7897 + 4297 = 12194"}
{"Question": "GANG + LONG = UNION", "Answer": "7347 + 6947 = 14294"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = BREAD", "Answer": "7387 + 6487 = 13874"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ROAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "7427 + 6827 = 14254"}
{"Question": "GANG + LONG = LOOSE", "Answer": "8978 + 1078 = 10056"}
{"Question": "TEST + CAST = ISSUE", "Answer": "8678 + 9078 = 17756"}
{"Question": "ELSE + NOSE = OCEAN", "Answer": "8728 + 6128 = 14856"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = READY", "Answer": "8138 + 5738 = 13876"}
{"Question": "EASE + NOSE = OCEAN", "Answer": "8738 + 6138 = 14876"}
{"Question": "GANG + RING = INNER", "Answer": "8348 + 6148 = 14496"}
{"Question": "GANG + RING = ANGER", "Answer": "8148 + 6748 = 14896"}
{"Question": "TEST + CAST = ESSAY", "Answer": "8178 + 9578 = 17756"}
{"Question": "EASE + RISE = BASIS", "Answer": "8268 + 4368 = 12636"}
{"Question": "ELSE + CASE = BASIC", "Answer": "8278 + 6478 = 14756"}
{"Question": "EASE + ROSE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8318 + 6418 = 14736"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GLAD = ANGLE", "Answer": "8618 + 9318 = 17936"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = BRAIN", "Answer": "8378 + 5478 = 13856"}
{"Question": "TEST + LIST = VITAL", "Answer": "8378 + 6478 = 14856"}
{"Question": "AREA + IDEA = INNER", "Answer": "8698 + 1398 = 10096"}
{"Question": "TEST + LIST = BIBLE", "Answer": "8678 + 5478 = 14156"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GLAD = GREEN", "Answer": "8578 + 1978 = 10556"}
{"Question": "TEST + DUST = ISSUE", "Answer": "8638 + 4738 = 13376"}
{"Question": "ONTO + AUTO = ASIAN", "Answer": "8658 + 1758 = 10416"}
{"Question": "TENT + PANT = PIECE", "Answer": "8678 + 1978 = 10656"}
{"Question": "STEP + POET = PAUSE", "Answer": "8341 + 1943 = 10284"}
{"Question": "GENE + HANG = GUESS", "Answer": "1373 + 8971 = 10344"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = TRACE", "Answer": "1381 + 9483 = 10864"}
{"Question": "UNIT + THIN = TOUCH", "Answer": "9431 + 1534 = 10965"}
{"Question": "TENT + BONE = THROW", "Answer": "1461 + 9264 = 10725"}
{"Question": "GRAB + BEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "9471 + 1274 = 10745"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = TITLE", "Answer": "1521 + 8625 = 10146"}
{"Question": "SNAP + PLAN = PHASE", "Answer": "8541 + 1945 = 10486"}
{"Question": "MERE + FARM = AREA", "Answer": "1636 + 5731 = 7367"}
{"Question": "BELT + TALE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8671 + 1476 = 10147"}
{"Question": "TENT + WINE = TOWER", "Answer": "1681 + 9286 = 10967"}
{"Question": "TRIP + PAIR = POINT", "Answer": "8721 + 1527 = 10248"}
{"Question": "TEST + ROSE = THEIR", "Answer": "1761 + 8967 = 10728"}
{"Question": "ONTO + DATA = THAN", "Answer": "1941 + 2848 = 4789"}
{"Question": "UNIT + TWIN = WHERE", "Answer": "8372 + 2173 = 10545"}
{"Question": "HELP + PILE = APPLY", "Answer": "9402 + 2804 = 12206"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = SCENE", "Answer": "2572 + 8175 = 10747"}
{"Question": "GLAD + DEAL = ASIDE", "Answer": "7612 + 2816 = 10428"}
{"Question": "TEST + NOSE = ONTO", "Answer": "2712 + 6917 = 9629"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = ERROR", "Answer": "2862 + 7168 = 10030"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVER = GRAVE", "Answer": "3253 + 9052 = 12305"}
{"Question": "GENE + SING = BASIS", "Answer": "3464 + 7263 = 10727"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = CLASS", "Answer": "3543 + 6845 = 10388"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = HATE", "Answer": "3913 + 5219 = 9132"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSE = ODDS", "Answer": "4154 + 3851 = 8005"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = SHARE", "Answer": "4264 + 9162 = 13426"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GEAR = JUDGE", "Answer": "9274 + 4672 = 13946"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GEAR = TRADE", "Answer": "8294 + 4692 = 12986"}
{"Question": "TEST + NOSE = SOON", "Answer": "4984 + 3789 = 8773"}
{"Question": "TEST + RISE = BASIS", "Answer": "5275 + 8472 = 13747"}
{"Question": "DRAG + GEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "9415 + 5214 = 14629"}
{"Question": "GENE + HANG = ANGER", "Answer": "5424 + 7125 = 12549"}
{"Question": "TEST + RISE = METER", "Answer": "5475 + 9074 = 14549"}
{"Question": "UNIT + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "6825 + 5328 = 12153"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = SALAD", "Answer": "5875 + 9178 = 15053"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = WASTE", "Answer": "5925 + 6429 = 12354"}
{"Question": "MERE + FORM = ORDER", "Answer": "5949 + 8145 = 14094"}
{"Question": "STEP + POET = THESE", "Answer": "4176 + 6571 = 10747"}
{"Question": "BELT + TALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9516 + 6315 = 15831"}
{"Question": "UNIT + THIN = ISSUE", "Answer": "3816 + 6218 = 10034"}
{"Question": "GENE + HANG = NIGHT", "Answer": "6919 + 3716 = 10635"}
{"Question": "GLAD + DEAL = LARGE", "Answer": "6137 + 7831 = 13968"}
{"Question": "GENE + LONG = NOVEL", "Answer": "7212 + 9617 = 16829"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = BASIS", "Answer": "7257 + 8652 = 15909"}
{"Question": "ONTO + DATA = TOTAL", "Answer": "7817 + 9313 = 17130"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVER = TREAT", "Answer": "7437 + 6934 = 14371"}
{"Question": "MERE + FIRM = INNER", "Answer": "7525 + 9127 = 16652"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "7647 + 9346 = 16993"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = STATE", "Answer": "7837 + 9538 = 17375"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = APPLY", "Answer": "7917 + 6519 = 14436"}
{"Question": "STEP + POET = HELLO", "Answer": "4927 + 7629 = 12556"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAH = HAPPY", "Answer": "8178 + 9271 = 17449"}
{"Question": "SNAP + PLAN = SENSE", "Answer": "1258 + 8952 = 10210"}
{"Question": "TENT + ZONE = BASIS", "Answer": "8268 + 5762 = 14030"}
{"Question": "MERE + FARM = REFER", "Answer": "8313 + 5218 = 13531"}
{"Question": "GRAB + BEAR = ARGUE", "Answer": "6418 + 8214 = 14632"}
{"Question": "TENT + BONE = BASIS", "Answer": "8468 + 1764 = 10232"}
{"Question": "TENT + PINE = PRESS", "Answer": "8568 + 1965 = 10533"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVER = DRESS", "Answer": "8568 + 7065 = 15633"}
{"Question": "TENT + WINE = WHEEL", "Answer": "8578 + 1975 = 10553"}
{"Question": "TRIP + PAIR = TOOTH", "Answer": "1658 + 8356 = 10014"}
{"Question": "SNAP + PLAN = SHALL", "Answer": "1728 + 8527 = 10255"}
{"Question": "SNAP + PLAN = STEEL", "Answer": "1768 + 8567 = 10335"}
{"Question": "SNAP + PLAN = STEAL", "Answer": "1798 + 8597 = 10395"}
{"Question": "GLAD + DEAL = GRASS", "Answer": "1938 + 8439 = 10377"}
{"Question": "TERM + MORE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1958 + 8059 = 10017"}
{"Question": "TENT + BONE = BLOOD", "Answer": "8968 + 1369 = 10337"}
{"Question": "PLUS + SOUL = PHOTO", "Answer": "1968 + 8769 = 10737"}
{"Question": "MERE + FORM = PROOF", "Answer": "8969 + 7368 = 16337"}
{"Question": "MERE + FORM = FLOOR", "Answer": "8979 + 1578 = 10557"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = ISSUE", "Answer": "8978 + 5479 = 14457"}
{"Question": "GENE + HANG = ENTER", "Answer": "9151 + 6259 = 15410"}
{"Question": "STOP + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6159 + 9351 = 15510"}
{"Question": "TENT + BONE = ENTER", "Answer": "9159 + 6751 = 15910"}
{"Question": "GENE + HANG = EAGER", "Answer": "9151 + 8759 = 17910"}
{"Question": "TEST + BASE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9179 + 8571 = 17750"}
{"Question": "GLAD + DEAL = GUIDE", "Answer": "1349 + 9243 = 10592"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "9419 + 3014 = 12433"}
{"Question": "TENT + LINE = UNTIL", "Answer": "9429 + 3524 = 12953"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVER = CROSS", "Answer": "9469 + 5064 = 14533"}
{"Question": "GLAD + DEAL = GRAVE", "Answer": "1489 + 9384 = 10873"}
{"Question": "TEST + ROSE = RATIO", "Answer": "9539 + 1435 = 10974"}
{"Question": "TENT + FINE = FINAL", "Answer": "9569 + 1065 = 10634"}
{"Question": "TEST + ROSE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9569 + 4365 = 13934"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSE = HOTEL", "Answer": "9579 + 4375 = 13954"}
{"Question": "MERE + FARM = FAVOR", "Answer": "9767 + 1069 = 10836"}
{"Question": "AREA + USER = STATE", "Answer": "9769 + 4167 = 13936"}
{"Question": "TEST + NOSE = OFTEN", "Answer": "9789 + 6187 = 15976"}
{"Question": "PRAY + YEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "5819 + 9718 = 15537"}
{"Question": "TEST + CASE = CATCH", "Answer": "9859 + 1058 = 10917"}
{"Question": "TEST + NOSE = ONION", "Answer": "9859 + 7158 = 17017"}
{"Question": "TENT + PINE = PITCH", "Answer": "9869 + 1068 = 10937"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = ALLOW", "Answer": "1961 + 8066 = 10027"}
{"Question": "TEST + MASS = TABLE", "Answer": "1761 + 9066 = 10827"}
{"Question": "FILL + GOLF = FIGHT", "Answer": "1066 + 9861 = 10927"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CHEF = FLOOR", "Answer": "1077 + 9371 = 10448"}
{"Question": "TOSS + REST = TOWER", "Answer": "1088 + 9681 = 10769"}
{"Question": "TREE + DIET = TREND", "Answer": "1088 + 9781 = 10869"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = TROOP", "Answer": "1961 + 8266 = 10227"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MASS = EQUAL", "Answer": "1321 + 9422 = 10743"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = APPLY", "Answer": "1621 + 8422 = 10043"}
{"Question": "TOSS + REST = THROW", "Answer": "1422 + 9521 = 10943"}
{"Question": "TOSS + PAST = TROOP", "Answer": "1477 + 8971 = 10448"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSS = TITLE", "Answer": "1541 + 8644 = 10185"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = TRIBE", "Answer": "1541 + 8744 = 10285"}
{"Question": "FILL + SELF = FALSE", "Answer": "1944 + 8541 = 10485"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = THEME", "Answer": "1761 + 8966 = 10727"}
{"Question": "AREA + KNEE = BREAK", "Answer": "2062 + 8566 = 10628"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BOSS = STEEL", "Answer": "2312 + 7911 = 10223"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = STATE", "Answer": "2312 + 9711 = 12023"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = LEAF", "Answer": "2512 + 3611 = 6123"}
{"Question": "YELL + ONLY = ALONE", "Answer": "3522 + 9423 = 12945"}
{"Question": "FALL + GOLF = ERROR", "Answer": "3477 + 6573 = 10050"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSS = HOTEL", "Answer": "4054 + 9355 = 13409"}
{"Question": "AREA + KNEE = EARN", "Answer": "4364 + 2066 = 6430"}
{"Question": "ELSE + TOSS = HOTEL", "Answer": "4624 + 9322 = 13946"}
{"Question": "EASE + BOSS = OCEAN", "Answer": "5425 + 8122 = 13547"}
{"Question": "EASE + BOSS = ORDER", "Answer": "5875 + 6177 = 12052"}
{"Question": "KILL + TALK = LIMIT", "Answer": "5211 + 6815 = 12026"}
{"Question": "TEST + KISS = BIBLE", "Answer": "5945 + 6244 = 12189"}
{"Question": "TALL + BELT = SALES", "Answer": "5266 + 7365 = 12631"}
{"Question": "YELL + ONLY = NONE", "Answer": "5388 + 1785 = 7173"}
{"Question": "YELL + ONLY = PLANE", "Answer": "5833 + 7635 = 13468"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSS = FLEE", "Answer": "6156 + 2055 = 8211"}
{"Question": "ELSE + MASS = ALBUM", "Answer": "6086 + 4188 = 10274"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = ERROR", "Answer": "6146 + 3944 = 10090"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = RADIO", "Answer": "6176 + 9877 = 16053"}
{"Question": "TELL + SALT = FALSE", "Answer": "6488 + 7386 = 13874"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = START", "Answer": "6946 + 3744 = 10690"}
{"Question": "EASE + BOSS = ONION", "Answer": "7857 + 4155 = 12012"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CHEF = SHELL", "Answer": "7366 + 5267 = 12633"}
{"Question": "EASE + TOSS = TOOTH", "Answer": "8958 + 1055 = 10013"}
{"Question": "TEST + BOSS = ORDER", "Answer": "8948 + 3144 = 12092"}
{"Question": "TEST + LOSS = HELLO", "Answer": "8748 + 9244 = 17992"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = SHALL", "Answer": "8278 + 6577 = 14855"}
{"Question": "AREA + KNEE = ONION", "Answer": "8658 + 4355 = 13013"}
{"Question": "KISS + TASK = TOTAL", "Answer": "8766 + 1368 = 10134"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = FULLY", "Answer": "8968 + 1366 = 10334"}
{"Question": "TALL + BELT = BIBLE", "Answer": "8399 + 1798 = 10197"}
{"Question": "FILL + SELF = BIBLE", "Answer": "8399 + 4798 = 13197"}
{"Question": "TEST + PASS = PIECE", "Answer": "8468 + 1966 = 10434"}
{"Question": "AREA + FLEE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8468 + 5766 = 14234"}
{"Question": "YELL + ONLY = ORDER", "Answer": "8522 + 1928 = 10450"}
{"Question": "FILL + SELF = SALES", "Answer": "8633 + 1738 = 10371"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BOSS = BLOOD", "Answer": "9039 + 1733 = 10772"}
{"Question": "TOSS + CAST = CATCH", "Answer": "9855 + 1059 = 10914"}
{"Question": "EASE + LOSS = LABOR", "Answer": "9069 + 1366 = 10435"}
{"Question": "TALL + BELT = BASIS", "Answer": "9066 + 1469 = 10535"}
{"Question": "TEST + KISS = ISSUE", "Answer": "9239 + 4133 = 13372"}
{"Question": "TOSS + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "9755 + 4159 = 13914"}
{"Question": "TEST + MASS = ESSAY", "Answer": "9179 + 8577 = 17756"}
{"Question": "TOSS + EAST = EXTRA", "Answer": "9277 + 1679 = 10956"}
{"Question": "KISS + TASK = WASTE", "Answer": "9277 + 5479 = 14756"}
{"Question": "EASE + BOSS = BREAD", "Answer": "9579 + 1377 = 10956"}
{"Question": "EASE + TOSS = TREAT", "Answer": "9529 + 1422 = 10951"}
{"Question": "FALL + SELF = REFER", "Answer": "9422 + 6529 = 15951"}
{"Question": "FREE + CHEF = OCCUR", "Answer": "9566 + 4869 = 14435"}
{"Question": "FULL + SELF = ISSUE", "Answer": "9577 + 2679 = 12256"}
{"Question": "THAT + DEAD = TITLE", "Answer": "1231 + 8938 = 10169"}
{"Question": "PLUS + SOUP = UPON", "Answer": "1864 + 4261 = 6125"}
{"Question": "THAT + DEAD = TRADE", "Answer": "1541 + 8948 = 10489"}
{"Question": "LOAD + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "4927 + 7524 = 12451"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LOAD = EARLY", "Answer": "5137 + 7935 = 13072"}
{"Question": "DEAD + THAT = WASTE", "Answer": "5235 + 7837 = 13072"}
{"Question": "SUIT + THIS = FIFTH", "Answer": "5937 + 7235 = 13172"}
{"Question": "THAT + DEAD = STATE", "Answer": "5825 + 9429 = 15254"}
{"Question": "THAT + DEAD = STAGE", "Answer": "6836 + 9539 = 16375"}
{"Question": "LOAD + DEAL = BLADE", "Answer": "7849 + 9647 = 17496"}
{"Question": "TERM + MARK = METER", "Answer": "9051 + 1854 = 10905"}
{"Question": "THAT + WEAR = THROW", "Answer": "1061 + 9768 = 10829"}
{"Question": "TENT + BAND = TABLE", "Answer": "1861 + 9067 = 10928"}
{"Question": "THAT + PRAY = TROOP", "Answer": "1371 + 9078 = 10449"}
{"Question": "THAT + ROAD = THREE", "Answer": "1071 + 9873 = 10944"}
{"Question": "TERM + MARK = MAKER", "Answer": "9681 + 1087 = 10768"}
{"Question": "DEAD + WHAT = DEATH", "Answer": "1081 + 9786 = 10867"}
{"Question": "TENT + BAND = THREE", "Answer": "1631 + 9235 = 10866"}
{"Question": "POET + THEM = TROOP", "Answer": "8261 + 1967 = 10228"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVEN = ABOVE", "Answer": "1281 + 9687 = 10968"}
{"Question": "EASE + COST = ERROR", "Answer": "1471 + 8579 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BITE = OFTEN", "Answer": "1521 + 8724 = 10245"}
{"Question": "AREA + CHEF = AWARE", "Answer": "1631 + 8532 = 10163"}
{"Question": "TENT + LAND = TOTAL", "Answer": "1531 + 8637 = 10168"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BUSY = STEEL", "Answer": "2812 + 7416 = 10228"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "3523 + 9126 = 12649"}
{"Question": "DEAL + LOAN = APPLE", "Answer": "6213 + 3819 = 10032"}
{"Question": "EASE + LIST = SALES", "Answer": "3213 + 9718 = 12931"}
{"Question": "TENT + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "3273 + 9578 = 12851"}
{"Question": "AREA + STEP = GRASS", "Answer": "4084 + 6382 = 10466"}
{"Question": "RANK + KING = AGREE", "Answer": "8134 + 4732 = 12866"}
{"Question": "LIST + TASK = SALES", "Answer": "8614 + 4217 = 12831"}
{"Question": "GRAB + BEAN = ANGER", "Answer": "9714 + 4213 = 13927"}
{"Question": "KICK + EACH = BIBLE", "Answer": "4254 + 7853 = 12107"}
{"Question": "AREA + OVEN = LEAVE", "Answer": "4924 + 7528 = 12452"}
{"Question": "TOWN + NEWS = ASSET", "Answer": "8065 + 5263 = 13328"}
{"Question": "AREA + THEM = SMART", "Answer": "5475 + 8073 = 13548"}
{"Question": "GANG + BONE = OCEAN", "Answer": "5735 + 9138 = 14873"}
{"Question": "THAT + READ = HEART", "Answer": "5145 + 8340 = 13485"}
{"Question": "ELSE + BUSY = LEVEL", "Answer": "5175 + 9876 = 15051"}
{"Question": "HEAD + DRAW = AWARE", "Answer": "8915 + 5214 = 14129"}
{"Question": "EASE + LIST = STEAL", "Answer": "5215 + 9314 = 14529"}
{"Question": "DEAD + PLAY = CYCLE", "Answer": "5865 + 7263 = 13128"}
{"Question": "EASE + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5895 + 6291 = 12186"}
{"Question": "SHIT + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "6425 + 5729 = 12154"}
{"Question": "AREA + DIET = TRADE", "Answer": "6076 + 4571 = 10647"}
{"Question": "ONTO + CITE = KNOCK", "Answer": "6386 + 7285 = 13671"}
{"Question": "AREA + POET = MOTOR", "Answer": "6926 + 7423 = 14349"}
{"Question": "PORT + TIRE = ORDER", "Answer": "4127 + 7925 = 12052"}
{"Question": "DEAD + STAR = TRADE", "Answer": "7237 + 8135 = 15372"}
{"Question": "FIRE + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "9137 + 7536 = 16673"}
{"Question": "THAN + NEAR = HEART", "Answer": "6147 + 7349 = 13496"}
{"Question": "TEST + ALSO = ERROR", "Answer": "7167 + 2863 = 10030"}
{"Question": "NOSE + EAST = OFTEN", "Answer": "3187 + 7486 = 10673"}
{"Question": "ELSE + CAST = LATER", "Answer": "7187 + 6385 = 13572"}
{"Question": "CORE + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "4937 + 7236 = 12173"}
{"Question": "TOWN + NEWS = SWEET", "Answer": "8967 + 7261 = 16228"}
{"Question": "AREA + STEP = PRESS", "Answer": "7597 + 8391 = 15988"}
{"Question": "TEST + ALSO = ALLOW", "Answer": "8978 + 1075 = 10053"}
{"Question": "STAY + YEAH = THOSE", "Answer": "9148 + 8547 = 17695"}
{"Question": "STAR + READ = ADAPT", "Answer": "5218 + 8914 = 14132"}
{"Question": "STAR + REAL = LEAST", "Answer": "4928 + 8321 = 13249"}
{"Question": "AREA + POET = PHOTO", "Answer": "8978 + 1375 = 10353"}
{"Question": "AREA + CHEF = TRACE", "Answer": "8378 + 5479 = 13857"}
{"Question": "BELT + TALK = BIBLE", "Answer": "1398 + 8795 = 10193"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BOAT = LEAVE", "Answer": "8438 + 5936 = 14374"}
{"Question": "TEST + ALSO = APPLE", "Answer": "8478 + 1576 = 10054"}
{"Question": "THAT + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "8518 + 3719 = 12237"}
{"Question": "DEAD + COAL = CYCLE", "Answer": "8538 + 1637 = 10175"}
{"Question": "KICK + RACE = PAPER", "Answer": "8548 + 7649 = 16197"}
{"Question": "SHOP + PLOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6059 + 9451 = 15510"}
{"Question": "GANG + BIND = BASIS", "Answer": "9069 + 1365 = 10434"}
{"Question": "AREA + DIET = DRESS", "Answer": "9069 + 1564 = 10633"}
{"Question": "AREA + FUEL = FRAME", "Answer": "9069 + 1867 = 10936"}
{"Question": "THAT + YEAR = HAPPY", "Answer": "9139 + 4635 = 13774"}
{"Question": "EDGE + SIGN = SPEND", "Answer": "9689 + 1287 = 10976"}
{"Question": "ELSE + CASH = WHEEL", "Answer": "9649 + 8347 = 17996"}
{"Question": "AREA + STEP = SMART", "Answer": "9579 + 1374 = 10953"}
{"Question": "GANG + TINY = NIGHT", "Answer": "9419 + 6517 = 15936"}
{"Question": "DEAD + THAN = STATE", "Answer": "9539 + 7836 = 17375"}
{"Question": "EASE + URGE = EAGER", "Answer": "1081 + 9231 = 10312"}
{"Question": "ONTO + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "1351 + 8721 = 10072"}
{"Question": "EDGE + SURE = DRESS", "Answer": "4164 + 8324 = 12488"}
{"Question": "ELSE + PURE = RURAL", "Answer": "4894 + 7214 = 12108"}
{"Question": "THAT + DIET = AHEAD", "Answer": "4314 + 8704 = 13018"}
{"Question": "THAT + BEST = STATE", "Answer": "4534 + 9814 = 14348"}
{"Question": "DEAD + WORD = ERROR", "Answer": "5185 + 4905 = 10090"}
{"Question": "EASE + BITE = ASSET", "Answer": "5145 + 9305 = 14450"}
{"Question": "THAT + SPOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "7327 + 6147 = 13474"}
{"Question": "EASE + ROPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7257 + 4917 = 12174"}
{"Question": "ELSE + COME = SMELL", "Answer": "7417 + 5327 = 12744"}
{"Question": "TENT + VAST = SEVEN", "Answer": "7647 + 9317 = 16964"}
{"Question": "EDGE + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "7357 + 9617 = 16974"}
{"Question": "ELSE + RATE = LATER", "Answer": "8128 + 6458 = 14586"}
{"Question": "EASE + ROLE = ALTER", "Answer": "8128 + 6958 = 15086"}
{"Question": "THAT + REST = EARTH", "Answer": "8658 + 7128 = 15786"}
{"Question": "TENT + PORT = ORDER", "Answer": "8928 + 7168 = 16096"}
{"Question": "ELSE + COPE = SLEEP", "Answer": "8518 + 7368 = 15886"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BIND = BRAIN", "Answer": "8328 + 1968 = 10296"}
{"Question": "EASE + URGE = USUAL", "Answer": "8408 + 1738 = 10146"}
{"Question": "DEAD + COLD = PLACE", "Answer": "8608 + 3428 = 12036"}
{"Question": "DEAD + WORD = WATER", "Answer": "8708 + 1568 = 10276"}
{"Question": "TENT + SHIT = SINCE", "Answer": "8638 + 1708 = 10346"}
{"Question": "TENT + WHAT = WASTE", "Answer": "8678 + 1908 = 10586"}
{"Question": "TENT + SHOT = LOOSE", "Answer": "8608 + 4738 = 13346"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BIND = BLAME", "Answer": "8638 + 1758 = 10396"}
{"Question": "EDGE + CLUE = COULD", "Answer": "8638 + 1958 = 10596"}
{"Question": "ELSE + RACE = CLEAR", "Answer": "9709 + 8219 = 17928"}
{"Question": "EDGE + SURE = GUESS", "Answer": "9219 + 8769 = 17988"}
{"Question": "EDGE + BIRD = EAGER", "Answer": "1281 + 9532 = 10813"}
{"Question": "ONTO + HERE = OFTEN", "Answer": "1481 + 9353 = 10834"}
{"Question": "ONTO + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "1431 + 8654 = 10085"}
{"Question": "GANG + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "1721 + 6857 = 8578"}
{"Question": "TENT + DARE = TIRED", "Answer": "1741 + 8637 = 10378"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BEAN = TOOTH", "Answer": "2412 + 9804 = 12216"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BEAN = TASTE", "Answer": "2612 + 7806 = 10418"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TYPE = HAPPY", "Answer": "2602 + 7846 = 10448"}
{"Question": "EDGE + COLD = HELLO", "Answer": "2602 + 9846 = 12448"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LOSE = ODDS", "Answer": "2732 + 1497 = 4229"}
{"Question": "ONTO + WHEN = SHOOT", "Answer": "3253 + 7082 = 10335"}
{"Question": "AREA + TOUR = ROUTE", "Answer": "4154 + 8231 = 12385"}
{"Question": "GANG + HERE = EAGER", "Answer": "4264 + 8151 = 12415"}
{"Question": "GANG + IDEA = ASIAN", "Answer": "4154 + 9761 = 13915"}
{"Question": "CHIP + PATH = THEME", "Answer": "8294 + 4312 = 12606"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ROPE = PAPER", "Answer": "4324 + 7813 = 12137"}
{"Question": "TEAR + RISE = ASSET", "Answer": "7314 + 4923 = 12237"}
{"Question": "TENT + CARE = PAPER", "Answer": "4954 + 7239 = 12193"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TRUE = HEART", "Answer": "5345 + 8063 = 13408"}
{"Question": "DATA + BIRD = ARAB", "Answer": "5686 + 1075 = 6761"}
{"Question": "SNOW + WHEN = NEWS", "Answer": "2765 + 5087 = 7852"}
{"Question": "DEAD + CLUE = BASIS", "Answer": "5825 + 6478 = 12303"}
{"Question": "TERM + MALE = ALTER", "Answer": "9835 + 5148 = 14983"}
{"Question": "YEAR + ROSE = SORRY", "Answer": "8256 + 6412 = 14668"}
{"Question": "ONTO + EARN = THEME", "Answer": "6216 + 8592 = 14808"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SHOE = BASIS", "Answer": "6246 + 8592 = 14838"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TIME = MEDIA", "Answer": "6406 + 8214 = 14620"}
{"Question": "DEAD + FIRE = REFER", "Answer": "6536 + 9415 = 15951"}
{"Question": "AREA + STIR = TREAT", "Answer": "6576 + 9185 = 15761"}
{"Question": "EDGE + ROAD = PAPER", "Answer": "6756 + 3407 = 10163"}
{"Question": "BEST + TRUE = SUPER", "Answer": "8716 + 6357 = 15073"}
{"Question": "GENE + FLAG = ANGER", "Answer": "6757 + 8916 = 15673"}
{"Question": "HIGH + DATA = EIGHT", "Answer": "6526 + 8737 = 15263"}
{"Question": "TENT + CARE = EAGER", "Answer": "7137 + 5281 = 12418"}
{"Question": "TEND + DARE = ENTER", "Answer": "6137 + 7481 = 13618"}
{"Question": "YEAR + RICE = CARRY", "Answer": "9267 + 7512 = 16779"}
{"Question": "SELF + FIVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "6417 + 7824 = 14241"}
{"Question": "ELSE + DATA = STEAL", "Answer": "7217 + 6535 = 13752"}
{"Question": "REST + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "3657 + 7106 = 10763"}
{"Question": "GANG + HERE = ANGER", "Answer": "7127 + 5636 = 12763"}
{"Question": "THUS + SIGH = TRUST", "Answer": "1328 + 8953 = 10281"}
{"Question": "TENT + AIDE = AGAIN", "Answer": "8538 + 1625 = 10163"}
{"Question": "TENT + AIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "8578 + 1935 = 10513"}
{"Question": "TENT + ABLE = ONION", "Answer": "8538 + 4675 = 13213"}
{"Question": "DEAD + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "8628 + 4736 = 13364"}
{"Question": "BOMB + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8678 + 1346 = 10024"}
{"Question": "TENT + URGE = UNDER", "Answer": "8708 + 1567 = 10275"}
{"Question": "DEAD + LINE = LATIN", "Answer": "8708 + 1657 = 10365"}
{"Question": "AREA + STIR = SHEET", "Answer": "8738 + 1597 = 10335"}
{"Question": "TENT + HIRE = HONOR", "Answer": "8748 + 1657 = 10405"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ALSO = SMALL", "Answer": "8958 + 6719 = 15677"}
{"Question": "LEAF + FIRE = REFER", "Answer": "3209 + 9712 = 12921"}
{"Question": "HIGH + DATA = TIGHT", "Answer": "9579 + 6212 = 15791"}
{"Question": "TENT + SALE = SALES", "Answer": "9289 + 1032 = 10321"}
{"Question": "LEFT + TRUE = REFER", "Answer": "3249 + 9172 = 12421"}
{"Question": "STEP + PLOT = SHELL", "Answer": "1369 + 9253 = 10622"}
{"Question": "DEAD + TRUE = AFTER", "Answer": "9419 + 7324 = 16743"}
{"Question": "BOMB + AUTO = ALBUM", "Answer": "9549 + 1385 = 10934"}
{"Question": "TENT + MORE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9829 + 1078 = 10907"}
{"Question": "AREA + BLUE = ALLOW", "Answer": "1951 + 8075 = 10026"}
{"Question": "TENT + RAIN = TERMS", "Answer": "1051 + 9875 = 10926"}
{"Question": "TEST + ROLL = TERMS", "Answer": "1071 + 9866 = 10937"}
{"Question": "TOSS + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "1077 + 8941 = 10018"}
{"Question": "EAST + THIS = TASTE", "Answer": "9081 + 1738 = 10819"}
{"Question": "EASE + PLUS = EQUAL", "Answer": "1241 + 9584 = 10825"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FARM = BLOOD", "Answer": "1251 + 8975 = 10226"}
{"Question": "AREA + ONCE = AGENT", "Answer": "1471 + 9257 = 10728"}
{"Question": "TENT + SIGN = TASTE", "Answer": "1541 + 9374 = 10915"}
{"Question": "GANG + BELL = GREEN", "Answer": "1971 + 8366 = 10337"}
{"Question": "ONTO + REST = OFFER", "Answer": "1371 + 8697 = 10068"}
{"Question": "AREA + TIME = ADMIT", "Answer": "1371 + 8927 = 10298"}
{"Question": "AREA + NICE = AGAIN", "Answer": "1471 + 8697 = 10168"}
{"Question": "AREA + BITE = ACTOR", "Answer": "1541 + 8724 = 10265"}
{"Question": "TENT + BORN = THEME", "Answer": "1651 + 8975 = 10626"}
{"Question": "EASE + THIS = CATCH", "Answer": "2052 + 8765 = 10817"}
{"Question": "KNEE + TASK = ASSET", "Answer": "2955 + 7102 = 10057"}
{"Question": "TENT + BORN = ERROR", "Answer": "2182 + 7908 = 10090"}
{"Question": "AREA + FILL = REFER", "Answer": "2102 + 8699 = 10801"}
{"Question": "AREA + FILE = RURAL", "Answer": "3153 + 6985 = 10138"}
{"Question": "ELSE + AIDS = LEVEL", "Answer": "4174 + 9867 = 14041"}
{"Question": "BOMB + LESS = SOLVE", "Answer": "4294 + 8511 = 12805"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TREE = MOTOR", "Answer": "4314 + 9622 = 13936"}
{"Question": "ONTO + WAIT = ASIAN", "Answer": "5725 + 8192 = 13917"}
{"Question": "TEST + KILL = STAKE", "Answer": "5215 + 9877 = 15092"}
{"Question": "THAT + BILL = FIFTH", "Answer": "5735 + 8422 = 14157"}
{"Question": "AREA + SHOE = IRISH", "Answer": "5425 + 8762 = 14187"}
{"Question": "NEWS + SHOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "6835 + 5423 = 12258"}
{"Question": "AREA + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "5735 + 8423 = 14158"}
{"Question": "MASS + ITEM = ASIAN", "Answer": "6133 + 7586 = 13719"}
{"Question": "HIGH + TALL = LIGHT", "Answer": "6356 + 7211 = 13567"}
{"Question": "GANG + THIN = NIGHT", "Answer": "6216 + 7431 = 13647"}
{"Question": "EASE + PLUS = USUAL", "Answer": "6326 + 5812 = 12138"}
{"Question": "LESS + FAIL = ISSUE", "Answer": "6822 + 5416 = 12238"}
{"Question": "EASE + ROLL = SORRY", "Answer": "6416 + 9577 = 15993"}
{"Question": "AREA + HUGE = RURAL", "Answer": "7127 + 3052 = 10179"}
{"Question": "THAT + BOSS = PHOTO", "Answer": "7057 + 3922 = 10979"}
{"Question": "HURT + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "3567 + 7106 = 10673"}
{"Question": "EASE + PLUS = SLEEP", "Answer": "7217 + 8561 = 15778"}
{"Question": "TREE + CAST = STEAL", "Answer": "7833 + 9517 = 17350"}
{"Question": "BOMB + ITEM = PRIOR", "Answer": "7657 + 4805 = 12462"}
{"Question": "AREA + BLUE = RURAL", "Answer": "8128 + 7052 = 15180"}
{"Question": "MALL + TERM = ALTER", "Answer": "8122 + 4308 = 12430"}
{"Question": "FREE + GOLF = REFER", "Answer": "8133 + 5698 = 13831"}
{"Question": "AREA + LIFE = REFER", "Answer": "8138 + 5793 = 13931"}
{"Question": "MALL + FROM = REFER", "Answer": "8533 + 6108 = 14641"}
{"Question": "NEWS + SLOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "5248 + 8134 = 13382"}
{"Question": "EASE + LOTS = ORDER", "Answer": "8958 + 4125 = 13083"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TERM = ORDER", "Answer": "8158 + 4935 = 13093"}
{"Question": "AREA + HIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8678 + 2107 = 10785"}
{"Question": "BEST + THIS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1248 + 8904 = 10152"}
{"Question": "THAT + FLEE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8238 + 1944 = 10182"}
{"Question": "ELSE + AIDS = USUAL", "Answer": "8248 + 5904 = 14152"}
{"Question": "KISS + TALK = TOTAL", "Answer": "8255 + 1938 = 10193"}
{"Question": "AREA + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8358 + 1705 = 10063"}
{"Question": "TENT + BALL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8398 + 1755 = 10153"}
{"Question": "DEAD + BOSS = BLADE", "Answer": "8328 + 1955 = 10283"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SHIT = UNION", "Answer": "8358 + 4925 = 13283"}
{"Question": "BOMB + FARM = FLOOR", "Answer": "8378 + 1957 = 10335"}
{"Question": "ONTO + REST = STORE", "Answer": "8378 + 9517 = 17895"}
{"Question": "THAT + SELL = SALES", "Answer": "8908 + 1433 = 10341"}
{"Question": "YELL + PRAY = PAPER", "Answer": "8766 + 1408 = 10174"}
{"Question": "TENT + PLAN = PAPER", "Answer": "8548 + 1604 = 10152"}
{"Question": "LESS + TAIL = TITLE", "Answer": "8577 + 1608 = 10185"}
{"Question": "AREA + SHOE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8578 + 1907 = 10485"}
{"Question": "GANG + THEN = TREAT", "Answer": "8938 + 1653 = 10591"}
{"Question": "EASE + BILL = BASIS", "Answer": "9079 + 1688 = 10767"}
{"Question": "TENT + IRON = RATIO", "Answer": "9839 + 6123 = 15962"}
{"Question": "TELL + PART = LATER", "Answer": "9211 + 8709 = 17920"}
{"Question": "BILL + GRAB = EAGER", "Answer": "9533 + 8279 = 17812"}
{"Question": "BOMB + TEAM = TRACE", "Answer": "9259 + 1475 = 10734"}
{"Question": "AREA + CITE = CHAIR", "Answer": "9679 + 1247 = 10926"}
{"Question": "AREA + MODE = DREAM", "Answer": "9579 + 6217 = 15796"}
{"Question": "AREA + CITE = CHART", "Answer": "9689 + 1278 = 10967"}
{"Question": "GANG + THIN = TIGHT", "Answer": "9629 + 1302 = 10931"}
{"Question": "ONTO + BEST = STONE", "Answer": "9649 + 5314 = 14963"}
{"Question": "TENT + PLAN = APPLE", "Answer": "9569 + 3816 = 13385"}
{"Question": "RING + GEAR = EARN", "Answer": "1576 + 6841 = 8417"}
{"Question": "EARN + NOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "3428 + 8913 = 12341"}
{"Question": "NOTE + EARN = OTHER", "Answer": "5148 + 8935 = 14083"}
{"Question": "HIRE + EACH = PAPER", "Answer": "5827 + 7345 = 13172"}
{"Question": "HOPE + EACH = PAPER", "Answer": "5718 + 8465 = 14183"}
{"Question": "AREA + BOMB = CREAM", "Answer": "6426 + 7837 = 14263"}
{"Question": "AREA + DOWN = ALLOW", "Answer": "1321 + 8754 = 10075"}
{"Question": "ONTO + EACH = OFTEN", "Answer": "1521 + 8764 = 10285"}
{"Question": "HIGH + NEAR = GRAIN", "Answer": "5015 + 7892 = 12907"}
{"Question": "DEAD + THIS = ASSET", "Answer": "5015 + 8293 = 13308"}
{"Question": "TENT + LUCK = UNCLE", "Answer": "5325 + 7148 = 12473"}
{"Question": "ONTO + SIGH = NIGHT", "Answer": "5125 + 8347 = 13472"}
{"Question": "DOWN + NEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "7235 + 5914 = 13149"}
{"Question": "BOMB + SHUT = MOUTH", "Answer": "5315 + 8479 = 13794"}
{"Question": "TENT + SOIL = NOISE", "Answer": "5315 + 9478 = 14793"}
{"Question": "HIGH + BEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "6436 + 7519 = 13955"}
{"Question": "GANG + VERY = NEVER", "Answer": "6416 + 9537 = 15953"}
{"Question": "DEAD + GROW = EAGER", "Answer": "7127 + 5386 = 12513"}
{"Question": "TENT + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "7127 + 6349 = 13476"}
{"Question": "WHOM + MEAL = HELLO", "Answer": "8137 + 7526 = 15663"}
{"Question": "GANG + LOVE = NOVEL", "Answer": "7417 + 5268 = 12685"}
{"Question": "LEAD + DROP = APPLE", "Answer": "8217 + 7365 = 15582"}
{"Question": "DEAD + STIR = ARISE", "Answer": "7217 + 8465 = 15682"}
{"Question": "AREA + CITY = TRACE", "Answer": "7567 + 8219 = 15786"}
{"Question": "AREA + MIND = DREAM", "Answer": "7657 + 8921 = 16578"}
{"Question": "EDGE + PRAY = PAPER", "Answer": "8978 + 1204 = 10182"}
{"Question": "DEAD + PORT = PAPER", "Answer": "8408 + 1735 = 10143"}
{"Question": "TENT + PRAY = PAPER", "Answer": "8438 + 1709 = 10147"}
{"Question": "HIGH + SNAP = AGAIN", "Answer": "8428 + 3719 = 12147"}
{"Question": "DEAD + WORK = WATER", "Answer": "8508 + 1746 = 10254"}
{"Question": "BOMB + PARK = PRIOR", "Answer": "8658 + 1702 = 10360"}
{"Question": "DEAD + SOIL = SALES", "Answer": "8608 + 1753 = 10361"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = CHEF", "Answer": "1575 + 1575 = 3150"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = SIGN", "Answer": "2363 + 2363 = 4726"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = EARN", "Answer": "2484 + 2484 = 4968"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = HANG", "Answer": "2696 + 2696 = 5392"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = TELL", "Answer": "4383 + 4383 = 8766"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = ERROR", "Answer": "6121 + 6121 = 12242"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = ERROR", "Answer": "6141 + 6141 = 12282"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = LATER", "Answer": "6252 + 6252 = 12504"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = WEIGH", "Answer": "6282 + 6282 = 12564"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = RURAL", "Answer": "6575 + 6575 = 13150"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = ENTER", "Answer": "6757 + 6757 = 13514"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "6858 + 6858 = 13716"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = ALONG", "Answer": "6898 + 6898 = 13796"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = COACH", "Answer": "6959 + 6959 = 13918"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = CHART", "Answer": "6989 + 6989 = 13978"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = ORDER", "Answer": "7262 + 7262 = 14524"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = FAULT", "Answer": "7484 + 7484 = 14968"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = PAPER", "Answer": "7565 + 7565 = 15130"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = CRACK", "Answer": "7656 + 7656 = 15312"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = ASIDE", "Answer": "8191 + 8191 = 16382"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = STEAL", "Answer": "8262 + 8262 = 16524"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = UNION", "Answer": "8363 + 8363 = 16726"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = BRUSH", "Answer": "8464 + 8464 = 16928"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = BREAD", "Answer": "8474 + 8474 = 16948"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = CHECK", "Answer": "8656 + 8656 = 17312"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = CATCH", "Answer": "8757 + 8757 = 17514"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = EARTH", "Answer": "8797 + 8797 = 17594"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = BOARD", "Answer": "8969 + 8969 = 17938"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = STAND", "Answer": "8979 + 8979 = 17958"}
{"Question": "GENE + GENE = ENJOY", "Answer": "9181 + 9181 = 18362"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = STILL", "Answer": "9383 + 9383 = 18766"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATA = IDEAL", "Answer": "9787 + 9787 = 19574"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = CHAIR", "Answer": "9868 + 9868 = 19736"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERE = SHRUG", "Answer": "9878 + 9878 = 19756"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = ROLE", "Answer": "1535 + 1530 = 3065"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TELL", "Answer": "1939 + 1938 = 3877"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = FOOD", "Answer": "2383 + 2389 = 4772"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = AREA", "Answer": "2454 + 2450 = 4904"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TALL", "Answer": "3979 + 3976 = 7955"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TEND", "Answer": "4181 + 4183 = 8364"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = ODDS", "Answer": "4272 + 4278 = 8550"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TEEN", "Answer": "4383 + 4387 = 8770"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TOOL", "Answer": "4383 + 4389 = 8772"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TIRED", "Answer": "5313 + 5312 = 10625"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = FLOOR", "Answer": "5383 + 5389 = 10772"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = ALLOW", "Answer": "6131 + 6139 = 12270"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = NAKED", "Answer": "6272 + 6274 = 12546"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = CARRY", "Answer": "6272 + 6278 = 12550"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = TODAY", "Answer": "6313 + 6317 = 12630"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = CHEEK", "Answer": "6383 + 6387 = 12770"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = RURAL", "Answer": "6575 + 6579 = 13154"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = FIFTH", "Answer": "6595 + 6597 = 13192"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = KNOCK", "Answer": "6727 + 6724 = 13451"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = BOARD", "Answer": "6797 + 6793 = 13590"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = PHOTO", "Answer": "6797 + 6798 = 13595"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = OWNER", "Answer": "6898 + 6891 = 13789"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = CHART", "Answer": "6979 + 6978 = 13957"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = OCCUR", "Answer": "7232 + 7231 = 14463"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = ROUGH", "Answer": "7313 + 7314 = 14627"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = REACH", "Answer": "7414 + 7413 = 14827"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = SALAD", "Answer": "7424 + 7423 = 14847"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = LEVEL", "Answer": "7525 + 7526 = 15051"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = OTHER", "Answer": "7898 + 7891 = 15789"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = BOARD", "Answer": "7969 + 7968 = 15937"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = READY", "Answer": "7989 + 7985 = 15974"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = EARTH", "Answer": "8121 + 8127 = 16248"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = ELECT", "Answer": "8565 + 8561 = 17126"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = FIFTH", "Answer": "8565 + 8563 = 17128"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = IRISH", "Answer": "8575 + 8573 = 17148"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = COLOR", "Answer": "8636 + 8637 = 17273"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = FEWER", "Answer": "8737 + 8736 = 17473"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = LATER", "Answer": "8747 + 8749 = 17496"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = HEART", "Answer": "8969 + 8967 = 17936"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = TREAT", "Answer": "8979 + 8972 = 17951"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = STAFF", "Answer": "8979 + 8976 = 17955"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = HELLO", "Answer": "9272 + 9278 = 18550"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = LEGAL", "Answer": "9363 + 9368 = 18731"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = STEEL", "Answer": "9383 + 9387 = 18770"}
{"Question": "DATA + DATE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9424 + 9421 = 18845"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = ASSET", "Answer": "9424 + 9423 = 18847"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = SHORT", "Answer": "9606 + 9602 = 19208"}
{"Question": "HERE + HERO = THROW", "Answer": "9878 + 9875 = 19753"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "1494 + 1429 = 2923"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = AFTER", "Answer": "6383 + 6355 = 12738"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = FLOOR", "Answer": "6707 + 6733 = 13440"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = SALES", "Answer": "6727 + 6744 = 13471"}
{"Question": "MERE + MESS = ARMED", "Answer": "6838 + 6844 = 13682"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = COLOR", "Answer": "6858 + 6877 = 13735"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = AGENT", "Answer": "6989 + 6918 = 13907"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "7121 + 7142 = 14263"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7252 + 7244 = 14496"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = PROOF", "Answer": "7343 + 7322 = 14665"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = OTHER", "Answer": "7383 + 7355 = 14738"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = BEACH", "Answer": "7434 + 7493 = 14927"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = REACH", "Answer": "7515 + 7522 = 15037"}
{"Question": "MERE + MESS = LEGAL", "Answer": "7525 + 7566 = 15091"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = FRESH", "Answer": "7959 + 7988 = 15947"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "8353 + 8365 = 16718"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = CROSS", "Answer": "8464 + 8436 = 16900"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "8474 + 8467 = 16941"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = ROUGH", "Answer": "8515 + 8533 = 17048"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = IRISH", "Answer": "8575 + 8533 = 17108"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = FIFTH", "Answer": "8535 + 8593 = 17128"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = REACH", "Answer": "8717 + 8741 = 17458"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = TREAT", "Answer": "8979 + 8922 = 17901"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELL = ORDER", "Answer": "9383 + 9355 = 18738"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAR = FAITH", "Answer": "9363 + 9386 = 18749"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = READ", "Answer": "3474 + 3469 = 6943"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = ASSET", "Answer": "6101 + 6189 = 12290"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAN = NEVER", "Answer": "6232 + 6291 = 12523"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAT = DEATH", "Answer": "6292 + 6254 = 12546"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAN = RANGE", "Answer": "6515 + 6530 = 13045"}
{"Question": "MERE + MENU = RURAL", "Answer": "6515 + 6593 = 13108"}
{"Question": "MERE + MENU = TRUST", "Answer": "6737 + 6754 = 13491"}
{"Question": "MERE + MENU = FUNNY", "Answer": "6797 + 6753 = 13550"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "7121 + 7146 = 14267"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAD = EARLY", "Answer": "7121 + 7148 = 14269"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "7494 + 7481 = 14975"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = REFER", "Answer": "7636 + 7615 = 15251"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAL = FRAME", "Answer": "7656 + 7620 = 15276"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = CLEAR", "Answer": "7838 + 7846 = 15684"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAL = EARLY", "Answer": "8121 + 8169 = 16290"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = ELECT", "Answer": "8565 + 8541 = 17106"}
{"Question": "HERE + HELP = PAPER", "Answer": "8565 + 8591 = 17156"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAD = IRISH", "Answer": "8575 + 8593 = 17168"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = GREAT", "Answer": "8696 + 8673 = 17369"}
{"Question": "DATA + DARE = CATCH", "Answer": "8757 + 8762 = 17519"}
{"Question": "MERE + MEAL = ALTER", "Answer": "9202 + 9218 = 18420"}
{"Question": "HERE + HEAT = DRAMA", "Answer": "9383 + 9374 = 18757"}
{"Question": "MERE + MENU = OCCUR", "Answer": "9404 + 9456 = 18860"}
{"Question": "GENE + GEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "9545 + 9510 = 19055"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = AREA", "Answer": "2787 + 2087 = 4874"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = WOMAN", "Answer": "5464 + 5064 = 10528"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = THEME", "Answer": "6080 + 6980 = 13060"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = BEGIN", "Answer": "6252 + 6052 = 12304"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = REACH", "Answer": "6313 + 6713 = 13026"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = HUMOR", "Answer": "6747 + 6947 = 13694"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6959 + 6359 = 13318"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = FLOOR", "Answer": "6989 + 6789 = 13778"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = LEMON", "Answer": "7464 + 7264 = 14728"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = LIMIT", "Answer": "7828 + 7928 = 15756"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = FORCE", "Answer": "8070 + 8670 = 16740"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = EIGHT", "Answer": "8141 + 8641 = 16782"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = DRESS", "Answer": "8272 + 8972 = 17244"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = TERMS", "Answer": "8676 + 8076 = 16752"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = IRISH", "Answer": "8979 + 8179 = 17158"}
{"Question": "MERE + MORE = EMPTY", "Answer": "9171 + 9871 = 19042"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIRE = CROSS", "Answer": "9383 + 9083 = 18466"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = SLOW", "Answer": "1533 + 1635 = 3168"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = BELL", "Answer": "1655 + 1956 = 3611"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = ELSE", "Answer": "3077 + 3970 = 7047"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "5077 + 5470 = 10547"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = ELECT", "Answer": "6311 + 6813 = 13124"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = SHELF", "Answer": "6422 + 6824 = 13246"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = GUEST", "Answer": "6588 + 6285 = 12873"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = ONION", "Answer": "6755 + 6057 = 12812"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = AHEAD", "Answer": "6755 + 6957 = 13712"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = CROSS", "Answer": "6877 + 6078 = 12955"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = DRESS", "Answer": "6877 + 6978 = 13855"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = SALAD", "Answer": "6911 + 6719 = 13630"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6977 + 6179 = 13156"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = VITAL", "Answer": "7088 + 7680 = 14768"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = LOVER", "Answer": "7211 + 7412 = 14623"}
{"Question": "SELL + SALE = BASIS", "Answer": "7255 + 7452 = 14707"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = USUAL", "Answer": "7255 + 7852 = 15107"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = WATER", "Answer": "7266 + 7462 = 14728"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = LEMON", "Answer": "7411 + 7214 = 14625"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = PILOT", "Answer": "7433 + 7934 = 15367"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "7488 + 7284 = 14772"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = ELECT", "Answer": "8177 + 8971 = 17148"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "8211 + 8612 = 16823"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8266 + 8762 = 17028"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8355 + 8753 = 17108"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "8366 + 8263 = 16629"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = UPPER", "Answer": "8499 + 8194 = 16693"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = SORRY", "Answer": "8511 + 8715 = 17226"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = SLEEP", "Answer": "8699 + 8296 = 16995"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = ASIAN", "Answer": "8755 + 8157 = 16912"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = CLOCK", "Answer": "8755 + 8657 = 17412"}
{"Question": "SELL + SALE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8966 + 8169 = 17135"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = PROOF", "Answer": "8966 + 8369 = 17335"}
{"Question": "SELL + SALE = DRAMA", "Answer": "8966 + 8569 = 17535"}
{"Question": "HELL + HOLE = BLOOD", "Answer": "8977 + 8579 = 17556"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FUEL = TOOTH", "Answer": "9755 + 9057 = 18812"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSE = ASSET", "Answer": "9788 + 9087 = 18875"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "9788 + 9187 = 18975"}
{"Question": "SELL + SALE = ASIAN", "Answer": "9855 + 9158 = 19013"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STOP = PASS", "Answer": "1358 + 1853 = 3211"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STOP = GHOST", "Answer": "6087 + 6780 = 12867"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STOP = PRESS", "Answer": "6185 + 6581 = 12766"}
{"Question": "STOP + SPOT = RATIO", "Answer": "6879 + 6978 = 13857"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STOP = TRUST", "Answer": "8091 + 8190 = 16281"}
{"Question": "STOP + SPOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8179 + 8971 = 17150"}
{"Question": "STOP + SPOT = FORTH", "Answer": "8475 + 8574 = 17049"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = STIR", "Answer": "1523 + 1328 = 2851"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = RARE", "Answer": "2571 + 2174 = 4745"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SPOT = MOTOR", "Answer": "5402 + 5206 = 10608"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SPIN = CIVIL", "Answer": "5602 + 5204 = 10806"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = BLADE", "Answer": "5483 + 5381 = 10864"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = GUARD", "Answer": "5274 + 5471 = 10745"}
{"Question": "TOUR + TRUE = SHEET", "Answer": "5346 + 5649 = 10995"}
{"Question": "SHOT + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "5098 + 5891 = 10989"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = RANGE", "Answer": "6931 + 6138 = 13069"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = TOOTH", "Answer": "6051 + 6159 = 12210"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = TASTE", "Answer": "6451 + 6159 = 12610"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = THESE", "Answer": "6281 + 6183 = 12464"}
{"Question": "WEAR + WRAP = APART", "Answer": "6912 + 6213 = 13125"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = AWARE", "Answer": "6912 + 6217 = 13129"}
{"Question": "MINE + MENU = AGAIN", "Answer": "6892 + 6297 = 13189"}
{"Question": "ROLE + RELY = HELLO", "Answer": "6703 + 6304 = 13007"}
{"Question": "SALE + SELF = LABEL", "Answer": "6213 + 6318 = 12531"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = LABEL", "Answer": "6523 + 6328 = 12851"}
{"Question": "GOAL + GLAD = BLADE", "Answer": "6923 + 6324 = 13247"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = BIRTH", "Answer": "6283 + 6387 = 12670"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = EARTH", "Answer": "6124 + 6425 = 12549"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = LABEL", "Answer": "6524 + 6427 = 12951"}
{"Question": "TONE + TEND = OFTEN", "Answer": "6174 + 6473 = 12647"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = GRASS", "Answer": "6384 + 6482 = 12866"}
{"Question": "WEAR + WRAP = APPLE", "Answer": "6815 + 6513 = 13328"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = LOOSE", "Answer": "6785 + 6582 = 13367"}
{"Question": "WEAR + WRAP = ADAPT", "Answer": "6417 + 6712 = 13129"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HERO = OTHER", "Answer": "6798 + 6891 = 13689"}
{"Question": "NICE + NECK = GIVEN", "Answer": "6349 + 6947 = 13296"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HELP = TOOTH", "Answer": "6359 + 6957 = 13316"}
{"Question": "RULE + RELY = USUAL", "Answer": "6179 + 6978 = 13157"}
{"Question": "HERE + HURT = EARTH", "Answer": "7131 + 7236 = 14367"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = THREE", "Answer": "7431 + 7135 = 14566"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = THIRD", "Answer": "7461 + 7162 = 14623"}
{"Question": "BASE + BEST = STEEL", "Answer": "7012 + 7214 = 14226"}
{"Question": "ROLE + RELY = LOVER", "Answer": "7412 + 7215 = 14627"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "7912 + 7215 = 15127"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = INNER", "Answer": "7162 + 7265 = 14427"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = TIRED", "Answer": "7462 + 7261 = 14723"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LEFT = STEEL", "Answer": "7962 + 7265 = 15227"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LEFT = STEAL", "Answer": "7982 + 7285 = 15267"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = STAIR", "Answer": "7213 + 7314 = 14527"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HERO = CROSS", "Answer": "7243 + 7345 = 14588"}
{"Question": "SOIL + SLIP = PRIOR", "Answer": "7263 + 7361 = 14624"}
{"Question": "WEAR + WRAP = PEACE", "Answer": "7483 + 7381 = 14864"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HERO = FORTH", "Answer": "7593 + 7394 = 14987"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = ARMED", "Answer": "7214 + 7413 = 14627"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = SERVE", "Answer": "7314 + 7410 = 14724"}
{"Question": "HERE + HURT = REACH", "Answer": "7414 + 7513 = 14927"}
{"Question": "WISE + WEST = FEWER", "Answer": "7324 + 7425 = 14749"}
{"Question": "DATA + DUTY = SALAD", "Answer": "7424 + 7523 = 14947"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "7254 + 7451 = 14705"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = IRISH", "Answer": "7454 + 7653 = 15107"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = ORDER", "Answer": "7264 + 7460 = 14724"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LEFT = UNTIL", "Answer": "7894 + 7493 = 15387"}
{"Question": "TOUR + TRUE = COLOR", "Answer": "7425 + 7520 = 14945"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = CABLE", "Answer": "7345 + 7548 = 14893"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "7395 + 7594 = 14989"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HELP = DEPTH", "Answer": "7695 + 7592 = 15287"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = AGREE", "Answer": "7686 + 7180 = 14866"}
{"Question": "ROSE + REST = TOWER", "Answer": "7586 + 7681 = 15267"}
{"Question": "TOUR + TRUE = ELECT", "Answer": "7496 + 7691 = 15187"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = IRISH", "Answer": "7239 + 7935 = 15174"}
{"Question": "HERE + HURT = OTHER", "Answer": "7949 + 7845 = 15794"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = SPEED", "Answer": "7369 + 7968 = 15337"}
{"Question": "HERE + HURT = TREAT", "Answer": "8070 + 8971 = 17041"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = RANGE", "Answer": "8361 + 8162 = 16523"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = ERROR", "Answer": "8161 + 8465 = 16626"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAW = AWARE", "Answer": "8912 + 8217 = 17129"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = WASTE", "Answer": "8562 + 8263 = 16825"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SPOT = THOSE", "Answer": "8692 + 8291 = 16983"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HELP = ALLOW", "Answer": "8263 + 8364 = 16627"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HERO = FIFTH", "Answer": "8763 + 8365 = 17128"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STIR = FIFTH", "Answer": "8674 + 8472 = 17146"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SPOT = IRISH", "Answer": "8694 + 8492 = 17186"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = BIBLE", "Answer": "8625 + 8521 = 17146"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAY = LAYER", "Answer": "8475 + 8570 = 17045"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = NAKED", "Answer": "8475 + 8573 = 17048"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = LARGE", "Answer": "8975 + 8574 = 17549"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAY = AWARE", "Answer": "8516 + 8619 = 17135"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SPOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8546 + 8649 = 17195"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = FRAME", "Answer": "8076 + 8674 = 16750"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = PAPER", "Answer": "8476 + 8670 = 17146"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRAG = GRAND", "Answer": "8527 + 8721 = 17248"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = FEWER", "Answer": "8737 + 8536 = 17273"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "8637 + 8734 = 17371"}
{"Question": "HERE + HURT = METER", "Answer": "8737 + 8936 = 17673"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SPIN = LEVEL", "Answer": "8139 + 8932 = 17071"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = UNDER", "Answer": "8949 + 8645 = 17594"}
{"Question": "HERE + HARD = DRAMA", "Answer": "8979 + 8071 = 17050"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = MOTOR", "Answer": "9542 + 9247 = 18789"}
{"Question": "WEAR + WRAP = AWARD", "Answer": "9813 + 9317 = 19130"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "9643 + 9341 = 18984"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HERO = SHORT", "Answer": "9804 + 9402 = 19206"}
{"Question": "ROSE + REST = THROW", "Answer": "9425 + 9521 = 18946"}
{"Question": "SEAT + STAR = HORSE", "Answer": "9245 + 9547 = 18792"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GRAB = ANGLE", "Answer": "9217 + 9715 = 18932"}
{"Question": "RISE + REST = IRAQI", "Answer": "9178 + 9873 = 19051"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIDE = AREA", "Answer": "1676 + 1086 = 2762"}
{"Question": "GENE + GATE = TEEN", "Answer": "1747 + 1027 = 2774"}
{"Question": "GENE + GIVE = RANGE", "Answer": "6090 + 6870 = 12960"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOLE = ERROR", "Answer": "6121 + 6081 = 12202"}
{"Question": "GENE + GAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "6292 + 6412 = 12704"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOPE = DEPTH", "Answer": "6353 + 6923 = 13276"}
{"Question": "HERE + HATE = AGREE", "Answer": "7020 + 7180 = 14200"}
{"Question": "HERE + HATE = EAGER", "Answer": "7121 + 7491 = 14612"}
{"Question": "MERE + MINE = ENEMY", "Answer": "7131 + 7041 = 14172"}
{"Question": "HERE + HIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "7242 + 7582 = 14824"}
{"Question": "GENE + GIVE = NIGHT", "Answer": "7313 + 7483 = 14796"}
{"Question": "GENE + GIVE = NEVER", "Answer": "7515 + 7835 = 15350"}
{"Question": "MERE + MAKE = TERMS", "Answer": "7545 + 7925 = 15470"}
{"Question": "HERE + HUGE = GREEN", "Answer": "7646 + 7016 = 14662"}
{"Question": "HERE + HATE = PAPER", "Answer": "7626 + 7536 = 15162"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7868 + 7318 = 15186"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOLE = LOVER", "Answer": "7868 + 7518 = 15386"}
{"Question": "GENE + GATE = ENTER", "Answer": "8161 + 8351 = 16512"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOLE = ORDER", "Answer": "8363 + 8173 = 16536"}
{"Question": "HERE + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8494 + 8724 = 17218"}
{"Question": "HERE + HATE = LATER", "Answer": "8626 + 8736 = 17362"}
{"Question": "GENE + GAME = ANGER", "Answer": "8767 + 8107 = 16874"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOPE = UPPER", "Answer": "9242 + 9582 = 18824"}
{"Question": "MERE + MODE = ORDER", "Answer": "9484 + 9164 = 18648"}
{"Question": "GENE + GIVE = INNER", "Answer": "9686 + 9176 = 18862"}
{"Question": "SELL + SAFE = FEEL", "Answer": "1077 + 1930 = 3007"}
{"Question": "RATE + REST = STAR", "Answer": "1956 + 1635 = 3591"}
{"Question": "MESS + MORE = ROOM", "Answer": "3944 + 3279 = 7223"}
{"Question": "RIDE + READ = AREA", "Answer": "4053 + 4385 = 8438"}
{"Question": "FIRE + FEAR = AREA", "Answer": "4153 + 4385 = 8538"}
{"Question": "FIRE + FEAR = REFER", "Answer": "5410 + 5091 = 10501"}
{"Question": "HELL + HAVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5011 + 5890 = 10901"}
{"Question": "RATE + REST = EAGER", "Answer": "5041 + 5174 = 10215"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "5032 + 5273 = 10305"}
{"Question": "RATE + REST = LATER", "Answer": "5032 + 5293 = 10325"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = BREAD", "Answer": "5232 + 5693 = 10925"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = FULLY", "Answer": "5266 + 5402 = 10668"}
{"Question": "MESS + MINE = DRAMA", "Answer": "5277 + 5682 = 10959"}
{"Question": "THEY + TYPE = SHEET", "Answer": "5087 + 5798 = 10885"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOUR = ERROR", "Answer": "6120 + 6082 = 12202"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FAIL = KNIFE", "Answer": "6077 + 6890 = 12967"}
{"Question": "RATE + REST = ASSET", "Answer": "6180 + 6028 = 12208"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "6341 + 6124 = 12465"}
{"Question": "HERE + HALL = EARTH", "Answer": "6131 + 6255 = 12386"}
{"Question": "WELL + WAGE = EAGER", "Answer": "6177 + 6241 = 12418"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEBT = EAGER", "Answer": "6232 + 6183 = 12415"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = ENTER", "Answer": "6532 + 6283 = 12815"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = BASIS", "Answer": "6252 + 6495 = 12747"}
{"Question": "BELL + BAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "6255 + 6972 = 13227"}
{"Question": "WELL + WAGE = FEWER", "Answer": "6277 + 6352 = 12629"}
{"Question": "USER + URGE = GRASS", "Answer": "6082 + 6218 = 12300"}
{"Question": "DATA + DUST = PIECE", "Answer": "6282 + 6758 = 13040"}
{"Question": "DATA + DUST = TASTE", "Answer": "6313 + 6701 = 13014"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FAIL = ELECT", "Answer": "6311 + 6793 = 13104"}
{"Question": "LESS + LINE = BEGIN", "Answer": "6322 + 6753 = 13075"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIRT = PAPER", "Answer": "6323 + 6852 = 13175"}
{"Question": "TELL + TYPE = REPLY", "Answer": "6344 + 6703 = 13047"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = PRINT", "Answer": "6253 + 6385 = 12638"}
{"Question": "WITH + WHAT = SHALL", "Answer": "6873 + 6327 = 13200"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAKE = LATER", "Answer": "6411 + 6234 = 12645"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = PIECE", "Answer": "6434 + 6273 = 12707"}
{"Question": "GENE + GAIN = INNER", "Answer": "6434 + 6913 = 13347"}
{"Question": "TELL + TONE = OFTEN", "Answer": "6455 + 6194 = 12649"}
{"Question": "DATA + DUST = SCENE", "Answer": "6484 + 6718 = 13202"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REAL = LOVER", "Answer": "6215 + 6541 = 12756"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "6515 + 6271 = 12786"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REAL = LABOR", "Answer": "6315 + 6521 = 12836"}
{"Question": "SELL + SHOE = CLOCK", "Answer": "6522 + 6395 = 12917"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOUR = NURSE", "Answer": "6945 + 6534 = 13479"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = ERROR", "Answer": "6585 + 6718 = 13303"}
{"Question": "MESS + MALE = USUAL", "Answer": "6733 + 6407 = 13140"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = MOTOR", "Answer": "6028 + 6892 = 12920"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = BUYER", "Answer": "6844 + 6238 = 13082"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "6877 + 6508 = 13385"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEBT = ORDER", "Answer": "6949 + 6724 = 13673"}
{"Question": "CELL + COPE = PROOF", "Answer": "6988 + 6019 = 13007"}
{"Question": "CELL + COPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "6988 + 6719 = 13707"}
{"Question": "RIDE + READ = EAGER", "Answer": "7861 + 7156 = 15017"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TEAR = RATIO", "Answer": "7512 + 7241 = 14753"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAPE = PILOT", "Answer": "7255 + 7312 = 14567"}
{"Question": "SELL + SAFE = BASIS", "Answer": "7255 + 7482 = 14737"}
{"Question": "HERE + HAIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7252 + 7915 = 15167"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAKE = USUAL", "Answer": "7255 + 7942 = 15197"}
{"Question": "USER + URGE = GLASS", "Answer": "7082 + 7218 = 14300"}
{"Question": "SORT + STAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7582 + 7218 = 14800"}
{"Question": "TREE + TOUR = HEART", "Answer": "7344 + 7293 = 14637"}
{"Question": "CELL + COPE = SLEEP", "Answer": "7355 + 7983 = 15338"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "7214 + 7461 = 14675"}
{"Question": "RATE + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "7314 + 7451 = 14765"}
{"Question": "RULE + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "7934 + 7423 = 15357"}
{"Question": "BELL + BITE = METER", "Answer": "7488 + 7054 = 14542"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = METER", "Answer": "7488 + 7254 = 14742"}
{"Question": "DATE + DEBT = MEDIA", "Answer": "7284 + 7468 = 14752"}
{"Question": "OPEN + ONCE = PHOTO", "Answer": "7125 + 7582 = 14707"}
{"Question": "TREE + TOUR = GREAT", "Answer": "7522 + 7685 = 15207"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEBT = PAPER", "Answer": "7545 + 7624 = 15169"}
{"Question": "FREE + FOUR = GUESS", "Answer": "7588 + 7245 = 14833"}
{"Question": "FREE + FOUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "7588 + 7625 = 15213"}
{"Question": "TREE + TOUR = ELECT", "Answer": "7611 + 7496 = 15107"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAPE = PAPER", "Answer": "7644 + 7516 = 15160"}
{"Question": "LESS + LATE = CATCH", "Answer": "7688 + 7526 = 15214"}
{"Question": "HERE + HALL = SALES", "Answer": "7848 + 7533 = 15381"}
{"Question": "MERE + MASS = USUAL", "Answer": "7868 + 7255 = 15123"}
{"Question": "SORT + STIR = IRISH", "Answer": "7259 + 7915 = 15174"}
{"Question": "HERE + HILL = IRISH", "Answer": "7959 + 7188 = 15147"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOUR = TOOTH", "Answer": "7989 + 7528 = 15517"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = OCCUR", "Answer": "8312 + 8291 = 16603"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAKE = SALAD", "Answer": "8211 + 8652 = 16863"}
{"Question": "HERE + HILL = FIFTH", "Answer": "8393 + 8755 = 17148"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = TITLE", "Answer": "8414 + 8751 = 17165"}
{"Question": "HERE + HILL = INNER", "Answer": "8494 + 8155 = 16649"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOVE = NOVEL", "Answer": "8533 + 8725 = 17258"}
{"Question": "OPEN + ONCE = CHEAP", "Answer": "8275 + 8517 = 16792"}
{"Question": "TIME + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "8216 + 8651 = 16867"}
{"Question": "DATA + DIET = FIELD", "Answer": "8626 + 8732 = 17358"}
{"Question": "WELL + WIFE = FEWER", "Answer": "8644 + 8216 = 16860"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = REFER", "Answer": "8655 + 8106 = 16761"}
{"Question": "LESS + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "8711 + 8067 = 16778"}
{"Question": "MESS + MOVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8744 + 8527 = 17271"}
{"Question": "FREE + FOUR = TREAT", "Answer": "8744 + 8657 = 17401"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = STILL", "Answer": "8057 + 8765 = 16822"}
{"Question": "DATA + DUST = BASIS", "Answer": "8767 + 8536 = 17303"}
{"Question": "TELL + TYPE = FIFTY", "Answer": "8933 + 8249 = 17182"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = PAPER", "Answer": "8933 + 8259 = 17192"}
{"Question": "TELL + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "9133 + 9781 = 18914"}
{"Question": "TELL + TIRE = ENTER", "Answer": "9155 + 9761 = 18916"}
{"Question": "MERE + MALL = EMPTY", "Answer": "9171 + 9855 = 19026"}
{"Question": "IRON + INTO = NIGHT", "Answer": "9861 + 9176 = 19037"}
{"Question": "HERE + HALL = ERROR", "Answer": "9181 + 9677 = 18858"}
{"Question": "SELL + SHOE = TOOTH", "Answer": "9233 + 9582 = 18815"}
{"Question": "LATE + LEFT = AFTER", "Answer": "9142 + 9284 = 18426"}
{"Question": "THEY + TYPE = PATCH", "Answer": "9752 + 9215 = 18967"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOUR = ONION", "Answer": "9262 + 9156 = 18418"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "9322 + 9513 = 18835"}
{"Question": "HERE + HAIR = ONION", "Answer": "9353 + 9265 = 18618"}
{"Question": "TELL + TIRE = OTHER", "Answer": "9355 + 9683 = 19038"}
{"Question": "DATA + DEBT = BLADE", "Answer": "9373 + 9017 = 18390"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = LATER", "Answer": "9411 + 9534 = 18945"}
{"Question": "TREE + TOUR = STEEL", "Answer": "9422 + 9804 = 19226"}
{"Question": "BELL + BONE = ONION", "Answer": "9533 + 9185 = 18718"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRUE = ALTER", "Answer": "9588 + 9365 = 18953"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOUR = SHARE", "Answer": "9826 + 9602 = 19428"}
{"Question": "BELL + BASE = ASSET", "Answer": "9677 + 9186 = 18863"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "9087 + 9718 = 18805"}
{"Question": "GENE + GAIN = LEGAL", "Answer": "9838 + 9063 = 18901"}
{"Question": "CELL + CARE = ACTOR", "Answer": "9877 + 9158 = 19035"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STEP = POSE", "Answer": "1263 + 1352 = 2615"}
{"Question": "HOME + HERO = THEM", "Answer": "4132 + 4291 = 8423"}
{"Question": "STEP + SPOT = TASTE", "Answer": "5143 + 5371 = 10514"}
{"Question": "SNAP + SPIN = NOISE", "Answer": "5167 + 5791 = 10958"}
{"Question": "STEP + SPOT = THOSE", "Answer": "5176 + 5681 = 10857"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STEP = CHEST", "Answer": "6078 + 6890 = 12968"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STEP = PAUSE", "Answer": "6178 + 6891 = 13069"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOLE = REACT", "Answer": "6215 + 6592 = 12807"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "6295 + 6582 = 12877"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TEAR = IRAQI", "Answer": "6378 + 6823 = 13201"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TRUE = AGENT", "Answer": "6719 + 6987 = 13706"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOME = ARMED", "Answer": "7345 + 7593 = 14938"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HERO = FEWER", "Answer": "7465 + 7594 = 15059"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HERO = LOCAL", "Answer": "7516 + 7685 = 15201"}
{"Question": "SPIN + SNAP = PEACE", "Answer": "8135 + 8571 = 16706"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOPE = PORCH", "Answer": "8296 + 8612 = 16908"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOLE = MODEL", "Answer": "8237 + 8792 = 17029"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TRUE = QUIET", "Answer": "8375 + 8563 = 16938"}
{"Question": "STEP + SPOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "9136 + 9681 = 18817"}
{"Question": "SPOT + STEP = PHONE", "Answer": "9175 + 9561 = 18736"}
{"Question": "HOPE + HERO = UPPER", "Answer": "9285 + 9572 = 18857"}
{"Question": "HERE + HANG = EAGER", "Answer": "5131 + 5082 = 10213"}
{"Question": "SALT + STEP = THESE", "Answer": "5761 + 5198 = 10959"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LEAD = SALES", "Answer": "5312 + 5209 = 10521"}
{"Question": "FUEL + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "5412 + 5206 = 10618"}
{"Question": "OPEN + ONLY = SLEEP", "Answer": "5682 + 5204 = 10886"}
{"Question": "RICE + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "5216 + 5689 = 10905"}
{"Question": "ROLE + REST = LATER", "Answer": "5316 + 5649 = 10965"}
{"Question": "HERE + HANG = ANGER", "Answer": "5878 + 5109 = 10987"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOST = MOTOR", "Answer": "5878 + 5029 = 10907"}
{"Question": "SIGH + SHUT = TRUST", "Answer": "6870 + 6091 = 12961"}
{"Question": "COAL + CLUE = PEACE", "Answer": "6890 + 6072 = 12962"}
{"Question": "DATA + DESK = ASSET", "Answer": "6181 + 6027 = 12208"}
{"Question": "HERE + HALF = REFER", "Answer": "6212 + 6709 = 12921"}
{"Question": "WITH + WHOM = THERE", "Answer": "6412 + 6295 = 12707"}
{"Question": "TYPE + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "6932 + 6214 = 13146"}
{"Question": "BLUE + BEST = USUAL", "Answer": "6912 + 6237 = 13149"}
{"Question": "CASH + CHEF = AHEAD", "Answer": "6172 + 6243 = 12415"}
{"Question": "DATA + DESK = TASTE", "Answer": "6313 + 6704 = 13017"}
{"Question": "COAL + CLUE = SALES", "Answer": "6023 + 6358 = 12381"}
{"Question": "WISH + WHAT = TASTE", "Answer": "6593 + 6321 = 12914"}
{"Question": "MERE + MOST = TERMS", "Answer": "6323 + 6941 = 13264"}
{"Question": "TONE + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "6283 + 6341 = 12624"}
{"Question": "ROPE + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "6714 + 6432 = 13146"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRUG = GUARD", "Answer": "6725 + 6531 = 13256"}
{"Question": "MERE + MASK = WORKS", "Answer": "6545 + 6927 = 13472"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOST = TRUTH", "Answer": "6535 + 6481 = 13016"}
{"Question": "BITE + BEAR = START", "Answer": "6935 + 6548 = 13483"}
{"Question": "LOVE + LEAN = NOVEL", "Answer": "6285 + 6571 = 12856"}
{"Question": "RACE + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "6257 + 6719 = 12976"}
{"Question": "SIGN + SNAP = AGAIN", "Answer": "6437 + 6710 = 13147"}
{"Question": "HUGE + HERO = OCCUR", "Answer": "6458 + 6891 = 13349"}
{"Question": "DATA + DESK = SPEED", "Answer": "6989 + 6017 = 13006"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SELF = OFFER", "Answer": "6419 + 6973 = 13392"}
{"Question": "GENE + GROW = OFFER", "Answer": "6979 + 6415 = 13394"}
{"Question": "SHIT + STOP = THOSE", "Answer": "7421 + 7158 = 14579"}
{"Question": "HERE + HOLD = ERROR", "Answer": "7141 + 7283 = 14424"}
{"Question": "DATA + DISH = THEME", "Answer": "7212 + 7394 = 14606"}
{"Question": "GENE + GLAD = ANGLE", "Answer": "7242 + 7510 = 14752"}
{"Question": "GENE + GRAB = ANGRY", "Answer": "7242 + 7516 = 14758"}
{"Question": "HERO + HOST = STATE", "Answer": "7632 + 7214 = 14846"}
{"Question": "GENE + GIRL = INNER", "Answer": "7242 + 7186 = 14428"}
{"Question": "FUEL + FLAT = STAFF", "Answer": "7583 + 7394 = 14977"}
{"Question": "SUCH + SHOE = CHEST", "Answer": "7214 + 7456 = 14670"}
{"Question": "GENE + GROW = OWNER", "Answer": "7434 + 7915 = 15349"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "7254 + 7491 = 14745"}
{"Question": "GENE + GRAB = PAPER", "Answer": "7494 + 7652 = 15146"}
{"Question": "DATA + DROP = TODAY", "Answer": "7515 + 7243 = 14758"}
{"Question": "ROLE + READ = LATER", "Answer": "7315 + 7542 = 14857"}
{"Question": "HIDE + HELP = DEPTH", "Answer": "7615 + 7592 = 15207"}
{"Question": "HAVE + HELP = LEVEL", "Answer": "7835 + 7516 = 15351"}
{"Question": "SAME + SEND = MEDIA", "Answer": "7915 + 7524 = 15439"}
{"Question": "FUEL + FLAG = GLASS", "Answer": "7925 + 7541 = 15466"}
{"Question": "RISE + READ = BASIS", "Answer": "7285 + 7543 = 14828"}
{"Question": "HUGE + HEAR = AGREE", "Answer": "7456 + 7610 = 15066"}
{"Question": "TAPE + TERM = PAPER", "Answer": "7516 + 7648 = 15164"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DRUG = EAGER", "Answer": "7158 + 7860 = 15018"}
{"Question": "SHOT + STEP = THOSE", "Answer": "8671 + 8109 = 16780"}
{"Question": "SHUT + STAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "8791 + 8126 = 16917"}
{"Question": "STEP + SPIN = PIECE", "Answer": "8241 + 8163 = 16404"}
{"Question": "SALT + STEP = TASTE", "Answer": "8671 + 8143 = 16814"}
{"Question": "HATE + HERO = TOOTH", "Answer": "8412 + 8206 = 16618"}
{"Question": "BAKE + BELT = LABEL", "Answer": "8602 + 8219 = 16821"}
{"Question": "FUEL + FLAG = ERROR", "Answer": "8312 + 8294 = 16606"}
{"Question": "HERE + HANG = RANGE", "Answer": "8212 + 8690 = 16902"}
{"Question": "TAKE + TERM = MAKER", "Answer": "8692 + 8231 = 16923"}
{"Question": "SHIP + SPOT = TOOTH", "Answer": "8352 + 8261 = 16613"}
{"Question": "DATA + DENY = ENTER", "Answer": "8353 + 8164 = 16517"}
{"Question": "BLUE + BEST = STEEL", "Answer": "8024 + 8416 = 16440"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SPOT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8625 + 8571 = 17196"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SPOT = ELITE", "Answer": "8725 + 8536 = 17261"}
{"Question": "WITH + WHEN = THEME", "Answer": "8216 + 8693 = 16909"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DROP = AWARE", "Answer": "8516 + 8649 = 17165"}
{"Question": "BITE + BEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "8716 + 8653 = 17369"}
{"Question": "TYPE + TEAM = APPLY", "Answer": "9285 + 9517 = 18802"}
{"Question": "SNAP + SPOT = ASIAN", "Answer": "9816 + 9602 = 19418"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TEAM = AFTER", "Answer": "9346 + 9617 = 18963"}
{"Question": "TINY + TYPE = ENTER", "Answer": "9286 + 9631 = 18917"}
{"Question": "SAFE + SEND = ASIAN", "Answer": "9178 + 9835 = 19013"}
{"Question": "HERE + MERE = HONEY", "Answer": "1262 + 9262 = 10524"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = MAJOR", "Answer": "1363 + 9363 = 10726"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = MORAL", "Answer": "1373 + 9373 = 10746"}
{"Question": "HERE + MERE = HUMAN", "Answer": "1464 + 9464 = 10928"}
{"Question": "HERE + MERE = HUMOR", "Answer": "1484 + 9484 = 10968"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = BOMB", "Answer": "1858 + 4858 = 6716"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = EACH", "Answer": "2767 + 4767 = 7534"}
{"Question": "HERE + MERE = LIMIT", "Answer": "3464 + 9464 = 12928"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = THEM", "Answer": "4262 + 5262 = 9524"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = TERMS", "Answer": "4373 + 9373 = 13746"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERE = BEACH", "Answer": "6454 + 8454 = 14908"}
{"Question": "HERE + MERE = CREAM", "Answer": "7969 + 8969 = 16938"}
{"Question": "DATA + FATE = DRESS", "Answer": "1232 + 9234 = 10466"}
{"Question": "DATA + FATE = DREAM", "Answer": "1262 + 9265 = 10527"}
{"Question": "HERE + TERM = TIGHT", "Answer": "9343 + 1348 = 10691"}
{"Question": "HERE + TERM = HONOR", "Answer": "1353 + 9352 = 10705"}
{"Question": "DATA + LATE = LOCAL", "Answer": "9363 + 1368 = 10731"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERO = HUMOR", "Answer": "9464 + 1462 = 10926"}
{"Question": "DATA + RATE = RURAL", "Answer": "8575 + 1579 = 10154"}
{"Question": "DATA + FATE = FIFTH", "Answer": "8595 + 1597 = 10192"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEND = GHOST", "Answer": "1646 + 8643 = 10289"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEND = GLASS", "Answer": "1696 + 8692 = 10388"}
{"Question": "DATA + HATE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8747 + 1749 = 10496"}
{"Question": "GENE + MENU = MOUNT", "Answer": "8797 + 1795 = 10592"}
{"Question": "DATA + FATE = DIRTY", "Answer": "1797 + 8796 = 10593"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEND = TEST", "Answer": "4959 + 1957 = 6916"}
{"Question": "DATA + GATE = DRAFT", "Answer": "1969 + 8967 = 10936"}
{"Question": "DATA + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "2656 + 3650 = 6306"}
{"Question": "GENE + DENY = EDGE", "Answer": "2717 + 4710 = 7427"}
{"Question": "HERE + VERY = EVER", "Answer": "2737 + 4736 = 7473"}
{"Question": "GENE + TEND = ASSET", "Answer": "6525 + 3528 = 10053"}
{"Question": "DATA + HATE = FIFTH", "Answer": "6595 + 3598 = 10193"}
{"Question": "DATA + GATE = LEGAL", "Answer": "3949 + 8942 = 12891"}
{"Question": "DATA + RATE = AFTER", "Answer": "8121 + 5124 = 13245"}
{"Question": "DATA + LATE = FULLY", "Answer": "9272 + 5278 = 14550"}
{"Question": "DATA + RATE = FEWER", "Answer": "8272 + 6274 = 14546"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERO = LEMON", "Answer": "6343 + 7349 = 13692"}
{"Question": "DATA + RATE = CARRY", "Answer": "6383 + 7389 = 13772"}
{"Question": "HERE + TERM = REACT", "Answer": "6515 + 8513 = 15028"}
{"Question": "MERE + HERO = IRISH", "Answer": "7565 + 8563 = 16128"}
{"Question": "GENE + HERE = GIVEN", "Answer": "1242 + 9282 = 10524"}
{"Question": "HERE + GENE = HONEY", "Answer": "1272 + 9252 = 10524"}
{"Question": "HERE + GENE = HUMOR", "Answer": "1363 + 9383 = 10746"}
{"Question": "HERE + GENE = HONOR", "Answer": "1747 + 8757 = 10504"}
{"Question": "GENE + HERE = EAGER", "Answer": "3191 + 7121 = 10312"}
{"Question": "MERE + GENE = TERMS", "Answer": "3252 + 9282 = 12534"}
{"Question": "GENE + HERE = OTHER", "Answer": "3464 + 9484 = 12948"}
{"Question": "HERE + GENE = REACH", "Answer": "4212 + 8292 = 12504"}
{"Question": "MERE + GENE = ARMED", "Answer": "5232 + 8292 = 13524"}
{"Question": "GENE + HERE = BENCH", "Answer": "6494 + 8434 = 14928"}
{"Question": "HERE + GENE = ANGER", "Answer": "7484 + 9464 = 16948"}
{"Question": "MERE + BEAR = MARRY", "Answer": "1242 + 9204 = 10446"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = ENTER", "Answer": "9252 + 1265 = 10517"}
{"Question": "DATA + HALL = THAT", "Answer": "1383 + 7355 = 8738"}
{"Question": "DATA + WANT = WOMAN", "Answer": "9353 + 1385 = 10738"}
{"Question": "HERE + YEAR = BABY", "Answer": "5383 + 1378 = 6761"}
{"Question": "DATA + LAST = LEGAL", "Answer": "9383 + 1348 = 10731"}
{"Question": "MERE + LESS = LIMIT", "Answer": "9484 + 1422 = 10906"}
{"Question": "MERE + TELL = MOTOR", "Answer": "1474 + 9433 = 10907"}
{"Question": "HERE + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "3474 + 1497 = 4971"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = SEED", "Answer": "7525 + 1592 = 9117"}
{"Question": "HERE + FEAR = FIFTH", "Answer": "8535 + 1593 = 10128"}
{"Question": "DATA + CAST = CYCLE", "Answer": "8575 + 1567 = 10142"}
{"Question": "DATA + FACT = FIFTH", "Answer": "8575 + 1597 = 10172"}
{"Question": "HERE + SELL = SOLAR", "Answer": "8696 + 1633 = 10329"}
{"Question": "GENE + LEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "8656 + 1605 = 10261"}
{"Question": "DATA + LAST = LEVEL", "Answer": "8656 + 1645 = 10301"}
{"Question": "DATA + PART = PRIDE", "Answer": "8676 + 1607 = 10283"}
{"Question": "DATA + PANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "8676 + 1697 = 10373"}
{"Question": "GENE + SELL = SALES", "Answer": "8727 + 1744 = 10471"}
{"Question": "DATA + PART = DRINK", "Answer": "1757 + 8705 = 10462"}
{"Question": "DATA + BALL = DOUBT", "Answer": "1727 + 8755 = 10482"}
{"Question": "HERE + WEAR = WORRY", "Answer": "8757 + 1795 = 10552"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = TEAM", "Answer": "1767 + 4706 = 6473"}
{"Question": "DATA + PART = DREAM", "Answer": "1767 + 8706 = 10473"}
{"Question": "DATA + CAST = DEPTH", "Answer": "1767 + 8796 = 10563"}
{"Question": "HERE + MESS = HUMOR", "Answer": "1929 + 8933 = 10862"}
{"Question": "DATA + CAST = AHEAD", "Answer": "8171 + 2147 = 10318"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = AHEAD", "Answer": "7161 + 3156 = 10317"}
{"Question": "HERE + TEAR = FIFTH", "Answer": "3585 + 6578 = 10163"}
{"Question": "HERE + BEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "4686 + 7628 = 12314"}
{"Question": "DATA + SALT = CROSS", "Answer": "7686 + 4658 = 12344"}
{"Question": "HERE + DEAR = NAKED", "Answer": "4878 + 5807 = 10685"}
{"Question": "HERE + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "7212 + 5241 = 12453"}
{"Question": "HERE + TEAR = CATCH", "Answer": "9272 + 5247 = 14519"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = SHELL", "Answer": "9282 + 5218 = 14500"}
{"Question": "DATA + CAST = SALAD", "Answer": "5323 + 8312 = 13635"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = STEAL", "Answer": "5434 + 8413 = 13847"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = SCENE", "Answer": "6787 + 5718 = 12505"}
{"Question": "GENE + TELL = ASSET", "Answer": "9282 + 6244 = 15526"}
{"Question": "DATA + SALT = BASIS", "Answer": "6343 + 7384 = 13727"}
{"Question": "HERE + WELL = FEWER", "Answer": "6383 + 7355 = 13738"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = TITLE", "Answer": "7515 + 6591 = 14106"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8515 + 6501 = 15016"}
{"Question": "DATA + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "6535 + 8503 = 15038"}
{"Question": "HERE + NEAR = SEVEN", "Answer": "6535 + 8523 = 15058"}
{"Question": "DATA + MASS = ASIDE", "Answer": "8131 + 7155 = 15286"}
{"Question": "HERE + BELL = OTHER", "Answer": "7383 + 9355 = 16738"}
{"Question": "DATA + BALL = SALAD", "Answer": "8646 + 7622 = 16268"}
{"Question": "HERE + BEAN = HONOR", "Answer": "1272 + 9235 = 10507"}
{"Question": "GENE + DEAR = GRADE", "Answer": "1252 + 9240 = 10492"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEAT = GLASS", "Answer": "1252 + 9247 = 10499"}
{"Question": "DATA + FAIR = FIRST", "Answer": "9424 + 1408 = 10832"}
{"Question": "DATA + CARE = DREAM", "Answer": "1434 + 9408 = 10842"}
{"Question": "DATA + SAFE = STEEL", "Answer": "9404 + 1478 = 10882"}
{"Question": "HERE + NECK = HONOR", "Answer": "1424 + 9478 = 10902"}
{"Question": "DATA + MALE = MODEL", "Answer": "9464 + 1473 = 10937"}
{"Question": "DATA + VARY = DRIVE", "Answer": "1676 + 8609 = 10285"}
{"Question": "DATA + GAIN = DRINK", "Answer": "1646 + 8627 = 10273"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEAT = STATE", "Answer": "8676 + 1630 = 10306"}
{"Question": "DATA + GAME = DREAM", "Answer": "1676 + 8693 = 10369"}
{"Question": "HERE + BEAN = BRAND", "Answer": "8707 + 1745 = 10452"}
{"Question": "DATA + EARN = DRINK", "Answer": "1757 + 8706 = 10463"}
{"Question": "GENE + SEAT = SALAD", "Answer": "8797 + 1706 = 10503"}
{"Question": "DATA + BASE = DRESS", "Answer": "1797 + 8725 = 10522"}
{"Question": "DATA + CASH = DRESS", "Answer": "1797 + 8736 = 10533"}
{"Question": "MERE + BELT = MARRY", "Answer": "1757 + 8796 = 10553"}
{"Question": "HERE + SEAT = CRASH", "Answer": "2808 + 7864 = 10672"}
{"Question": "MERE + SEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "9242 + 3251 = 12493"}
{"Question": "GENE + REST = ENTER", "Answer": "8121 + 4193 = 12314"}
{"Question": "DATA + EARN = TREAT", "Answer": "6212 + 4209 = 10421"}
{"Question": "DATA + CARE = TREND", "Answer": "4818 + 5806 = 10624"}
{"Question": "DATA + EACH = THEME", "Answer": "8212 + 5293 = 13505"}
{"Question": "GENE + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "5232 + 7241 = 12473"}
{"Question": "DATA + EASY = STEAL", "Answer": "5434 + 8412 = 13846"}
{"Question": "GENE + YEAH = HAPPY", "Answer": "7464 + 5421 = 12885"}
{"Question": "DATA + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "6131 + 8154 = 14285"}
{"Question": "GENE + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "6141 + 9152 = 15293"}
{"Question": "GENE + HEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "6282 + 7235 = 13517"}
{"Question": "DATA + PARK = RAPID", "Answer": "7383 + 6314 = 13697"}
{"Question": "DATA + EASY = TASTE", "Answer": "6515 + 8503 = 15018"}
{"Question": "GENE + READ = NEVER", "Answer": "6515 + 8543 = 15058"}
{"Question": "HERE + NEWS = IRISH", "Answer": "7545 + 6582 = 14127"}
{"Question": "GENE + WINE = WHEEL", "Answer": "8262 + 1962 = 10224"}
{"Question": "GENE + BONE = GUESS", "Answer": "1272 + 8972 = 10244"}
{"Question": "MERE + CORE = MATCH", "Answer": "1343 + 8943 = 10286"}
{"Question": "HERE + CORE = CLEAR", "Answer": "8363 + 1963 = 10326"}
{"Question": "GENE + TONE = GREAT", "Answer": "1464 + 8964 = 10428"}
{"Question": "HERE + PURE = HAPPY", "Answer": "1646 + 9346 = 10992"}
{"Question": "GENE + TONE = TRUTH", "Answer": "8656 + 1756 = 10412"}
{"Question": "MERE + CORE = MORAL", "Answer": "1676 + 9076 = 10752"}
{"Question": "GENE + FINE = GRAIN", "Answer": "1747 + 8947 = 10694"}
{"Question": "HERE + TIRE = TIRED", "Answer": "9787 + 1087 = 10874"}
{"Question": "GENE + TONE = ONTO", "Answer": "4858 + 1658 = 6516"}
{"Question": "MERE + SURE = MUSIC", "Answer": "1878 + 9078 = 10956"}
{"Question": "HERE + CORE = EARTH", "Answer": "2171 + 8571 = 10742"}
{"Question": "GENE + TONE = ELECT", "Answer": "7181 + 2981 = 10162"}
{"Question": "GENE + LINE = FIELD", "Answer": "2343 + 8043 = 10386"}
{"Question": "HERE + FIRE = RIGHT", "Answer": "3515 + 9215 = 12730"}
{"Question": "MERE + SURE = TERMS", "Answer": "8292 + 4692 = 12984"}
{"Question": "HERE + SURE = IRISH", "Answer": "6828 + 5328 = 12156"}
{"Question": "HERE + TIRE = FIFTH", "Answer": "6878 + 5278 = 12156"}
{"Question": "GENE + BONE = ANGLE", "Answer": "9060 + 7860 = 16920"}
{"Question": "MERE + HIRE = FIFTH", "Answer": "7454 + 8654 = 16108"}
{"Question": "MERE + HIRE = IRISH", "Answer": "7969 + 8169 = 16138"}
{"Question": "LESS + CASE = COLOR", "Answer": "9255 + 1652 = 10907"}
{"Question": "TELL + ABLE = ASSET", "Answer": "8266 + 1762 = 10028"}
{"Question": "SELL + PALE = SWEEP", "Answer": "1266 + 8962 = 10228"}
{"Question": "SELL + ABLE = START", "Answer": "1288 + 9682 = 10970"}
{"Question": "YELL + MALE = ALLY", "Answer": "1299 + 5692 = 6991"}
{"Question": "LESS + NOSE = LOCAL", "Answer": "1388 + 9083 = 10471"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ALSO = BLOOD", "Answer": "1422 + 9024 = 10446"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ALSO = APPLE", "Answer": "8433 + 1634 = 10067"}
{"Question": "CELL + ROLE = COLOR", "Answer": "1455 + 9054 = 10509"}
{"Question": "HELL + MALE = HUMAN", "Answer": "1522 + 9425 = 10947"}
{"Question": "SELL + TALE = SHOOT", "Answer": "1544 + 9345 = 10889"}
{"Question": "FREE + OVER = ROOF", "Answer": "1566 + 3765 = 5331"}
{"Question": "LESS + CASE = LOCAL", "Answer": "1566 + 9365 = 10931"}
{"Question": "CELL + ABLE = CHEEK", "Answer": "1577 + 8975 = 10552"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ALSO = TRAIL", "Answer": "1588 + 9385 = 10973"}
{"Question": "TELL + ABLE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8622 + 1526 = 10148"}
{"Question": "BELL + ROLE = BUYER", "Answer": "1633 + 9236 = 10869"}
{"Question": "SELL + ROLE = START", "Answer": "1644 + 9246 = 10890"}
{"Question": "BELL + FILE = BREAD", "Answer": "1677 + 8976 = 10653"}
{"Question": "SELL + HOLE = SOLAR", "Answer": "1677 + 9076 = 10753"}
{"Question": "CELL + MALE = CARRY", "Answer": "1688 + 9086 = 10774"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ALSO = BIBLE", "Answer": "1722 + 8427 = 10149"}
{"Question": "KNEE + THEN = TOOTH", "Answer": "8755 + 1257 = 10012"}
{"Question": "CELL + FILE = CATCH", "Answer": "1755 + 8657 = 10412"}
{"Question": "CELL + ABLE = CHECK", "Answer": "1755 + 8957 = 10712"}
{"Question": "CELL + MALE = CATCH", "Answer": "1755 + 9057 = 10812"}
{"Question": "CELL + ABLE = CROSS", "Answer": "1766 + 8467 = 10233"}
{"Question": "BELL + PALE = PRESS", "Answer": "8766 + 1967 = 10733"}
{"Question": "YELL + ABLE = BABY", "Answer": "1833 + 5738 = 7571"}
{"Question": "CELL + TALE = CATCH", "Answer": "1855 + 9058 = 10913"}
{"Question": "BELL + SALE = BASIC", "Answer": "1866 + 9068 = 10934"}
{"Question": "FREE + OVER = ROLL", "Answer": "6877 + 1278 = 8155"}
{"Question": "TELL + POLE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1955 + 8059 = 10014"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ALSO = LOTS", "Answer": "6088 + 2980 = 9068"}
{"Question": "TELL + ABLE = DATA", "Answer": "2166 + 7561 = 9727"}
{"Question": "LESS + BASE = RURAL", "Answer": "7344 + 2843 = 10187"}
{"Question": "HELL + TALE = CATCH", "Answer": "2755 + 8057 = 10812"}
{"Question": "KNEE + THEN = CATCH", "Answer": "7855 + 2358 = 10213"}
{"Question": "YELL + MALE = APPLY", "Answer": "7899 + 2198 = 10097"}
{"Question": "KNEE + THEN = EVENT", "Answer": "6211 + 3912 = 10123"}
{"Question": "TELL + ROLE = LATER", "Answer": "7211 + 3512 = 10723"}
{"Question": "LESS + ROSE = COLOR", "Answer": "3255 + 7052 = 10307"}
{"Question": "CELL + RULE = OCCUR", "Answer": "3544 + 9845 = 13389"}
{"Question": "KNEE + OPEN = SPEAK", "Answer": "3588 + 9285 = 12873"}
{"Question": "FREE + USER = STUFF", "Answer": "3766 + 9167 = 12933"}
{"Question": "HELL + MALE = CATCH", "Answer": "3855 + 7058 = 10913"}
{"Question": "LESS + NOSE = ONION", "Answer": "9855 + 3158 = 13013"}
{"Question": "TREE + OVER = PHOTO", "Answer": "4277 + 9672 = 13949"}
{"Question": "CELL + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "8322 + 4923 = 13245"}
{"Question": "BELL + RULE = FLOOR", "Answer": "8233 + 5432 = 13665"}
{"Question": "BELL + ROLE = COLOR", "Answer": "5277 + 9472 = 14749"}
{"Question": "TREE + OVER = GREAT", "Answer": "5322 + 7923 = 13245"}
{"Question": "KNEE + THEN = DEATH", "Answer": "5344 + 8743 = 14087"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ALSO = LEAST", "Answer": "5699 + 8196 = 13895"}
{"Question": "TREE + OVER = EVENT", "Answer": "8711 + 5417 = 14128"}
{"Question": "HELL + ROLE = OTHER", "Answer": "9788 + 5187 = 14975"}
{"Question": "FREE + USER = STAFF", "Answer": "5877 + 6178 = 12055"}
{"Question": "SELL + ABLE = GRASS", "Answer": "5877 + 9078 = 14955"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ALSO = USUAL", "Answer": "5933 + 7239 = 13172"}
{"Question": "TELL + PALE = ADAPT", "Answer": "6977 + 5179 = 12156"}
{"Question": "HELL + TALE = EARTH", "Answer": "9188 + 6581 = 15769"}
{"Question": "CELL + SALE = BASIS", "Answer": "6355 + 8453 = 14808"}
{"Question": "YELL + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "7433 + 6934 = 14367"}
{"Question": "BELL + MALE = ALBUM", "Answer": "6455 + 9154 = 15609"}
{"Question": "YELL + PALE = HAPPY", "Answer": "7344 + 8543 = 15887"}
{"Question": "BELL + MALE = LEMON", "Answer": "7511 + 8315 = 15826"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ALSO = METAL", "Answer": "9588 + 7385 = 16973"}
{"Question": "CELL + ABLE = BEACH", "Answer": "9644 + 7146 = 16790"}
{"Question": "BOSS + ALSO = COACH", "Answer": "9755 + 8057 = 17812"}
{"Question": "FREE + OVER = CROSS", "Answer": "9766 + 8067 = 17833"}
{"Question": "HERO + MORE = HUMOR", "Answer": "1286 + 9682 = 10968"}
{"Question": "MORE + HERO = BOMB", "Answer": "1759 + 4957 = 6716"}
{"Question": "CORE + HERO = CLEAR", "Answer": "1967 + 8769 = 10736"}
{"Question": "MORE + HERO = TERMS", "Answer": "6285 + 9582 = 15867"}
{"Question": "CORE + HERO = PORCH", "Answer": "6384 + 7483 = 13867"}
{"Question": "HERE + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "1252 + 9053 = 10305"}
{"Question": "MERE + TURN = MOTOR", "Answer": "1252 + 9653 = 10905"}
{"Question": "HERE + BORN = HONEY", "Answer": "1262 + 9063 = 10325"}
{"Question": "SKIN + UNIT = SCENE", "Answer": "1462 + 9265 = 10727"}
{"Question": "DATA + BITE = BREAD", "Answer": "9262 + 1467 = 10729"}
{"Question": "GENE + PANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "9272 + 1374 = 10646"}
{"Question": "RISE + BEST = BASIS", "Answer": "9472 + 1275 = 10747"}
{"Question": "MERE + HARD = MATCH", "Answer": "1282 + 9087 = 10369"}
{"Question": "STEP + OPEN = SCENE", "Answer": "1582 + 9286 = 10868"}
{"Question": "LEAN + SNAP = LOOSE", "Answer": "1792 + 8295 = 10087"}
{"Question": "HERE + FORM = HONOR", "Answer": "1353 + 9052 = 10405"}
{"Question": "MEAL + FLAT = METER", "Answer": "1053 + 9354 = 10407"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOTS = LOCAL", "Answer": "9363 + 1068 = 10431"}
{"Question": "ALSO + POSE = PRIOR", "Answer": "9463 + 1367 = 10830"}
{"Question": "ONCE + DECK = ORDER", "Answer": "1563 + 9367 = 10930"}
{"Question": "POET + ITEM = PRIME", "Answer": "1573 + 9374 = 10947"}
{"Question": "DATA + SITE = SPEED", "Answer": "9383 + 1286 = 10669"}
{"Question": "LINE + TEND = LATIN", "Answer": "1524 + 9428 = 10952"}
{"Question": "ALSO + COST = CIVIL", "Answer": "8754 + 1453 = 10207"}
{"Question": "COAL + FLAG = COACH", "Answer": "1054 + 9458 = 10512"}
{"Question": "DATA + CITE = CHECK", "Answer": "9454 + 1358 = 10812"}
{"Question": "WHAT + STAR = WORTH", "Answer": "1325 + 9528 = 10853"}
{"Question": "COAL + FLAG = CRAFT", "Answer": "1945 + 8542 = 10487"}
{"Question": "COAT + STAR = CLASS", "Answer": "1945 + 8543 = 10488"}
{"Question": "DATA + VOTE = VOTER", "Answer": "9565 + 1062 = 10627"}
{"Question": "CROP + UPON = CROSS", "Answer": "1065 + 9568 = 10633"}
{"Question": "MENU + LUNG = LEGAL", "Answer": "9085 + 1586 = 10671"}
{"Question": "BEAN + SNAP = SHAPE", "Answer": "9285 + 1587 = 10872"}
{"Question": "PILE + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "1536 + 8632 = 10168"}
{"Question": "THAN + SNAP = TOOTH", "Answer": "1356 + 8657 = 10013"}
{"Question": "SHOP + UPON = SENSE", "Answer": "1756 + 8654 = 10410"}
{"Question": "CASE + BEST = CATCH", "Answer": "1056 + 9657 = 10713"}
{"Question": "SOUL + BLUE = SALES", "Answer": "1976 + 8675 = 10651"}
{"Question": "LEAN + SNAP = LEAVE", "Answer": "1076 + 9674 = 10750"}
{"Question": "HAIR + TRIP = HAPPY", "Answer": "1086 + 9687 = 10773"}
{"Question": "STAR + DRAG = START", "Answer": "1087 + 9783 = 10870"}
{"Question": "SALE + BELT = SALES", "Answer": "1087 + 9784 = 10871"}
{"Question": "STOP + UPON = STUFF", "Answer": "1068 + 9865 = 10933"}
{"Question": "GENE + TINY = TIGHT", "Answer": "9878 + 1073 = 10951"}
{"Question": "HOUR + TRUE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1078 + 9875 = 10953"}
{"Question": "AUTO + BOTH = ADAPT", "Answer": "1239 + 8934 = 10173"}
{"Question": "HERE + FORM = FLOOR", "Answer": "8969 + 1367 = 10336"}
{"Question": "INTO + BOTH = ONION", "Answer": "2051 + 8159 = 10210"}
{"Question": "STEP + OPEN = TONE", "Answer": "5873 + 2374 = 8247"}
{"Question": "WEAK + OKAY = ALLOW", "Answer": "7614 + 2413 = 10027"}
{"Question": "MERE + YARD = ARMY", "Answer": "3515 + 2617 = 6132"}
{"Question": "ABLE + RELY = LEARN", "Answer": "9712 + 3218 = 12930"}
{"Question": "DARE + TERM = ARMED", "Answer": "9124 + 3425 = 12549"}
{"Question": "HERO + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "3245 + 9547 = 12792"}
{"Question": "AUTO + NOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "3916 + 8615 = 12531"}
{"Question": "HERE + BIRD = RIGHT", "Answer": "3616 + 9214 = 12830"}
{"Question": "HERE + GIRL = RIGHT", "Answer": "3717 + 9218 = 12935"}
{"Question": "HAIR + TRIP = PITCH", "Answer": "8627 + 3721 = 12348"}
{"Question": "REAL + FLAG = EAGER", "Answer": "7108 + 3809 = 10917"}
{"Question": "DROP + UPON = OCCUR", "Answer": "6218 + 3814 = 10032"}
{"Question": "NEAR + GRAB = RANGE", "Answer": "8721 + 4126 = 12847"}
{"Question": "GENE + FIND = BEGIN", "Answer": "4353 + 9052 = 13405"}
{"Question": "REAL + FLAT = EXTRA", "Answer": "6183 + 4385 = 10568"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ROSE = LOVER", "Answer": "4183 + 9386 = 13569"}
{"Question": "LINE + DENY = YIELD", "Answer": "4025 + 6521 = 10546"}
{"Question": "AUTO + NOTE = LEARN", "Answer": "4935 + 7532 = 12467"}
{"Question": "CORE + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "4265 + 8561 = 12826"}
{"Question": "STEP + OPEN = ASSET", "Answer": "4806 + 9602 = 14408"}
{"Question": "CROP + UPON = ROUND", "Answer": "4138 + 9837 = 13975"}
{"Question": "DROP + UPON = POUND", "Answer": "5621 + 7124 = 12745"}
{"Question": "HERE + PART = EARTH", "Answer": "7131 + 5236 = 12367"}
{"Question": "HERO + PORT = OTHER", "Answer": "7631 + 5132 = 12763"}
{"Question": "REAL + FLAT = LATER", "Answer": "8631 + 5137 = 13768"}
{"Question": "NEAR + DRAG = RANGE", "Answer": "8731 + 5136 = 13867"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOTS = USUAL", "Answer": "7262 + 5863 = 13125"}
{"Question": "ALSO + HOST = LOCAL", "Answer": "7182 + 5289 = 12471"}
{"Question": "INTO + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "5813 + 7314 = 13127"}
{"Question": "TAIL + SLIP = ELITE", "Answer": "5923 + 7328 = 13251"}
{"Question": "YEAR + WRAP = APPLY", "Answer": "7914 + 5413 = 13327"}
{"Question": "GENE + RANK = ANGER", "Answer": "5424 + 7123 = 12547"}
{"Question": "BEAT + STAR = GRASS", "Answer": "5934 + 6432 = 12366"}
{"Question": "ROSE + WEST = TOWER", "Answer": "5374 + 8471 = 13845"}
{"Question": "HERE + MARK = ARMED", "Answer": "5737 + 8139 = 13876"}
{"Question": "TEAR + DRAG = STATE", "Answer": "5428 + 9826 = 15254"}
{"Question": "GENE + RANK = PAPER", "Answer": "5949 + 6247 = 12196"}
{"Question": "WHAT + STAR = THESE", "Answer": "7381 + 6184 = 13565"}
{"Question": "BEAR + DRAG = GRADE", "Answer": "7483 + 6381 = 13864"}
{"Question": "DEAL + FLAG = GRADE", "Answer": "6483 + 9381 = 15864"}
{"Question": "ROLE + SELF = OFFER", "Answer": "9124 + 6425 = 15549"}
{"Question": "DATA + BOTH = HABIT", "Answer": "6454 + 8351 = 14805"}
{"Question": "DATA + INTO = BASIS", "Answer": "6494 + 8293 = 14787"}
{"Question": "MERE + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "8545 + 6941 = 15486"}
{"Question": "GAIN + UNIT = TIGHT", "Answer": "9860 + 7061 = 16921"}
{"Question": "MEAT + STAR = TERMS", "Answer": "8541 + 7146 = 15687"}
{"Question": "GENE + TANK = ENTER", "Answer": "7151 + 8659 = 15810"}
{"Question": "MERE + GIRL = LIMIT", "Answer": "9282 + 7681 = 16963"}
{"Question": "LOSE + REST = COLOR", "Answer": "9682 + 7285 = 16967"}
{"Question": "STAR + PRAY = TROOP", "Answer": "8135 + 7532 = 15667"}
{"Question": "BEAT + STAR = HORSE", "Answer": "7345 + 9548 = 16893"}
{"Question": "ALSO + COST = LOCAL", "Answer": "9146 + 7645 = 16791"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOTS = SALAD", "Answer": "7686 + 9281 = 16967"}
{"Question": "STAR + GRAB = BASIS", "Answer": "9068 + 7861 = 16929"}
{"Question": "REAL + FLAG = AGREE", "Answer": "9316 + 8617 = 17933"}
{"Question": "BEAR + GRAY = ARGUE", "Answer": "8217 + 9715 = 17932"}
{"Question": "GENE + HOLE = HONOR", "Answer": "9232 + 1072 = 10304"}
{"Question": "HERE + BITE = HABIT", "Answer": "1232 + 9742 = 10974"}
{"Question": "GENE + TALE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8252 + 1942 = 10194"}
{"Question": "HERE + FINE = HONOR", "Answer": "1242 + 9362 = 10604"}
{"Question": "HERE + ABLE = HONOR", "Answer": "1242 + 9562 = 10804"}
{"Question": "HERE + NAME = HONOR", "Answer": "1363 + 9543 = 10906"}
{"Question": "HERE + BITE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1353 + 9483 = 10836"}
{"Question": "GENE + ABLE = GREEN", "Answer": "1363 + 8973 = 10336"}
{"Question": "HERE + COME = HUMOR", "Answer": "1363 + 9483 = 10846"}
{"Question": "HERE + CITE = CATCH", "Answer": "8494 + 1724 = 10218"}
{"Question": "MERE + LAKE = MORAL", "Answer": "1434 + 8964 = 10398"}
{"Question": "MERE + FILE = MORAL", "Answer": "1474 + 9284 = 10758"}
{"Question": "GENE + AIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "8636 + 1506 = 10142"}
{"Question": "HERE + TAPE = TROOP", "Answer": "8606 + 1726 = 10332"}
{"Question": "HERE + PILE = PAPER", "Answer": "8626 + 1536 = 10162"}
{"Question": "GENE + BIKE = GRAIN", "Answer": "1626 + 8746 = 10372"}
{"Question": "HERE + BONE = HONEY", "Answer": "1686 + 9076 = 10762"}
{"Question": "GENE + ABLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "8757 + 1307 = 10064"}
{"Question": "GENE + FIRE = GRAIN", "Answer": "1747 + 8507 = 10254"}
{"Question": "GENE + SURE = GROUP", "Answer": "1757 + 8607 = 10364"}
{"Question": "GENE + ABLE = GLASS", "Answer": "1737 + 9207 = 10944"}
{"Question": "MERE + TYPE = MARRY", "Answer": "1727 + 8497 = 10224"}
{"Question": "HERE + NOSE = HONOR", "Answer": "1868 + 9038 = 10906"}
{"Question": "HERE + TIME = EARTH", "Answer": "2151 + 8431 = 10582"}
{"Question": "GENE + POLE = OPEN", "Answer": "5363 + 2873 = 8236"}
{"Question": "GENE + TYPE = ENTRY", "Answer": "9131 + 4271 = 13402"}
{"Question": "GENE + TRUE = ENTER", "Answer": "9131 + 4281 = 13412"}
{"Question": "MERE + SITE = TERMS", "Answer": "8272 + 4512 = 12784"}
{"Question": "HERE + BLUE = TRUTH", "Answer": "4232 + 9582 = 13814"}
{"Question": "GENE + ROLE = OWNER", "Answer": "4353 + 6183 = 10536"}
{"Question": "HERE + LAKE = EARLY", "Answer": "6151 + 8431 = 14582"}
{"Question": "HERE + TAPE = PATCH", "Answer": "6393 + 8413 = 14806"}
{"Question": "GENE + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "9353 + 6183 = 15536"}
{"Question": "HERE + NOTE = OTHER", "Answer": "6505 + 8145 = 14650"}
{"Question": "GENE + RACE = ANGER", "Answer": "9858 + 6128 = 15986"}
{"Question": "HERE + ABLE = DRAMA", "Answer": "9474 + 8354 = 17828"}
{"Question": "HELL + TRUE = HONOR", "Answer": "1233 + 9572 = 10805"}
{"Question": "CELL + TIME = CATCH", "Answer": "1233 + 9682 = 10915"}
{"Question": "DATA + BEST = DELAY", "Answer": "1242 + 9084 = 10326"}
{"Question": "PART + STIR = PHOTO", "Answer": "1342 + 9284 = 10626"}
{"Question": "GENE + POLL = OPEN", "Answer": "6272 + 1855 = 8127"}
{"Question": "GENE + THAN = TOOTH", "Answer": "8252 + 1765 = 10017"}
{"Question": "GENE + BALL = GREEN", "Answer": "1272 + 8955 = 10227"}
{"Question": "MERE + KILL = MAKER", "Answer": "1272 + 9655 = 10927"}
{"Question": "DATA + MOST = METER", "Answer": "9262 + 1346 = 10608"}
{"Question": "DATA + POET = PIECE", "Answer": "9262 + 1586 = 10848"}
{"Question": "CORE + YEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "1572 + 9207 = 10779"}
{"Question": "FREE + STAR = START", "Answer": "9288 + 1032 = 10320"}
{"Question": "POLL + INTO = PRIOR", "Answer": "1288 + 9632 = 10920"}
{"Question": "MESS + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "1322 + 9583 = 10905"}
{"Question": "LATE + DEBT = LABEL", "Answer": "1083 + 9348 = 10431"}
{"Question": "GENE + THAN = TIGHT", "Answer": "9383 + 1568 = 10951"}
{"Question": "HERE + POLL = PAPER", "Answer": "8494 + 1655 = 10149"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEFT = LEGAL", "Answer": "9474 + 1067 = 10541"}
{"Question": "KNEE + TURN = TREAT", "Answer": "9477 + 1304 = 10781"}
{"Question": "IDEA + BAKE = BREAD", "Answer": "8725 + 1532 = 10257"}
{"Question": "INTO + LOST = LATIN", "Answer": "8725 + 1562 = 10287"}
{"Question": "SELL + ROPE = SUPER", "Answer": "1533 + 8725 = 10258"}
{"Question": "GENE + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "1545 + 7934 = 9479"}
{"Question": "TRUE + MENU = TRUST", "Answer": "1065 + 9576 = 10641"}
{"Question": "SELL + BAKE = SALES", "Answer": "1566 + 9085 = 10651"}
{"Question": "CODE + READ = RADIO", "Answer": "9275 + 1507 = 10782"}
{"Question": "MERE + TALL = MOTOR", "Answer": "1525 + 9377 = 10902"}
{"Question": "GENE + MAIN = MIGHT", "Answer": "9575 + 1407 = 10982"}
{"Question": "DATA + POLL = PILOT", "Answer": "9535 + 1288 = 10823"}
{"Question": "DATA + FLEE = DRESS", "Answer": "1545 + 9288 = 10833"}
{"Question": "SIDE + READ = START", "Answer": "1746 + 8634 = 10380"}
{"Question": "LINE + BEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "1356 + 9605 = 10961"}
{"Question": "LAWN + SNOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "1476 + 8607 = 10083"}
{"Question": "GENE + PAIN = PANEL", "Answer": "9676 + 1087 = 10763"}
{"Question": "PURE + TEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "1286 + 9608 = 10894"}
{"Question": "TELL + SHOE = SHEET", "Answer": "9722 + 1057 = 10779"}
{"Question": "BELL + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8755 + 1307 = 10062"}
{"Question": "GENE + BURN = GROUP", "Answer": "1757 + 8605 = 10362"}
{"Question": "DATA + BELL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8797 + 1366 = 10163"}
{"Question": "GENE + PLAN = PAPER", "Answer": "8767 + 1406 = 10173"}
{"Question": "DATA + HURT = DREAM", "Answer": "1767 + 8506 = 10273"}
{"Question": "FLEE + JAIL = FIELD", "Answer": "1766 + 8907 = 10673"}
{"Question": "PURE + NEAR = PANEL", "Answer": "1267 + 9706 = 10973"}
{"Question": "SELL + CODE = SOLID", "Answer": "1788 + 9057 = 10845"}
{"Question": "MESS + ROLE = MORAL", "Answer": "1877 + 9058 = 10935"}
{"Question": "GLAD + IDEA = IMAGE", "Answer": "8549 + 1934 = 10483"}
{"Question": "BALL + IDEA = BREAD", "Answer": "1955 + 8439 = 10394"}
{"Question": "YELL + WIPE = IMPLY", "Answer": "2755 + 8197 = 10952"}
{"Question": "DATA + COST = PIECE", "Answer": "7858 + 2465 = 10323"}
{"Question": "HERE + STAR = ASSET", "Answer": "9868 + 2416 = 12284"}
{"Question": "TELL + BASE = ASSET", "Answer": "7988 + 2109 = 10097"}
{"Question": "AUTO + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "8912 + 3271 = 12183"}
{"Question": "HERE + TALL = CATCH", "Answer": "7262 + 3055 = 10317"}
{"Question": "DATA + BELL = CABLE", "Answer": "3202 + 9755 = 12957"}
{"Question": "DATA + LEFT = METAL", "Answer": "9585 + 3268 = 12853"}
{"Question": "BELL + ROPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "9766 + 3817 = 13583"}
{"Question": "CITE + HEAT = MATCH", "Answer": "6758 + 3805 = 10563"}
{"Question": "HERE + STIR = ASSET", "Answer": "9878 + 3507 = 13385"}
{"Question": "RIDE + TEND = ENTER", "Answer": "9281 + 4138 = 13419"}
{"Question": "DATA + REST = LATER", "Answer": "4262 + 8376 = 12638"}
{"Question": "MALL + IDEA = THEME", "Answer": "4266 + 9582 = 13848"}
{"Question": "HERE + BILL = FIBER", "Answer": "6383 + 4055 = 10438"}
{"Question": "IDEA + SAFE = BASIS", "Answer": "4563 + 9386 = 13949"}
{"Question": "DATA + BELT = LABEL", "Answer": "9383 + 4018 = 13401"}
{"Question": "DATA + FREE = OFFER", "Answer": "9606 + 4822 = 14428"}
{"Question": "LOAD + IDEA = HELLO", "Answer": "9257 + 4735 = 13992"}
{"Question": "GENE + ROLL = INNER", "Answer": "4808 + 5277 = 10085"}
{"Question": "MASS + IDEA = ASIDE", "Answer": "5133 + 8741 = 13874"}
{"Question": "HERE + TALL = EARTH", "Answer": "5131 + 7244 = 12375"}
{"Question": "DATA + POET = AHEAD", "Answer": "8171 + 5247 = 13418"}
{"Question": "DATA + REST = EAGER", "Answer": "7232 + 5183 = 12415"}
{"Question": "GENE + IRON = ANGER", "Answer": "9242 + 5684 = 14926"}
{"Question": "DATA + REST = METER", "Answer": "5262 + 8376 = 13638"}
{"Question": "HERO + TOUR = ROUTE", "Answer": "5413 + 8371 = 13784"}
{"Question": "GENE + THIN = NIGHT", "Answer": "7414 + 5321 = 12735"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5717 + 8461 = 14178"}
{"Question": "DATA + LOSS = TOTAL", "Answer": "5919 + 6277 = 12196"}
{"Question": "ROLL + AUTO = ORDER", "Answer": "6155 + 9871 = 16026"}
{"Question": "MESS + NOTE = LEMON", "Answer": "6344 + 7283 = 13627"}
{"Question": "DATA + PLOT = TODAY", "Answer": "6414 + 7231 = 13645"}
{"Question": "FREE + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "6477 + 8104 = 14581"}
{"Question": "HERE + STIR = FIRST", "Answer": "6535 + 7843 = 14378"}
{"Question": "POLL + AUTO = STAFF", "Answer": "8577 + 6045 = 14622"}
{"Question": "MESS + ONCE = LEMON", "Answer": "9588 + 6375 = 15963"}
{"Question": "HERE + STAR = TRUTH", "Answer": "7252 + 8165 = 15417"}
{"Question": "DATA + HELL = CATCH", "Answer": "8595 + 7322 = 15917"}
{"Question": "KNEE + THAN = CHECK", "Answer": "7522 + 8695 = 16217"}
{"Question": "DATA + PORT = RAPID", "Answer": "8535 + 7213 = 15748"}
{"Question": "TELL + HIDE = FIFTH", "Answer": "7533 + 8645 = 16178"}
{"Question": "TELL + HOPE = DEPTH", "Answer": "7622 + 8956 = 16578"}
{"Question": "DATA + FREE = REFER", "Answer": "7696 + 8155 = 15851"}
{"Question": "GENE + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "8242 + 9674 = 17916"}
{"Question": "BELL + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "8255 + 9672 = 17927"}
{"Question": "HERO + COME = HUMOR", "Answer": "1275 + 9582 = 10857"}
{"Question": "HERO + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "4187 + 9731 = 13918"}
{"Question": "CODE + HERO = PORCH", "Answer": "4256 + 8692 = 12948"}
{"Question": "DATA + HERE = OTHER", "Answer": "5646 + 9282 = 14928"}
{"Question": "IDEA + SAND = TASTE", "Answer": "7286 + 9632 = 16918"}
{"Question": "DATA + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "7595 + 8323 = 15918"}
{"Question": "DATA + SHOE = SHEET", "Answer": "9252 + 1083 = 10335"}
{"Question": "SHOE + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "1523 + 9308 = 10831"}
{"Question": "HERE + BLOW = HOTEL", "Answer": "1434 + 9208 = 10642"}
{"Question": "MERE + SHOT = MONTH", "Answer": "1474 + 9208 = 10682"}
{"Question": "LINE + TEAM = LATIN", "Answer": "1435 + 9508 = 10943"}
{"Question": "DATA + CREW = DREAM", "Answer": "1585 + 9067 = 10652"}
{"Question": "DATA + CORE = DREAM", "Answer": "1656 + 9208 = 10864"}
{"Question": "ABLE + HERO = ALLOW", "Answer": "1307 + 8745 = 10052"}
{"Question": "LEAN + KNOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "1347 + 8706 = 10053"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HELP = ADAPT", "Answer": "1407 + 8756 = 10163"}
{"Question": "DATA + SHIP = STILL", "Answer": "8707 + 1526 = 10233"}
{"Question": "HERE + FILM = FLOOR", "Answer": "8727 + 1605 = 10332"}
{"Question": "DATA + SLOW = STILL", "Answer": "8707 + 1659 = 10366"}
{"Question": "RUSH + CHEF = REFER", "Answer": "1697 + 8704 = 10401"}
{"Question": "HERE + DOWN = HONOR", "Answer": "1757 + 9048 = 10805"}
{"Question": "GENE + STAR = START", "Answer": "9747 + 1083 = 10830"}
{"Question": "TRUE + NEWS = TRUST", "Answer": "1087 + 9754 = 10841"}
{"Question": "STAR + URGE = ASSET", "Answer": "2517 + 9768 = 12285"}
{"Question": "DATA + SELF = TASTE", "Answer": "3212 + 9705 = 12917"}
{"Question": "DATA + CHEF = PIECE", "Answer": "3292 + 7586 = 10878"}
{"Question": "COME + HEAT = MATCH", "Answer": "4512 + 9237 = 13749"}
{"Question": "TYPE + READ = PARTY", "Answer": "4712 + 9235 = 13947"}
{"Question": "GENE + DIRT = TIRED", "Answer": "8373 + 4261 = 12634"}
{"Question": "WHAT + STIR = IRISH", "Answer": "4269 + 8913 = 13182"}
{"Question": "LIFE + YEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "5621 + 8137 = 13758"}
{"Question": "NEAR + GROW = RANGE", "Answer": "8731 + 5126 = 13857"}
{"Question": "HERE + TOWN = ENTER", "Answer": "5141 + 8673 = 13814"}
{"Question": "ALSO + BOTH = TOTAL", "Answer": "5942 + 6217 = 12159"}
{"Question": "BEAT + STIR = ARISE", "Answer": "5612 + 9284 = 14896"}
{"Question": "IDEA + SALT = TASTE", "Answer": "5432 + 7281 = 12713"}
{"Question": "THEN + SNAP = PHASE", "Answer": "5432 + 9261 = 14693"}
{"Question": "GENE + DARK = NAKED", "Answer": "8616 + 5349 = 13965"}
{"Question": "BEAR + DRUG = GUARD", "Answer": "5637 + 8741 = 14378"}
{"Question": "HERE + CAST = EARTH", "Answer": "8151 + 6427 = 14578"}
{"Question": "HERO + BOAT = OTHER", "Answer": "8751 + 6124 = 14875"}
{"Question": "DIET + STAR = TRADE", "Answer": "8251 + 6134 = 14385"}
{"Question": "FILE + TEAM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6512 + 9247 = 15759"}
{"Question": "INTO + SOUP = POINT", "Answer": "6243 + 7381 = 13624"}
{"Question": "GENE + DROP = ORDER", "Answer": "6424 + 7319 = 13743"}
{"Question": "COME + REST = METER", "Answer": "7814 + 6432 = 14246"}
{"Question": "HERE + MOST = TERMS", "Answer": "6424 + 7851 = 14275"}
{"Question": "MERE + STAY = TERMS", "Answer": "8454 + 6132 = 14586"}
{"Question": "RISE + MEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "6254 + 8431 = 14685"}
{"Question": "GENE + RAIL = INNER", "Answer": "6545 + 7912 = 14457"}
{"Question": "TRUE + LEAF = FAULT", "Answer": "6835 + 7541 = 14376"}
{"Question": "TRIP + OPEN = PRIOR", "Answer": "7561 + 8124 = 15685"}
{"Question": "AUTO + CORE = REACT", "Answer": "7582 + 9216 = 16798"}
{"Question": "NOTE + LEAF = OFTEN", "Answer": "9153 + 7386 = 16539"}
{"Question": "LAST + ITEM = STILL", "Answer": "7315 + 8562 = 15877"}
{"Question": "GENE + STAR = BASIS", "Answer": "9232 + 8576 = 17808"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "1255 + 1255 = 2510"}
{"Question": "MASS + MASS = ALLY", "Answer": "1277 + 1277 = 2554"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = AREA", "Answer": "1366 + 1366 = 2732"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLL = ARAB", "Answer": "1566 + 1566 = 3132"}
{"Question": "FREE + FREE = LEFT", "Answer": "1755 + 1755 = 3510"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLEE = DEAD", "Answer": "2377 + 2377 = 4754"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = ALLY", "Answer": "2499 + 2499 = 4998"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALL = CASH", "Answer": "2966 + 2966 = 5932"}
{"Question": "LESS + LESS = SALE", "Answer": "3266 + 3266 = 6532"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = LEAD", "Answer": "3577 + 3577 = 7154"}
{"Question": "LESS + LESS = SLIP", "Answer": "3677 + 3677 = 7354"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = ALSO", "Answer": "3755 + 3755 = 7510"}
{"Question": "CELL + CELL = EACH", "Answer": "3766 + 3766 = 7532"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = LOOK", "Answer": "4388 + 4388 = 8776"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KNEE = EVEN", "Answer": "4899 + 4899 = 9798"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TOSS = WASTE", "Answer": "5377 + 5377 = 10754"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELL = EARTH", "Answer": "6188 + 6188 = 12376"}
{"Question": "FREE + FREE = DRESS", "Answer": "6244 + 6244 = 12488"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = CARRY", "Answer": "6277 + 6277 = 12554"}
{"Question": "CALL + CALL = BASIC", "Answer": "6288 + 6288 = 12576"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = DAILY", "Answer": "6299 + 6299 = 12598"}
{"Question": "FALL + FALL = PROOF", "Answer": "6388 + 6388 = 12776"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOSS = CLIMB", "Answer": "6488 + 6488 = 12976"}
{"Question": "BILL + BILL = AGAIN", "Answer": "6577 + 6577 = 13154"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KNEE = DRINK", "Answer": "6788 + 6788 = 13576"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = ANGLE", "Answer": "6899 + 6899 = 13798"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILL = BRIEF", "Answer": "6988 + 6988 = 13976"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLL = ADAPT", "Answer": "7088 + 7088 = 14176"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = DOUBT", "Answer": "7288 + 7288 = 14576"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = CLASS", "Answer": "7344 + 7344 = 14688"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = URBAN", "Answer": "7366 + 7366 = 14732"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = CATCH", "Answer": "7455 + 7455 = 14910"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = MAYBE", "Answer": "7488 + 7488 = 14976"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = HELLO", "Answer": "7499 + 7499 = 14998"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOSS = ASIAN", "Answer": "7655 + 7655 = 15310"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = CABLE", "Answer": "7899 + 7899 = 15798"}
{"Question": "KISS + KISS = ASIAN", "Answer": "7955 + 7955 = 15910"}
{"Question": "BILL + BILL = TRIBE", "Answer": "7988 + 7988 = 15976"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALL = ADULT", "Answer": "8199 + 8199 = 16398"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = ALIVE", "Answer": "8266 + 8266 = 16532"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = CLEAN", "Answer": "8366 + 8366 = 16732"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KNEE = CHEEK", "Answer": "8499 + 8499 = 16998"}
{"Question": "MASS + MASS = USUAL", "Answer": "8577 + 8577 = 17154"}
{"Question": "FREE + FREE = BRIEF", "Answer": "8799 + 8799 = 17598"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = CLAIM", "Answer": "8977 + 8977 = 17954"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = ALIVE", "Answer": "9188 + 9188 = 18376"}
{"Question": "BALL + BALL = FLOOR", "Answer": "9388 + 9388 = 18776"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = ALBUM", "Answer": "9488 + 9488 = 18976"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELL = ABOVE", "Answer": "9688 + 9688 = 19376"}
{"Question": "CALL + CALL = OCEAN", "Answer": "9788 + 9788 = 19576"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLL = SPLIT", "Answer": "9877 + 9877 = 19754"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = ELSE", "Answer": "1255 + 1257 = 2512"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOST = STOP", "Answer": "1633 + 1632 = 3265"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = ARAB", "Answer": "1866 + 1865 = 3731"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = POLL", "Answer": "1955 + 1956 = 3911"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = EAST", "Answer": "1988 + 1983 = 3971"}
{"Question": "PASS + PAST = TAPE", "Answer": "2011 + 2014 = 4025"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = TALE", "Answer": "2399 + 2394 = 4793"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = EVER", "Answer": "2677 + 2675 = 5352"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = NINE", "Answer": "2677 + 2679 = 5356"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = TEAM", "Answer": "2944 + 2948 = 5892"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOST = TALL", "Answer": "3566 + 3567 = 7133"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = PIPE", "Answer": "3588 + 3587 = 7175"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = BEER", "Answer": "3611 + 3612 = 7223"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = ODDS", "Answer": "3722 + 3720 = 7442"}
{"Question": "MASS + MASK = SEEM", "Answer": "4388 + 4386 = 8774"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = TREE", "Answer": "4788 + 4789 = 9577"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "5066 + 5069 = 10135"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "5211 + 5210 = 10421"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "5266 + 5260 = 10526"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = WASTE", "Answer": "5288 + 5284 = 10572"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = CABLE", "Answer": "5299 + 5293 = 10592"}
{"Question": "PASS + PAST = STATE", "Answer": "6011 + 6012 = 12023"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = LEVEL", "Answer": "6211 + 6210 = 12421"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6211 + 6214 = 12425"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALF = SALES", "Answer": "6244 + 6247 = 12491"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = EARTH", "Answer": "6288 + 6281 = 12569"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = FAULT", "Answer": "6299 + 6297 = 12596"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = TASTE", "Answer": "6355 + 6358 = 12713"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILM = LEVEL", "Answer": "6411 + 6410 = 12821"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = SEVEN", "Answer": "6411 + 6412 = 12823"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = LIMIT", "Answer": "6411 + 6415 = 12826"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = ONION", "Answer": "6455 + 6457 = 12912"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = CLOSE", "Answer": "6533 + 6532 = 13065"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALF = LIMIT", "Answer": "6711 + 6719 = 13430"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = AGREE", "Answer": "6788 + 6789 = 13577"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = AHEAD", "Answer": "6955 + 6957 = 13912"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = ONION", "Answer": "6955 + 6958 = 13913"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = DRESS", "Answer": "6977 + 6978 = 13955"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLE = ADAPT", "Answer": "7088 + 7085 = 14173"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = ALBUM", "Answer": "7144 + 7143 = 14287"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = ERROR", "Answer": "7233 + 7231 = 14464"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7244 + 7241 = 14485"}
{"Question": "WILL + WILD = ALLOW", "Answer": "7244 + 7243 = 14487"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = ASSET", "Answer": "7244 + 7249 = 14493"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = PLATE", "Answer": "7344 + 7349 = 14693"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = TASTE", "Answer": "7355 + 7358 = 14713"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7422 + 7420 = 14842"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = FEWER", "Answer": "7422 + 7421 = 14843"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = HONOR", "Answer": "7422 + 7425 = 14847"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = PANEL", "Answer": "7455 + 7450 = 14905"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = CATCH", "Answer": "7455 + 7458 = 14913"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALF = FAITH", "Answer": "7466 + 7461 = 14927"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = REFER", "Answer": "7522 + 7529 = 15051"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOST = TOTAL", "Answer": "7566 + 7561 = 15127"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = PLACE", "Answer": "7655 + 7651 = 15306"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = CLIMB", "Answer": "7655 + 7652 = 15307"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = ASIAN", "Answer": "7655 + 7659 = 15314"}
{"Question": "MASS + MASK = LEVEL", "Answer": "7822 + 7829 = 15651"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLE = REPLY", "Answer": "7899 + 7895 = 15794"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLE = CLOCK", "Answer": "7955 + 7958 = 15913"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = PIECE", "Answer": "7988 + 7981 = 15969"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = ELECT", "Answer": "8066 + 8061 = 16127"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILM = IMPLY", "Answer": "8199 + 8196 = 16395"}
{"Question": "PASS + PAST = STEAL", "Answer": "8211 + 8216 = 16427"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = LABOR", "Answer": "8211 + 8217 = 16428"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = APPLY", "Answer": "8344 + 8345 = 16689"}
{"Question": "WALL + WALK = FEWER", "Answer": "8433 + 8432 = 16865"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = HELLO", "Answer": "8499 + 8496 = 16995"}
{"Question": "MASS + MASK = CIVIL", "Answer": "8533 + 8539 = 17072"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = PAPER", "Answer": "8566 + 8562 = 17128"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = BIBLE", "Answer": "8599 + 8596 = 17195"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOST = STEEL", "Answer": "8611 + 8617 = 17228"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = STYLE", "Answer": "8699 + 8697 = 17396"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8755 + 8753 = 17508"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = HOTEL", "Answer": "8766 + 8762 = 17528"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALE = LEAST", "Answer": "9011 + 9018 = 18029"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = DRAMA", "Answer": "9044 + 9046 = 18090"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALF = FEWER", "Answer": "9344 + 9341 = 18685"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9388 + 9387 = 18775"}
{"Question": "BELL + BELT = LOOSE", "Answer": "9411 + 9413 = 18824"}
{"Question": "MALL + MALE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9422 + 9421 = 18843"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOST = ERROR", "Answer": "9422 + 9426 = 18848"}
{"Question": "FILL + FILM = ERROR", "Answer": "9433 + 9435 = 18868"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = INNER", "Answer": "9433 + 9436 = 18869"}
{"Question": "TALL + TALK = ENTER", "Answer": "9455 + 9457 = 18912"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9611 + 9612 = 19223"}
{"Question": "SELL + SELF = ASIAN", "Answer": "9655 + 9657 = 19312"}
{"Question": "HALL + HALF = THREE", "Answer": "9677 + 9678 = 19355"}
{"Question": "POLL + POLE = SPEED", "Answer": "9722 + 9724 = 19446"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = PRIOR", "Answer": "9844 + 9845 = 19689"}
{"Question": "HELL + HELP = SHAPE", "Answer": "9866 + 9862 = 19728"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROLE = DRESS", "Answer": "9866 + 9867 = 19733"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = ELSE", "Answer": "1366 + 1326 = 2692"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = PLOT", "Answer": "1588 + 1568 = 3156"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = SHOT", "Answer": "1933 + 1963 = 3896"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = BOMB", "Answer": "2077 + 2017 = 4094"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = REST", "Answer": "2511 + 2591 = 5102"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = TALL", "Answer": "2866 + 2856 = 5722"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = LIFE", "Answer": "4288 + 4258 = 8546"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = LESS", "Answer": "4388 + 4378 = 8766"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = SELF", "Answer": "4522 + 4502 = 9024"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = USER", "Answer": "4688 + 4698 = 9386"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = HELLO", "Answer": "5244 + 5204 = 10448"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = MOTOR", "Answer": "5266 + 5236 = 10502"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = DRESS", "Answer": "5388 + 5378 = 10766"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = BUYER", "Answer": "5422 + 5402 = 10824"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = APART", "Answer": "6033 + 6073 = 12106"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = APPLE", "Answer": "6144 + 6104 = 12248"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = SEIZE", "Answer": "6311 + 6391 = 12702"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = VISIT", "Answer": "6377 + 6347 = 12724"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = SENSE", "Answer": "6411 + 6401 = 12812"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6411 + 6421 = 12832"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = STUFF", "Answer": "6488 + 6478 = 12966"}
{"Question": "TALL + TAIL = FLOAT", "Answer": "6533 + 6523 = 13056"}
{"Question": "TALL + TAIL = PLANT", "Answer": "6933 + 6973 = 13906"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = STAFF", "Answer": "6988 + 6978 = 13966"}
{"Question": "MALL + MAIL = BLAME", "Answer": "7044 + 7034 = 14078"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "7422 + 7402 = 14824"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = CROSS", "Answer": "7466 + 7456 = 14922"}
{"Question": "TALL + TAIL = FAITH", "Answer": "7566 + 7506 = 15072"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = PIECE", "Answer": "7833 + 7863 = 15696"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = PRIOR", "Answer": "8233 + 8293 = 16526"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = SHEET", "Answer": "8244 + 8204 = 16448"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = ASSET", "Answer": "8344 + 8304 = 16648"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = ASSET", "Answer": "8366 + 8326 = 16692"}
{"Question": "MALL + MAIL = CLIMB", "Answer": "8577 + 8507 = 17084"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = COURT", "Answer": "8644 + 8624 = 17268"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = KNIFE", "Answer": "8655 + 8625 = 17280"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = SORRY", "Answer": "8711 + 8731 = 17442"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOTS = MOTOR", "Answer": "8733 + 8743 = 17476"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = GUESS", "Answer": "8766 + 8756 = 17522"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = ONION", "Answer": "9244 + 9274 = 18518"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = UNION", "Answer": "9344 + 9314 = 18658"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIL = ONION", "Answer": "9344 + 9374 = 18718"}
{"Question": "FULL + FUEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "9411 + 9421 = 18832"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "9422 + 9402 = 18824"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRUE = STUFF", "Answer": "9766 + 9756 = 19522"}
{"Question": "KILL + KISS = SLIP", "Answer": "3255 + 3266 = 6521"}
{"Question": "MALL + MASS = LOOK", "Answer": "3266 + 3288 = 6554"}
{"Question": "KILL + KISS = SLOW", "Answer": "4377 + 4388 = 8765"}
{"Question": "KISS + KILL = SENSE", "Answer": "5311 + 5399 = 10710"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOST = METAL", "Answer": "5378 + 5387 = 10765"}
{"Question": "KILL + KISS = PILOT", "Answer": "6255 + 6288 = 12543"}
{"Question": "SING + SIGN = FENCE", "Answer": "6758 + 6785 = 13543"}
{"Question": "SIGN + SING = TIGHT", "Answer": "8756 + 8765 = 17521"}
{"Question": "POLL + POEM = LESS", "Answer": "1322 + 1378 = 2700"}
{"Question": "CALL + CARE = REAL", "Answer": "1522 + 1530 = 3052"}
{"Question": "PANT + PATH = THAT", "Answer": "1523 + 1530 = 3053"}
{"Question": "MASS + MAKE = SEEM", "Answer": "1933 + 1948 = 3881"}
{"Question": "POSE + POEM = SOME", "Answer": "1937 + 1970 = 3907"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEAT = EASE", "Answer": "2433 + 2491 = 4924"}
{"Question": "MASS + MAKE = SEEK", "Answer": "2655 + 2683 = 5338"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KNOW = WEEK", "Answer": "2877 + 2895 = 5772"}
{"Question": "POSE + POEM = MESS", "Answer": "3459 + 3496 = 6955"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = LATE", "Answer": "3577 + 3508 = 7085"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAD = MALE", "Answer": "3611 + 3625 = 7236"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEAT = ELSE", "Answer": "3755 + 3782 = 7537"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "3811 + 3867 = 7678"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAT = TELL", "Answer": "4133 + 4178 = 8311"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HERO = AREA", "Answer": "4183 + 4135 = 8318"}
{"Question": "MESS + MEAN = NAME", "Answer": "4788 + 4759 = 9547"}
{"Question": "YELL + YEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "5133 + 5102 = 10235"}
{"Question": "HELL + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "5177 + 5108 = 10285"}
{"Question": "BORN + BOND = ORDER", "Answer": "5108 + 5182 = 10290"}
{"Question": "TEAR + TERM = PARTY", "Answer": "5204 + 5249 = 10453"}
{"Question": "BALL + BAKE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5311 + 5390 = 10701"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = MAYBE", "Answer": "5344 + 5309 = 10653"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIR = TRIAL", "Answer": "5366 + 5370 = 10736"}
{"Question": "FALL + FADE = ORDER", "Answer": "5366 + 5374 = 10740"}
{"Question": "POSE + POET = STATE", "Answer": "5319 + 5390 = 10709"}
{"Question": "FILL + FIVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "5411 + 5490 = 10901"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAD = STATE", "Answer": "5411 + 5493 = 10904"}
{"Question": "YELL + YEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "5477 + 5408 = 10885"}
{"Question": "FAIR + FARM = IRAQI", "Answer": "6012 + 6029 = 12041"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAD = BIBLE", "Answer": "6077 + 6083 = 12160"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROAD = OCCUR", "Answer": "6177 + 6109 = 12286"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TOUR = SOUTH", "Answer": "6211 + 6249 = 12460"}
{"Question": "FILL + FIVE = RIVER", "Answer": "6233 + 6248 = 12481"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAST = CATCH", "Answer": "6244 + 6275 = 12519"}
{"Question": "KNEE + KNOW = ONION", "Answer": "6299 + 6213 = 12512"}
{"Question": "FREE + FROM = PROOF", "Answer": "6299 + 6257 = 12556"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "6311 + 6320 = 12631"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "6355 + 6328 = 12683"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAG = SHALL", "Answer": "6355 + 6378 = 12733"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BONE = SHELL", "Answer": "6411 + 6489 = 12900"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = ALTER", "Answer": "6422 + 6418 = 12840"}
{"Question": "CALL + CARE = FEWER", "Answer": "6455 + 6472 = 12927"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "6522 + 6530 = 13052"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "6577 + 6508 = 13085"}
{"Question": "MALL + MAIN = ENEMY", "Answer": "6577 + 6583 = 13160"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = AWARE", "Answer": "6588 + 6517 = 13105"}
{"Question": "MASS + MALE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6711 + 6734 = 13445"}
{"Question": "PASS + PALM = SLEEP", "Answer": "6711 + 6735 = 13446"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "6722 + 6735 = 13457"}
{"Question": "WALL + WAIT = ELITE", "Answer": "6733 + 6748 = 13481"}
{"Question": "TALK + TAKE = METAL", "Answer": "6807 + 6873 = 13680"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEND = DANCE", "Answer": "6837 + 6871 = 13708"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEFT = TASTE", "Answer": "6877 + 6841 = 13718"}
{"Question": "FACT + FATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "6857 + 6871 = 13728"}
{"Question": "BILL + BITE = LEAST", "Answer": "6911 + 6943 = 13854"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROPE = LATER", "Answer": "6911 + 6945 = 13856"}
{"Question": "HALL + HATE = LIGHT", "Answer": "6911 + 6954 = 13865"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAD = BADLY", "Answer": "6922 + 6938 = 13860"}
{"Question": "MALL + MATH = THEME", "Answer": "6955 + 6913 = 13868"}
{"Question": "PASS + PART = TROOP", "Answer": "6955 + 6931 = 13886"}
{"Question": "BILL + BITE = QUIET", "Answer": "6955 + 6972 = 13927"}
{"Question": "CALL + CAKE = BLACK", "Answer": "7044 + 7028 = 14072"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HERO = EARTH", "Answer": "7142 + 7125 = 14267"}
{"Question": "TOWN + TONE = OWNER", "Answer": "7142 + 7126 = 14268"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7133 + 7142 = 14275"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAG = LEAVE", "Answer": "7144 + 7120 = 14264"}
{"Question": "FREE + FROM = OCCUR", "Answer": "7233 + 7219 = 14452"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEST = ISSUE", "Answer": "7233 + 7249 = 14482"}
{"Question": "MEAN + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "7253 + 7239 = 14492"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = ALLOW", "Answer": "7244 + 7219 = 14463"}
{"Question": "FAIR + FARM = ERROR", "Answer": "7254 + 7240 = 14494"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TOUR = ASSET", "Answer": "7244 + 7253 = 14497"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROPE = ALTER", "Answer": "7244 + 7293 = 14537"}
{"Question": "FREE + FROM = LOOSE", "Answer": "7255 + 7240 = 14495"}
{"Question": "POLL + POSE = ESSAY", "Answer": "7255 + 7241 = 14496"}
{"Question": "BALL + BACK = OCCUR", "Answer": "7255 + 7243 = 14498"}
{"Question": "BILL + BIKE = EAGER", "Answer": "7288 + 7231 = 14519"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "7288 + 7254 = 14542"}
{"Question": "MESS + MENU = SUPER", "Answer": "7311 + 7324 = 14635"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = LARGE", "Answer": "7311 + 7342 = 14653"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOSE = STEAL", "Answer": "7341 + 7316 = 14657"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOTH = SHEET", "Answer": "7311 + 7354 = 14665"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAD = SCALE", "Answer": "7311 + 7362 = 14673"}
{"Question": "BALL + BASE = SLEEP", "Answer": "7344 + 7316 = 14660"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOAT = LABEL", "Answer": "7355 + 7346 = 14701"}
{"Question": "WILL + WIRE = FEWER", "Answer": "7355 + 7394 = 14749"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROAD = AGREE", "Answer": "7388 + 7312 = 14700"}
{"Question": "HALL + HANG = LAUGH", "Answer": "7411 + 7456 = 14867"}
{"Question": "MASS + MALE = SALES", "Answer": "7411 + 7490 = 14901"}
{"Question": "PASS + PAGE = EAGER", "Answer": "7422 + 7491 = 14913"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAF = REFER", "Answer": "7433 + 7408 = 14841"}
{"Question": "MESS + MEAL = LEAVE", "Answer": "7433 + 7491 = 14924"}
{"Question": "CALL + CARE = EAGER", "Answer": "7455 + 7461 = 14916"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BONE = DOZEN", "Answer": "7455 + 7483 = 14938"}
{"Question": "TREE + TRIP = WRITE", "Answer": "7488 + 7490 = 14978"}
{"Question": "MESS + MENU = SENSE", "Answer": "7511 + 7504 = 15015"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "7518 + 7589 = 15107"}
{"Question": "MESS + MEAL = SLAVE", "Answer": "7611 + 7625 = 15236"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEFT = STATE", "Answer": "7611 + 7645 = 15256"}
{"Question": "HELL + HEAD = LABEL", "Answer": "7611 + 7650 = 15261"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = LATER", "Answer": "7611 + 7652 = 15263"}
{"Question": "LAST + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "7642 + 7625 = 15267"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOVE = WHEEL", "Answer": "7644 + 7693 = 15337"}
{"Question": "FREE + FROM = METER", "Answer": "7655 + 7601 = 15256"}
{"Question": "LAST + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "7615 + 7652 = 15267"}
{"Question": "HELL + HERO = FLOOR", "Answer": "7655 + 7683 = 15338"}
{"Question": "FILL + FIRE = ALTER", "Answer": "7655 + 7694 = 15349"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7811 + 7846 = 15657"}
{"Question": "PASS + PALE = SLEEP", "Answer": "7811 + 7856 = 15667"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOWL = HELLO", "Answer": "7822 + 7846 = 15668"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAT = WATER", "Answer": "7833 + 7856 = 15689"}
{"Question": "POLL + POST = SLEEP", "Answer": "7855 + 7812 = 15667"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAG = REFER", "Answer": "7855 + 7896 = 15751"}
{"Question": "BALL + BASE = SOLAR", "Answer": "7866 + 7814 = 15680"}
{"Question": "BALL + BACK = CLIMB", "Answer": "7955 + 7912 = 15867"}
{"Question": "MASS + MAKE = LEGAL", "Answer": "7966 + 7925 = 15891"}
{"Question": "CALL + CARD = DRAMA", "Answer": "7988 + 7951 = 15939"}
{"Question": "BILL + BITE = ELECT", "Answer": "8066 + 8071 = 16137"}
{"Question": "TALK + TAKE = ELECT", "Answer": "8067 + 8071 = 16138"}
{"Question": "POLL + PORT = OTHER", "Answer": "8144 + 8106 = 16250"}
{"Question": "WILD + WIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8196 + 8163 = 16359"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAG = LEVEL", "Answer": "8166 + 8195 = 16361"}
{"Question": "PASS + PAIR = SERVE", "Answer": "8211 + 8295 = 16506"}
{"Question": "HALL + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "8277 + 8204 = 16481"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROPE = EAGER", "Answer": "8277 + 8241 = 16518"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEAT = LOOSE", "Answer": "8311 + 8372 = 16683"}
{"Question": "FALL + FAIR = ONION", "Answer": "8344 + 8372 = 16716"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BONE = ASSET", "Answer": "8366 + 8329 = 16695"}
{"Question": "TELL + TERM = LATER", "Answer": "8411 + 8432 = 16843"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAM = PLANT", "Answer": "8466 + 8492 = 16958"}
{"Question": "POLE + POEM = SMELL", "Answer": "8459 + 8496 = 16955"}
{"Question": "TAIL + TALK = ELITE", "Answer": "8507 + 8574 = 17081"}
{"Question": "MASS + MALE = LEGAL", "Answer": "8644 + 8617 = 17261"}
{"Question": "CALL + CARE = ORDER", "Answer": "8655 + 8672 = 17327"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "8677 + 8619 = 17296"}
{"Question": "COLD + CODE = HELLO", "Answer": "8639 + 8697 = 17336"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAR = LEARN", "Answer": "8711 + 8745 = 17456"}
{"Question": "WALL + WANT = LATIN", "Answer": "8711 + 8754 = 17465"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEFT = REFER", "Answer": "8722 + 8749 = 17471"}
{"Question": "TOWN + TONE = MONTH", "Answer": "8734 + 8746 = 17480"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FLAG = CLASS", "Answer": "8744 + 8756 = 17500"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEND = SENSE", "Answer": "8765 + 8752 = 17517"}
{"Question": "MASS + MAIL = TASTE", "Answer": "8755 + 8764 = 17519"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROCK = SOLAR", "Answer": "8755 + 8793 = 17548"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LOVE = HELLO", "Answer": "8922 + 8967 = 17889"}
{"Question": "TELL + TERM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8933 + 8941 = 17874"}
{"Question": "HELL + HERO = OTHER", "Answer": "8944 + 8951 = 17895"}
{"Question": "BILL + BIND = ONION", "Answer": "8944 + 8973 = 17917"}
{"Question": "FALL + FARM = DRAMA", "Answer": "8966 + 8973 = 17939"}
{"Question": "CALL + CAST = STATE", "Answer": "9066 + 9018 = 18084"}
{"Question": "COLD + CODE = ORDER", "Answer": "9142 + 9126 = 18268"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAM = ELITE", "Answer": "9188 + 9103 = 18291"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "9244 + 9285 = 18529"}
{"Question": "MASK + MAKE = TERMS", "Answer": "9235 + 9258 = 18493"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "9288 + 9254 = 18542"}
{"Question": "PAIR + PART = TROOP", "Answer": "9278 + 9281 = 18559"}
{"Question": "FILL + FIRE = EAGER", "Answer": "9355 + 9361 = 18716"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEND = FALSE", "Answer": "9366 + 9327 = 18693"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROCK = CLASS", "Answer": "9388 + 9312 = 18700"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BOND = ASIAN", "Answer": "9388 + 9324 = 18712"}
{"Question": "HELL + HERO = CLOCK", "Answer": "9388 + 9327 = 18715"}
{"Question": "BELL + BEND = SLIDE", "Answer": "9388 + 9365 = 18753"}
{"Question": "HELL + HERO = INNER", "Answer": "9433 + 9407 = 18840"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "9433 + 9416 = 18849"}
{"Question": "SELL + SEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9433 + 9481 = 18914"}
{"Question": "HILL + HIRE = OTHER", "Answer": "9455 + 9472 = 18927"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "9522 + 9513 = 19035"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOSE = ELECT", "Answer": "9576 + 9561 = 19137"}
{"Question": "HELL + HEAD = SHADE", "Answer": "9577 + 9508 = 19085"}
{"Question": "WELL + WEAK = AWARE", "Answer": "9588 + 9517 = 19105"}
{"Question": "HELL + HEAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "9644 + 9638 = 19282"}
{"Question": "LACK + LAKE = CLEAN", "Answer": "9615 + 9652 = 19267"}
{"Question": "LESS + LEAF = FLAME", "Answer": "9655 + 9621 = 19276"}
{"Question": "FILL + FINE = OFTEN", "Answer": "9655 + 9672 = 19327"}
{"Question": "HALL + HATE = SHEET", "Answer": "9655 + 9683 = 19338"}
{"Question": "HALL + HATE = SHOOT", "Answer": "9677 + 9658 = 19335"}
{"Question": "HILL + HIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9766 + 9704 = 19470"}
{"Question": "POLL + POSE = SPEED", "Answer": "9844 + 9816 = 19660"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ROAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "9866 + 9871 = 19737"}
{"Question": "TELL + TEAR = START", "Answer": "9866 + 9873 = 19739"}
{"Question": "MASS + MESS = ALLY", "Answer": "1288 + 1488 = 2776"}
{"Question": "PULL + POLL = UPON", "Answer": "1388 + 1788 = 3176"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = LEAF", "Answer": "2166 + 2466 = 4632"}
{"Question": "MESS + MISS = ITEM", "Answer": "2366 + 2466 = 4832"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LESS = COOL", "Answer": "2366 + 2966 = 5332"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = ROOF", "Answer": "2566 + 2766 = 5332"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = ELSE", "Answer": "3188 + 3688 = 6876"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSS = SHOE", "Answer": "3477 + 3577 = 7054"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FREE = LEFT", "Answer": "3766 + 3866 = 7632"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = SELF", "Answer": "4177 + 4577 = 8754"}
{"Question": "HILL + HELL = EIGHT", "Answer": "5077 + 5177 = 10254"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSS = HELLO", "Answer": "5077 + 5477 = 10554"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = EARTH", "Answer": "5088 + 5188 = 10276"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = DELAY", "Answer": "5088 + 5788 = 10876"}
{"Question": "MASS + MESS = ARMED", "Answer": "5166 + 5366 = 10532"}
{"Question": "CELL + CALL = BASIC", "Answer": "6088 + 6288 = 12376"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = SHELF", "Answer": "6088 + 6788 = 12876"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALL = EXTRA", "Answer": "6177 + 6477 = 12654"}
{"Question": "HELL + HALL = EARTH", "Answer": "6188 + 6288 = 12476"}
{"Question": "HELL + HILL = EARTH", "Answer": "6188 + 6388 = 12576"}
{"Question": "TALL + TELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "6188 + 6988 = 13176"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = FALSE", "Answer": "6277 + 6477 = 12754"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = PROOF", "Answer": "6288 + 6488 = 12776"}
{"Question": "WELL + WALL = BELOW", "Answer": "6288 + 6588 = 12876"}
{"Question": "FILL + FALL = BIBLE", "Answer": "6399 + 6799 = 13198"}
{"Question": "BALL + BILL = MEDIA", "Answer": "6477 + 6577 = 13054"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOSS = WHEEL", "Answer": "6788 + 6988 = 13776"}
{"Question": "BILL + BELL = CABLE", "Answer": "6799 + 6899 = 13698"}
{"Question": "MESS + MASS = TASTE", "Answer": "7055 + 7455 = 14510"}
{"Question": "MESS + MASS = ENEMY", "Answer": "7188 + 7988 = 15176"}
{"Question": "BELL + BILL = AWARE", "Answer": "7266 + 7866 = 15132"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "7488 + 7688 = 15176"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = MAYBE", "Answer": "7588 + 7688 = 15276"}
{"Question": "MASS + MESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "7688 + 7988 = 15676"}
{"Question": "BALL + BILL = PILOT", "Answer": "8077 + 8677 = 16754"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = ALIVE", "Answer": "8166 + 8266 = 16432"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = ALTER", "Answer": "8166 + 8366 = 16532"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = ALLOW", "Answer": "8166 + 8466 = 16632"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = ELECT", "Answer": "8177 + 8977 = 17154"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = CLOSE", "Answer": "8266 + 8466 = 16732"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELL = MEDIA", "Answer": "8266 + 8766 = 17032"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = PAPER", "Answer": "8366 + 8766 = 17132"}
{"Question": "FREE + FLEE = AWFUL", "Answer": "8377 + 8477 = 16854"}
{"Question": "CELL + CALL = BASIS", "Answer": "8466 + 8766 = 17232"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = CARRY", "Answer": "8566 + 8766 = 17332"}
{"Question": "BELL + BALL = SLEEP", "Answer": "8577 + 8977 = 17554"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LESS = ASSET", "Answer": "9088 + 9788 = 18876"}
{"Question": "MISS + MESS = ISSUE", "Answer": "9188 + 9688 = 18876"}
{"Question": "TALL + TELL = ALTER", "Answer": "9188 + 9788 = 18976"}
{"Question": "PASS + POST = STOP", "Answer": "1422 + 1529 = 2951"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LAST = TOOL", "Answer": "1788 + 1983 = 3771"}
{"Question": "HELL + HALF = FLEE", "Answer": "4577 + 4178 = 8755"}
{"Question": "TREE + THEM = SHEET", "Answer": "5899 + 5096 = 10995"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELT = ALTER", "Answer": "6122 + 6425 = 12547"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALK = ENTER", "Answer": "6155 + 6458 = 12613"}
{"Question": "FALL + FILM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6511 + 6217 = 12728"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = WASTE", "Answer": "6588 + 6287 = 12875"}
{"Question": "HILL + HELP = PLACE", "Answer": "6522 + 6321 = 12843"}
{"Question": "HILL + HALF = FIFTH", "Answer": "6355 + 6751 = 13106"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BASE = TOOTH", "Answer": "6355 + 6957 = 13312"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LIST = TITLE", "Answer": "6788 + 6381 = 13169"}
{"Question": "TREE + THEM = AHEAD", "Answer": "7055 + 7458 = 14513"}
{"Question": "MALL + MILK = ALBUM", "Answer": "7144 + 7543 = 14687"}
{"Question": "TREE + THEM = HEART", "Answer": "7844 + 7143 = 14987"}
{"Question": "MASS + MOST = ASIAN", "Answer": "7155 + 7859 = 15014"}
{"Question": "HELL + HALF = LABEL", "Answer": "7211 + 7410 = 14621"}
{"Question": "TELL + TALK = METAL", "Answer": "7466 + 7260 = 14726"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "7866 + 7261 = 15127"}
{"Question": "CELL + COLD = LOCAL", "Answer": "7311 + 7410 = 14721"}
{"Question": "BILL + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "7322 + 7624 = 14946"}
{"Question": "BILL + BELT = CIVIL", "Answer": "7422 + 7520 = 14942"}
{"Question": "HELL + HALF = FEWER", "Answer": "7422 + 7521 = 14943"}
{"Question": "MESS + MASK = LEVEL", "Answer": "7522 + 7829 = 15351"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LIST = BIBLE", "Answer": "7633 + 7539 = 15172"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = METAL", "Answer": "7544 + 7843 = 15387"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "8511 + 8217 = 16728"}
{"Question": "CALL + COLD = LOCAL", "Answer": "8211 + 8610 = 16821"}
{"Question": "PASS + POSE = ESSAY", "Answer": "8266 + 8361 = 16627"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELT = METAL", "Answer": "8266 + 8760 = 17026"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RELY = HELLO", "Answer": "8299 + 8693 = 16992"}
{"Question": "SELL + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "8311 + 8619 = 16930"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = TITLE", "Answer": "8544 + 8641 = 17185"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = TABLE", "Answer": "8544 + 8741 = 17285"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BEST = HELLO", "Answer": "8566 + 8769 = 17335"}
{"Question": "FALL + FOLK = COLOR", "Answer": "8633 + 8739 = 17372"}
{"Question": "LESS + LAST = STEEL", "Answer": "9211 + 9018 = 18229"}
{"Question": "MESS + MUST = ISSUE", "Answer": "9088 + 9782 = 18870"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RULE = OFFER", "Answer": "9133 + 9736 = 18869"}
{"Question": "HALL + HOLY = AHEAD", "Answer": "9155 + 9857 = 19012"}
{"Question": "BALL + BELT = AGREE", "Answer": "9166 + 9367 = 18533"}
{"Question": "FALL + FILE = AFTER", "Answer": "9177 + 9875 = 19052"}
{"Question": "FALL + FILM = AFTER", "Answer": "9177 + 9876 = 19053"}
{"Question": "PASS + POSE = ASSET", "Answer": "9188 + 9687 = 18875"}
{"Question": "MESS + MASK = SMOKE", "Answer": "9311 + 9712 = 19023"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOTS = TOOL", "Answer": "2011 + 2541 = 4552"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FATE = THAT", "Answer": "3188 + 3568 = 6756"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FACE = CELL", "Answer": "3477 + 3267 = 6744"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FADE = DEAD", "Answer": "3288 + 3568 = 6856"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FATE = LEFT", "Answer": "3711 + 3421 = 7132"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THIS = FORTH", "Answer": "5066 + 5286 = 10352"}
{"Question": "TREE + TALE = ALTER", "Answer": "5422 + 5102 = 10524"}
{"Question": "ROLL + REAL = EARLY", "Answer": "5433 + 5103 = 10536"}
{"Question": "TREE + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "5211 + 5301 = 10512"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAIL = ASSET", "Answer": "6033 + 6173 = 12206"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RAIL = SOLAR", "Answer": "6233 + 6073 = 12306"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RAIL = FLOOR", "Answer": "6033 + 6973 = 13006"}
{"Question": "TREE + TYPE = REPLY", "Answer": "6122 + 6452 = 12574"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAIL = ELECT", "Answer": "6133 + 6973 = 13106"}
{"Question": "CELL + COAL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6211 + 6571 = 12782"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "6788 + 6318 = 13106"}
{"Question": "FREE + FIVE = EVERY", "Answer": "6411 + 6731 = 13142"}
{"Question": "ROLL + REAL = ALTER", "Answer": "6833 + 6413 = 13246"}
{"Question": "CELL + COAL = ELECT", "Answer": "7144 + 7034 = 14178"}
{"Question": "BALL + BOWL = ALLOW", "Answer": "7144 + 7284 = 14428"}
{"Question": "FREE + FACE = EAGER", "Answer": "7211 + 7401 = 14612"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THUS = SOUTH", "Answer": "7411 + 7261 = 14672"}
{"Question": "TELL + TAIL = LARGE", "Answer": "7211 + 7481 = 14692"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOTS = BIBLE", "Answer": "7266 + 7906 = 15172"}
{"Question": "ROLL + REAL = PEACE", "Answer": "7322 + 7482 = 14804"}
{"Question": "FREE + FACE = ORDER", "Answer": "7422 + 7502 = 14924"}
{"Question": "TREE + TAPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "7422 + 7512 = 14934"}
{"Question": "PASS + PLUS = RURAL", "Answer": "7488 + 7658 = 15146"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THUS = MOUTH", "Answer": "7544 + 7834 = 15378"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FIVE = VITAL", "Answer": "7688 + 7518 = 15206"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THUS = COUCH", "Answer": "7588 + 7628 = 15216"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THUS = OUGHT", "Answer": "8144 + 8064 = 16208"}
{"Question": "ROLL + REAL = THREE", "Answer": "8755 + 8045 = 16800"}
{"Question": "TREE + TYPE = EMPTY", "Answer": "8511 + 8271 = 16782"}
{"Question": "TREE + TAKE = METER", "Answer": "8266 + 8596 = 16862"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOTS = TITLE", "Answer": "8266 + 8916 = 17182"}
{"Question": "CELL + COAL = PLACE", "Answer": "8477 + 8607 = 17084"}
{"Question": "CELL + COAL = SLICE", "Answer": "8477 + 8907 = 17384"}
{"Question": "FREE + FACE = EVERY", "Answer": "8511 + 8641 = 17152"}
{"Question": "FALL + FUEL = VALUE", "Answer": "8766 + 8926 = 17692"}
{"Question": "TOSS + THIS = PRIOR", "Answer": "9044 + 9564 = 18608"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FADE = IDEAL", "Answer": "9055 + 9485 = 18540"}
{"Question": "ROLL + REAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "9088 + 9718 = 18806"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RAIL = ONION", "Answer": "9144 + 9574 = 18718"}
{"Question": "TREE + TAKE = EXTRA", "Answer": "9711 + 9261 = 18972"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOTS = TABLE", "Answer": "9477 + 9217 = 18694"}
{"Question": "TREE + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "9388 + 9568 = 18956"}
{"Question": "FALL + FREE = SALES", "Answer": "5099 + 5822 = 10921"}
{"Question": "FREE + FALL = TREAT", "Answer": "5033 + 5288 = 10321"}
{"Question": "BILL + BOSS = PILOT", "Answer": "5044 + 5388 = 10432"}
{"Question": "TREE + TALL = GREAT", "Answer": "5077 + 5688 = 10765"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TELL = WASTE", "Answer": "5388 + 5466 = 10854"}
{"Question": "FREE + FALL = REFER", "Answer": "6122 + 6499 = 12621"}
{"Question": "TONE + THEN = MONTH", "Answer": "6287 + 6578 = 12865"}
{"Question": "FREE + FALL = SOLAR", "Answer": "6355 + 6488 = 12843"}
{"Question": "BALL + BOSS = COLOR", "Answer": "7055 + 7488 = 14543"}
{"Question": "FREE + FILL = RIVER", "Answer": "7122 + 7499 = 14621"}
{"Question": "WHEN + WINE = HONOR", "Answer": "7158 + 7685 = 14843"}
{"Question": "FREE + FILL = CLEAR", "Answer": "7288 + 7544 = 14832"}
{"Question": "MALL + MESS = ALIVE", "Answer": "8166 + 8377 = 16543"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8219 + 8691 = 16910"}
{"Question": "MESS + MALL = FALSE", "Answer": "8233 + 8699 = 16932"}
{"Question": "TALL + TREE = METER", "Answer": "8299 + 8566 = 16865"}
{"Question": "DATE + DIET = MEDIA", "Answer": "8376 + 8467 = 16843"}
{"Question": "POLL + PINE = OPEN", "Answer": "1355 + 1794 = 3149"}
{"Question": "SELL + SHIT = THESE", "Answer": "5433 + 5021 = 10454"}
{"Question": "HALL + HURT = EARTH", "Answer": "5033 + 5892 = 10925"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "5166 + 5074 = 10240"}
{"Question": "TALL + THEM = CATCH", "Answer": "5088 + 5426 = 10514"}
{"Question": "SPOT + SITE = PRESS", "Answer": "5186 + 5769 = 10955"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HURT = EARTH", "Answer": "5107 + 5678 = 10785"}
{"Question": "HOLD + HIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "5138 + 5682 = 10820"}
{"Question": "PASS + PORT = TROOP", "Answer": "6055 + 6721 = 12776"}
{"Question": "TELL + TASK = ASSET", "Answer": "6077 + 6129 = 12206"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FISH = SHELL", "Answer": "6088 + 6712 = 12800"}
{"Question": "MALL + MODE = ARMED", "Answer": "6155 + 6483 = 12638"}
{"Question": "PASS + PLOT = USUAL", "Answer": "6233 + 6895 = 13128"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FAST = USUAL", "Answer": "6255 + 6937 = 13192"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LINE = NOVEL", "Answer": "6277 + 6319 = 12596"}
{"Question": "SURE + STEP = GUESS", "Answer": "6287 + 6479 = 12766"}
{"Question": "SHOE + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "6287 + 6571 = 12858"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LEFT = TITLE", "Answer": "6277 + 6891 = 13168"}
{"Question": "LEFT + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "6791 + 6315 = 13106"}
{"Question": "LOST + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "6371 + 6815 = 13186"}
{"Question": "DARE + DIET = TIRED", "Answer": "6705 + 6351 = 13056"}
{"Question": "PALE + POET = TOTAL", "Answer": "6798 + 6381 = 13179"}
{"Question": "FOUR + FARM = RURAL", "Answer": "6731 + 6418 = 13149"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RING = AGAIN", "Answer": "6422 + 6753 = 13175"}
{"Question": "CELL + CITY = ELECT", "Answer": "7144 + 7028 = 14172"}
{"Question": "PASS + POET = TASTE", "Answer": "7455 + 7061 = 14516"}
{"Question": "PASS + POET = WASTE", "Answer": "7455 + 7083 = 14538"}
{"Question": "FREE + FACT = ACTOR", "Answer": "7088 + 7142 = 14230"}
{"Question": "CELL + CROP = OFFER", "Answer": "7088 + 7315 = 14403"}
{"Question": "URGE + USED = GRASS", "Answer": "7418 + 7082 = 14500"}
{"Question": "BELL + BOAT = AGREE", "Answer": "7088 + 7512 = 14600"}
{"Question": "ROLL + READ = AGREE", "Answer": "7688 + 7012 = 14700"}
{"Question": "BILL + BONE = INNER", "Answer": "7122 + 7346 = 14468"}
{"Question": "TREE + TWIN = WRITE", "Answer": "7422 + 7150 = 14572"}
{"Question": "TALL + TERM = EARTH", "Answer": "7422 + 7156 = 14578"}
{"Question": "HELL + HAIR = EARTH", "Answer": "7122 + 7465 = 14587"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BORN = ERROR", "Answer": "7184 + 7240 = 14424"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "7244 + 7193 = 14437"}
{"Question": "SHOE + STEP = THESE", "Answer": "7425 + 7150 = 14575"}
{"Question": "HAIR + HERO = EARTH", "Answer": "7435 + 7152 = 14587"}
{"Question": "CALL + CORE = ALTER", "Answer": "7155 + 7894 = 15049"}
{"Question": "HELL + HARD = EARTH", "Answer": "7188 + 7469 = 14657"}
{"Question": "TREE + THAN = ENTER", "Answer": "7511 + 7204 = 14715"}
{"Question": "BILL + BEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "7211 + 7540 = 14751"}
{"Question": "BELL + BOAT = LABOR", "Answer": "7211 + 7548 = 14759"}
{"Question": "TYPE + THEN = ENTRY", "Answer": "7581 + 7214 = 14795"}
{"Question": "TRUE + THEM = METER", "Answer": "7504 + 7241 = 14745"}
{"Question": "BELL + BODY = CYCLE", "Answer": "7944 + 7205 = 15149"}
{"Question": "LESS + LADY = CYCLE", "Answer": "7944 + 7235 = 15179"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BLUE = USUAL", "Answer": "7255 + 7914 = 15169"}
{"Question": "TALL + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "7322 + 7856 = 15178"}
{"Question": "TELL + TRIP = APART", "Answer": "7322 + 7865 = 15187"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FISH = SHELF", "Answer": "7322 + 7915 = 15237"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GIRL = LARGE", "Answer": "7352 + 7921 = 15273"}
{"Question": "CASE + CHEF = SHELL", "Answer": "7318 + 7482 = 14800"}
{"Question": "MISS + MEAL = SALES", "Answer": "7411 + 7650 = 15061"}
{"Question": "LESS + LOAD = SHADE", "Answer": "7411 + 7823 = 15234"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TEAM = WASTE", "Answer": "7422 + 7856 = 15278"}
{"Question": "LESS + LACK = USUAL", "Answer": "7655 + 7492 = 15147"}
{"Question": "BANK + BIKE = NAKED", "Answer": "7514 + 7946 = 15460"}
{"Question": "FULL + FACE = GUESS", "Answer": "7566 + 7834 = 15400"}
{"Question": "PULL + PAGE = GUESS", "Answer": "7588 + 7612 = 15200"}
{"Question": "TELL + THIS = ASSET", "Answer": "7622 + 7945 = 15567"}
{"Question": "TOSS + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "7955 + 7612 = 15567"}
{"Question": "RAIL + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "8691 + 8017 = 16708"}
{"Question": "MISS + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "8166 + 8529 = 16695"}
{"Question": "TALL + TERM = ALTER", "Answer": "8166 + 8704 = 16870"}
{"Question": "TELL + THIN = ELITE", "Answer": "8177 + 8904 = 17081"}
{"Question": "WELL + WORD = LOWER", "Answer": "8211 + 8609 = 16820"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FIRM = REFER", "Answer": "8651 + 8210 = 16861"}
{"Question": "MISS + MALE = SALES", "Answer": "8211 + 8690 = 16901"}
{"Question": "BOSS + BELT = STATE", "Answer": "8211 + 8756 = 16967"}
{"Question": "PLUS + PAST = USUAL", "Answer": "8217 + 8975 = 17192"}
{"Question": "MESS + MATH = TASTE", "Answer": "8299 + 8613 = 16912"}
{"Question": "MESS + MAIL = SALES", "Answer": "8311 + 8720 = 17031"}
{"Question": "SELL + SHOW = WHOLE", "Answer": "8322 + 8701 = 17023"}
{"Question": "FLEE + FAST = STEAL", "Answer": "8922 + 8317 = 17239"}
{"Question": "TRIP + TAPE = PAPER", "Answer": "8421 + 8713 = 17134"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8733 + 8415 = 17148"}
{"Question": "LESS + LIFT = TITLE", "Answer": "8433 + 8751 = 17184"}
{"Question": "MISS + MEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "8755 + 8439 = 17194"}
{"Question": "BALL + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "8622 + 8753 = 17375"}
{"Question": "SELL + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "8644 + 8951 = 17595"}
{"Question": "SELL + SHOT = THOSE", "Answer": "8655 + 8731 = 17386"}
{"Question": "SELF + SOFT = LOOSE", "Answer": "9017 + 9873 = 18890"}
{"Question": "HALL + HERO = ERROR", "Answer": "9655 + 9183 = 18838"}
{"Question": "FALL + FIRE = AFTER", "Answer": "9155 + 9872 = 19027"}
{"Question": "TAKE + THEN = AGENT", "Answer": "9176 + 9463 = 18639"}
{"Question": "LOSS + LEFT = ELITE", "Answer": "9877 + 9164 = 19041"}
{"Question": "BILL + BOAT = RATIO", "Answer": "9455 + 9287 = 18742"}
{"Question": "ROLL + READ = THREE", "Answer": "9677 + 9245 = 18922"}
{"Question": "TREE + TASK = STEAL", "Answer": "9833 + 9517 = 19350"}
{"Question": "ROLL + RATE = TREAT", "Answer": "9766 + 9815 = 19581"}
{"Question": "CELL + BELL = CAUSE", "Answer": "1266 + 9266 = 10532"}
{"Question": "CALL + BALL = ARAB", "Answer": "1366 + 2366 = 3732"}
{"Question": "BALL + CALL = BREAD", "Answer": "1366 + 9366 = 10732"}
{"Question": "BALL + CALL = BELOW", "Answer": "1377 + 9377 = 10754"}
{"Question": "WELL + SELL = WASTE", "Answer": "1477 + 9477 = 10954"}
{"Question": "BOSS + TOSS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1566 + 8566 = 10132"}
{"Question": "HALL + BALL = THAT", "Answer": "1577 + 2577 = 4154"}
{"Question": "CELL + SELL = CROSS", "Answer": "1644 + 8644 = 10288"}
{"Question": "BELL + SELL = LOSE", "Answer": "2477 + 5477 = 7954"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELL = ENTER", "Answer": "3155 + 9155 = 12310"}
{"Question": "CELL + BELL = FENCE", "Answer": "3266 + 9266 = 12532"}
{"Question": "SELL + BELL = ISSUE", "Answer": "3688 + 9688 = 13376"}
{"Question": "FREE + TREE = REST", "Answer": "3877 + 4877 = 8754"}
{"Question": "ROLL + POLL = OCCUR", "Answer": "4177 + 9177 = 13354"}
{"Question": "FREE + TREE = PROOF", "Answer": "4277 + 8277 = 12554"}
{"Question": "TREE + FREE = LEFT", "Answer": "4377 + 5377 = 9754"}
{"Question": "ROLL + POLL = SOLAR", "Answer": "4377 + 9377 = 13754"}
{"Question": "TREE + FREE = APART", "Answer": "4577 + 8577 = 13154"}
{"Question": "POLL + ROLL = NERVE", "Answer": "4866 + 7866 = 12732"}
{"Question": "BELL + CELL = EXACT", "Answer": "5188 + 7188 = 12376"}
{"Question": "TALL + CALL = MATCH", "Answer": "5288 + 7288 = 12576"}
{"Question": "MESS + LESS = APPLE", "Answer": "5688 + 7688 = 13376"}
{"Question": "LOSS + TOSS = PILOT", "Answer": "5788 + 6788 = 12576"}
{"Question": "LOSS + BOSS = ALLOW", "Answer": "5788 + 9788 = 15576"}
{"Question": "MESS + LESS = COLOR", "Answer": "5866 + 7866 = 13732"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BOSS = WASTE", "Answer": "5877 + 6877 = 12754"}
{"Question": "BALL + TALL = CATCH", "Answer": "6355 + 7355 = 13710"}
{"Question": "TREE + FREE = START", "Answer": "6788 + 9788 = 16576"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELL = ALTER", "Answer": "7366 + 9366 = 16732"}
{"Question": "CELL + BELL = ALBUM", "Answer": "7466 + 9466 = 16932"}
{"Question": "TELL + BELL = STATE", "Answer": "7688 + 9688 = 17376"}
{"Question": "MASS + EAST = SEEM", "Answer": "4055 + 1059 = 5114"}
{"Question": "CALL + HALF = CROSS", "Answer": "1266 + 9267 = 10533"}
{"Question": "TALL + HALF = TIGHT", "Answer": "1344 + 9347 = 10691"}
{"Question": "HELL + RELY = HONOR", "Answer": "1355 + 9354 = 10709"}
{"Question": "CELL + BELT = CATCH", "Answer": "1355 + 9357 = 10712"}
{"Question": "TELL + HELP = TASTE", "Answer": "1355 + 9358 = 10713"}
{"Question": "POLL + COLD = PRIOR", "Answer": "1366 + 9364 = 10730"}
{"Question": "LESS + DESK = LABEL", "Answer": "1366 + 9365 = 10731"}
{"Question": "SELL + BELT = SOLVE", "Answer": "1377 + 9376 = 10753"}
{"Question": "BILL + FILE = BASIS", "Answer": "1422 + 9426 = 10848"}
{"Question": "MALL + TALE = METAL", "Answer": "1477 + 9470 = 10947"}
{"Question": "MASS + EAST = ERROR", "Answer": "8544 + 1546 = 10090"}
{"Question": "POLL + ROLE = PAPER", "Answer": "1566 + 8562 = 10128"}
{"Question": "MESS + BEST = BIBLE", "Answer": "8566 + 1569 = 10135"}
{"Question": "BELL + HELP = BIBLE", "Answer": "1599 + 8596 = 10195"}
{"Question": "LESS + WEST = WASTE", "Answer": "8622 + 1624 = 10246"}
{"Question": "BALL + MALE = BREAD", "Answer": "1633 + 8632 = 10265"}
{"Question": "MESS + REST = MOTOR", "Answer": "1655 + 8653 = 10308"}
{"Question": "MISS + LIST = ITEM", "Answer": "1688 + 4683 = 6371"}
{"Question": "CELL + HELP = CABLE", "Answer": "1699 + 8697 = 10396"}
{"Question": "BALL + SALT = STEEL", "Answer": "8722 + 1720 = 10442"}
{"Question": "PASS + FAST = PROOF", "Answer": "1722 + 8726 = 10448"}
{"Question": "ROLL + COLD = RADIO", "Answer": "1733 + 8734 = 10467"}
{"Question": "LOSS + HOST = HELLO", "Answer": "8944 + 1945 = 10889"}
{"Question": "LESS + BEST = LABEL", "Answer": "1944 + 8947 = 10891"}
{"Question": "CELL + BELT = CHECK", "Answer": "1955 + 8957 = 10912"}
{"Question": "BILL + FILE = BRIEF", "Answer": "1966 + 8962 = 10928"}
{"Question": "BALL + SALE = STAFF", "Answer": "8966 + 1967 = 10933"}
{"Question": "BILL + PILE = BRIEF", "Answer": "1977 + 8975 = 10952"}
{"Question": "BALL + HALF = BOARD", "Answer": "1977 + 8976 = 10953"}
{"Question": "LOSS + NOSE = SHELF", "Answer": "2311 + 8316 = 10627"}
{"Question": "HELL + BELT = CATCH", "Answer": "2355 + 8357 = 10712"}
{"Question": "SELL + BELT = LOOSE", "Answer": "2511 + 7514 = 10025"}
{"Question": "TELL + RELY = START", "Answer": "2544 + 9548 = 12092"}
{"Question": "MASS + EAST = STATE", "Answer": "9011 + 3012 = 12023"}
{"Question": "TELL + HELP = ENTER", "Answer": "3155 + 7159 = 10314"}
{"Question": "TOSS + POSE = STEP", "Answer": "3188 + 5187 = 8375"}
{"Question": "HALL + SALE = FRESH", "Answer": "3288 + 7285 = 10573"}
{"Question": "BELL + SELF = ELSE", "Answer": "3877 + 4871 = 8748"}
{"Question": "HALL + MALE = COACH", "Answer": "3955 + 6958 = 10913"}
{"Question": "BOSS + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "4077 + 6079 = 10156"}
{"Question": "BELL + HELP = LABEL", "Answer": "4211 + 9210 = 13421"}
{"Question": "YELL + HELP = REPLY", "Answer": "4299 + 8295 = 12594"}
{"Question": "LESS + BEST = TABLE", "Answer": "4322 + 6321 = 10643"}
{"Question": "CELL + HELP = SPACE", "Answer": "4522 + 8523 = 13045"}
{"Question": "HALL + MALE = TOOTH", "Answer": "4655 + 8659 = 13314"}
{"Question": "FULL + RULE = OFFER", "Answer": "4733 + 9736 = 14469"}
{"Question": "BELL + SELF = FALSE", "Answer": "5877 + 4871 = 10748"}
{"Question": "LOSS + POSE = REPLY", "Answer": "4922 + 8923 = 13845"}
{"Question": "BALL + TALE = ASSET", "Answer": "5166 + 8162 = 13328"}
{"Question": "BELL + RELY = LAYER", "Answer": "8211 + 5214 = 13425"}
{"Question": "YELL + BELT = STYLE", "Answer": "5299 + 8293 = 13592"}
{"Question": "FREE + CREW = BRIEF", "Answer": "5399 + 8396 = 13795"}
{"Question": "PULL + RULE = SUPER", "Answer": "9488 + 5487 = 14975"}
{"Question": "PASS + EAST = METER", "Answer": "9677 + 5673 = 15350"}
{"Question": "BALL + PALE = SLEEP", "Answer": "5722 + 6724 = 12446"}
{"Question": "TALL + MALE = LIMIT", "Answer": "5811 + 6814 = 12625"}
{"Question": "FULL + RULE = ALTER", "Answer": "5922 + 6924 = 12846"}
{"Question": "TREE + CREW = REACT", "Answer": "7133 + 6134 = 13267"}
{"Question": "POLL + HOLE = DEPTH", "Answer": "6344 + 9345 = 15689"}
{"Question": "BALL + TALE = CATCH", "Answer": "6355 + 7359 = 13714"}
{"Question": "CELL + HELP = PATCH", "Answer": "6388 + 9381 = 15769"}
{"Question": "BALL + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "6411 + 8412 = 14823"}
{"Question": "LESS + REST = SERVE", "Answer": "6411 + 8413 = 14824"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ROSE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8411 + 6415 = 14826"}
{"Question": "MASS + CASH = THEME", "Answer": "6433 + 9435 = 15868"}
{"Question": "TELL + RELY = ALTER", "Answer": "6844 + 7843 = 14687"}
{"Question": "ROLL + COLD = ERROR", "Answer": "6844 + 9842 = 16686"}
{"Question": "TELL + SELF = ASSET", "Answer": "9844 + 6845 = 16689"}
{"Question": "BOSS + LOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "6944 + 8945 = 15889"}
{"Question": "SELL + HELP = TASTE", "Answer": "7355 + 9358 = 16713"}
{"Question": "MASS + VAST = LEVEL", "Answer": "7422 + 8429 = 15851"}
{"Question": "SELL + BELT = ISSUE", "Answer": "7855 + 9853 = 17708"}
{"Question": "CELL + DEAL = CAUSE", "Answer": "1266 + 9206 = 10472"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CLUE = CIVIL", "Answer": "9266 + 1236 = 10502"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEAL = BASIS", "Answer": "1277 + 9207 = 10484"}
{"Question": "POLL + SOIL = PRIOR", "Answer": "1355 + 9375 = 10730"}
{"Question": "CALL + FAIL = COLOR", "Answer": "1377 + 9327 = 10704"}
{"Question": "PULL + FUEL = FALSE", "Answer": "9377 + 1347 = 10724"}
{"Question": "FLEE + BLUE = FIELD", "Answer": "1377 + 9357 = 10734"}
{"Question": "TELL + REAL = THREE", "Answer": "1477 + 9467 = 10944"}
{"Question": "KNEE + ONCE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8566 + 1506 = 10072"}
{"Question": "KISS + AIDS = AWARD", "Answer": "8577 + 1547 = 10124"}
{"Question": "POLL + BOWL = BELOW", "Answer": "8622 + 1642 = 10264"}
{"Question": "SELL + DEAL = ELSE", "Answer": "1633 + 4683 = 6316"}
{"Question": "CELL + DEAL = CHASE", "Answer": "1633 + 8623 = 10256"}
{"Question": "SELL + DEAL = SOLVE", "Answer": "1633 + 8693 = 10326"}
{"Question": "YELL + DEAL = DAILY", "Answer": "8644 + 1604 = 10248"}
{"Question": "MISS + AIDS = MEDIA", "Answer": "1644 + 8624 = 10268"}
{"Question": "HALL + TAIL = TRUTH", "Answer": "8644 + 1674 = 10318"}
{"Question": "PULL + FUEL = PROOF", "Answer": "1644 + 8694 = 10338"}
{"Question": "POLL + COAL = PEACE", "Answer": "1655 + 8625 = 10280"}
{"Question": "KNEE + ONCE = ORDER", "Answer": "8655 + 1695 = 10350"}
{"Question": "PULL + FUEL = PHOTO", "Answer": "1722 + 8732 = 10454"}
{"Question": "PULL + FUEL = PIECE", "Answer": "1722 + 8742 = 10464"}
{"Question": "BILL + GIRL = BASIS", "Answer": "1722 + 8752 = 10474"}
{"Question": "POLL + COAL = PIECE", "Answer": "1722 + 8762 = 10484"}
{"Question": "FLEE + BLUE = FAULT", "Answer": "1733 + 8743 = 10476"}
{"Question": "FALL + RAIL = FEWER", "Answer": "1744 + 8764 = 10508"}
{"Question": "POLL + SOIL = KISS", "Answer": "1766 + 2756 = 4522"}
{"Question": "BILL + GIRL = BRAIN", "Answer": "1766 + 8706 = 10472"}
{"Question": "BALL + RAIL = BIRTH", "Answer": "1966 + 8906 = 10872"}
{"Question": "LESS + NEWS = WELL", "Answer": "4977 + 1967 = 6944"}
{"Question": "CELL + REAL = CARRY", "Answer": "1977 + 8907 = 10884"}
{"Question": "PULL + FUEL = PAUSE", "Answer": "1977 + 8947 = 10924"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = EARLY", "Answer": "8133 + 2103 = 10236"}
{"Question": "TELL + REAL = ENTRY", "Answer": "2133 + 8153 = 10286"}
{"Question": "YELL + REAL = EARLY", "Answer": "8144 + 2104 = 10248"}
{"Question": "TELL + REAL = EARTH", "Answer": "8177 + 2107 = 10284"}
{"Question": "TREE + URGE = EIGHT", "Answer": "2311 + 8361 = 10672"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BOWL = LABOR", "Answer": "2411 + 8431 = 10842"}
{"Question": "TELL + MEAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "2811 + 7891 = 10702"}
{"Question": "BALL + FAIL = ALBUM", "Answer": "3122 + 9182 = 12304"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = EARTH", "Answer": "9177 + 3127 = 12304"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = THREE", "Answer": "3477 + 9467 = 12944"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = PAPER", "Answer": "8077 + 4027 = 12104"}
{"Question": "YELL + DEAL = EARLY", "Answer": "6133 + 4103 = 10236"}
{"Question": "LESS + NEWS = SENSE", "Answer": "8211 + 4201 = 12412"}
{"Question": "TREE + URGE = ENTER", "Answer": "4211 + 9201 = 13412"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BOWL = WORRY", "Answer": "4233 + 8213 = 12446"}
{"Question": "HALL + FAIL = CATCH", "Answer": "4277 + 8237 = 12514"}
{"Question": "MISS + AIDS = DRAMA", "Answer": "9277 + 4217 = 13494"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BOWL = FEWER", "Answer": "4277 + 9257 = 13534"}
{"Question": "YELL + DEAL = ALLY", "Answer": "4377 + 5397 = 9774"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BOWL = COLOR", "Answer": "4377 + 9357 = 13734"}
{"Question": "SELL + DEAL = ASSET", "Answer": "4755 + 9715 = 14470"}
{"Question": "SELL + DEAL = TASTE", "Answer": "5266 + 9246 = 14512"}
{"Question": "TELL + DEAL = LATER", "Answer": "8411 + 5431 = 13842"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = LEARN", "Answer": "5411 + 9481 = 14892"}
{"Question": "TELL + DEAL = ALTER", "Answer": "8433 + 5413 = 13846"}
{"Question": "CELL + DEAL = PLACE", "Answer": "5633 + 7623 = 13256"}
{"Question": "ROLL + GOAL = EAGER", "Answer": "6788 + 5728 = 12516"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = INNER", "Answer": "9288 + 6238 = 15526"}
{"Question": "BELL + MEAL = ALBUM", "Answer": "6344 + 8314 = 14658"}
{"Question": "HILL + GIRL = RIGHT", "Answer": "7355 + 6315 = 13670"}
{"Question": "HALL + TAIL = CATCH", "Answer": "6388 + 7328 = 13716"}
{"Question": "WELL + REAL = FEWER", "Answer": "7388 + 6348 = 13736"}
{"Question": "HILL + GIRL = LIGHT", "Answer": "6411 + 8451 = 14862"}
{"Question": "BALL + FAIL = CLIMB", "Answer": "6433 + 7493 = 13926"}
{"Question": "TELL + REAL = WATER", "Answer": "9488 + 6458 = 15946"}
{"Question": "TELL + MEAL = ADAPT", "Answer": "6588 + 7518 = 14106"}
{"Question": "TELL + REAL = START", "Answer": "6588 + 9508 = 16096"}
{"Question": "TREE + URGE = METER", "Answer": "6844 + 7804 = 14648"}
{"Question": "YELL + REAL = CARRY", "Answer": "6933 + 8953 = 15886"}
{"Question": "KISS + AIDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "9366 + 7306 = 16672"}
{"Question": "CALL + FAIL = SLICE", "Answer": "7566 + 8506 = 16072"}
{"Question": "FREE + URGE = GROUP", "Answer": "8655 + 7615 = 16270"}
{"Question": "BELL + REAL = EAGER", "Answer": "9144 + 8174 = 17318"}
{"Question": "DIET + SITE = DRESS", "Answer": "1245 + 9254 = 10499"}
{"Question": "MESS + HELL = SHOE", "Answer": "1388 + 7355 = 8743"}
{"Question": "BILL + KISS = BASIC", "Answer": "1355 + 9377 = 10732"}
{"Question": "TOSS + POLL = STOP", "Answer": "1566 + 4588 = 6154"}
{"Question": "BELL + MESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1566 + 8599 = 10165"}
{"Question": "SIGN + KING = SENSE", "Answer": "1673 + 8637 = 10310"}
{"Question": "CELL + MESS = CABLE", "Answer": "1677 + 8699 = 10376"}
{"Question": "TOSS + ROLL = PILOT", "Answer": "2355 + 8377 = 10732"}
{"Question": "WELL + MESS = BELOW", "Answer": "3255 + 9288 = 12543"}
{"Question": "TELL + MESS = WASTE", "Answer": "4366 + 8377 = 12743"}
{"Question": "TALL + MASS = FAULT", "Answer": "5366 + 8399 = 13765"}
{"Question": "BELL + FEAR = FALSE", "Answer": "9244 + 1208 = 10452"}
{"Question": "BURN + FUND = FENCE", "Answer": "9234 + 1246 = 10480"}
{"Question": "ROLL + SOFT = REFER", "Answer": "1244 + 9257 = 10501"}
{"Question": "SELL + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "1244 + 9258 = 10502"}
{"Question": "KILL + CITE = CHECK", "Answer": "9244 + 1275 = 10519"}
{"Question": "BALL + DATE = BREAD", "Answer": "1244 + 9285 = 10529"}
{"Question": "TOSS + MORE = TERMS", "Answer": "1255 + 9240 = 10495"}
{"Question": "TOSS + CORE = TREAT", "Answer": "1277 + 9204 = 10481"}
{"Question": "TELL + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "1277 + 9245 = 10522"}
{"Question": "LESS + GEAR = LARGE", "Answer": "1288 + 9204 = 10492"}
{"Question": "BALL + CAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "1288 + 9235 = 10523"}
{"Question": "SELL + BEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "1288 + 9254 = 10542"}
{"Question": "POLL + COAT = PEACE", "Answer": "1322 + 9368 = 10690"}
{"Question": "TALL + BAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "1344 + 9387 = 10731"}
{"Question": "TOSS + POEM = THEME", "Answer": "1355 + 9372 = 10727"}
{"Question": "TELL + VERY = THREE", "Answer": "1355 + 9378 = 10733"}
{"Question": "SELL + VERY = SOLVE", "Answer": "1366 + 9327 = 10693"}
{"Question": "SURE + FUEL = SHELF", "Answer": "1357 + 9372 = 10729"}
{"Question": "MISS + NICE = MUSIC", "Answer": "1377 + 9358 = 10735"}
{"Question": "BILL + SIDE = SALES", "Answer": "9377 + 1364 = 10741"}
{"Question": "BOSS + LOAD = BADLY", "Answer": "1388 + 9306 = 10694"}
{"Question": "BALL + MAIN = BEING", "Answer": "1388 + 9376 = 10764"}
{"Question": "FOUR + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "1462 + 9428 = 10890"}
{"Question": "TALL + CARE = TREAT", "Answer": "1433 + 9408 = 10841"}
{"Question": "TALL + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1433 + 9458 = 10891"}
{"Question": "BALL + FAIR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1455 + 9408 = 10863"}
{"Question": "CELL + BEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "1477 + 9408 = 10885"}
{"Question": "SELL + FEAR = FALSE", "Answer": "9488 + 1406 = 10894"}
{"Question": "TELL + SEND = TASTE", "Answer": "1488 + 9426 = 10914"}
{"Question": "LEAN + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "1562 + 8523 = 10085"}
{"Question": "ALSO + BLOW = ASSET", "Answer": "1503 + 8539 = 10042"}
{"Question": "FULL + AUTO = ASSET", "Answer": "8533 + 1529 = 10062"}
{"Question": "BALL + EAST = ESSAY", "Answer": "8544 + 1509 = 10053"}
{"Question": "DRAG + URGE = UPPER", "Answer": "8526 + 1569 = 10095"}
{"Question": "FALL + HAND = FIFTH", "Answer": "1566 + 8572 = 10138"}
{"Question": "MESS + BEAN = BIBLE", "Answer": "8566 + 1579 = 10145"}
{"Question": "TREE + ARMY = APART", "Answer": "8566 + 1592 = 10158"}
{"Question": "MASS + TALE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8566 + 1593 = 10159"}
{"Question": "BILL + DISH = BASIS", "Answer": "1633 + 8629 = 10262"}
{"Question": "CALL + RAIN = COLOR", "Answer": "1633 + 8675 = 10308"}
{"Question": "MESS + DEAL = DRAMA", "Answer": "8655 + 1627 = 10282"}
{"Question": "TELL + DESK = TASTE", "Answer": "1677 + 8639 = 10316"}
{"Question": "FREE + CROP = COLOR", "Answer": "8699 + 1607 = 10306"}
{"Question": "FREE + CROP = FLOOR", "Answer": "1699 + 8637 = 10336"}
{"Question": "FULL + SUCH = FOCUS", "Answer": "1733 + 8745 = 10478"}
{"Question": "LESS + TEND = TASTE", "Answer": "8755 + 1762 = 10517"}
{"Question": "LESS + DEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "1766 + 8705 = 10471"}
{"Question": "SURE + FUEL = SALES", "Answer": "1796 + 8765 = 10561"}
{"Question": "LOAN + BONE = LABEL", "Answer": "1905 + 8956 = 10861"}
{"Question": "BALL + RAIN = BIRTH", "Answer": "1955 + 8907 = 10862"}
{"Question": "BILL + SIGN = BEING", "Answer": "1955 + 8972 = 10927"}
{"Question": "TALL + EARN = TREND", "Answer": "1966 + 8907 = 10873"}
{"Question": "TALL + EARN = AFTER", "Answer": "2144 + 8139 = 10283"}
{"Question": "MALL + CARE = ARMED", "Answer": "2166 + 8107 = 10273"}
{"Question": "ROLL + POEM = ERROR", "Answer": "2644 + 9618 = 12262"}
{"Question": "BILL + TIME = ITEM", "Answer": "2655 + 3694 = 6349"}
{"Question": "YEAR + TERM = MARRY", "Answer": "7806 + 2861 = 10667"}
{"Question": "HILL + DIET = FIFTH", "Answer": "3088 + 7065 = 10153"}
{"Question": "BALL + CAMP = ALBUM", "Answer": "3122 + 9186 = 12308"}
{"Question": "BALL + MAIN = ALBUM", "Answer": "3122 + 9187 = 12309"}
{"Question": "BELL + YEAR = EARLY", "Answer": "3155 + 7102 = 10257"}
{"Question": "FROM + ARMY = REFER", "Answer": "3145 + 7156 = 10301"}
{"Question": "MALL + FADE = ARMED", "Answer": "3155 + 7194 = 10349"}
{"Question": "ROLL + HOST = OTHER", "Answer": "9177 + 3182 = 12359"}
{"Question": "DOWN + BONE = ORDER", "Answer": "3158 + 9184 = 12342"}
{"Question": "BELL + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "3255 + 9241 = 12496"}
{"Question": "SURE + FUEL = GUESS", "Answer": "3275 + 9258 = 12533"}
{"Question": "HALL + CAMP = MATCH", "Answer": "3277 + 9216 = 12493"}
{"Question": "FULL + SURE = GUESS", "Answer": "9288 + 3245 = 12533"}
{"Question": "TALL + FAIR = ELITE", "Answer": "3522 + 8509 = 12031"}
{"Question": "FREE + TRIP = APART", "Answer": "3566 + 8592 = 12158"}
{"Question": "FALL + CARE = OFFER", "Answer": "3655 + 9672 = 13327"}
{"Question": "TALL + RACE = LATER", "Answer": "4211 + 8267 = 12478"}
{"Question": "TALL + EARN = LATER", "Answer": "4211 + 8276 = 12487"}
{"Question": "ROLL + TOWN = NORTH", "Answer": "4255 + 8231 = 12486"}
{"Question": "HILL + KING = TIGHT", "Answer": "4266 + 8275 = 12541"}
{"Question": "LESS + GEAR = ANGLE", "Answer": "9277 + 4215 = 13492"}
{"Question": "MASS + TAIL = ELITE", "Answer": "9288 + 4253 = 13541"}
{"Question": "HALL + FACT = CATCH", "Answer": "4299 + 8215 = 12514"}
{"Question": "BALL + RACE = CLEAR", "Answer": "4322 + 8316 = 12638"}
{"Question": "MEAL + SELF = FLAME", "Answer": "8362 + 4321 = 12683"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SLIP = CLASS", "Answer": "9388 + 4356 = 13744"}
{"Question": "HILL + TIME = EIGHT", "Answer": "4388 + 9361 = 13749"}
{"Question": "BELL + HEAD = DEATH", "Answer": "4388 + 9371 = 13759"}
{"Question": "BELL + WEAK = ALLOW", "Answer": "4622 + 7615 = 12237"}
{"Question": "KISS + AIDE = ESSAY", "Answer": "4622 + 7651 = 12273"}
{"Question": "KNEE + SNOW = LOOSE", "Answer": "4655 + 7620 = 12275"}
{"Question": "TEAR + HERO = FORTH", "Answer": "4795 + 8753 = 13548"}
{"Question": "BALL + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "5177 + 8103 = 13280"}
{"Question": "SELL + TEAM = LEAST", "Answer": "5211 + 7246 = 12457"}
{"Question": "JOIN + BONE = ENJOY", "Answer": "5293 + 8231 = 13524"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BONE = ENTER", "Answer": "5277 + 9241 = 14518"}
{"Question": "MASS + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "5311 + 7326 = 12637"}
{"Question": "BALL + RATE = LATER", "Answer": "5311 + 8367 = 13678"}
{"Question": "BALL + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "8344 + 5371 = 13715"}
{"Question": "LIFE + VIEW = FIELD", "Answer": "8316 + 5364 = 13680"}
{"Question": "TREE + DRUG = GREAT", "Answer": "8377 + 5391 = 13768"}
{"Question": "HALL + BACK = CATCH", "Answer": "5399 + 8316 = 13715"}
{"Question": "FREE + GROW = PROOF", "Answer": "5399 + 8376 = 13775"}
{"Question": "TREE + IRON = ENTER", "Answer": "8411 + 5403 = 13814"}
{"Question": "CELL + BEAN = LABEL", "Answer": "5411 + 8430 = 13841"}
{"Question": "BELL + TEAM = LATER", "Answer": "5411 + 8436 = 13847"}
{"Question": "LESS + VERY = SERVE", "Answer": "5411 + 9483 = 14894"}
{"Question": "ROLL + NOTE = METER", "Answer": "5433 + 7492 = 12925"}
{"Question": "TREE + FROM = METER", "Answer": "8433 + 5401 = 13834"}
{"Question": "TELL + READ = ALTER", "Answer": "8433 + 5412 = 13845"}
{"Question": "BALL + EACH = CLEAN", "Answer": "5433 + 8416 = 13849"}
{"Question": "ALSO + PLOT = SLEEP", "Answer": "5417 + 9472 = 14889"}
{"Question": "BILL + AIDS = SALAD", "Answer": "9622 + 5631 = 15253"}
{"Question": "RAIN + TANK = ENTER", "Answer": "6792 + 5724 = 12516"}
{"Question": "BALL + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "5722 + 8764 = 14486"}
{"Question": "COME + POET = EMPTY", "Answer": "5821 + 6813 = 12634"}
{"Question": "BILL + MINE = LEMON", "Answer": "5811 + 6832 = 12643"}
{"Question": "PALM + GAME = LEGAL", "Answer": "5917 + 8974 = 14891"}
{"Question": "FULL + HURT = TRUTH", "Answer": "5977 + 8941 = 14918"}
{"Question": "ROLL + POSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6233 + 7214 = 13447"}
{"Question": "HALL + SAFE = FLESH", "Answer": "9255 + 6214 = 15469"}
{"Question": "BELL + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "6288 + 9231 = 15519"}
{"Question": "MESS + VERY = LEVEL", "Answer": "7322 + 6309 = 13631"}
{"Question": "LOSS + ROCK = COLOR", "Answer": "6322 + 7315 = 13637"}
{"Question": "LESS + YEAH = HELLO", "Answer": "6344 + 7321 = 13665"}
{"Question": "BILL + RIDE = TIRED", "Answer": "6355 + 7394 = 13749"}
{"Question": "GEAR + HERO = ARGUE", "Answer": "6315 + 9358 = 15673"}
{"Question": "GOLD + CODE = LEGAL", "Answer": "6317 + 8374 = 14691"}
{"Question": "PANT + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "6347 + 8371 = 14718"}
{"Question": "BOSS + LOCK = COLOR", "Answer": "6433 + 8412 = 14845"}
{"Question": "FACT + HATE = CATCH", "Answer": "8419 + 6497 = 14916"}
{"Question": "EAST + MATH = TASTE", "Answer": "8501 + 6517 = 15018"}
{"Question": "POET + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "6591 + 8517 = 15108"}
{"Question": "FIRE + DIET = TIRED", "Answer": "6507 + 8571 = 15078"}
{"Question": "BOSS + VOTE = SEVEN", "Answer": "7811 + 6834 = 14645"}
{"Question": "LESS + WEAK = ALLOW", "Answer": "6822 + 9817 = 16639"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BONE = ERROR", "Answer": "6855 + 9831 = 16686"}
{"Question": "LOSS + WORD = ALLOW", "Answer": "6855 + 9834 = 16689"}
{"Question": "URGE + CREW = OCCUR", "Answer": "9845 + 6853 = 16698"}
{"Question": "POLL + COST = SLEEP", "Answer": "7355 + 8312 = 15667"}
{"Question": "BORN + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "8365 + 7351 = 15716"}
{"Question": "FLEE + ALSO = REFER", "Answer": "7355 + 8396 = 15751"}
{"Question": "LESS + BEAN = APPLE", "Answer": "7355 + 9318 = 16673"}
{"Question": "FAIR + EARN = TREAT", "Answer": "7926 + 8965 = 16891"}
{"Question": "BALL + EARN = ALONE", "Answer": "8177 + 9152 = 17329"}
{"Question": "BALL + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "8455 + 9472 = 17927"}
{"Question": "BELL + POLL = BELOW", "Answer": "1088 + 9788 = 10876"}
{"Question": "FILL + BELL = FALSE", "Answer": "1277 + 9477 = 10754"}
{"Question": "WILL + SELL = WASTE", "Answer": "1288 + 9688 = 10976"}
{"Question": "POLL + BELL = PAPER", "Answer": "1766 + 8366 = 10132"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CALL = ARAB", "Answer": "1388 + 5788 = 7176"}
{"Question": "TELL + ROLL = THREE", "Answer": "1422 + 9522 = 10944"}
{"Question": "BOSS + MESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1677 + 8477 = 10154"}
{"Question": "TREE + FLEE = LEFT", "Answer": "2066 + 3566 = 5632"}
{"Question": "HILL + CELL = EACH", "Answer": "2166 + 3566 = 5732"}
{"Question": "SELL + FILL = BASIS", "Answer": "2866 + 7366 = 10232"}
{"Question": "TOSS + MASS = WASTE", "Answer": "3566 + 7066 = 10632"}
{"Question": "ROLL + CALL = FORCE", "Answer": "3088 + 7288 = 10376"}
{"Question": "BALL + ROLL = SOLAR", "Answer": "4788 + 6088 = 10876"}
{"Question": "TOSS + KISS = RATIO", "Answer": "4688 + 5788 = 10476"}
{"Question": "SELL + FULL = ISSUE", "Answer": "4688 + 9788 = 14476"}
{"Question": "MASS + LESS = APPLY", "Answer": "5188 + 7088 = 12276"}
{"Question": "LOSS + KISS = BIBLE", "Answer": "5877 + 6277 = 12154"}
{"Question": "TOSS + LESS = WASTE", "Answer": "5277 + 8477 = 13754"}
{"Question": "BALL + POLL = HAPPY", "Answer": "5288 + 7488 = 12776"}
{"Question": "BALL + YELL = MAYBE", "Answer": "5377 + 8477 = 13854"}
{"Question": "FLEE + TREE = APART", "Answer": "5388 + 6788 = 12176"}
{"Question": "TALL + BILL = SPLIT", "Answer": "6088 + 9788 = 15876"}
{"Question": "HELL + TALL = EARTH", "Answer": "6188 + 7388 = 13576"}
{"Question": "ROLL + HELL = OTHER", "Answer": "6188 + 9788 = 15976"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BASE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1055 + 8957 = 10012"}
{"Question": "MESS + CAST = METER", "Answer": "1055 + 9253 = 10308"}
{"Question": "MASS + REST = METER", "Answer": "1355 + 9054 = 10409"}
{"Question": "SELL + ONLY = SEVEN", "Answer": "1055 + 9752 = 10807"}
{"Question": "MESS + TASK = METER", "Answer": "1055 + 9852 = 10907"}
{"Question": "TREE + USED = TRUTH", "Answer": "1055 + 9857 = 10912"}
{"Question": "MESS + LAST = METAL", "Answer": "1066 + 9263 = 10329"}
{"Question": "BALL + FILE = BASIS", "Answer": "1066 + 9368 = 10434"}
{"Question": "BELL + FILM = BELOW", "Answer": "1066 + 9568 = 10634"}
{"Question": "WELL + SALT = WASTE", "Answer": "1866 + 9062 = 10928"}
{"Question": "KISS + ALSO = ALLOW", "Answer": "8977 + 1075 = 10052"}
{"Question": "YELL + HALF = HAPPY", "Answer": "9377 + 1072 = 10449"}
{"Question": "FALL + ROLE = FAVOR", "Answer": "1077 + 9472 = 10549"}
{"Question": "FREE + POEM = PRIOR", "Answer": "9077 + 1573 = 10650"}
{"Question": "MALL + HOLY = MAYOR", "Answer": "1077 + 9576 = 10653"}
{"Question": "TREE + CHEF = TREAT", "Answer": "1077 + 9674 = 10751"}
{"Question": "FREE + OPEN = FRONT", "Answer": "1077 + 9875 = 10952"}
{"Question": "BALL + SELF = BASIC", "Answer": "1077 + 9876 = 10953"}
{"Question": "SELL + HALF = SALES", "Answer": "1788 + 9083 = 10871"}
{"Question": "FREE + OPEN = FLOOR", "Answer": "1244 + 9748 = 10992"}
{"Question": "TREE + CHEF = CATCH", "Answer": "9655 + 1257 = 10912"}
{"Question": "FLEE + STEP = SHELL", "Answer": "9366 + 1267 = 10633"}
{"Question": "POLL + BELT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1277 + 8975 = 10252"}
{"Question": "TELL + COLD = THREE", "Answer": "1366 + 9467 = 10833"}
{"Question": "MALL + WILD = MEDIA", "Answer": "1466 + 9368 = 10834"}
{"Question": "POLL + ABLE = PHOTO", "Answer": "1377 + 8976 = 10353"}
{"Question": "POLL + RELY = PAPER", "Answer": "1722 + 8426 = 10148"}
{"Question": "BALL + FILE = BREAD", "Answer": "1422 + 8923 = 10345"}
{"Question": "BILL + SELF = BASIS", "Answer": "1422 + 9527 = 10949"}
{"Question": "BOSS + EAST = ERROR", "Answer": "8577 + 1473 = 10050"}
{"Question": "BOSS + CASE = BLOOD", "Answer": "1577 + 8976 = 10553"}
{"Question": "TREE + VIEW = THEIR", "Answer": "1733 + 8634 = 10367"}
{"Question": "MISS + CASE = MUSIC", "Answer": "1633 + 8735 = 10368"}
{"Question": "SELL + COLD = STATE", "Answer": "1755 + 8652 = 10407"}
{"Question": "MASS + NOSE = ONION", "Answer": "9855 + 2157 = 12012"}
{"Question": "ROLL + ABLE = ORDER", "Answer": "2177 + 9875 = 12052"}
{"Question": "MALL + ONLY = LEMON", "Answer": "8311 + 2514 = 10825"}
{"Question": "FREE + POET = TROOP", "Answer": "7022 + 3421 = 10443"}
{"Question": "HALL + COLD = TOOTH", "Answer": "3955 + 6058 = 10013"}
{"Question": "TREE + POEM = MOTOR", "Answer": "7655 + 3051 = 10706"}
{"Question": "FREE + OPEN = PRIOR", "Answer": "7066 + 3164 = 10230"}
{"Question": "ROLL + FILM = ORDER", "Answer": "3177 + 9876 = 13053"}
{"Question": "LOSS + WEST = ALLOW", "Answer": "3477 + 9872 = 13349"}
{"Question": "SELL + HALF = TASTE", "Answer": "4355 + 6058 = 10413"}
{"Question": "MASS + LIST = VITAL", "Answer": "4055 + 8253 = 12308"}
{"Question": "BELL + PALM = MAYBE", "Answer": "4877 + 6071 = 10948"}
{"Question": "TOSS + BASE = ASSET", "Answer": "9233 + 4136 = 13369"}
{"Question": "KISS + HOST = FIFTH", "Answer": "4366 + 8762 = 13128"}
{"Question": "BALL + RELY = AGREE", "Answer": "9166 + 5367 = 14533"}
{"Question": "FLEE + IDEA = LIMIT", "Answer": "9177 + 5876 = 15053"}
{"Question": "HELL + SALT = EARTH", "Answer": "5188 + 9487 = 14675"}
{"Question": "LOSS + CAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "5344 + 7841 = 13185"}
{"Question": "MASS + NOSE = LEMON", "Answer": "5744 + 6842 = 12586"}
{"Question": "FLEE + VIEW = CIVIL", "Answer": "9077 + 6573 = 15650"}
{"Question": "BILL + TALE = LATER", "Answer": "6411 + 9512 = 15923"}
{"Question": "ROLL + SELF = OFFER", "Answer": "7122 + 8425 = 15547"}
{"Question": "CALL + ONLY = KNOCK", "Answer": "7288 + 9683 = 16971"}
{"Question": "MESS + LIST = TITLE", "Answer": "7544 + 8641 = 16185"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CORE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1022 + 9642 = 10664"}
{"Question": "TREE + HOLE = TOOTH", "Answer": "1944 + 8074 = 10018"}
{"Question": "TREE + MODE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9844 + 1064 = 10908"}
{"Question": "SELL + TAIL = TASTE", "Answer": "9844 + 1074 = 10918"}
{"Question": "BALL + GIRL = BASIC", "Answer": "1066 + 9476 = 10542"}
{"Question": "BELL + FAIL = BEING", "Answer": "1066 + 9786 = 10852"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SHOE = LOSS", "Answer": "1577 + 4067 = 5644"}
{"Question": "BALL + GIRL = BASIS", "Answer": "1077 + 9357 = 10434"}
{"Question": "FLEE + MINE = FINAL", "Answer": "1477 + 9057 = 10534"}
{"Question": "BOSS + AIDS = BOARD", "Answer": "1077 + 9847 = 10924"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CARE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1088 + 9468 = 10556"}
{"Question": "TREE + MAKE = MOTOR", "Answer": "9633 + 1273 = 10906"}
{"Question": "TELL + SOIL = TASTE", "Answer": "1633 + 9283 = 10916"}
{"Question": "MESS + THIS = TITLE", "Answer": "8266 + 1906 = 10172"}
{"Question": "FREE + ABLE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1266 + 9506 = 10772"}
{"Question": "TELL + BOWL = TASTE", "Answer": "1266 + 9546 = 10812"}
{"Question": "BOSS + AIDS = BLOOD", "Answer": "1277 + 8947 = 10224"}
{"Question": "TELL + RAIL = THREE", "Answer": "1688 + 9278 = 10966"}
{"Question": "SELL + COAL = STATE", "Answer": "1422 + 9382 = 10804"}
{"Question": "FLEE + TYPE = FIFTY", "Answer": "1722 + 8462 = 10184"}
{"Question": "CELL + SOIL = CAUSE", "Answer": "1422 + 8962 = 10384"}
{"Question": "BELL + COAL = CABLE", "Answer": "9422 + 1502 = 10924"}
{"Question": "FREE + ONCE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1422 + 9572 = 10994"}
{"Question": "LESS + AIDS = APPLE", "Answer": "8633 + 1453 = 10086"}
{"Question": "POLL + DEAL = PAPER", "Answer": "1466 + 8706 = 10172"}
{"Question": "BELL + COAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "1477 + 8697 = 10174"}
{"Question": "SELL + COAL = SAUCE", "Answer": "1477 + 8907 = 10384"}
{"Question": "ROLL + DEAL = RADIO", "Answer": "1477 + 9507 = 10984"}
{"Question": "BOSS + PLUS = BIBLE", "Answer": "1622 + 8532 = 10154"}
{"Question": "BALL + FUEL = BREAD", "Answer": "1533 + 8723 = 10256"}
{"Question": "BILL + COAL = BASIS", "Answer": "1766 + 8506 = 10272"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SITE = STEEL", "Answer": "8633 + 1703 = 10336"}
{"Question": "TREE + AIDE = THEIR", "Answer": "1633 + 8743 = 10376"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SHOE = FRESH", "Answer": "1733 + 8653 = 10386"}
{"Question": "MISS + PLUS = MUSIC", "Answer": "1766 + 8906 = 10672"}
{"Question": "WILL + REAL = LOWER", "Answer": "8311 + 2541 = 10852"}
{"Question": "ROLL + FUEL = ERROR", "Answer": "2866 + 9416 = 12282"}
{"Question": "TREE + ONCE = EVENT", "Answer": "2611 + 7541 = 10152"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SAKE = LESS", "Answer": "4766 + 2856 = 7622"}
{"Question": "CELL + SOIL = VOICE", "Answer": "3844 + 7094 = 10938"}
{"Question": "FREE + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "3211 + 7501 = 10712"}
{"Question": "TREE + BASE = ASSET", "Answer": "4922 + 5102 = 10024"}
{"Question": "TELL + RAIL = ALTER", "Answer": "8722 + 4152 = 12874"}
{"Question": "BELL + RAIL = AGREE", "Answer": "9266 + 4156 = 13422"}
{"Question": "WELL + COAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "4922 + 7312 = 12234"}
{"Question": "BOSS + THIS = FIFTH", "Answer": "5344 + 6824 = 12168"}
{"Question": "TREE + ONCE = ACTOR", "Answer": "5844 + 6724 = 12568"}
{"Question": "FREE + AIDE = DRAMA", "Answer": "7388 + 6218 = 13606"}
{"Question": "FLEE + SURE = GUESS", "Answer": "9288 + 6578 = 15866"}
{"Question": "FREE + TONE = ENTRY", "Answer": "6511 + 8341 = 14852"}
{"Question": "ROLL + JAIL = MAJOR", "Answer": "6388 + 9548 = 15936"}
{"Question": "BALL + GIRL = LABOR", "Answer": "9511 + 6421 = 15932"}
{"Question": "BOSS + THUS = DOUBT", "Answer": "6544 + 8724 = 15268"}
{"Question": "HALL + GIRL = RIGHT", "Answer": "7355 + 9615 = 16970"}
{"Question": "MASS + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "7544 + 8614 = 16158"}
{"Question": "TREE + HIDE = FIFTH", "Answer": "7544 + 8634 = 16178"}
{"Question": "TREE + BALL = TREAT", "Answer": "1033 + 9288 = 10321"}
{"Question": "FLEE + MASS = LEAF", "Answer": "1588 + 4233 = 5821"}
{"Question": "TREE + BILL = THEIR", "Answer": "1388 + 9455 = 10843"}
{"Question": "TALL + MESS = WASTE", "Answer": "4277 + 8366 = 12643"}
{"Question": "BELL + JOIN = BEING", "Answer": "1044 + 9782 = 10826"}
{"Question": "DIET + LOTS = LOOSE", "Answer": "8975 + 1052 = 10027"}
{"Question": "AUTO + SHOE = SHEET", "Answer": "9285 + 1053 = 10338"}
{"Question": "KNEE + ACID = KNOCK", "Answer": "1055 + 9376 = 10431"}
{"Question": "TOSS + YARD = TODAY", "Answer": "1055 + 9384 = 10439"}
{"Question": "KNEE + BLOW = KNOCK", "Answer": "1055 + 9786 = 10841"}
{"Question": "LOSS + WIRE = LOWER", "Answer": "1055 + 9872 = 10927"}
{"Question": "CALL + YOUR = CARRY", "Answer": "1066 + 9273 = 10339"}
{"Question": "BELL + GAIN = BEING", "Answer": "1077 + 9452 = 10529"}
{"Question": "BELL + STAR = START", "Answer": "9477 + 1053 = 10530"}
{"Question": "LOSS + BAKE = LABEL", "Answer": "1877 + 9064 = 10941"}
{"Question": "BALL + SHOE = SALES", "Answer": "9088 + 1743 = 10831"}
{"Question": "TELL + BUSY = TASTE", "Answer": "1244 + 9368 = 10612"}
{"Question": "TOSS + CARE = TREAT", "Answer": "1244 + 9507 = 10751"}
{"Question": "LESS + WHAT = WASTE", "Answer": "9577 + 1208 = 10785"}
{"Question": "BEST + INTO = ISSUE", "Answer": "8304 + 1749 = 10053"}
{"Question": "MALL + DIET = MEDIA", "Answer": "1355 + 9608 = 10963"}
{"Question": "BELL + DISH = BASIS", "Answer": "1366 + 9482 = 10848"}
{"Question": "EAST + MYTH = ESSAY", "Answer": "1605 + 8459 = 10064"}
{"Question": "WILL + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "1477 + 9508 = 10985"}
{"Question": "FLEE + CHIP = FIELD", "Answer": "1655 + 8907 = 10562"}
{"Question": "HALL + REST = EARTH", "Answer": "9322 + 4157 = 13479"}
{"Question": "FLEE + ACID = IDEAL", "Answer": "7533 + 4812 = 12345"}
{"Question": "LATE + USED = ADULT", "Answer": "8107 + 5473 = 13580"}
{"Question": "PASS + RULE = SUPER", "Answer": "5211 + 8367 = 13578"}
{"Question": "LOSS + VIEW = SOLVE", "Answer": "5311 + 8276 = 13587"}
{"Question": "FREE + LOTS = TOTAL", "Answer": "5722 + 8416 = 14138"}
{"Question": "ROLL + BEAN = AGREE", "Answer": "6588 + 7012 = 13600"}
{"Question": "LESS + YARD = EARLY", "Answer": "6122 + 7345 = 13467"}
{"Question": "ROLL + HEAT = OTHER", "Answer": "6122 + 8754 = 14876"}
{"Question": "MASS + INTO = ASIAN", "Answer": "6133 + 7582 = 13715"}
{"Question": "PASS + TRUE = SUPER", "Answer": "7211 + 6534 = 13745"}
{"Question": "POLL + MINE = LEMON", "Answer": "6511 + 7243 = 13754"}
{"Question": "BOSS + LATE = STEAL", "Answer": "6211 + 8547 = 14758"}
{"Question": "KISS + BEAT = STAKE", "Answer": "8211 + 6574 = 14785"}
{"Question": "TELL + DRAG = ALTER", "Answer": "7533 + 6219 = 13752"}
{"Question": "TELL + DRAG = LATER", "Answer": "8511 + 6342 = 14853"}
{"Question": "ROLL + EACH = CLEAR", "Answer": "6344 + 8512 = 14856"}
{"Question": "DARE + ITEM = MEDIA", "Answer": "8524 + 6341 = 14865"}
{"Question": "EARN + KING = RANGE", "Answer": "6417 + 8379 = 14796"}
{"Question": "LOSS + IDEA = SALAD", "Answer": "8211 + 7645 = 15856"}
{"Question": "LESS + BACK = CABLE", "Answer": "7355 + 9618 = 16973"}
{"Question": "BOSS + DARE = ORDER", "Answer": "9155 + 8672 = 17827"}
{"Question": "HILL + GATE = TIGHT", "Answer": "8766 + 9215 = 17981"}
{"Question": "LESS + UNIT = ISSUE", "Answer": "8377 + 9416 = 17793"}
{"Question": "DARE + DARE = IDEA", "Answer": "1075 + 1075 = 2150"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = AREA", "Answer": "1206 + 1206 = 2412"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARD = AREA", "Answer": "1246 + 1246 = 2492"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "1256 + 1256 = 2512"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEST = EASE", "Answer": "1296 + 1296 = 2592"}
{"Question": "STAR + STAR = AREA", "Answer": "1326 + 1326 = 2652"}
{"Question": "GRAB + GRAB = BALL", "Answer": "1372 + 1372 = 2744"}
{"Question": "ONCE + ONCE = EVEN", "Answer": "1462 + 1462 = 2924"}
{"Question": "CLUB + CLUB = BALL", "Answer": "1472 + 1472 = 2944"}
{"Question": "HUGE + HUGE = GENE", "Answer": "1530 + 1530 = 3060"}
{"Question": "AUTO + AUTO = TOUR", "Answer": "1632 + 1632 = 3264"}
{"Question": "HANG + HANG = GENE", "Answer": "1803 + 1803 = 3606"}
{"Question": "GRAY + GRAY = ALLY", "Answer": "1830 + 1830 = 3660"}
{"Question": "INTO + INTO = TEEN", "Answer": "1834 + 1834 = 3668"}
{"Question": "COAT + COAT = BALL", "Answer": "1872 + 1872 = 3744"}
{"Question": "DIET + DIET = NINE", "Answer": "1968 + 1968 = 3936"}
{"Question": "CASH + CASH = HALL", "Answer": "1983 + 1983 = 3966"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TRUE = AREA", "Answer": "2037 + 2037 = 4074"}
{"Question": "FADE + FADE = DATA", "Answer": "2045 + 2045 = 4090"}
{"Question": "LAKE + LAKE = BELL", "Answer": "2061 + 2061 = 4122"}
{"Question": "RICE + RICE = AREA", "Answer": "2137 + 2137 = 4274"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = DATA", "Answer": "2146 + 2146 = 4292"}
{"Question": "ROAD + ROAD = AREA", "Answer": "2147 + 2147 = 4294"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = DEAL", "Answer": "2163 + 2163 = 4326"}
{"Question": "ACID + ACID = IDEA", "Answer": "2346 + 2346 = 4692"}
{"Question": "BAKE + BAKE = DEAD", "Answer": "2367 + 2367 = 4734"}
{"Question": "GRAY + GRAY = BABY", "Answer": "2370 + 2370 = 4740"}
{"Question": "OVER + OVER = AREA", "Answer": "2397 + 2397 = 4794"}
{"Question": "PLUS + PLUS = LESS", "Answer": "2450 + 2450 = 4900"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SLIP = LESS", "Answer": "2461 + 2461 = 4922"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = LOTS", "Answer": "2489 + 2489 = 4978"}
{"Question": "OKAY + OKAY = BOOK", "Answer": "2613 + 2613 = 5226"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = RARE", "Answer": "2879 + 2879 = 5758"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOTS = TOSS", "Answer": "2950 + 2950 = 5900"}
{"Question": "ARMY + ARMY = GRAY", "Answer": "2960 + 2960 = 5920"}
{"Question": "LACK + LACK = BALL", "Answer": "2961 + 2961 = 5922"}
{"Question": "YARD + YARD = BABY", "Answer": "2976 + 2976 = 5952"}
{"Question": "TAIL + TAIL = DATA", "Answer": "3015 + 3015 = 6030"}
{"Question": "MODE + MODE = BOMB", "Answer": "3018 + 3018 = 6036"}
{"Question": "GLAD + GLAD = DATA", "Answer": "3126 + 3126 = 6252"}
{"Question": "ARMY + ARMY = BABY", "Answer": "3180 + 3180 = 6360"}
{"Question": "ARMY + ARMY = YEAR", "Answer": "3216 + 3216 = 6432"}
{"Question": "LEFT + LEFT = FREE", "Answer": "3261 + 3261 = 6522"}
{"Question": "GRAB + GRAB = BEER", "Answer": "3276 + 3276 = 6552"}
{"Question": "BELT + BELT = LATE", "Answer": "3462 + 3462 = 6924"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = CELL", "Answer": "3672 + 3672 = 7344"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = ABLE", "Answer": "3678 + 3678 = 7356"}
{"Question": "EASY + EASY = ALLY", "Answer": "3720 + 3720 = 7440"}
{"Question": "COST + COST = ODDS", "Answer": "3721 + 3721 = 7442"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = BEAN", "Answer": "3765 + 3765 = 7530"}
{"Question": "FAIR + FAIR = ARAB", "Answer": "3785 + 3785 = 7570"}
{"Question": "BASE + BASE = SAFE", "Answer": "3970 + 3970 = 7940"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DEBT = BELL", "Answer": "3972 + 3972 = 7944"}
{"Question": "BIRD + BIRD = DEER", "Answer": "4168 + 4168 = 8336"}
{"Question": "RIDE + RIDE = DEER", "Answer": "4387 + 4387 = 8774"}
{"Question": "KNOW + KNOW = BOOK", "Answer": "4502 + 4502 = 9004"}
{"Question": "NAME + NAME = GENE", "Answer": "4520 + 4520 = 9040"}
{"Question": "RACE + RACE = BEER", "Answer": "4612 + 4612 = 9224"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TEAM = DATA", "Answer": "4621 + 4621 = 9242"}
{"Question": "CHIP + CHIP = RICH", "Answer": "4623 + 4623 = 9246"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = COAL", "Answer": "4673 + 4673 = 9346"}
{"Question": "CREW + CREW = EVER", "Answer": "4698 + 4698 = 9396"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = BEER", "Answer": "4721 + 4721 = 9442"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "4795 + 4795 = 9590"}
{"Question": "BUCK + BUCK = CLUB", "Answer": "4892 + 4892 = 9784"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "4897 + 4897 = 9794"}
{"Question": "USED + USED = ISSUE", "Answer": "5026 + 5026 = 10052"}
{"Question": "STEP + STEP = THESE", "Answer": "5126 + 5126 = 10252"}
{"Question": "FROM + FROM = MOTOR", "Answer": "5201 + 5201 = 10402"}
{"Question": "VIEW + VIEW = FEWER", "Answer": "5204 + 5204 = 10408"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAR = ORDER", "Answer": "5260 + 5260 = 10520"}
{"Question": "REST + REST = THREE", "Answer": "5261 + 5261 = 10522"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LOAD = HELLO", "Answer": "5276 + 5276 = 10552"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SLIP = CIVIL", "Answer": "5402 + 5402 = 10804"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "5412 + 5412 = 10824"}
{"Question": "AIDS + AIDS = SOLID", "Answer": "5421 + 5421 = 10842"}
{"Question": "CAST + CAST = STATE", "Answer": "6012 + 6012 = 12024"}
{"Question": "EASY + EASY = STATE", "Answer": "6013 + 6013 = 12026"}
{"Question": "CASH + CASH = STATE", "Answer": "6014 + 6014 = 12028"}
{"Question": "FARM + FARM = DRAMA", "Answer": "6025 + 6025 = 12050"}
{"Question": "CAMP + CAMP = PEACE", "Answer": "6031 + 6031 = 12062"}
{"Question": "FAIL + FAIL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6041 + 6041 = 12082"}
{"Question": "LADY + LADY = CYCLE", "Answer": "6082 + 6082 = 12164"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = LOOSE", "Answer": "6102 + 6102 = 12204"}
{"Question": "YEAH + YEAH = ESSAY", "Answer": "6103 + 6103 = 12206"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = ESSAY", "Answer": "6104 + 6104 = 12208"}
{"Question": "CAST + CAST = ASSET", "Answer": "6120 + 6120 = 12240"}
{"Question": "LADY + LADY = APPLY", "Answer": "6130 + 6130 = 12260"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = ASSET", "Answer": "6134 + 6134 = 12268"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = ISSUE", "Answer": "6140 + 6140 = 12280"}
{"Question": "BIRD + BIRD = INNER", "Answer": "6147 + 6147 = 12294"}
{"Question": "CROP + CROP = PRIOR", "Answer": "6201 + 6201 = 12402"}
{"Question": "ROCK + ROCK = COLOR", "Answer": "6213 + 6213 = 12426"}
{"Question": "FILM + FILM = LIMIT", "Answer": "6214 + 6214 = 12428"}
{"Question": "FROM + FROM = DRAMA", "Answer": "6237 + 6237 = 12474"}
{"Question": "CASE + CASE = BASIS", "Answer": "6247 + 6247 = 12494"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = VIDEO", "Answer": "6249 + 6249 = 12498"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = BLOOD", "Answer": "6275 + 6275 = 12550"}
{"Question": "PLAN + PLAN = SLEEP", "Answer": "6278 + 6278 = 12556"}
{"Question": "ARMY + ARMY = CREAM", "Answer": "6284 + 6284 = 12568"}
{"Question": "WIFE + WIFE = FEWER", "Answer": "6312 + 6312 = 12624"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SEAT = BASIS", "Answer": "6328 + 6328 = 12656"}
{"Question": "RAIN + RAIN = NERVE", "Answer": "6341 + 6341 = 12682"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAR = GRASS", "Answer": "6372 + 6372 = 12744"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SHOP = PRIOR", "Answer": "6401 + 6401 = 12802"}
{"Question": "BELT + BELT = LIMIT", "Answer": "6410 + 6410 = 12820"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEST = STATE", "Answer": "6412 + 6412 = 12824"}
{"Question": "DATE + DATE = TREND", "Answer": "6418 + 6418 = 12836"}
{"Question": "OVEN + OVEN = NERVE", "Answer": "6421 + 6421 = 12842"}
{"Question": "SOUP + SOUP = PRIOR", "Answer": "6471 + 6471 = 12942"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FLAT = STILL", "Answer": "6472 + 6472 = 12944"}
{"Question": "NICE + NICE = SCENE", "Answer": "6530 + 6530 = 13060"}
{"Question": "LOTS + LOTS = THESE", "Answer": "6712 + 6712 = 13424"}
{"Question": "AIDS + AIDS = SPEED", "Answer": "6721 + 6721 = 13442"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = CLEAN", "Answer": "6734 + 6734 = 13468"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = THREE", "Answer": "6783 + 6783 = 13566"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = THEME", "Answer": "6823 + 6823 = 13646"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = GREEN", "Answer": "6830 + 6830 = 13660"}
{"Question": "LOUD + LOUD = FULLY", "Answer": "6832 + 6832 = 13664"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "6874 + 6874 = 13748"}
{"Question": "FEAR + FEAR = BRIEF", "Answer": "6893 + 6893 = 13786"}
{"Question": "DATE + DATE = BREAD", "Answer": "6948 + 6948 = 13896"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DEBT = AHEAD", "Answer": "6958 + 6958 = 13916"}
{"Question": "BIKE + BIKE = TRIBE", "Answer": "6980 + 6980 = 13960"}
{"Question": "FACT + FACT = STAFF", "Answer": "6983 + 6983 = 13966"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = COLOR", "Answer": "7024 + 7024 = 14048"}
{"Question": "CREW + CREW = NERVE", "Answer": "7042 + 7042 = 14084"}
{"Question": "CARE + CARE = DRAMA", "Answer": "7045 + 7045 = 14090"}
{"Question": "INTO + INTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "7085 + 7085 = 14170"}
{"Question": "SPIN + SPIN = PIECE", "Answer": "7146 + 7146 = 14292"}
{"Question": "BURN + BURN = UNDER", "Answer": "7184 + 7184 = 14368"}
{"Question": "CHEF + CHEF = OFFER", "Answer": "7204 + 7204 = 14408"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAT = ASSET", "Answer": "7210 + 7210 = 14420"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAL = LOOSE", "Answer": "7231 + 7231 = 14462"}
{"Question": "LEFT + LEFT = APPLE", "Answer": "7236 + 7236 = 14472"}
{"Question": "BASE + BASE = ISSUE", "Answer": "7240 + 7240 = 14480"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEST = ISSUE", "Answer": "7246 + 7246 = 14492"}
{"Question": "BONE + BONE = INNER", "Answer": "7249 + 7249 = 14498"}
{"Question": "BACK + BACK = SKILL", "Answer": "7294 + 7294 = 14588"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SHOE = ORDER", "Answer": "7312 + 7312 = 14624"}
{"Question": "FARM + FARM = METER", "Answer": "7321 + 7321 = 14642"}
{"Question": "DATE + DATE = ORDER", "Answer": "7362 + 7362 = 14724"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = SHELL", "Answer": "7394 + 7394 = 14788"}
{"Question": "DECK + DECK = FENCE", "Answer": "7402 + 7402 = 14804"}
{"Question": "BANK + BANK = NAKED", "Answer": "7418 + 7418 = 14836"}
{"Question": "GIRL + GIRL = CIVIL", "Answer": "7420 + 7420 = 14840"}
{"Question": "FORM + FORM = MOTOR", "Answer": "7421 + 7421 = 14842"}
{"Question": "THAN + THAN = PHOTO", "Answer": "7439 + 7439 = 14878"}
{"Question": "PLUS + PLUS = CLASS", "Answer": "7450 + 7450 = 14900"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TRUE = ORDER", "Answer": "7462 + 7462 = 14924"}
{"Question": "BEND + BEND = FENCE", "Answer": "7492 + 7492 = 14984"}
{"Question": "CROP + CROP = PROOF", "Answer": "7501 + 7501 = 15002"}
{"Question": "WIPE + WIPE = PIECE", "Answer": "7510 + 7510 = 15020"}
{"Question": "BITE + BITE = TIRED", "Answer": "7512 + 7512 = 15024"}
{"Question": "AUTO + AUTO = OUGHT", "Answer": "7521 + 7521 = 15042"}
{"Question": "FILE + FILE = CIVIL", "Answer": "7526 + 7526 = 15052"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = PAPER", "Answer": "7589 + 7589 = 15178"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = SHEET", "Answer": "7614 + 7614 = 15228"}
{"Question": "BITE + BITE = METER", "Answer": "7625 + 7625 = 15250"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "7628 + 7628 = 15256"}
{"Question": "CLUB + CLUB = BASIS", "Answer": "7641 + 7641 = 15282"}
{"Question": "HUGE + HUGE = AGREE", "Answer": "7650 + 7650 = 15300"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "7683 + 7683 = 15366"}
{"Question": "GIRL + GIRL = COLOR", "Answer": "7826 + 7826 = 15652"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = CIVIL", "Answer": "7829 + 7829 = 15658"}
{"Question": "CITE + CITE = BASIS", "Answer": "7843 + 7843 = 15686"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TEAM = CATCH", "Answer": "7856 + 7856 = 15712"}
{"Question": "THAN + THAN = CATCH", "Answer": "7859 + 7859 = 15718"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAL = COLOR", "Answer": "7928 + 7928 = 15856"}
{"Question": "URGE + URGE = AGREE", "Answer": "7950 + 7950 = 15900"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = STATE", "Answer": "8034 + 8034 = 16068"}
{"Question": "VARY + VARY = LEAVE", "Answer": "8043 + 8043 = 16086"}
{"Question": "TRIP + TRIP = ADAPT", "Answer": "8074 + 8074 = 16148"}
{"Question": "FLAG + FLAG = LEAVE", "Answer": "8123 + 8123 = 16246"}
{"Question": "NOTE + NOTE = OFTEN", "Answer": "8124 + 8124 = 16248"}
{"Question": "DRUG + DRUG = ROUND", "Answer": "8129 + 8129 = 16258"}
{"Question": "THAN + THAN = HONOR", "Answer": "8132 + 8132 = 16264"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OPEN = PRIOR", "Answer": "8143 + 8143 = 16286"}
{"Question": "DARK + DARK = ARMED", "Answer": "8164 + 8164 = 16328"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = AGREE", "Answer": "8194 + 8194 = 16388"}
{"Question": "ACID + ACID = MEDIA", "Answer": "8204 + 8204 = 16408"}
{"Question": "IRON + IRON = ENTER", "Answer": "8206 + 8206 = 16412"}
{"Question": "COPE + COPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "8213 + 8213 = 16426"}
{"Question": "PACE + PACE = CHEAP", "Answer": "8214 + 8214 = 16428"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "8216 + 8216 = 16432"}
{"Question": "FROM + FROM = METER", "Answer": "8231 + 8231 = 16462"}
{"Question": "RAIL + RAIL = COLOR", "Answer": "8234 + 8234 = 16468"}
{"Question": "RATE + RATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "8241 + 8241 = 16482"}
{"Question": "OVEN + OVEN = LEAVE", "Answer": "8263 + 8263 = 16526"}
{"Question": "BONE + BONE = HELLO", "Answer": "8276 + 8276 = 16552"}
{"Question": "DARE + DARE = BLOOD", "Answer": "8279 + 8279 = 16558"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAT = TRIBE", "Answer": "8291 + 8291 = 16582"}
{"Question": "CAMP + CAMP = FENCE", "Answer": "8293 + 8293 = 16586"}
{"Question": "EAST + EAST = LOOSE", "Answer": "8304 + 8304 = 16608"}
{"Question": "HAIR + HAIR = TOOTH", "Answer": "8309 + 8309 = 16618"}
{"Question": "BLUE + BLUE = UPPER", "Answer": "8312 + 8312 = 16624"}
{"Question": "RAIL + RAIL = INNER", "Answer": "8314 + 8314 = 16628"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "8319 + 8319 = 16638"}
{"Question": "FUEL + FUEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "8321 + 8321 = 16642"}
{"Question": "BORN + BORN = INNER", "Answer": "8326 + 8326 = 16652"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = ISSUE", "Answer": "8329 + 8329 = 16658"}
{"Question": "ARMY + ARMY = ESSAY", "Answer": "8340 + 8340 = 16680"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = ESSAY", "Answer": "8341 + 8341 = 16682"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = OFFER", "Answer": "8342 + 8342 = 16684"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "8367 + 8367 = 16734"}
{"Question": "DIET + DIET = ORDER", "Answer": "8403 + 8403 = 16806"}
{"Question": "RANK + RANK = NERVE", "Answer": "8413 + 8413 = 16826"}
{"Question": "HERO + HERO = OTHER", "Answer": "8421 + 8421 = 16842"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAL = ORDER", "Answer": "8423 + 8423 = 16846"}
{"Question": "NEAR + NEAR = HONOR", "Answer": "8430 + 8430 = 16860"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MEAL = LIMIT", "Answer": "8431 + 8431 = 16862"}
{"Question": "WRAP + WRAP = FEWER", "Answer": "8432 + 8432 = 16864"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "8462 + 8462 = 16924"}
{"Question": "CHIP + CHIP = PRICE", "Answer": "8491 + 8491 = 16982"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = HELLO", "Answer": "8496 + 8496 = 16992"}
{"Question": "CAKE + CAKE = PIECE", "Answer": "8540 + 8540 = 17080"}
{"Question": "SALT + SALT = ELECT", "Answer": "8570 + 8570 = 17140"}
{"Question": "SIGH + SIGH = AGAIN", "Answer": "8576 + 8576 = 17152"}
{"Question": "READ + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "8579 + 8579 = 17158"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DEBT = BLOOD", "Answer": "8614 + 8614 = 17228"}
{"Question": "MIND + MIND = DRAMA", "Answer": "8641 + 8641 = 17282"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HEAT = FAITH", "Answer": "8674 + 8674 = 17348"}
{"Question": "ITEM + ITEM = ADMIT", "Answer": "8693 + 8693 = 17386"}
{"Question": "FAIL + FAIL = BASIS", "Answer": "8702 + 8702 = 17404"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = RANGE", "Answer": "8714 + 8714 = 17428"}
{"Question": "BODY + BODY = SORRY", "Answer": "8720 + 8720 = 17440"}
{"Question": "YOUR + YOUR = SORRY", "Answer": "8724 + 8724 = 17448"}
{"Question": "DARK + DARK = NAKED", "Answer": "8734 + 8734 = 17468"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LIFE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8739 + 8739 = 17478"}
{"Question": "CORE + CORE = FORCE", "Answer": "8740 + 8740 = 17480"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAR = READY", "Answer": "8741 + 8741 = 17482"}
{"Question": "CHIP + CHIP = THICK", "Answer": "8743 + 8743 = 17486"}
{"Question": "EAST + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "8749 + 8749 = 17498"}
{"Question": "BOND + BOND = DOUBT", "Answer": "8791 + 8791 = 17582"}
{"Question": "SHIP + SHIP = BASIS", "Answer": "8904 + 8904 = 17808"}
{"Question": "EARN + EARN = SCENE", "Answer": "8924 + 8924 = 17848"}
{"Question": "WAGE + WAGE = FEWER", "Answer": "8937 + 8937 = 17874"}
{"Question": "LADY + LADY = FULLY", "Answer": "8940 + 8940 = 17880"}
{"Question": "LEAF + LEAF = FULLY", "Answer": "8941 + 8941 = 17882"}
{"Question": "INTO + INTO = JOINT", "Answer": "8947 + 8947 = 17894"}
{"Question": "YEAH + YEAH = CHECK", "Answer": "8957 + 8957 = 17914"}
{"Question": "BURY + BURY = TRULY", "Answer": "8970 + 8970 = 17940"}
{"Question": "AUTO + AUTO = STUFF", "Answer": "8972 + 8972 = 17944"}
{"Question": "FIRE + FIRE = BRIEF", "Answer": "8974 + 8974 = 17948"}
{"Question": "FAIR + FAIR = START", "Answer": "9024 + 9024 = 18048"}
{"Question": "CODE + CODE = ORDER", "Answer": "9124 + 9124 = 18248"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = BELOW", "Answer": "9128 + 9128 = 18256"}
{"Question": "ACID + ACID = COLOR", "Answer": "9143 + 9143 = 18286"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SHOE = HELLO", "Answer": "9168 + 9168 = 18336"}
{"Question": "BORN + BORN = ORDER", "Answer": "9184 + 9184 = 18368"}
{"Question": "USED + USED = ORDER", "Answer": "9204 + 9204 = 18408"}
{"Question": "BORN + BORN = FENCE", "Answer": "9234 + 9234 = 18468"}
{"Question": "COLD + COLD = SALAD", "Answer": "9240 + 9240 = 18480"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MEAL = DRAMA", "Answer": "9247 + 9247 = 18494"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = DELAY", "Answer": "9248 + 9248 = 18496"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = HELLO", "Answer": "9278 + 9278 = 18556"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAR = RAISE", "Answer": "9281 + 9281 = 18562"}
{"Question": "GIFT + GIFT = FENCE", "Answer": "9314 + 9314 = 18628"}
{"Question": "FOUR + FOUR = DRAMA", "Answer": "9328 + 9328 = 18656"}
{"Question": "GOLF + GOLF = FEWER", "Answer": "9341 + 9341 = 18682"}
{"Question": "IDEA + IDEA = BASIS", "Answer": "9348 + 9348 = 18696"}
{"Question": "BONE + BONE = LEMON", "Answer": "9368 + 9368 = 18736"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "9374 + 9374 = 18748"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9387 + 9387 = 18774"}
{"Question": "BELT + BELT = APPLE", "Answer": "9402 + 9402 = 18804"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "9412 + 9412 = 18824"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAL = ALLOW", "Answer": "9418 + 9418 = 18836"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAR = INNER", "Answer": "9420 + 9420 = 18840"}
{"Question": "HERO + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "9421 + 9421 = 18842"}
{"Question": "AUTO + AUTO = ISSUE", "Answer": "9423 + 9423 = 18846"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = OCCUR", "Answer": "9431 + 9431 = 18862"}
{"Question": "MENU + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "9437 + 9437 = 18874"}
{"Question": "ABLE + ABLE = CLASS", "Answer": "9483 + 9483 = 18966"}
{"Question": "SEAT + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "9487 + 9487 = 18974"}
{"Question": "CASE + CASE = SCENE", "Answer": "9510 + 9510 = 19020"}
{"Question": "HURT + HURT = THERE", "Answer": "9601 + 9601 = 19202"}
{"Question": "HOST + HOST = SHEET", "Answer": "9610 + 9610 = 19220"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LOSE = SLEEP", "Answer": "9612 + 9612 = 19224"}
{"Question": "LAST + LAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "9614 + 9614 = 19228"}
{"Question": "READ + READ = DRAMA", "Answer": "9621 + 9621 = 19242"}
{"Question": "HELP + HELP = PHOTO", "Answer": "9641 + 9641 = 19282"}
{"Question": "TEND + TEND = STATE", "Answer": "9648 + 9648 = 19296"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HEAR = THREE", "Answer": "9683 + 9683 = 19366"}
{"Question": "RING + RING = GREEN", "Answer": "9721 + 9721 = 19442"}
{"Question": "HATE + HATE = CHEEK", "Answer": "9724 + 9724 = 19448"}
{"Question": "ALSO + ALSO = BASIS", "Answer": "9742 + 9742 = 19484"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HIRE = THREE", "Answer": "9750 + 9750 = 19500"}
{"Question": "RIDE + RIDE = DRAMA", "Answer": "9813 + 9813 = 19626"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HEAR = SHORE", "Answer": "9824 + 9824 = 19648"}
{"Question": "EACH + EACH = HELLO", "Answer": "9831 + 9831 = 19662"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDE = BASIS", "Answer": "9843 + 9843 = 19686"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OPEN = HONOR", "Answer": "9846 + 9846 = 19692"}
{"Question": "GIRL + GIRL = AGREE", "Answer": "9872 + 9872 = 19744"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HEAD = SHADE", "Answer": "9874 + 9874 = 19748"}
{"Question": "SOUP + SOUL = PLUS", "Answer": "2895 + 2897 = 5792"}
{"Question": "SALT + SALE = EASE", "Answer": "2960 + 2965 = 5925"}
{"Question": "SALE + SALT = LESS", "Answer": "3265 + 3268 = 6533"}
{"Question": "THEM + THEY = MYTH", "Answer": "3416 + 3418 = 6834"}
{"Question": "AIDS + AIDE = DEAD", "Answer": "3467 + 3469 = 6936"}
{"Question": "THEM + THEN = MEET", "Answer": "3496 + 3497 = 6993"}
{"Question": "CLUE + CLUB = BELL", "Answer": "4153 + 4158 = 8311"}
{"Question": "SALE + SALT = TEST", "Answer": "4520 + 4529 = 9049"}
{"Question": "AIDS + AIDE = SPEND", "Answer": "5381 + 5387 = 10768"}
{"Question": "LEAD + LEAF = AWFUL", "Answer": "5417 + 5418 = 10835"}
{"Question": "EAST + EASY = STATE", "Answer": "6012 + 6014 = 12026"}
{"Question": "KING + KIND = AGAIN", "Answer": "6052 + 6053 = 12105"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAR = ERROR", "Answer": "6140 + 6142 = 12282"}
{"Question": "CORN + CORE = OFFER", "Answer": "6145 + 6149 = 12294"}
{"Question": "DRAG + DRAW = GRASS", "Answer": "6241 + 6247 = 12488"}
{"Question": "EASY + EAST = WASTE", "Answer": "6247 + 6249 = 12496"}
{"Question": "BOND + BONE = DOZEN", "Answer": "6291 + 6298 = 12589"}
{"Question": "EAST + EASY = STEAL", "Answer": "6312 + 6318 = 12630"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TEAR = SMART", "Answer": "6372 + 6374 = 12746"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAR = TRIBE", "Answer": "6381 + 6382 = 12763"}
{"Question": "DARE + DARK = SPEED", "Answer": "6387 + 6389 = 12776"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = DREAM", "Answer": "6421 + 6428 = 12849"}
{"Question": "MEAL + MEAN = ANGLE", "Answer": "6512 + 6513 = 13025"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MEAL = TITLE", "Answer": "6571 + 6574 = 13145"}
{"Question": "AIDS + AIDE = SHEET", "Answer": "6721 + 6724 = 13445"}
{"Question": "COAT + COAL = MATCH", "Answer": "6734 + 6735 = 13469"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "6891 + 6897 = 13788"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = PEACE", "Answer": "6980 + 6983 = 13963"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = READY", "Answer": "7012 + 7014 = 14026"}
{"Question": "EASY + EAST = STAGE", "Answer": "7013 + 7014 = 14027"}
{"Question": "PART + PARK = STATE", "Answer": "7024 + 7025 = 14049"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MEAL = THEME", "Answer": "7031 + 7039 = 14070"}
{"Question": "FIRM + FIRE = BRIEF", "Answer": "7048 + 7049 = 14097"}
{"Question": "DARK + DARE = ARMED", "Answer": "7148 + 7149 = 14297"}
{"Question": "THEN + THEM = INNER", "Answer": "7204 + 7205 = 14409"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "7213 + 7219 = 14432"}
{"Question": "CARE + CARD = ERROR", "Answer": "7241 + 7243 = 14484"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LOST = ESSAY", "Answer": "7241 + 7245 = 14486"}
{"Question": "BOND + BONE = INNER", "Answer": "7246 + 7249 = 14495"}
{"Question": "TALE + TALK = ENTER", "Answer": "7351 + 7359 = 14710"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LIFT = HELLO", "Answer": "7384 + 7386 = 14770"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAL = LEVEL", "Answer": "7420 + 7421 = 14841"}
{"Question": "POEM + POET = MOTOR", "Answer": "7421 + 7428 = 14849"}
{"Question": "SHOP + SHOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "7491 + 7498 = 14989"}
{"Question": "CLUE + CLUB = ELECT", "Answer": "7581 + 7589 = 15170"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LOST = STEEL", "Answer": "7612 + 7615 = 15227"}
{"Question": "RICE + RICH = THEIR", "Answer": "7632 + 7635 = 15267"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LIFT = STEAL", "Answer": "7642 + 7645 = 15287"}
{"Question": "SALT + SALE = ELITE", "Answer": "7650 + 7651 = 15301"}
{"Question": "BONE + BOND = ENTER", "Answer": "7651 + 7659 = 15310"}
{"Question": "SALT + SALE = METAL", "Answer": "7683 + 7685 = 15368"}
{"Question": "OVEN + OVER = PROVE", "Answer": "7894 + 7895 = 15789"}
{"Question": "CASH + CASE = SHELL", "Answer": "7915 + 7918 = 15833"}
{"Question": "BURY + BURN = HONOR", "Answer": "7924 + 7928 = 15852"}
{"Question": "SHOE + SHOW = FEWER", "Answer": "7925 + 7928 = 15853"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDS = LEGAL", "Answer": "7935 + 7936 = 15871"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAR = TROOP", "Answer": "7941 + 7945 = 15886"}
{"Question": "DEAL + DEAR = TREND", "Answer": "7982 + 7985 = 15967"}
{"Question": "TALE + TALK = ELECT", "Answer": "8061 + 8067 = 16128"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MEAL = ELITE", "Answer": "8175 + 8176 = 16351"}
{"Question": "STAY + STAR = TREAT", "Answer": "8195 + 8196 = 16391"}
{"Question": "RICH + RICE = HONOR", "Answer": "8231 + 8237 = 16468"}
{"Question": "OVEN + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "8261 + 8265 = 16526"}
{"Question": "DARK + DARE = BREAD", "Answer": "8263 + 8265 = 16528"}
{"Question": "AIDE + AIDS = ESSAY", "Answer": "8341 + 8346 = 16687"}
{"Question": "MEAT + MEAL = TABLE", "Answer": "8361 + 8362 = 16723"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "8364 + 8367 = 16731"}
{"Question": "FAIL + FAIR = REFER", "Answer": "8430 + 8431 = 16861"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEAL = RAPID", "Answer": "8461 + 8467 = 16928"}
{"Question": "PALM + PALE = METAL", "Answer": "8471 + 8476 = 16947"}
{"Question": "COAT + COAL = TEACH", "Answer": "8491 + 8492 = 16983"}
{"Question": "FLAG + FLAT = STAFF", "Answer": "8492 + 8496 = 16988"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = FEWER", "Answer": "8536 + 8537 = 17073"}
{"Question": "CORN + CORE = FENCE", "Answer": "8540 + 8547 = 17087"}
{"Question": "CASE + CASH = SLEEP", "Answer": "8612 + 8613 = 17225"}
{"Question": "CASE + CASH = SHEET", "Answer": "8612 + 8617 = 17229"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = ORDER", "Answer": "8673 + 8674 = 17347"}
{"Question": "SALE + SALT = LATER", "Answer": "8712 + 8714 = 17426"}
{"Question": "SHOW + SHOE = WHEEL", "Answer": "8721 + 8724 = 17445"}
{"Question": "SOUL + SOUP = COLOR", "Answer": "8734 + 8736 = 17470"}
{"Question": "CORN + CORE = HONOR", "Answer": "8734 + 8739 = 17473"}
{"Question": "PALM + PALE = SALES", "Answer": "8742 + 8749 = 17491"}
{"Question": "FACT + FACE = REFER", "Answer": "8934 + 8937 = 17871"}
{"Question": "WIND + WINE = FEWER", "Answer": "8935 + 8937 = 17872"}
{"Question": "YEAR + YEAH = THERE", "Answer": "8962 + 8967 = 17929"}
{"Question": "FILM + FILE = ELITE", "Answer": "8970 + 8971 = 17941"}
{"Question": "WARM + WARN = DRAMA", "Answer": "8974 + 8975 = 17949"}
{"Question": "STAY + STAR = TRUST", "Answer": "9143 + 9148 = 18291"}
{"Question": "WORD + WORK = ORDER", "Answer": "9183 + 9185 = 18368"}
{"Question": "HEAR + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "9183 + 9186 = 18369"}
{"Question": "CARD + CARE = MEDIA", "Answer": "9234 + 9238 = 18472"}
{"Question": "BOND + BONE = HELLO", "Answer": "9274 + 9278 = 18552"}
{"Question": "CASE + CASH = WHEEL", "Answer": "9275 + 9278 = 18553"}
{"Question": "BEAR + BEAT = STARE", "Answer": "9375 + 9378 = 18753"}
{"Question": "WORD + WORK = DRESS", "Answer": "9381 + 9385 = 18766"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "9385 + 9387 = 18772"}
{"Question": "BONE + BOND = ERROR", "Answer": "9421 + 9427 = 18848"}
{"Question": "BURY + BURN = INNER", "Answer": "9435 + 9438 = 18873"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEAN = TABLE", "Answer": "9481 + 9483 = 18964"}
{"Question": "TALE + TALK = STEAL", "Answer": "9683 + 9685 = 19368"}
{"Question": "COPE + COME = POEM", "Answer": "1027 + 1047 = 2074"}
{"Question": "DARE + DATE = READ", "Answer": "2041 + 2061 = 4102"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LIKE = FILL", "Answer": "2951 + 2971 = 5922"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BELT = LATE", "Answer": "3251 + 3261 = 6512"}
{"Question": "DARE + DATE = TEAR", "Answer": "4021 + 4081 = 8102"}
{"Question": "PALE + PACE = CELL", "Answer": "4705 + 4795 = 9500"}
{"Question": "CARE + CASE = DRESS", "Answer": "5204 + 5284 = 10488"}
{"Question": "CASE + CARE = SUPER", "Answer": "5218 + 5268 = 10486"}
{"Question": "COAT + COST = BASIS", "Answer": "5308 + 5368 = 10676"}
{"Question": "COPE + CODE = PEACE", "Answer": "5310 + 5340 = 10650"}
{"Question": "TERM + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "5409 + 5489 = 10898"}
{"Question": "BIRD + BIND = INNER", "Answer": "6105 + 6125 = 12230"}
{"Question": "FINE + FIRE = INNER", "Answer": "6127 + 6147 = 12274"}
{"Question": "BAKE + BASE = MAKER", "Answer": "6254 + 6294 = 12548"}
{"Question": "MORE + MODE = ARMED", "Answer": "6327 + 6347 = 12674"}
{"Question": "DIRT + DIET = STAIR", "Answer": "6342 + 6392 = 12734"}
{"Question": "THAN + THEN = SCENE", "Answer": "6409 + 6489 = 12898"}
{"Question": "BELT + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "6432 + 6492 = 12924"}
{"Question": "RISE + RICE = SCENE", "Answer": "6510 + 6530 = 13040"}
{"Question": "THEN + THIN = EIGHT", "Answer": "6518 + 6538 = 13056"}
{"Question": "THAN + THEN = AWARE", "Answer": "6519 + 6589 = 13108"}
{"Question": "TERM + TEAM = MAKER", "Answer": "6521 + 6531 = 13052"}
{"Question": "BITE + BIKE = ELECT", "Answer": "6521 + 6581 = 13102"}
{"Question": "RATE + RACE = OTHER", "Answer": "6538 + 6548 = 13086"}
{"Question": "PAST + PART = STRIP", "Answer": "6713 + 6743 = 13456"}
{"Question": "THAN + THIN = PAINT", "Answer": "6738 + 6748 = 13486"}
{"Question": "RATE + RACE = METER", "Answer": "6753 + 6783 = 13536"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SHUT = COUCH", "Answer": "6839 + 6879 = 13718"}
{"Question": "LIST + LIFT = STEEL", "Answer": "6913 + 6973 = 13886"}
{"Question": "PACE + PAGE = CHEAP", "Answer": "6918 + 6978 = 13896"}
{"Question": "DIET + DIRT = TRIBE", "Answer": "7021 + 7041 = 14062"}
{"Question": "CAKE + CARE = TRACK", "Answer": "7026 + 7046 = 14072"}
{"Question": "BIRD + BIND = PRIOR", "Answer": "7042 + 7052 = 14094"}
{"Question": "SOIL + SOUL = ONION", "Answer": "7132 + 7182 = 14314"}
{"Question": "CODE + COME = ORDER", "Answer": "7132 + 7192 = 14324"}
{"Question": "CORE + COPE = UPPER", "Answer": "7205 + 7245 = 14450"}
{"Question": "BASE + BAKE = ISSUE", "Answer": "7240 + 7250 = 14490"}
{"Question": "THIS + THUS = ASIAN", "Answer": "7254 + 7264 = 14518"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LOUD = ADULT", "Answer": "7314 + 7364 = 14678"}
{"Question": "DARE + DATE = ORDER", "Answer": "7342 + 7382 = 14724"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BEST = SENSE", "Answer": "7402 + 7412 = 14814"}
{"Question": "SHIT + SHOT = PHOTO", "Answer": "7409 + 7489 = 14898"}
{"Question": "BELT + BEST = LEAVE", "Answer": "7412 + 7452 = 14864"}
{"Question": "FILM + FIRM = LIMIT", "Answer": "7418 + 7428 = 14846"}
{"Question": "DRUG + DRAG = GRASS", "Answer": "7431 + 7491 = 14922"}
{"Question": "POET + PORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "7459 + 7489 = 14948"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEAT = LEAVE", "Answer": "7462 + 7492 = 14954"}
{"Question": "CODE + CORE = FORCE", "Answer": "7480 + 7490 = 14970"}
{"Question": "DRUG + DRAG = GRADE", "Answer": "7481 + 7491 = 14972"}
{"Question": "THIN + THEN = WHITE", "Answer": "7508 + 7568 = 15076"}
{"Question": "COPE + CORE = POWER", "Answer": "7518 + 7568 = 15086"}
{"Question": "DIET + DIRT = TITLE", "Answer": "7521 + 7581 = 15102"}
{"Question": "WITH + WISH = SHEET", "Answer": "7605 + 7615 = 15220"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SHUT = OUGHT", "Answer": "7610 + 7650 = 15260"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BELT = ALTER", "Answer": "7612 + 7652 = 15264"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BELT = PLATE", "Answer": "7628 + 7658 = 15286"}
{"Question": "GAME + GATE = METAL", "Answer": "7815 + 7865 = 15680"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TERM = AGREE", "Answer": "7819 + 7869 = 15688"}
{"Question": "DIRT + DIET = THEIR", "Answer": "7821 + 7861 = 15682"}
{"Question": "LIFT + LIST = BASIS", "Answer": "7823 + 7863 = 15686"}
{"Question": "BAKE + BASE = CHEEK", "Answer": "7826 + 7836 = 15662"}
{"Question": "BANK + BACK = OCEAN", "Answer": "7942 + 7952 = 15894"}
{"Question": "RATE + RACE = ACTOR", "Answer": "8139 + 8169 = 16308"}
{"Question": "THUS + THIS = VISIT", "Answer": "8204 + 8264 = 16468"}
{"Question": "RISE + RICE = START", "Answer": "8213 + 8273 = 16486"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LOVE = STEEL", "Answer": "8214 + 8234 = 16448"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEAT = STATE", "Answer": "8216 + 8246 = 16462"}
{"Question": "MODE + MORE = DRAMA", "Answer": "8217 + 8267 = 16484"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "8251 + 8261 = 16512"}
{"Question": "WAIT + WANT = ONION", "Answer": "8253 + 8263 = 16516"}
{"Question": "HAVE + HATE = TOOTH", "Answer": "8304 + 8314 = 16618"}
{"Question": "HARD + HAND = INNER", "Answer": "8305 + 8365 = 16670"}
{"Question": "RATE + RACE = OCCUR", "Answer": "8309 + 8369 = 16678"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TERM = ASSET", "Answer": "8314 + 8324 = 16638"}
{"Question": "ROLE + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "8329 + 8369 = 16698"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TERM = ADAPT", "Answer": "8514 + 8594 = 17108"}
{"Question": "SAME + SALE = METAL", "Answer": "8617 + 8647 = 17264"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LOUD = DRAMA", "Answer": "8621 + 8631 = 17252"}
{"Question": "DATE + DARE = METER", "Answer": "8627 + 8647 = 17274"}
{"Question": "DRUG + DRAG = EAGER", "Answer": "8643 + 8673 = 17316"}
{"Question": "DARE + DATE = BROAD", "Answer": "8674 + 8694 = 17368"}
{"Question": "COME + CODE = MODEL", "Answer": "8716 + 8746 = 17462"}
{"Question": "CARE + CAKE = EAGER", "Answer": "8721 + 8791 = 17512"}
{"Question": "FILE + FIVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8726 + 8746 = 17472"}
{"Question": "PAGE + PACE = EAGER", "Answer": "8751 + 8761 = 17512"}
{"Question": "HATE + HAVE = CATCH", "Answer": "8754 + 8764 = 17518"}
{"Question": "WIFE + WIDE = FEWER", "Answer": "8917 + 8957 = 17874"}
{"Question": "TERM + TEAM = MOTOR", "Answer": "8921 + 8951 = 17872"}
{"Question": "SHOT + SHIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "9065 + 9085 = 18150"}
{"Question": "COME + CORE = METER", "Answer": "9218 + 9268 = 18486"}
{"Question": "BELT + BEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9231 + 9281 = 18512"}
{"Question": "RATE + RACE = EXTRA", "Answer": "9241 + 9251 = 18492"}
{"Question": "SHUT + SHOT = TOUCH", "Answer": "9251 + 9281 = 18532"}
{"Question": "STIR + STAR = DRAMA", "Answer": "9308 + 9368 = 18676"}
{"Question": "COPE + CODE = PRIOR", "Answer": "9314 + 9324 = 18638"}
{"Question": "TEAM + TERM = ORDER", "Answer": "9354 + 9384 = 18738"}
{"Question": "STEP + STOP = LOOSE", "Answer": "9405 + 9485 = 18890"}
{"Question": "SHIP + SHOP = LOOSE", "Answer": "9406 + 9486 = 18892"}
{"Question": "LATE + LAKE = ELECT", "Answer": "9521 + 9581 = 19102"}
{"Question": "SAFE + SALE = USUAL", "Answer": "9574 + 9584 = 19158"}
{"Question": "HATE + HAVE = SHEET", "Answer": "9826 + 9836 = 19662"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HIDE = THEIR", "Answer": "9826 + 9856 = 19682"}
{"Question": "HIDE + HIRE = AHEAD", "Answer": "9847 + 9867 = 19714"}
{"Question": "THIS + THUS = STUFF", "Answer": "9851 + 9871 = 19722"}
{"Question": "SURE + SUCH = DRESS", "Answer": "5306 + 5349 = 10655"}
{"Question": "MATH + MAKE = THEME", "Answer": "5310 + 5346 = 10656"}
{"Question": "DENY + DECK = NAKED", "Answer": "5417 + 5428 = 10845"}
{"Question": "RING + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "6129 + 6147 = 12276"}
{"Question": "WITH + WING = TIGHT", "Answer": "6217 + 6254 = 12471"}
{"Question": "BANK + BASE = NAKED", "Answer": "6214 + 6279 = 12493"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LOAD = SALES", "Answer": "6314 + 6327 = 12641"}
{"Question": "DEAR + DEBT = TRADE", "Answer": "6372 + 6391 = 12763"}
{"Question": "FLAT + FLOW = STAFF", "Answer": "6372 + 6394 = 12766"}
{"Question": "BEAN + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "6423 + 6491 = 12914"}
{"Question": "STAY + STEP = APART", "Answer": "6512 + 6593 = 13105"}
{"Question": "PACE + PART = TREAT", "Answer": "6520 + 6531 = 13051"}
{"Question": "PAST + PALE = SLEEP", "Answer": "6712 + 6734 = 13446"}
{"Question": "DRUG + DRAW = GUARD", "Answer": "6731 + 6745 = 13476"}
{"Question": "LOVE + LOAN = NEVER", "Answer": "6753 + 6781 = 13534"}
{"Question": "FATE + FAIR = TREAT", "Answer": "6918 + 6973 = 13891"}
{"Question": "HURT + HUGE = TRUTH", "Answer": "6931 + 6985 = 13916"}
{"Question": "PARK + PAGE = AGREE", "Answer": "7120 + 7146 = 14266"}
{"Question": "TEND + TEAR = EARTH", "Answer": "7136 + 7142 = 14278"}
{"Question": "BOWL + BOAT = ALLOW", "Answer": "7204 + 7216 = 14420"}
{"Question": "SUIT + SURE = INNER", "Answer": "7218 + 7235 = 14453"}
{"Question": "CODE + COST = ESSAY", "Answer": "7231 + 7249 = 14480"}
{"Question": "CORN + COPE = UPPER", "Answer": "7235 + 7248 = 14483"}
{"Question": "RACE + RANK = INNER", "Answer": "7238 + 7249 = 14487"}
{"Question": "CARE + CAMP = ERROR", "Answer": "7241 + 7253 = 14494"}
{"Question": "COME + COAT = METER", "Answer": "7314 + 7326 = 14640"}
{"Question": "LOVE + LOTS = STEEL", "Answer": "7326 + 7341 = 14667"}
{"Question": "TURN + TUBE = ENTER", "Answer": "7354 + 7361 = 14715"}
{"Question": "HERO + HEAT = OTHER", "Answer": "7351 + 7384 = 14735"}
{"Question": "EACH + EAST = TASTE", "Answer": "7426 + 7491 = 14917"}
{"Question": "SOUL + SORT = TRUST", "Answer": "7620 + 7651 = 15271"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DEAL = BLADE", "Answer": "7813 + 7865 = 15678"}
{"Question": "SOUP + SOIL = PRIOR", "Answer": "7821 + 7864 = 15685"}
{"Question": "REST + REAL = LATER", "Answer": "7836 + 7851 = 15687"}
{"Question": "LAST + LACK = SKILL", "Answer": "7912 + 7965 = 15877"}
{"Question": "CASH + CAKE = SHEET", "Answer": "7915 + 7968 = 15883"}
{"Question": "SONG + SORT = GRASS", "Answer": "7921 + 7956 = 15877"}
{"Question": "EAST + EACH = STATE", "Answer": "8016 + 8052 = 16068"}
{"Question": "RATE + RAIL = ALTER", "Answer": "8132 + 8196 = 16328"}
{"Question": "PALE + PAST = STEAL", "Answer": "8204 + 8216 = 16420"}
{"Question": "HURT + HUGE = METER", "Answer": "8204 + 8256 = 16460"}
{"Question": "FILM + FIVE = LEVEL", "Answer": "8215 + 8246 = 16461"}
{"Question": "HERO + HEAD = OFFER", "Answer": "8301 + 8329 = 16630"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DEAR = BRAND", "Answer": "8412 + 8496 = 16908"}
{"Question": "POET + POUR = TRUTH", "Answer": "8421 + 8496 = 16917"}
{"Question": "SELF + SEAT = WASTE", "Answer": "8425 + 8469 = 16894"}
{"Question": "LACK + LATE = METAL", "Answer": "8452 + 8496 = 16948"}
{"Question": "CHEF + CHIP = PIECE", "Answer": "8509 + 8571 = 17080"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LONG = AGAIN", "Answer": "8512 + 8597 = 17109"}
{"Question": "HATE + HAIR = EIGHT", "Answer": "8601 + 8679 = 17280"}
{"Question": "CASE + CAMP = SPEAK", "Answer": "8612 + 8657 = 17269"}
{"Question": "SOME + SORT = MOTOR", "Answer": "8712 + 8764 = 17476"}
{"Question": "LONG + LOVE = NOVEL", "Answer": "8713 + 8745 = 17458"}
{"Question": "BOTH + BORN = HONOR", "Answer": "8721 + 8754 = 17475"}
{"Question": "RIDE + RICH = AHEAD", "Answer": "9235 + 9278 = 18513"}
{"Question": "STEP + STAR = PRESS", "Answer": "9241 + 9258 = 18499"}
{"Question": "BEST + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "9318 + 9365 = 18683"}
{"Question": "FADE + FAIR = DRESS", "Answer": "9316 + 9328 = 18644"}
{"Question": "WISE + WITH = SHEET", "Answer": "9316 + 9348 = 18664"}
{"Question": "HEAD + HERO = ORDER", "Answer": "9357 + 9381 = 18738"}
{"Question": "TIRE + TINY = ENTER", "Answer": "9431 + 9482 = 18913"}
{"Question": "CORE + CARE = AREA", "Answer": "2387 + 2487 = 4874"}
{"Question": "PLAY + PRAY = ALLY", "Answer": "3470 + 3970 = 7440"}
{"Question": "MYTH + MATH = THAT", "Answer": "4189 + 4789 = 8978"}
{"Question": "PAST + POST = STOP", "Answer": "4392 + 4892 = 9284"}
{"Question": "SHOP + STOP = THESE", "Answer": "5076 + 5176 = 10252"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OVEN = PROVE", "Answer": "5168 + 5368 = 10536"}
{"Question": "PRAY + PLAY = SHALL", "Answer": "6094 + 6894 = 12988"}
{"Question": "PLAY + PRAY = LAYER", "Answer": "6129 + 6829 = 12958"}
{"Question": "STOP + SHOP = THOSE", "Answer": "6134 + 6234 = 12368"}
{"Question": "LIKE + LAKE = IDEAL", "Answer": "6138 + 6738 = 12876"}
{"Question": "PART + PORT = ADAPT", "Answer": "6180 + 6980 = 13160"}
{"Question": "LAST + LIST = STEAL", "Answer": "6213 + 6813 = 13026"}
{"Question": "RACE + RICE = CLEAR", "Answer": "6318 + 6518 = 12836"}
{"Question": "SOME + SAME = LOOSE", "Answer": "6380 + 6980 = 13360"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LEAD = TOTAL", "Answer": "6398 + 6798 = 13196"}
{"Question": "THIN + TWIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "6432 + 6732 = 13164"}
{"Question": "ROAD + READ = PAPER", "Answer": "6438 + 6738 = 13176"}
{"Question": "BAND + BIND = IDEAL", "Answer": "7054 + 7154 = 14208"}
{"Question": "VERY + VARY = EARLY", "Answer": "7160 + 7460 = 14620"}
{"Question": "BORN + BURN = OCCUR", "Answer": "7163 + 7263 = 14426"}
{"Question": "BEND + BAND = NAKED", "Answer": "7210 + 7410 = 14620"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BOAT = TABLE", "Answer": "7241 + 7541 = 14782"}
{"Question": "LOST + LIST = PILOT", "Answer": "7260 + 7460 = 14720"}
{"Question": "BIND + BAND = CABIN", "Answer": "7263 + 7463 = 14726"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LEAD = HELLO", "Answer": "7286 + 7486 = 14772"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LEAD = DELAY", "Answer": "7301 + 7401 = 14702"}
{"Question": "SNOW + SHOW = UNION", "Answer": "7402 + 7502 = 14904"}
{"Question": "BAND + BEND = SALAD", "Answer": "7420 + 7520 = 14940"}
{"Question": "FORM + FARM = MOTOR", "Answer": "7421 + 7521 = 14942"}
{"Question": "LOAD + LEAD = STATE", "Answer": "7429 + 7829 = 15258"}
{"Question": "BOND + BEND = NOISE", "Answer": "7514 + 7814 = 15328"}
{"Question": "LIFT + LEFT = BIBLE", "Answer": "7538 + 7638 = 15176"}
{"Question": "BEND + BOND = VIDEO", "Answer": "7634 + 7834 = 15468"}
{"Question": "SLOW + SHOW = TOOTH", "Answer": "7659 + 7859 = 15518"}
{"Question": "ROAD + READ = INNER", "Answer": "8079 + 8579 = 16658"}
{"Question": "BIND + BEND = INDEX", "Answer": "8165 + 8365 = 16530"}
{"Question": "TAPE + TYPE = APPLY", "Answer": "8167 + 8467 = 16634"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BOAT = ERROR", "Answer": "8173 + 8473 = 16646"}
{"Question": "SONG + SING = AGAIN", "Answer": "8247 + 8947 = 17194"}
{"Question": "VARY + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "8293 + 8693 = 16986"}
{"Question": "LACK + LUCK = RURAL", "Answer": "8369 + 8769 = 17138"}
{"Question": "LEFT + LIFT = STATE", "Answer": "8437 + 8637 = 17074"}
{"Question": "BEAT + BOAT = STATE", "Answer": "8437 + 8937 = 17374"}
{"Question": "PRAY + PLAY = CARRY", "Answer": "8470 + 8970 = 17440"}
{"Question": "LAKE + LIKE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8539 + 8739 = 17278"}
{"Question": "PALE + POLE = COLOR", "Answer": "8635 + 8735 = 17370"}
{"Question": "LOVE + LIVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "8639 + 8739 = 17378"}
{"Question": "LOAN + LEAN = HONOR", "Answer": "8736 + 8936 = 17672"}
{"Question": "ROAD + READ = NERVE", "Answer": "9064 + 9864 = 18928"}
{"Question": "THIN + TWIN = HONOR", "Answer": "9143 + 9243 = 18386"}
{"Question": "LAKE + LIKE = ALTER", "Answer": "9162 + 9862 = 19024"}
{"Question": "FARM + FIRM = AFTER", "Answer": "9163 + 9863 = 19026"}
{"Question": "BAND + BEND = ABOVE", "Answer": "9164 + 9864 = 19028"}
{"Question": "SAND + SEND = ASIDE", "Answer": "9174 + 9874 = 19048"}
{"Question": "BIND + BEND = INNER", "Answer": "9182 + 9682 = 18864"}
{"Question": "TYPE + TAPE = ESSAY", "Answer": "9231 + 9631 = 18862"}
{"Question": "LIVE + LOVE = HELLO", "Answer": "9348 + 9648 = 18996"}
{"Question": "THUS + TOUR = SHOOT", "Answer": "5031 + 5634 = 10665"}
{"Question": "TOUR + THUS = HORSE", "Answer": "5072 + 5174 = 10246"}
{"Question": "TAIL + TRIP = ALTER", "Answer": "6142 + 6543 = 12685"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OVER = PROVE", "Answer": "6175 + 6472 = 12647"}
{"Question": "LAST + LOSE = SALES", "Answer": "6218 + 6413 = 12631"}
{"Question": "DRAG + DEAL = GRADE", "Answer": "6281 + 6584 = 12865"}
{"Question": "SLIP + SHIT = ELITE", "Answer": "6284 + 6587 = 12871"}
{"Question": "TOUR + THUS = COURT", "Answer": "6287 + 6589 = 12876"}
{"Question": "LOSE + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "6345 + 6841 = 13186"}
{"Question": "WHAT + WEAK = THREE", "Answer": "6391 + 6897 = 13288"}
{"Question": "SHIT + SKIN = TOOTH", "Answer": "7051 + 7359 = 14410"}
{"Question": "WEST + WASH = TASTE", "Answer": "7051 + 7459 = 14510"}
{"Question": "HERO + HARD = ERROR", "Answer": "7149 + 7345 = 14494"}
{"Question": "TANK + TEND = ADAPT", "Answer": "7182 + 7985 = 15167"}
{"Question": "HOLY + HELP = CYCLE", "Answer": "7205 + 7904 = 15109"}
{"Question": "RISK + REST = STAIR", "Answer": "7213 + 7614 = 14827"}
{"Question": "DRAW + DEAL = AWARE", "Answer": "7215 + 7914 = 15129"}
{"Question": "GEAR + GOAL = LEVEL", "Answer": "7420 + 7521 = 14941"}
{"Question": "ROCK + RICH = HONOR", "Answer": "7426 + 7521 = 14947"}
{"Question": "WRAP + WHAT = PAPER", "Answer": "7451 + 7653 = 15104"}
{"Question": "TRIP + THIS = IRISH", "Answer": "7514 + 7612 = 15126"}
{"Question": "ROAD + REAL = FLOOR", "Answer": "7682 + 7985 = 15667"}
{"Question": "LAND + LINE = IDEAL", "Answer": "8056 + 8152 = 16208"}
{"Question": "LATE + LOTS = ASSET", "Answer": "8137 + 8536 = 16673"}
{"Question": "TEAR + THAN = ENTRY", "Answer": "8149 + 8746 = 16895"}
{"Question": "CORE + CARD = ERROR", "Answer": "8261 + 8365 = 16626"}
{"Question": "LATE + LOTS = STEAL", "Answer": "8267 + 8461 = 16728"}
{"Question": "STIR + SPIN = APART", "Answer": "8425 + 8729 = 17154"}
{"Question": "DARE + DIRT = TREAT", "Answer": "8470 + 8571 = 17041"}
{"Question": "WEAK + WRAP = PAPER", "Answer": "8475 + 8671 = 17146"}
{"Question": "SELF + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "8532 + 8631 = 17163"}
{"Question": "SHIP + STIR = APART", "Answer": "8547 + 8649 = 17196"}
{"Question": "STOP + SHOE = PHOTO", "Answer": "8631 + 8732 = 17363"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "9081 + 9687 = 18768"}
{"Question": "CARD + CORE = ORDER", "Answer": "9082 + 9186 = 18268"}
{"Question": "OPEN + OVER = PRESS", "Answer": "9165 + 9468 = 18633"}
{"Question": "MENU + MANY = HUMAN", "Answer": "9238 + 9735 = 18973"}
{"Question": "HURT + HIRE = THEIR", "Answer": "9541 + 9843 = 19384"}
{"Question": "RACE + RICH = TREAT", "Answer": "9735 + 9836 = 19571"}
{"Question": "DECK + DARK = AREA", "Answer": "3028 + 3678 = 6706"}
{"Question": "PAGE + PURE = EAGER", "Answer": "5091 + 5821 = 10912"}
{"Question": "LAST + LEFT = TASTE", "Answer": "5031 + 5281 = 10312"}
{"Question": "BEND + BIRD = INNER", "Answer": "6024 + 6184 = 12208"}
{"Question": "HEAT + HURT = EARTH", "Answer": "6128 + 6458 = 12586"}
{"Question": "TALE + TRUE = LATER", "Answer": "6217 + 6457 = 12674"}
{"Question": "CITE + COPE = PIECE", "Answer": "6350 + 6710 = 13060"}
{"Question": "LIFE + LATE = TITLE", "Answer": "6350 + 6810 = 13160"}
{"Question": "PLOT + PAST = STEEL", "Answer": "6482 + 6512 = 12994"}
{"Question": "TAPE + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "6534 + 6814 = 13348"}
{"Question": "FOUR + FAIR = UNION", "Answer": "7012 + 7892 = 14904"}
{"Question": "SIDE + SAME = MEDIA", "Answer": "7094 + 7814 = 14908"}
{"Question": "ROPE + RATE = APART", "Answer": "7046 + 7126 = 14172"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TONE = ROUTE", "Answer": "7150 + 7420 = 14570"}
{"Question": "HOLE + HUGE = OUGHT", "Answer": "7123 + 7453 = 14576"}
{"Question": "LAST + LEFT = ASSET", "Answer": "7140 + 7280 = 14420"}
{"Question": "SUIT + SOFT = UNION", "Answer": "7152 + 7382 = 14534"}
{"Question": "SPOT + SEAT = PLATE", "Answer": "7153 + 7683 = 14836"}
{"Question": "DEBT + DIRT = TRADE", "Answer": "7231 + 7641 = 14872"}
{"Question": "PLOT + PANT = TOTAL", "Answer": "7251 + 7941 = 15192"}
{"Question": "SOFT + SEAT = FENCE", "Answer": "7312 + 7492 = 14804"}
{"Question": "CORE + CLUE = RURAL", "Answer": "7314 + 7854 = 15168"}
{"Question": "POSE + PURE = SUPER", "Answer": "7318 + 7468 = 14786"}
{"Question": "GATE + GIVE = EIGHT", "Answer": "7321 + 7461 = 14782"}
{"Question": "CAMP + CHIP = WHICH", "Answer": "7392 + 7482 = 14874"}
{"Question": "SNAP + SHOP = ONION", "Answer": "7402 + 7512 = 14914"}
{"Question": "SLIP + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "7461 + 7821 = 15282"}
{"Question": "CAMP + CHIP = MATCH", "Answer": "7514 + 7864 = 15378"}
{"Question": "SOFT + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "7541 + 7621 = 15162"}
{"Question": "THAN + TOWN = WATCH", "Answer": "7854 + 7914 = 15768"}
{"Question": "STEP + SHOP = THOSE", "Answer": "8105 + 8675 = 16780"}
{"Question": "RULE + ROPE = UPPER", "Answer": "8129 + 8569 = 16698"}
{"Question": "PAGE + PURE = AGREE", "Answer": "8160 + 8240 = 16400"}
{"Question": "LAKE + LOSE = SOLAR", "Answer": "8207 + 8617 = 16824"}
{"Question": "HOLD + HEAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "8213 + 8693 = 16906"}
{"Question": "BLUE + BASE = USUAL", "Answer": "8216 + 8976 = 17192"}
{"Question": "HATE + HOLE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8416 + 8726 = 17142"}
{"Question": "LATE + LOSE = TOTAL", "Answer": "8419 + 8729 = 17148"}
{"Question": "LINE + LOVE = NOVEL", "Answer": "8614 + 8734 = 17348"}
{"Question": "CODE + CITE = VIDEO", "Answer": "8643 + 8793 = 17436"}
{"Question": "ROLE + RACE = COLOR", "Answer": "8764 + 8914 = 17678"}
{"Question": "HOST + HEAT = TASTE", "Answer": "9031 + 9281 = 18312"}
{"Question": "SHOP + STEP = HELLO", "Answer": "9163 + 9283 = 18446"}
{"Question": "FACE + FIRE = AFTER", "Answer": "9173 + 9863 = 19036"}
{"Question": "TRUE + TONE = ENTER", "Answer": "9231 + 9681 = 18912"}
{"Question": "HIRE + HATE = THEIR", "Answer": "9542 + 9712 = 19254"}
{"Question": "CHIP + CREW = WHICH", "Answer": "5089 + 5761 = 10850"}
{"Question": "CHEF + COAL = HELLO", "Answer": "6129 + 6758 = 12887"}
{"Question": "CHIP + COAT = PATCH", "Answer": "7421 + 7953 = 15374"}
{"Question": "CLUE + CROP = UPPER", "Answer": "7614 + 7935 = 15549"}
{"Question": "STOP + SIGH = PHOTO", "Answer": "8271 + 8456 = 16727"}
{"Question": "DRAW + DEBT = AWARE", "Answer": "8517 + 8639 = 17156"}
{"Question": "HERO + HANG = RANGE", "Answer": "8612 + 8734 = 17346"}
{"Question": "PANT + WANT = PHOTO", "Answer": "1237 + 9237 = 10474"}
{"Question": "BEAN + MEAN = BLAME", "Answer": "1246 + 9246 = 10492"}
{"Question": "HOST + COST = HELLO", "Answer": "1276 + 9276 = 10552"}
{"Question": "BIKE + LIKE = BREAK", "Answer": "1326 + 9326 = 10652"}
{"Question": "FAST + CAST = FENCE", "Answer": "1345 + 9345 = 10690"}
{"Question": "BEAR + TEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1346 + 9346 = 10692"}
{"Question": "BAKE + CAKE = BLOCK", "Answer": "1347 + 9347 = 10694"}
{"Question": "DUST + MUST = DRAMA", "Answer": "1348 + 9348 = 10696"}
{"Question": "COST + LOST = CATCH", "Answer": "1357 + 9357 = 10714"}
{"Question": "COAT + BOAT = CLASS", "Answer": "1372 + 9372 = 10744"}
{"Question": "BEAR + DEAR = CARD", "Answer": "1374 + 8374 = 9748"}
{"Question": "BEAN + LEAN = BRAND", "Answer": "1374 + 9374 = 10748"}
{"Question": "CARE + DARE = CHEEK", "Answer": "1387 + 9387 = 10774"}
{"Question": "BEND + SEND = BLADE", "Answer": "1437 + 9437 = 10874"}
{"Question": "CAST + VAST = CIVIL", "Answer": "1453 + 9453 = 10906"}
{"Question": "TEND + SEND = TASTE", "Answer": "1457 + 9457 = 10914"}
{"Question": "SIDE + AIDE = SHALL", "Answer": "1483 + 9483 = 10966"}
{"Question": "EARN + WARN = ESSAY", "Answer": "1527 + 8527 = 10054"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HIDE = ASSET", "Answer": "1537 + 8537 = 10074"}
{"Question": "LAND + SAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "1543 + 8543 = 10086"}
{"Question": "COAL + GOAL = CYCLE", "Answer": "1562 + 8562 = 10124"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "1563 + 8563 = 10126"}
{"Question": "POLE + ROLE = PAPER", "Answer": "1574 + 8574 = 10148"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HIDE = AGAIN", "Answer": "1576 + 8576 = 10152"}
{"Question": "RATE + LATE = RURAL", "Answer": "1579 + 8579 = 10158"}
{"Question": "BEAN + MEAN = BLADE", "Answer": "1623 + 8623 = 10246"}
{"Question": "BAND + HAND = BENCH", "Answer": "1629 + 8629 = 10258"}
{"Question": "CITE + SITE = CHEST", "Answer": "1642 + 8642 = 10284"}
{"Question": "CHIP + SHIP = CRASH", "Answer": "1643 + 8643 = 10286"}
{"Question": "CAKE + LAKE = CIVIL", "Answer": "1654 + 8654 = 10308"}
{"Question": "COLD + HOLD = CATCH", "Answer": "1659 + 8659 = 10318"}
{"Question": "DOWN + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "1673 + 4673 = 6346"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = EXTRA", "Answer": "1673 + 8673 = 10346"}
{"Question": "PICK + SICK = PEACE", "Answer": "1695 + 8695 = 10390"}
{"Question": "GAME + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "1724 + 8724 = 10448"}
{"Question": "BEAR + HEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "1734 + 8734 = 10468"}
{"Question": "FIND + BIND = FENCE", "Answer": "1745 + 8745 = 10490"}
{"Question": "BEND + SEND = BASIS", "Answer": "1934 + 8934 = 10868"}
{"Question": "BEST + REST = BIRTH", "Answer": "1937 + 8937 = 10874"}
{"Question": "CAST + EAST = CHEEK", "Answer": "1943 + 8943 = 10886"}
{"Question": "BAND + HAND = BLADE", "Answer": "1962 + 8962 = 10924"}
{"Question": "BAKE + MAKE = BLACK", "Answer": "1963 + 8963 = 10926"}
{"Question": "BAND + HAND = BEACH", "Answer": "1964 + 8964 = 10928"}
{"Question": "LACK + BACK = LEAVE", "Answer": "1965 + 8965 = 10930"}
{"Question": "CAKE + BAKE = CLASS", "Answer": "1972 + 8972 = 10944"}
{"Question": "PAST + EAST = PLATE", "Answer": "1974 + 8974 = 10948"}
{"Question": "PORT + SORT = LOOSE", "Answer": "2043 + 8043 = 10086"}
{"Question": "LOST + COST = TOTAL", "Answer": "2071 + 8071 = 10142"}
{"Question": "TEND + BEND = ENTER", "Answer": "2107 + 8107 = 10214"}
{"Question": "GATE + RATE = ANGER", "Answer": "2149 + 8149 = 10298"}
{"Question": "EARN + WARN = NURSE", "Answer": "2371 + 8371 = 10742"}
{"Question": "TAIL + MAIL = LIMIT", "Answer": "2401 + 8401 = 10802"}
{"Question": "CAST + PAST = TOPIC", "Answer": "2431 + 8431 = 10862"}
{"Question": "HIRE + TIRE = EARTH", "Answer": "2491 + 8491 = 10982"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = SLEEP", "Answer": "2614 + 7614 = 10228"}
{"Question": "ROLE + HOLE = ERROR", "Answer": "2631 + 9631 = 12262"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = THEME", "Answer": "2641 + 7641 = 10282"}
{"Question": "RACE + FACE = ERROR", "Answer": "2641 + 9641 = 12282"}
{"Question": "LAKE + BAKE = ABLE", "Answer": "2710 + 4710 = 7420"}
{"Question": "REST + WEST = TOWER", "Answer": "2891 + 7891 = 10782"}
{"Question": "SEND + BEND = DRESS", "Answer": "2961 + 7961 = 10922"}
{"Question": "EAST + FAST = SAFE", "Answer": "2971 + 4971 = 7942"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = TRADE", "Answer": "2981 + 7981 = 10962"}
{"Question": "RACE + FACE = AGREE", "Answer": "3150 + 9150 = 12300"}
{"Question": "RAIL + FAIL = AGREE", "Answer": "3194 + 7194 = 10388"}
{"Question": "BEAR + DEAR = NAKED", "Answer": "3529 + 8529 = 12058"}
{"Question": "WARN + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "3642 + 8642 = 12284"}
{"Question": "AIDE + RIDE = OFFER", "Answer": "3649 + 8649 = 12298"}
{"Question": "RING + KING = AGREE", "Answer": "3672 + 8672 = 12344"}
{"Question": "BEAR + YEAR = CARRY", "Answer": "3724 + 8724 = 12448"}
{"Question": "BLOW + SLOW = LOSS", "Answer": "3872 + 4872 = 8744"}
{"Question": "BEAN + MEAN = NAME", "Answer": "3879 + 5879 = 9758"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = STATE", "Answer": "4012 + 8012 = 12024"}
{"Question": "YARD + CARD = READY", "Answer": "4012 + 9012 = 13024"}
{"Question": "SITE + BITE = EXIST", "Answer": "4021 + 9021 = 13042"}
{"Question": "EAST + CAST = ASSET", "Answer": "4120 + 8120 = 12240"}
{"Question": "CLUE + BLUE = UNCLE", "Answer": "4210 + 9210 = 13420"}
{"Question": "BEAT + HEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "4231 + 9231 = 13462"}
{"Question": "BAKE + TAKE = HABIT", "Answer": "4239 + 8239 = 12478"}
{"Question": "CARD + YARD = HAPPY", "Answer": "4279 + 8279 = 12558"}
{"Question": "DOWN + TOWN = WOUND", "Answer": "4312 + 9312 = 13624"}
{"Question": "REST + BEST = METER", "Answer": "4367 + 9367 = 13734"}
{"Question": "YOUR + FOUR = SORRY", "Answer": "4387 + 9387 = 13774"}
{"Question": "DEAR + WEAR = CROWD", "Answer": "4392 + 8392 = 12784"}
{"Question": "BEAR + DEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "4397 + 5397 = 9794"}
{"Question": "NICE + RICE = SCENE", "Answer": "4520 + 7520 = 12040"}
{"Question": "DEAL + MEAL = SALAD", "Answer": "4602 + 5602 = 10204"}
{"Question": "READ + HEAD = ORDER", "Answer": "4632 + 9632 = 14264"}
{"Question": "BEAT + SEAT = LOOSE", "Answer": "4638 + 7638 = 12276"}
{"Question": "DEAL + MEAL = BLOOD", "Answer": "4832 + 7832 = 12664"}
{"Question": "LAKE + TAKE = METAL", "Answer": "4892 + 7892 = 12784"}
{"Question": "LAST + EAST = APPLE", "Answer": "5179 + 8179 = 13358"}
{"Question": "BEAR + YEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "5234 + 8234 = 13468"}
{"Question": "SITE + BITE = VISIT", "Answer": "5263 + 7263 = 12526"}
{"Question": "CAST + LAST = STEEL", "Answer": "5614 + 8614 = 14228"}
{"Question": "SHIP + CHIP = PIECE", "Answer": "5641 + 8641 = 14282"}
{"Question": "GAIN + RAIN = INNER", "Answer": "5714 + 8714 = 14428"}
{"Question": "LOAD + ROAD = EARLY", "Answer": "5827 + 6827 = 12654"}
{"Question": "BEAR + YEAR = MAYBE", "Answer": "5829 + 6829 = 12658"}
{"Question": "CITE + SITE = BASIS", "Answer": "5843 + 6843 = 12686"}
{"Question": "GRAY + PRAY = HAPPY", "Answer": "5940 + 8940 = 14880"}
{"Question": "DEAL + REAL = CARRY", "Answer": "5943 + 8943 = 14886"}
{"Question": "CAKE + TAKE = REACT", "Answer": "6034 + 8034 = 14068"}
{"Question": "PARK + MARK = DRAMA", "Answer": "6035 + 7035 = 13070"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "6132 + 7132 = 13264"}
{"Question": "YEAR + BEAR = ESSAY", "Answer": "6198 + 7198 = 13396"}
{"Question": "DEAR + BEAR = ARMED", "Answer": "6213 + 7213 = 13426"}
{"Question": "TEAR + BEAR = ASSET", "Answer": "6213 + 8213 = 14426"}
{"Question": "CHIP + SHIP = PITCH", "Answer": "6231 + 7231 = 13462"}
{"Question": "BEAR + NEAR = URBAN", "Answer": "6304 + 8304 = 14608"}
{"Question": "TALE + MALE = LATER", "Answer": "6312 + 7312 = 13624"}
{"Question": "AIDE + HIDE = DEATH", "Answer": "6314 + 8314 = 14628"}
{"Question": "REST + BEST = TERMS", "Answer": "6321 + 7321 = 13642"}
{"Question": "BACK + PACK = HAPPY", "Answer": "6385 + 7385 = 13770"}
{"Question": "DUST + JUST = STAND", "Answer": "6413 + 7413 = 13826"}
{"Question": "ROAD + LOAD = COLOR", "Answer": "6423 + 8423 = 14846"}
{"Question": "GOAL + COAL = LARGE", "Answer": "6431 + 7431 = 13862"}
{"Question": "BANK + RANK = MAKER", "Answer": "6479 + 8479 = 14958"}
{"Question": "FINE + LINE = BIBLE", "Answer": "6590 + 8590 = 15180"}
{"Question": "LOSE + NOSE = HELLO", "Answer": "6834 + 7834 = 14668"}
{"Question": "ROAD + LOAD = ERROR", "Answer": "6843 + 9843 = 16686"}
{"Question": "BAND + LAND = PANEL", "Answer": "7629 + 8629 = 16258"}
{"Question": "WARN + EARN = ANGER", "Answer": "8147 + 9147 = 17294"}
{"Question": "RIDE + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "8624 + 9624 = 18248"}
{"Question": "SEAT + DEAL = SALAD", "Answer": "1205 + 9204 = 10409"}
{"Question": "BELT + RELY = BUYER", "Answer": "1264 + 9265 = 10529"}
{"Question": "TANK + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "1345 + 9346 = 10691"}
{"Question": "LEAD + TEAM = LIMIT", "Answer": "1352 + 9357 = 10709"}
{"Question": "CHIP + SHIT = CATCH", "Answer": "1356 + 9357 = 10713"}
{"Question": "AIDS + RIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1358 + 9357 = 10715"}
{"Question": "LAND + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "1364 + 9367 = 10731"}
{"Question": "BEAN + DEAL = BRAND", "Answer": "1374 + 9375 = 10749"}
{"Question": "WEST + DESK = WASTE", "Answer": "1375 + 9378 = 10753"}
{"Question": "BEAN + DEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "1563 + 8562 = 10125"}
{"Question": "TEAR + BEAN = THREE", "Answer": "1632 + 8634 = 10266"}
{"Question": "HARD + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "1652 + 8653 = 10305"}
{"Question": "FLOW + PLOT = FEWER", "Answer": "1653 + 8654 = 10307"}
{"Question": "SHIP + THIN = SENSE", "Answer": "1657 + 8653 = 10310"}
{"Question": "COST + LOSE = CATCH", "Answer": "1653 + 8659 = 10312"}
{"Question": "HERO + TERM = HUMOR", "Answer": "1674 + 8673 = 10347"}
{"Question": "AUTO + DUTY = ABOUT", "Answer": "1734 + 8739 = 10473"}
{"Question": "DARE + FARM = AHEAD", "Answer": "2153 + 8159 = 10312"}
{"Question": "PILE + WILD = DEEP", "Answer": "2163 + 7169 = 9332"}
{"Question": "EACH + BACK = AHEAD", "Answer": "3152 + 9158 = 12310"}
{"Question": "GAIN + FAIL = ANGLE", "Answer": "3172 + 9174 = 12346"}
{"Question": "RANK + HANG = AGREE", "Answer": "3184 + 9182 = 12366"}
{"Question": "LIFE + GIFT = FIELD", "Answer": "3214 + 9216 = 12430"}
{"Question": "HANG + TANK = NIGHT", "Answer": "3418 + 7419 = 10837"}
{"Question": "BEAT + REAL = LATER", "Answer": "3428 + 9421 = 12849"}
{"Question": "SEND + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "3672 + 9674 = 13346"}
{"Question": "EARN + CARD = FENCE", "Answer": "3846 + 9847 = 13693"}
{"Question": "EACH + PACK = CHEAP", "Answer": "4213 + 9216 = 13429"}
{"Question": "FIRE + BIRD = REFER", "Answer": "4213 + 9218 = 13431"}
{"Question": "PEAK + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "4715 + 9712 = 14427"}
{"Question": "EACH + LACK = WHEEL", "Answer": "4723 + 8725 = 13448"}
{"Question": "SALE + HALF = FLESH", "Answer": "4826 + 7821 = 12647"}
{"Question": "YEAH + READ = THREE", "Answer": "4892 + 7896 = 12788"}
{"Question": "CHIP + SHIT = PITCH", "Answer": "4921 + 7928 = 12849"}
{"Question": "FACT + EACH = STATE", "Answer": "4962 + 7965 = 12927"}
{"Question": "MATH + RATE = HEART", "Answer": "5041 + 8043 = 13084"}
{"Question": "BEAR + HEAT = EARTH", "Answer": "5132 + 8136 = 13268"}
{"Question": "TINY + KING = NIGHT", "Answer": "5417 + 9418 = 14835"}
{"Question": "HERO + TERM = METER", "Answer": "5476 + 9471 = 14947"}
{"Question": "LOSE + COST = STEEL", "Answer": "5612 + 7613 = 13225"}
{"Question": "YARD + CARE = ESSAY", "Answer": "5684 + 7681 = 13365"}
{"Question": "EACH + LACK = SHELL", "Answer": "5782 + 6784 = 12566"}
{"Question": "GOAL + ROAD = LARGE", "Answer": "5821 + 6829 = 12650"}
{"Question": "YEAH + LEAF = FULLY", "Answer": "5834 + 6831 = 12665"}
{"Question": "TEAR + HEAD = EARTH", "Answer": "6132 + 7135 = 13267"}
{"Question": "BEAT + LEAD = TABLE", "Answer": "6341 + 8342 = 14683"}
{"Question": "PANT + SAND = TASTE", "Answer": "6351 + 7359 = 13710"}
{"Question": "RATE + PATH = METER", "Answer": "6374 + 8372 = 14746"}
{"Question": "CASH + PAST = HAPPY", "Answer": "6381 + 7389 = 13770"}
{"Question": "READ + TEAM = METER", "Answer": "6425 + 8421 = 14846"}
{"Question": "CROP + FROM = PROOF", "Answer": "6501 + 8507 = 15008"}
{"Question": "PAIR + WAIT = TROOP", "Answer": "6725 + 8721 = 15446"}
{"Question": "ITEM + STEP = LIMIT", "Answer": "6785 + 9782 = 16567"}
{"Question": "WISH + RISE = FEWER", "Answer": "6823 + 7824 = 14647"}
{"Question": "LATE + MATH = HELLO", "Answer": "6834 + 7831 = 14665"}
{"Question": "MALE + TALK = ELECT", "Answer": "7061 + 9068 = 16129"}
{"Question": "BEAR + LEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "7264 + 9265 = 16529"}
{"Question": "TONE + BOND = ENTER", "Answer": "7351 + 8359 = 15710"}
{"Question": "BASE + VAST = LEVEL", "Answer": "7425 + 8426 = 15851"}
{"Question": "HOST + POET = HELLO", "Answer": "1236 + 9206 = 10442"}
{"Question": "BELT + HEAT = BLADE", "Answer": "1206 + 9246 = 10452"}
{"Question": "MEAT + BELT = MAYBE", "Answer": "1206 + 9286 = 10492"}
{"Question": "FINE + CITE = FENCE", "Answer": "1240 + 9250 = 10490"}
{"Question": "SEND + HEAD = STATE", "Answer": "1246 + 9256 = 10502"}
{"Question": "CARE + GAME = CREAM", "Answer": "1306 + 9326 = 10632"}
{"Question": "FILE + SIDE = FLESH", "Answer": "1306 + 9386 = 10692"}
{"Question": "BORN + JOIN = BRING", "Answer": "1307 + 9367 = 10674"}
{"Question": "AIDE + LIFE = ADULT", "Answer": "1307 + 9387 = 10694"}
{"Question": "HEAD + TEND = DATA", "Answer": "1368 + 7308 = 8676"}
{"Question": "DEBT + MEAT = DRAMA", "Answer": "1328 + 9368 = 10696"}
{"Question": "MOST + PORT = METER", "Answer": "1357 + 9347 = 10704"}
{"Question": "AIDE + BIKE = AHEAD", "Answer": "1347 + 9367 = 10714"}
{"Question": "BAKE + CASE = BREAK", "Answer": "1347 + 9387 = 10734"}
{"Question": "BAKE + FADE = BROAD", "Answer": "1354 + 9384 = 10738"}
{"Question": "POET + COAT = PEACE", "Answer": "1405 + 9485 = 10890"}
{"Question": "COAL + SOUL = CAUSE", "Answer": "1406 + 9486 = 10892"}
{"Question": "BELT + MEAT = BLAME", "Answer": "1407 + 9487 = 10894"}
{"Question": "CARE + BAKE = CREAM", "Answer": "1408 + 9438 = 10846"}
{"Question": "DARE + BAKE = DRESS", "Answer": "1408 + 9458 = 10866"}
{"Question": "CORE + HOME = CREAM", "Answer": "1408 + 9468 = 10876"}
{"Question": "BIKE + AIDE = BREAD", "Answer": "1428 + 9468 = 10896"}
{"Question": "EAST + FACT = ESSAY", "Answer": "1506 + 8546 = 10052"}
{"Question": "AIDE + RISE = ASSET", "Answer": "1567 + 8507 = 10074"}
{"Question": "AIDE + BIKE = AWARD", "Answer": "1542 + 8592 = 10134"}
{"Question": "PURE + HUGE = PAPER", "Answer": "1563 + 8573 = 10136"}
{"Question": "TALE + BAKE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1563 + 8593 = 10156"}
{"Question": "CARD + SAND = CROSS", "Answer": "1609 + 8679 = 10288"}
{"Question": "HATE + MALE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1627 + 8647 = 10274"}
{"Question": "SAND + CARD = SENSE", "Answer": "1635 + 8675 = 10310"}
{"Question": "FILE + RICE = FLOOR", "Answer": "1709 + 8739 = 10448"}
{"Question": "BIKE + RISE = BASIS", "Answer": "1732 + 8742 = 10474"}
{"Question": "HATE + LAKE = HOTEL", "Answer": "1754 + 8794 = 10548"}
{"Question": "MEAT + REST = MARRY", "Answer": "1906 + 8976 = 10882"}
{"Question": "SITE + AIDE = STAFF", "Answer": "1907 + 8937 = 10844"}
{"Question": "BIKE + LIFE = BRIEF", "Answer": "1973 + 8963 = 10936"}
{"Question": "TALE + BAKE = ALTER", "Answer": "2107 + 8167 = 10274"}
{"Question": "BEAT + REST = START", "Answer": "2860 + 7810 = 10670"}
{"Question": "RACE + PAGE = AGREE", "Answer": "3180 + 9120 = 12300"}
{"Question": "GAIN + WARN = ANGER", "Answer": "3162 + 9142 = 12304"}
{"Question": "BEAT + REST = STARE", "Answer": "3482 + 9412 = 12894"}
{"Question": "BASE + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "4129 + 8169 = 12298"}
{"Question": "LIFE + AIDE = IDEAL", "Answer": "4162 + 9132 = 13294"}
{"Question": "VERY + DENY = NEVER", "Answer": "4205 + 8215 = 12420"}
{"Question": "RISE + BITE = STRIP", "Answer": "4219 + 6209 = 10428"}
{"Question": "BEAT + LEFT = TABLE", "Answer": "4231 + 9261 = 13492"}
{"Question": "EARN + LAWN = RANGE", "Answer": "4317 + 9387 = 13704"}
{"Question": "WHOM + THEM = PHOTO", "Answer": "4368 + 9328 = 13696"}
{"Question": "TEND + HEAD = ADAPT", "Answer": "4592 + 7512 = 12104"}
{"Question": "COPE + LOSE = APPLE", "Answer": "4620 + 7650 = 12270"}
{"Question": "TALE + GAME = METAL", "Answer": "4763 + 8713 = 13476"}
{"Question": "EACH + MATH = CREAM", "Answer": "4719 + 8759 = 13478"}
{"Question": "AIDE + TIME = MEDIA", "Answer": "4982 + 7912 = 12894"}
{"Question": "BASE + LATE = STEEL", "Answer": "5214 + 8234 = 13448"}
{"Question": "GAIN + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "5214 + 9284 = 14498"}
{"Question": "SEAT + BELT = TASTE", "Answer": "5241 + 9271 = 14512"}
{"Question": "DENY + VERY = NERVE", "Answer": "5412 + 9482 = 14894"}
{"Question": "BOAT + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "5439 + 8479 = 13918"}
{"Question": "RATE + MALE = ALTER", "Answer": "6128 + 9158 = 15286"}
{"Question": "EACH + PATH = CHEAP", "Answer": "6314 + 8324 = 14638"}
{"Question": "REST + MEAT = TERMS", "Answer": "6321 + 7351 = 13672"}
{"Question": "CARE + GAME = EAGER", "Answer": "6321 + 7391 = 13712"}
{"Question": "HAVE + DATE = CATCH", "Answer": "6423 + 8493 = 14916"}
{"Question": "BOND + LOUD = DOUBT", "Answer": "6471 + 8491 = 14962"}
{"Question": "WIPE + CITE = PIECE", "Answer": "6510 + 8570 = 15080"}
{"Question": "BASE + NAME = ASIAN", "Answer": "7154 + 8164 = 15318"}
{"Question": "EARN + LAWN = INNER", "Answer": "7326 + 9346 = 16672"}
{"Question": "RISE + NICE = ASIAN", "Answer": "7964 + 8954 = 16918"}
{"Question": "BELT + HEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "1207 + 9245 = 10452"}
{"Question": "WHAT + CHEF = WATCH", "Answer": "1306 + 9387 = 10693"}
{"Question": "CARD + GAME = CREAM", "Answer": "1405 + 9438 = 10843"}
{"Question": "FUND + AUTO = FLOAT", "Answer": "1437 + 9458 = 10895"}
{"Question": "SITE + FILM = STEEL", "Answer": "1704 + 8739 = 10443"}
{"Question": "REAL + BEND = EARLY", "Answer": "2106 + 8157 = 10263"}
{"Question": "LOTS + ROAD = START", "Answer": "2801 + 7869 = 10670"}
{"Question": "GAIN + CARD = ANGER", "Answer": "3172 + 9186 = 12358"}
{"Question": "TEAM + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "3756 + 9781 = 13537"}
{"Question": "RATE + MASK = TERMS", "Answer": "4213 + 9285 = 13498"}
{"Question": "TONE + YOUR = ENTRY", "Answer": "4231 + 9258 = 13489"}
{"Question": "BEND + HEAT = DEATH", "Answer": "4321 + 9368 = 13689"}
{"Question": "AUTO + HUGE = TOOTH", "Answer": "4612 + 7605 = 12217"}
{"Question": "EACH + RAIN = INNER", "Answer": "4635 + 7612 = 12247"}
{"Question": "BASE + FAIL = SHELF", "Answer": "4816 + 5879 = 10695"}
{"Question": "DISH + LIFE = SHELF", "Answer": "5213 + 8274 = 13487"}
{"Question": "SHOP + THIN = POINT", "Answer": "5231 + 8247 = 13478"}
{"Question": "BOWL + ROAD = LABOR", "Answer": "5291 + 8237 = 13528"}
{"Question": "ROCK + BOWL = COLOR", "Answer": "5417 + 9428 = 14845"}
{"Question": "BACK + MAIL = CLIMB", "Answer": "5812 + 7863 = 13675"}
{"Question": "HANG + TAIL = LIGHT", "Answer": "5826 + 7831 = 13657"}
{"Question": "SUCH + TUBE = CHEST", "Answer": "6213 + 7254 = 13467"}
{"Question": "YARD + TAIL = DIRTY", "Answer": "6241 + 7235 = 13476"}
{"Question": "VERY + DEAL = LEAVE", "Answer": "6473 + 8491 = 14964"}
{"Question": "RAIL + DATE = TIRED", "Answer": "6842 + 7815 = 14657"}
{"Question": "ROLE + MOST = TERMS", "Answer": "6824 + 7851 = 14675"}
{"Question": "WEST + HERO = TOWER", "Answer": "6831 + 7854 = 14685"}
{"Question": "GIRL + SITE = LEAST", "Answer": "6921 + 7954 = 14875"}
{"Question": "LIFE + AIDS = IDEAL", "Answer": "7132 + 9165 = 16297"}
{"Question": "DIET + RICH = THERE", "Answer": "7361 + 8325 = 15686"}
{"Question": "STAR + BEAR = STATE", "Answer": "1052 + 9452 = 10504"}
{"Question": "COLD + WILD = COLOR", "Answer": "1053 + 9453 = 10506"}
{"Question": "COAT + WHAT = COACH", "Answer": "1057 + 9457 = 10514"}
{"Question": "FINE + BONE = FIBER", "Answer": "1062 + 9862 = 10924"}
{"Question": "BURY + VERY = BUYER", "Answer": "1063 + 9263 = 10326"}
{"Question": "LAND + TEND = LATIN", "Answer": "1063 + 9863 = 10926"}
{"Question": "CAST + BEST = CABLE", "Answer": "1064 + 9864 = 10928"}
{"Question": "STOP + CROP = START", "Answer": "1065 + 9365 = 10430"}
{"Question": "NECK + ROCK = NERVE", "Answer": "1065 + 9865 = 10930"}
{"Question": "THIN + RAIN = THREE", "Answer": "1072 + 9872 = 10944"}
{"Question": "STAR + BEAR = START", "Answer": "1075 + 9675 = 10750"}
{"Question": "HOST + BEST = HOTEL", "Answer": "1076 + 9576 = 10652"}
{"Question": "PAGE + URGE = PRESS", "Answer": "1283 + 9083 = 10366"}
{"Question": "STAY + GRAY = START", "Answer": "1085 + 9785 = 10870"}
{"Question": "BASE + RISE = BASIC", "Answer": "1086 + 9786 = 10872"}
{"Question": "POEM + ITEM = PRIOR", "Answer": "1735 + 9235 = 10970"}
{"Question": "ROLE + MALE = RURAL", "Answer": "1247 + 8947 = 10194"}
{"Question": "FROM + WHOM = FEWER", "Answer": "1653 + 9253 = 10906"}
{"Question": "THAN + BEAN = TOOTH", "Answer": "1256 + 8756 = 10012"}
{"Question": "AUTO + INTO = ASIAN", "Answer": "1258 + 9658 = 10916"}
{"Question": "FORM + TERM = FLOOR", "Answer": "1263 + 8963 = 10226"}
{"Question": "POLE + FILE = PROOF", "Answer": "1264 + 8964 = 10228"}
{"Question": "AUTO + INTO = ABOUT", "Answer": "1368 + 9468 = 10836"}
{"Question": "SEAT + FLAT = SKILL", "Answer": "1372 + 9472 = 10844"}
{"Question": "BACK + NECK = KNEE", "Answer": "1394 + 2894 = 4288"}
{"Question": "SHIT + UNIT = SOUTH", "Answer": "1437 + 9537 = 10974"}
{"Question": "FLOW + GROW = FEWER", "Answer": "1752 + 8452 = 10204"}
{"Question": "POET + DIET = PHOTO", "Answer": "1462 + 8962 = 10424"}
{"Question": "LAND + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "1592 + 8492 = 10084"}
{"Question": "BELT + SALT = BIBLE", "Answer": "1497 + 8697 = 10194"}
{"Question": "SPIN + RAIN = APART", "Answer": "2043 + 8143 = 10186"}
{"Question": "JOIN + THIN = PHOTO", "Answer": "2643 + 8043 = 10686"}
{"Question": "PLUS + THUS = SLEEP", "Answer": "2071 + 8371 = 10442"}
{"Question": "COST + LIST = TOPIC", "Answer": "2071 + 8471 = 10542"}
{"Question": "COAT + BEAT = TOPIC", "Answer": "2071 + 8571 = 10642"}
{"Question": "DIRT + HURT = TIRED", "Answer": "2071 + 8671 = 10742"}
{"Question": "SEND + FUND = ISSUE", "Answer": "2678 + 9578 = 12256"}
{"Question": "RATE + NOTE = ERROR", "Answer": "2581 + 9681 = 12262"}
{"Question": "DRAG + FLAG = GUARD", "Answer": "2841 + 7641 = 10482"}
{"Question": "POET + DIET = TROOP", "Answer": "2681 + 7981 = 10662"}
{"Question": "SELF + GOLF = LOOSE", "Answer": "3015 + 9215 = 12230"}
{"Question": "REST + VAST = NERVE", "Answer": "3085 + 7285 = 10370"}
{"Question": "VAST + BEST = SERVE", "Answer": "3516 + 9216 = 12732"}
{"Question": "VAST + REST = SERVE", "Answer": "3716 + 9216 = 12932"}
{"Question": "CAST + BEST = SAUCE", "Answer": "3217 + 9417 = 12634"}
{"Question": "LIFE + SAFE = FIELD", "Answer": "3217 + 9517 = 12734"}
{"Question": "WHAT + MEAT = THEME", "Answer": "4031 + 6231 = 10262"}
{"Question": "STAR + BEAR = TERMS", "Answer": "4192 + 6092 = 10284"}
{"Question": "ROLE + ABLE = ORDER", "Answer": "4162 + 9862 = 14024"}
{"Question": "USER + OVER = CROSS", "Answer": "4683 + 9283 = 13966"}
{"Question": "ROPE + WIPE = POWER", "Answer": "4312 + 9612 = 13924"}
{"Question": "MOST + REST = TERMS", "Answer": "4621 + 9321 = 13942"}
{"Question": "TRIP + CHIP = APART", "Answer": "4632 + 7532 = 12164"}
{"Question": "GLAD + READ = LARGE", "Answer": "5128 + 7628 = 12756"}
{"Question": "FLAT + SEAT = LEAST", "Answer": "5140 + 8340 = 13480"}
{"Question": "FLAT + BEAT = TABLE", "Answer": "5631 + 8231 = 13862"}
{"Question": "UGLY + RELY = AGREE", "Answer": "5372 + 8472 = 13844"}
{"Question": "SEAT + BOAT = WASTE", "Answer": "5824 + 6724 = 12548"}
{"Question": "TIME + NAME = AGENT", "Answer": "6748 + 9148 = 15896"}
{"Question": "REST + CAST = AGREE", "Answer": "6472 + 9172 = 15644"}
{"Question": "LIST + EAST = STEAL", "Answer": "6513 + 7213 = 13726"}
{"Question": "RISK + DESK = SERVE", "Answer": "6217 + 8417 = 14634"}
{"Question": "CHIP + TRIP = PITCH", "Answer": "6231 + 7531 = 13762"}
{"Question": "SELF + HALF = FALSE", "Answer": "6281 + 9581 = 15862"}
{"Question": "DESK + RISK = TIRED", "Answer": "6423 + 9523 = 15946"}
{"Question": "VERY + BURY = NERVE", "Answer": "6432 + 7932 = 14364"}
{"Question": "DEAR + STAR = TRADE", "Answer": "7236 + 9136 = 16372"}
{"Question": "STAR + BEAN = START", "Answer": "1063 + 9567 = 10630"}
{"Question": "SALE + COLD = SALES", "Answer": "1063 + 9568 = 10631"}
{"Question": "STIR + ACID = START", "Answer": "1063 + 9867 = 10930"}
{"Question": "BEND + KING = BEGIN", "Answer": "1072 + 9475 = 10547"}
{"Question": "DIRT + BORN = DIRTY", "Answer": "1075 + 9678 = 10753"}
{"Question": "LATE + BOTH = LABEL", "Answer": "1075 + 9876 = 10951"}
{"Question": "ALSO + REST = ALTER", "Answer": "1082 + 9687 = 10769"}
{"Question": "BUSY + RISE = BUYER", "Answer": "1083 + 9286 = 10369"}
{"Question": "BAND + KING = BEGIN", "Answer": "1324 + 9528 = 10852"}
{"Question": "BASE + DISH = BREAD", "Answer": "1423 + 8925 = 10348"}
{"Question": "RISE + DUST = TIRED", "Answer": "3086 + 7281 = 10367"}
{"Question": "LIFT + SAFE = FIELD", "Answer": "3217 + 9618 = 12835"}
{"Question": "DARE + FIRM = MEDIA", "Answer": "4352 + 8051 = 12403"}
{"Question": "TRUE + CLUB = ELECT", "Answer": "5931 + 6234 = 12165"}
{"Question": "BEST + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "5781 + 6382 = 12163"}
{"Question": "RELY + WILD = ORDER", "Answer": "5472 + 9873 = 15345"}
{"Question": "GOAL + READ = LARGE", "Answer": "6231 + 7534 = 13765"}
{"Question": "NOSE + LAST = SALES", "Answer": "6413 + 9518 = 15931"}
{"Question": "SEAT + COAL = TASTE", "Answer": "7051 + 8659 = 15710"}
{"Question": "EASY + LIST = STEAL", "Answer": "7213 + 9516 = 16729"}
{"Question": "RISE + PUSH = SUPER", "Answer": "7312 + 9615 = 16927"}
{"Question": "STIR + BEAR = STATE", "Answer": "1028 + 9678 = 10706"}
{"Question": "BASE + CITE = BASIS", "Answer": "1047 + 9387 = 10434"}
{"Question": "GIVE + ONCE = GIVEN", "Answer": "1052 + 9472 = 10524"}
{"Question": "BUSY + VERY = BUYER", "Answer": "1054 + 9384 = 10438"}
{"Question": "FIRE + BAKE = FIBER", "Answer": "1063 + 9873 = 10936"}
{"Question": "STIR + BEAR = START", "Answer": "1065 + 9785 = 10850"}
{"Question": "FACT + SHIT = FIFTH", "Answer": "1956 + 8206 = 10162"}
{"Question": "THIN + LEAN = TITLE", "Answer": "1906 + 8276 = 10182"}
{"Question": "CROP + HELP = COVER", "Answer": "1206 + 9546 = 10752"}
{"Question": "BELT + COAT = BLADE", "Answer": "1206 + 9576 = 10782"}
{"Question": "CARD + USED = CROSS", "Answer": "1207 + 9437 = 10644"}
{"Question": "CORE + GAME = CREAM", "Answer": "1207 + 9547 = 10754"}
{"Question": "SAME + BLUE = SMELL", "Answer": "1208 + 9658 = 10866"}
{"Question": "LEAN + BORN = LABOR", "Answer": "1208 + 9768 = 10976"}
{"Question": "ONCE + PURE = OCCUR", "Answer": "1706 + 8326 = 10032"}
{"Question": "WEAR + STIR = WASTE", "Answer": "1608 + 9328 = 10936"}
{"Question": "TALE + BIKE = TOTAL", "Answer": "1342 + 8792 = 10134"}
{"Question": "PEAK + BUCK = PAPER", "Answer": "1406 + 8736 = 10142"}
{"Question": "LEAN + IRON = LOOSE", "Answer": "1427 + 8607 = 10034"}
{"Question": "SHOT + BEAT = SOUTH", "Answer": "1407 + 8967 = 10374"}
{"Question": "BEAN + DOWN = BLADE", "Answer": "1432 + 8952 = 10384"}
{"Question": "PEAK + WORK = PAPER", "Answer": "1507 + 8647 = 10154"}
{"Question": "DIRT + BOAT = TIRED", "Answer": "2061 + 8571 = 10632"}
{"Question": "TEAM + SWIM = WASTE", "Answer": "3608 + 7128 = 10736"}
{"Question": "SHUT + POET = HOUSE", "Answer": "4135 + 8205 = 12340"}
{"Question": "READ + GOLD = EAGER", "Answer": "4132 + 9782 = 13914"}
{"Question": "LIST + WHAT = SHALL", "Answer": "4917 + 8327 = 13244"}
{"Question": "DIRT + LEFT = RIFLE", "Answer": "5312 + 8472 = 13784"}
{"Question": "LIFE + TYPE = FIFTY", "Answer": "5314 + 7864 = 13178"}
{"Question": "BEAT + LIFT = TABLE", "Answer": "7261 + 9531 = 16792"}
{"Question": "HATE + GIVE = EIGHT", "Answer": "7321 + 9651 = 16972"}
{"Question": "COPE + RATE = PAPER", "Answer": "7514 + 8634 = 16148"}
